1	GASTROENTEROLOGY	NN	O	gastroenterology	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1506t81r1819b105],
2	2011	CD	DATE	2011	num	1	SENT_1	[p1l1831t81r2040b109],
3	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1831t81r2040b109],
4	141:338	CD	NUMBER	141:338	number	5	SENT_1	[p1l1831t81r2040b109],
5	-347	CD	NUMBER	-347	dep	1	SENT_1	[p1l2046t81r2118b105],

1	Susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	nsubj	6	SENT_2	[p1l45t184r418b238],
2	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l437t187r491b228],
3	Amoxicillin-Clavulanate-Induced	JJ	O	amoxicillin-clavulanate-induced	amod	5	SENT_2	[p1l512t184r1413b228],
4	Liver	NN	O	liver	nn	5	SENT_2	[p1l1439t185r1571b228],
5	Injury	NNP	O	Injury	prep_to	1	SENT_2	[p1l1594t185r1746b238],
6	ls	VBZ	O	l	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1769t185r1813b228],
7	Influenced	NNP	O	Influenced	dobj	6	SENT_2	[p1l48t251r334b294],
8	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l359t251r422b304],
9	Multiple	JJ	MISC	multiple	amod	11	SENT_2	[p1l445t251r662b304],
10	HLA	NN	MISC	hlum	nn	11	SENT_2	[p1l687t251r801b294],
11	Class	NN	MISC	class	prep_by	6	SENT_2	[p1l823t250r974b295],
12	I	CD	NUMBER	i	dep	11	SENT_2	[p1l998t251r1008b294],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1033t251r1132b294],
14	II	CD	NUMBER	ii	num	15	SENT_2	[p1l1158t251r1185b294],
15	Alleles	NNS	O	allele	conj_and	11	SENT_2	[p1l1208t251r1390b294],

1	M.	NNP	O	M.	nn	3	SENT_3	[p1l46t341r82b369],
2	ISABEL	NNP	O	ISABEL	nn	3	SENT_3	[p1l104t341r225b370],
3	LUCENA	NNP	LOCATION	LUCENA	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l242t341r407b374],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l242t341r407b374],
5	*	CD	NUMBER	*	appos	3	SENT_3	[p1l242t341r407b374],
6	MARIAM	NNP	O	MARIAM	nn	9	SENT_3	[p1l426t341r564b369],
7	MOLOKHIAF	NNP	O	MOLOKHIAF	nn	9	SENT_3	[p1l585t336r797b374],
8	YUFENG	NNP	LOCATION	YUFENG	nn	9	SENT_3	[p1l814t341r958b370],
9	SHEN	NNP	LOCATION	SHEN	dep	5	SENT_3	[p1l976t336r1099b374],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l976t336r1099b374],
11	§	CD	NUMBER	§	num	14	SENT_3	[p1l976t336r1099b374],
12	THOMAS	NNP	O	THOMAS	nn	14	SENT_3	[p1l1116t341r1268b370],
13	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	14	SENT_3	[p1l1286t341r1311b370],
14	URBAN	NNP	O	URBAN	appos	3	SENT_3	[p1l1332t334r1475b374],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1332t334r1475b374],
16	”	CD	NUMBER	”	num	19	SENT_3	[p1l1332t334r1475b374],
17	GURUPRASAD	NNP	O	GURUPRASAD	nn	19	SENT_3	[p1l1493t341r1740b370],
18	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	19	SENT_3	[p1l1759t341r1787b369],
19	AITHAL	NNP	PERSON	AITHAL	appos	3	SENT_3	[p1l1806t336r1955b374],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1806t336r1955b374],
21	“	CD	NUMBER	“	num	24	SENT_3	[p1l1806t336r1955b374],
22	RAUL	NNP	PERSON	RAUL	nn	24	SENT_3	[p1l46t380r139b416],
23	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	24	SENT_3	[p1l155t387r180b416],
24	ANDRADE	NNP	PERSON	ANDRADE	appos	3	SENT_3	[p1l199t387r394b420],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l199t387r394b420],
26	*	CD	NUMBER	*	num	28	SENT_3	[p1l199t387r394b420],
27	CHRISTOPHER	NNP	PERSON	CHRISTOPHER	nn	28	SENT_3	[p1l412t387r665b416],
28	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	appos	3	SENT_3	[p1l684t387r712b415],
29	DAY	NNP	PERSON	DAY	tmod	28	SENT_3	[p1l734t383r830b420],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l734t383r830b420],
31	#	#	O	#	prep	3	SENT_3	[p1l734t383r830b420],
32	FRANCISCO	NNP	O	FRANCISCO	nn	33	SENT_3	[p1l848t387r1053b416],
33	RUIZ	NNP	O	RUIZ	dep	31	SENT_3	[p1l1072t382r1410b420],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1072t382r1410b420],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1072t382r1410b420],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1072t382r1410b420],

1	CABELLO	NNP	LOCATION	CABELLO	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1072t382r1410b420],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1072t382r1410b420],
3	**	CD	NUMBER	**	num	8	SENT_5	[p1l1072t382r1410b420],
4	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	8	SENT_5	[p1l1072t382r1410b420],
5	**	CD	NUMBER	**	num	8	SENT_5	[p1l1072t382r1410b420],
6	PETER	NNP	PERSON	PETER	nn	8	SENT_5	[p1l1429t387r1540b415],
7	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	nn	8	SENT_5	[p1l1556t387r1585b415],
8	DONALDSON	NNP	PERSON	DONALDSON	appos	1	SENT_5	[p1l1606t383r1857b420],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1606t383r1857b420],
10	#	#	O	#	dep	12	SENT_5	[p1l1606t383r1857b420],
11	CAMILLA	NNP	PERSON	CAMILLA	nn	12	SENT_5	[p1l45t433r198b461],
12	STEPHENS	NNP	PERSON	STEPHENS	appos	1	SENT_5	[p1l214t433r425b466],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l214t433r425b466],
14	*	NNP	O	*	nn	16	SENT_5	[p1l214t433r425b466],
15	MUNIR	NNP	O	MUNIR	nn	16	SENT_5	[p1l444t434r557b461],
16	PIRMOHAMED	NNP	LOCATION	PIRMOHAMED	appos	1	SENT_5	[p1l576t428r861b466],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l576t428r861b466],
18	§	CD	NUMBER	§	number	19	SENT_5	[p1l576t428r861b466],
19	§	CD	NUMBER	§	appos	1	SENT_5	[p1l576t428r861b466],
20	MANUEL	NNP	PERSON	MANUEL	nn	21	SENT_5	[p1l880t434r1027b461],
21	ROMERO	NNP	PERSON	ROMERO	dep	19	SENT_5	[p1l1045t426r1384b466],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1045t426r1384b466],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1045t426r1384b466],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1045t426r1384b466],

1	GOMEZ	NNP	LOCATION	GOMEZ	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1045t426r1384b466],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1045t426r1384b466],
3	"	``	O	"	punct	4	SENT_7	[p1l1045t426r1384b466],
4	”	CD	NUMBER	”	dep	1	SENT_7	[p1l1045t426r1384b466],
5	JOSE	NNP	PERSON	JOSE	nn	7	SENT_7	[p1l1401t433r1492b461],
6	MARIA	NNP	PERSON	MARIA	nn	7	SENT_7	[p1l1511t434r1621b461],
7	NAVARRO	NNP	PERSON	NAVARRO	dep	4	SENT_7	[p1l1639t428r1853b466],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1639t428r1853b466],
9	“	CD	NUMBER	“	dep	1	SENT_7	[p1l1639t428r1853b466],
10	ROBERT	NNP	PERSON	ROBERT	nn	12	SENT_7	[p1l46t478r190b507],
11	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	12	SENT_7	[p1l206t479r231b507],
12	FONTANA	NNP	PERSON	FONTANA	dep	9	SENT_7	[p1l253t474r461b511],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l253t474r461b511],
14	**	CD	MONEY	**	dep	1	SENT_7	[p1l253t474r461b511],
15	#	#	MONEY	#	dep	1	SENT_7	[p1l253t474r461b511],
16	MICHAEL	NNP	O	MICHAEL	nn	17	SENT_7	[p1l480t478r636b507],
17	MILLER	NNP	O	MILLER	dep	1	SENT_7	[p1l654t479r828b511],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l654t479r828b511],
19	***	CD	NUMBER	***	num	21	SENT_7	[p1l654t479r828b511],
20	MAX	NNP	PERSON	MAX	nn	21	SENT_7	[p1l847t479r921b506],
21	GROOME	NNP	PERSON	GROOME	appos	17	SENT_7	[p1l938t478r1148b511],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l938t478r1148b511],
23	***	CD	NUMBER	***	num	25	SENT_7	[p1l938t478r1148b511],
24	EMMANUELLE	NNP	PERSON	EMMANUELLE	nn	25	SENT_7	[p1l1167t479r1409b507],
25	BONDON	NNP	PERSON	BONDON	appos	17	SENT_7	[p1l1427t474r1818b511],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1427t474r1818b511],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1427t474r1818b511],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1427t474r1818b511],

1	GUITTON	NNP	LOCATION	GUITTON	nsubj	15	SENT_9	[p1l1427t474r1818b511],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1427t474r1818b511],
3	***	CD	NUMBER	***	num	6	SENT_9	[p1l1427t474r1818b511],
4	ANITA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ANITA	nn	6	SENT_9	[p1l44t524r147b552],
5	CONFORT	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CONFORT	nn	6	SENT_9	[p1l164t519r403b557],
6	|	NNP	O	|	appos	1	SENT_9	[p1l164t519r403b557],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l164t519r403b557],
8	§	CD	NUMBER	§	num	12	SENT_9	[p1l164t519r403b557],
9	§	CD	NUMBER	§	num	12	SENT_9	[p1l164t519r403b557],
10	§	CD	NUMBER	§	num	12	SENT_9	[p1l164t519r403b557],
11	BRUNO	NNP	PERSON	BRUNO	nn	12	SENT_9	[p1l422t524r549b553],
12	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	appos	1	SENT_9	[p1l568t524r599b552],
13	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	14	SENT_9	[p1l619t524r651b553],
14	STR	NNP	O	STR	dep	12	SENT_9	[p1l672t517r893b557],
15	|	VBD	O	|	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l672t517r893b557],
16	CKER	NNP	O	CKER	nsubj	28	SENT_9	[p1l672t517r893b557],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l672t517r893b557],
18	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l672t517r893b557],
19	““	NN	O	““	dep	16	SENT_9	[p1l672t517r893b557],
20	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l672t517r893b557],
21	ALFONSO	NNP	PERSON	ALFONSO	nn	22	SENT_9	[p1l909t524r1078b553],
22	CARVAJAL	NNP	PERSON	CARVAJAL	dep	19	SENT_9	[p1l1096t519r1339b557],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1096t519r1339b557],
24	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1096t519r1339b557],
25	“‘	CD	NUMBER	“‘	num	28	SENT_9	[p1l1096t519r1339b557],
26	“	CD	NUMBER	“	num	28	SENT_9	[p1l1096t519r1339b557],
27	LUISA	NNP	LOCATION	LUISA	nn	28	SENT_9	[p1l1359t524r1459b553],
28	IBANEZ	NNP	LOCATION	IBANEZ	xcomp	15	SENT_9	[p1l1477t520r1660b557],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1477t520r1660b557],
30	“”	CD	NUMBER	“”	number	31	SENT_9	[p1l1477t520r1660b557],
31	*	CD	NUMBER	*	appos	28	SENT_9	[p1l1477t520r1660b557],
32	QUN	NNP	O	QUN	dep	31	SENT_9	[p1l1677t524r1858b553],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1677t524r1858b553],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1677t524r1858b553],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1677t524r1858b553],

1	YING	NNP	O	YING	nn	2	SENT_11	[p1l1677t524r1858b553],
2	YUE	NNP	O	YUE	dep	24	SENT_11	[p1l1875t524r2009b557],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1875t524r2009b557],
4	****	CD	NUMBER	****	num	6	SENT_11	[p1l1875t524r2009b557],
5	MICHEL	NNP	PERSON	MICHEL	nn	6	SENT_11	[p1l46t570r179b598],
6	EICHELBAUM	NNP	PERSON	EICHELBAUM	appos	2	SENT_11	[p1l197t565r500b603],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l197t565r500b603],
8	****	CD	NUMBER	****	num	10	SENT_11	[p1l197t565r500b603],
9	ARIS	NN	O	ari	nn	10	SENT_11	[p1l516t570r596b598],
10	FLORATOS	NN	O	florato	appos	2	SENT_11	[p1l615t565r827b603],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l615t565r827b603],
12	§	CD	NUMBER	§	num	14	SENT_11	[p1l615t565r827b603],
13	ITSIK	NN	O	itsik	nn	14	SENT_11	[p1l847t570r930b598],
14	PE’ER	NN	O	pe’er	appos	2	SENT_11	[p1l948t565r1074b603],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l948t565r1074b603],
16	§	CD	NUMBER	§	appos	2	SENT_11	[p1l948t565r1074b603],
17	MARK	NNP	PERSON	MARK	nn	19	SENT_11	[p1l1093t571r1196b598],
18	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	19	SENT_11	[p1l1211t571r1237b598],
19	DALY	NNP	PERSON	DALY	dep	16	SENT_11	[p1l1258t565r1422b603],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1258t565r1422b603],
21	§	CD	NUMBER	§	appos	2	SENT_11	[p1l1258t565r1422b603],
22	§	CD	NUMBER	§	num	23	SENT_11	[p1l1258t565r1422b603],
23	§	NN	O	§	dep	24	SENT_11	[p1l1258t565r1422b603],
24	§	CD	NUMBER	§	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1258t565r1422b603],
25	DAVID	NNP	PERSON	DAVID	nn	27	SENT_11	[p1l1441t571r1543b598],
26	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	27	SENT_11	[p1l1563t571r1592b598],
27	GOLDSTEIN	NNP	PERSON	GOLDSTEIN	dep	24	SENT_11	[p1l1613t563r1833b603],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1613t563r1833b603],
29	"	``	O	"	punct	32	SENT_11	[p1l1613t563r1833b603],
30	JOHN	NNP	PERSON	JOHN	nn	32	SENT_11	[p1l45t615r141b644],
31	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	32	SENT_11	[p1l161t615r186b643],
32	DILLON	NNP	PERSON	DILLON	appos	27	SENT_11	[p1l208t615r383b648],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l208t615r383b648],
34	***	CD	NUMBER	***	num	37	SENT_11	[p1l208t615r383b648],
35	MATTHEW	NNP	PERSON	MATTHEW	nn	37	SENT_11	[p1l402t615r579b643],
36	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	37	SENT_11	[p1l597t615r626b643],
37	NELSON	NNP	PERSON	NELSON	appos	32	SENT_11	[p1l648t608r852b648],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l648t608r852b648],
39	i	FW	O	i	appos	32	SENT_11	[p1l648t608r852b648],
40	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l648t608r852b648],
41	l	NN	O	l	tmod	32	SENT_11	[p1l648t608r852b648],
42	”	CD	NUMBER	”	dep	59	SENT_11	[p1l648t608r852b648],
43	"	``	O	"	punct	50	SENT_11	[p1l648t608r852b648],
44	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l648t608r852b648],
45	PAUL	NNP	PERSON	PAUL	dep	50	SENT_11	[p1l872t615r963b644],
46	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	prep	45	SENT_11	[p1l981t615r1010b643],
47	WATKINS	NNP	PERSON	WATKINS	dep	46	SENT_11	[p1l1029t610r1269b648],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1029t610r1269b648],
49	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1029t610r1269b648],
50	“‘	CD	NUMBER	“‘	npadvmod	59	SENT_11	[p1l1029t610r1269b648],
51	"	``	O	"	punct	50	SENT_11	[p1l1029t610r1269b648],
52	“‘	NN	O	“‘	nn	56	SENT_11	[p1l1029t610r1269b648],
53	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1287t615r1345b644],
54	ANN	NNP	PERSON	ANN	conj_and	52	SENT_11	[p1l1363t615r1437b643],
55	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	nn	56	SENT_11	[p1l1458t615r1487b643],
56	DALY	NNP	PERSON	DALY	dep	50	SENT_11	[p1l1508t611r1624b648],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1508t611r1624b648],
58	#	#	O	#	advmod	50	SENT_11	[p1l1508t611r1624b648],
59	for	IN	O	for	dep	24	SENT_11	[p1l1640t615r1683b644],
60	the	DT	O	the	det	61	SENT_11	[p1l1698t615r1748b644],
61	Spanish	JJ	MISC	spanish	pobj	59	SENT_11	[p1l1766t615r1892b650],
62	DILI	NNP	MISC	DILI	nn	63	SENT_11	[p1l1913t615r1970b643],
63	Registry	NNP	MISC	Registry	tmod	61	SENT_11	[p1l46t661r182b696],
64	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l46t661r182b696],
65	EUDRAGENE	NNP	LOCATION	EUDRAGENE	nn	69	SENT_11	[p1l203t661r429b693],
66	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l203t661r429b693],
67	DILIN	NNP	LOCATION	DILIN	appos	69	SENT_11	[p1l450t661r544b693],
68	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l450t661r544b693],
69	DILIGEN	NNP	O	DILIGEN	appos	63	SENT_11	[p1l565t661r709b693],
70	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l565t661r709b693],
71	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l729t661r787b689],
72	International	NNP	O	International	nn	73	SENT_11	[p1l807t661r998b689],
73	SAEC	NNP	O	SAEC	appos	63	SENT_11	[p1l1017t661r1111b689],

1	‘	NN	O	‘	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l46t733r162b755],
2	Facultad	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Facultad	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l46t733r162b755],
3	de	IN	ORGANIZATION	de	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l170t733r201b755],
4	Medicina	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicina	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l210t733r327b759],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l210t733r327b759],
6	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l340t733r442b761],
7	Universitario	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universitario	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l451t733r602b755],
8	I/irgen	NNP	O	I/irgen	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l613t733r689b761],
9	de	FW	O	de	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l699t733r730b755],
10	la	FW	O	la	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l738t733r757b755],
11	I/ictoria	NN	O	i/ictoria	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l769t733r863b759],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l769t733r863b759],
13	Campus	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Campus	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l877t733r981b761],
14	Universitario	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universitario	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l991t733r1142b755],
15	s/n	NNP	O	s/n	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1152t733r1195b759],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1152t733r1195b759],
17	Malaga	NNP	LOCATION	Malaga	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1207t733r1298b761],
18	and	CC	O	and	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1307t733r1356b755],
19	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1364t733r1447b755],
20	de	IN	O	de	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1457t733r1488b755],
21	lnvestigacion	NNP	O	lnvestigacion	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1497t733r1658b761],
22	Biomédica	NNP	O	Biomédica	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1667t733r1799b755],
23	en	IN	O	en	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1809t739r1838b755],
24	Red	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Red	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1847t733r1899b755],
25	de	IN	ORGANIZATION	de	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1906t733r1937b755],
26	Enfermedades	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Enfermedades	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l44t771r224b793],
27	Hepaticas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hepaticas	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l234t770r358b798],
28	y	NN	O	y	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l366t777r382b798],
29	Digestivas	NNP	O	Digestivas	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l389t771r516b798],
30	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l526t770r674b798],
31	ClBERehd	NNP	O	ClBERehd	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l526t770r674b798],
32	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l526t770r674b798],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l526t770r674b798],
34	Barcelona	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barcelona	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l686t771r816b796],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l686t771r816b796],
36	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l829t771r906b798],
37	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l829t771r906b798],
38	‘	NNP	ORGANIZATION	‘	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l916t767r1078b798],
39	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l916t767r1078b798],
40	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1086t771r1112b793],
41	Primary	JJ	ORGANIZATION	primary	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1117t771r1213b798],
42	Care	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Care	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1221t770r1280b793],
43	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	&	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1289t771r1305b793],
44	Public	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Public	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1315t771r1391b793],
45	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1400t771r1479b793],
46	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1488t770r1606b796],
47	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1488t770r1606b796],
48	Kings	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Kings	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1618t771r1688b798],
49	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1698t770r1795b798],
50	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1698t770r1795b798],
51	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1807t771r1907b796],
52	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1807t771r1907b796],
53	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1921t771r2002b793],
54	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l44t808r164b835],
55	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l44t808r164b835],
56	§	NNP	O	§	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l174t804r304b830],
57	Columbia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Columbia	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l174t804r304b830],
58	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l315t808r439b835],
59	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l315t808r439b835],
60	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l451t808r509b830],
61	York	NNP	LOCATION	York	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l518t808r576b833],
62	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l518t808r576b833],
63	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l588t808r646b830],
64	York	NNP	LOCATION	York	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l656t808r716b833],
65	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l656t808r716b833],
66	“	CD	NUMBER	“	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l727t802r797b830],
67	Duke	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Duke	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l727t802r797b830],
68	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l807t808r931b835],
69	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l807t808r931b835],
70	Durham	NNP	LOCATION	Durham	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l943t808r1047b833],
71	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l943t808r1047b833],
72	North	NNP	LOCATION	North	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1059t808r1128b830],
73	Carolina	NNP	LOCATION	Carolina	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1138t807r1247b833],
74	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1138t807r1247b833],
75	7	CD	NUMBER	7	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1258t804r1415b835],
76	’N	NN	O	’n	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1258t804r1415b835],
77	ottingham	NN	O	ottingham	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1258t804r1415b835],
78	Digestive	JJ	O	digestive	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1425t808r1538b835],
79	Diseases	NNS	O	disease	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1546t808r1658b830],
80	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1668t807r1756b833],
81	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1668t807r1756b833],
82	NIHR	NNP	ORGANIZATION	NIHR	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1768t808r1835b829],
83	Biomedical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biomedical	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1842t808r1982b830],
84	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1989t808r2106b830],
85	Unit	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Unit	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l45t844r98b870],
86	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l45t844r98b870],
87	Nottingham	NNP	LOCATION	Nottingham	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l110t844r261b872],
88	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l110t844r261b872],
89	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l274t844r356b867],
90	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l363t844r483b872],
91	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l363t844r483b872],
92	“	CD	NUMBER	“	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l494t841r603b866],
93	institute	NN	O	institute	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l494t841r603b866],
94	of	IN	O	of	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l612t844r639b866],
95	Cellular	JJ	O	cellular	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l645t844r737b866],
96	Medicine	NN	O	medicine	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l744t844r861b870],
97	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l744t844r861b870],
98	Newcastle	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Newcastle	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l874t844r1004b866],
99	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1014t844r1137b872],
100	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1014t844r1137b872],
101	Newcastle	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Newcastle	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1150t844r1280b866],
102	upon	IN	O	upon	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1289t850r1352b872],
103	Tyne	NNP	PERSON	Tyne	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1363t844r1426b872],
104	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1363t844r1426b872],
105	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1439t844r1521b866],
106	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1528t844r1648b872],
107	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1528t844r1648b872],
108	“	NNP	O	“	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1660t844r1781b872],
109	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1660t844r1781b872],
110	Universitario	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universitario	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1790t844r1941b866],
111	I/irgen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	I/irgen	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1952t844r2028b872],
112	de	IN	ORGANIZATION	de	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l2037t844r2068b866],
113	las	FW	ORGANIZATION	las	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l2077t844r2111b866],
114	Nieves	FW	ORGANIZATION	nieves	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l44t882r132b907],
115	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l44t882r132b907],
116	Facultad	NNP	PERSON	Facultad	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l144t882r252b904],
117	de	IN	PERSON	de	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l260t882r291b904],
118	Medicina	NNP	PERSON	Medicina	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l299t882r417b907],
119	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l299t882r417b907],
120	Granada	NNP	LOCATION	Granada	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l430t882r542b907],
121	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l430t882r542b907],
122	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l554t882r632b909],
123	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l554t882r632b909],
124	“	NNP	O	“	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l641t878r719b904],
125	Red	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Red	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l641t878r719b904],
126	Genomica	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genomica	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l727t881r853b904],
127	del	NNP	O	del	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l863t882r901b904],
128	Ca	MD	O	can	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l909t881r1003b907],
129	’n	VB	O	’n	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l909t881r1003b907],
130	cer	NN	O	cer	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l909t881r1003b907],
131	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l909t881r1003b907],
132	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1015t881r1093b909],
133	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1015t881r1093b909],
134	“	NNP	O	“	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1103t878r1250b909],
135	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1103t878r1250b909],
136	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1258t882r1284b904],
137	Liverpool	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Liverpool	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1289t882r1407b909],
138	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1289t882r1407b909],
139	Liverpool	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Liverpool	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1419t882r1536b909],
140	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1419t882r1536b909],
141	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1550t882r1632b904],
142	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1639t882r1759b909],
143	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1639t882r1759b909],
144	ll	NN	O	ll	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1770t876r1775b896],
145	"	''	O	"	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1781t876r1891b909],
146	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1781t876r1891b909],
147	Universitario	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universitario	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1900t882r2051b904],
148	de	IN	ORGANIZATION	de	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l2060t882r2091b904],
149	Valme	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Valme	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l46t919r125b944],
150	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l46t919r125b944],
151	Sevilla	NNP	LOCATION	Sevilla	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l138t919r220b944],
152	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l138t919r220b944],
153	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l232t919r310b946],
154	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l232t919r310b946],
155	777	CD	NUMBER	777	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l321t915r450b946],
156	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l321t915r450b946],
157	Hospltal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospltal	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l321t915r450b946],
158	Costa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Costa	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l458t918r530b941],
159	del	NNP	ORGANIZATION	del	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l540t919r578b941],
160	Sol	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sol	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l585t918r629b944],
161	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l585t918r629b944],
162	Marbella	NNP	LOCATION	Marbella	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l642t919r752b944],
163	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l642t919r752b944],
164	Ma	NNP	O	Ma	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l765t918r861b946],
165	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l765t918r861b946],
166	laga	NN	O	laga	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l765t918r861b946],
167	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l765t918r861b946],
168	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l873t918r951b946],
169	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l873t918r951b946],
170	“	NNP	O	“	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l961t915r1108b946],
171	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l961t915r1108b946],
172	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1115t919r1142b941],
173	Michigan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Michigan	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1147t919r1259b946],
174	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1268t919r1367b941],
175	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1375t918r1465b944],
176	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1375t918r1465b944],
177	Ann	NNP	PERSON	Ann	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1476t919r1526b940],
178	Arbor	NNP	PERSON	Arbor	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1533t919r1609b944],
179	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1533t919r1609b944],
180	Michigan	NNP	LOCATION	Michigan	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1621t919r1742b946],
181	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1621t919r1742b946],
182	***	CD	NUMBER	***	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1753t919r1899b941],
183	Ninewells	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ninewells	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1753t919r1899b941],
184	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1908t919r2011b946],
185	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l2018t919r2067b941],
186	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l44t956r142b978],
187	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l150t956r241b981],
188	Dundee	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dundee	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l253t956r355b981],
189	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l253t956r355b981],
190	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l369t956r450b978],
191	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l458t956r578b983],
192	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l458t956r578b983],
193	#	#	MONEY	#	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l587t952r748b978],
194	‘	CD	MONEY	‘	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l587t952r748b978],
195	Université	NNP	O	Université	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l587t952r748b978],
196	de	IN	O	de	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l757t956r788b978],
197	Toulouse	NNP	LOCATION	Toulouse	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l798t956r915b981],
198	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l798t956r915b981],
199	Toulouse	NNP	LOCATION	Toulouse	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l929t956r1046b981],
200	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l929t956r1046b981],
201	France	NNP	LOCATION	France	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1058t956r1151b981],
202	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1058t956r1151b981],
203	§	CD	NUMBER	§	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1160t952r1320b983],
204	§	CD	NUMBER	§	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1160t952r1320b983],
205	§	NNP	O	§	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1160t952r1320b983],
206	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1160t952r1320b983],
207	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1328t956r1434b983],
208	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1328t956r1434b983],
209	Verona	NNP	LOCATION	Verona	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1448t956r1539b981],
210	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1448t956r1539b981],
211	Italy	NNP	LOCATION	Italy	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1551t956r1607b983],
212	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1551t956r1607b983],
213	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1617t950r1756b978],
214	“	NN	O	“	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1617t950r1756b978],
215	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1617t950r1756b978],
216	“	CD	NUMBER	“	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1617t950r1756b978],
217	Erasmus	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Erasmus	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1617t950r1756b978],
218	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1765t956r1863b978],
219	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1871t955r1959b981],
220	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1871t955r1959b981],
221	Rotterdam	NNP	LOCATION	Rotterdam	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1971t956r2108b981],
222	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1971t956r2108b981],
223	The	DT	LOCATION	the	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l46t993r90b1015],
224	Netherlands	NNP	LOCATION	Netherlands	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l99t993r257b1018],
225	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l99t993r257b1018],
226	777	CD	NUMBER	777	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l268t989r456b1015],
227	”	NN	O	”	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l268t989r456b1015],
228	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l268t989r456b1015],
229	Universidad	NNP	O	Universidad	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l268t989r456b1015],
230	de	NNP	O	de	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l464t993r495b1015],
231	Valladolid	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Valladolid	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l505t993r626b1018],
232	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l505t993r626b1018],
233	Valladolid	NNP	LOCATION	Valladolid	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l640t993r761b1018],
234	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l640t993r761b1018],
235	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l774t992r852b1020],
236	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l774t992r852b1020],
237	“	CD	NUMBER	“	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l862t989r960b1015],
238	***	CD	NUMBER	***	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l862t989r960b1015],
239	‘	NN	O	‘	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l862t989r960b1015],
240	l	NN	O	l	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l862t989r960b1015],
241	—	NN	O	—	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l862t989r960b1015],
242	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l862t989r960b1015],
243	lCF	NN	O	lcf	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l862t989r960b1015],
244	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l967t992r1068b1020],
245	Catalan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Catalan	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l967t992r1068b1020],
246	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1077t993r1175b1015],
247	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1184t993r1210b1015],
248	Pharmacology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmacology	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1216t993r1397b1020],
249	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Foundation	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1404t992r1557b1020],
250	)	NN	O	)	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1404t992r1557b1020],
251	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1404t992r1557b1020],
252	Barcelona	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barcelona	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1569t993r1699b1018],
253	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1569t993r1699b1018],
254	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1712t992r1790b1020],
255	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1712t992r1790b1020],
256	****	NNP	O	****	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1801t993r1939b1015],
257	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1801t993r1939b1015],
258	Products	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Products	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1946t993r2059b1015],
259	Agency	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Agency	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l42t1030r142b1057],
260	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l42t1030r142b1057],
261	Uppsala	NNP	LOCATION	Uppsala	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l155t1029r262b1057],
262	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l155t1029r262b1057],
263	Sweden	NNP	LOCATION	Sweden	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l274t1029r383b1055],
264	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l274t1029r383b1055],
265	**	CD	NUMBER	**	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l393t1025r477b1051],
266	”	CD	NUMBER	”	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l393t1025r477b1051],
267	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l393t1025r477b1051],
268	Margarete	NNP	PERSON	Margarete	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l489t1029r617b1057],
269	Fischer-Bosch	NNP	PERSON	Fischer-Bosch	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l626t1029r806b1051],
270	institute	NN	O	institute	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l816t1029r913b1051],
271	for	IN	O	for	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l923t1029r957b1051],
272	Clinical	JJ	O	clinical	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l964t1029r1052b1051],
273	Pharmacology	NN	O	pharmacology	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1060t1029r1244b1057],
274	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1060t1029r1244b1057],
275	Stuttgart	NNP	LOCATION	Stuttgart	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1256t1029r1369b1057],
276	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1256t1029r1369b1057],
277	and	CC	O	and	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1381t1029r1430b1051],
278	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1439t1029r1559b1057],
279	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1567t1029r1593b1051],
280	Tuebingen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tuebingen	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1600t1029r1734b1057],
281	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1600t1029r1734b1057],
282	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1747t1029r1868b1057],
283	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1747t1029r1868b1057],
284	§	CD	NUMBER	§	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1877t1025r2028b1051],
285	§	CD	NUMBER	§	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1877t1025r2028b1051],
286	§	CD	NUMBER	§	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1877t1025r2028b1051],
287	§	NN	O	§	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1877t1025r2028b1051],
288	Harvard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Harvard	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1877t1025r2028b1051],
289	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l44t1067r142b1089],
290	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l150t1067r241b1092],
291	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l150t1067r241b1092],
292	Boston	NNP	LOCATION	Boston	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l253t1067r347b1092],
293	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l253t1067r347b1092],
294	Massachusetts	NNP	LOCATION	Massachusetts	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l359t1067r556b1092],
295	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l359t1067r556b1092],
296	l	NN	O	l	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l567t1061r572b1081],
297	l	NN	O	l	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l579t1061r584b1081],
298	l	NN	O	l	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l591t1061r596b1081],
299	"	''	O	"	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l602t1061r818b1092],
300	GlaxoSmithKline	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GlaxoSmithKline	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l602t1061r818b1092],
301	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l602t1061r818b1092],
302	Research	NNP	O	Research	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l830t1067r947b1089],
303	Triangle	NNP	O	Triangle	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l958t1067r1054b1094],
304	Park	NNP	O	Park	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1063t1067r1123b1092],
305	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1063t1067r1123b1092],
306	North	NNP	LOCATION	North	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1135t1067r1204b1089],
307	Carolina	NNP	LOCATION	Carolina	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1215t1066r1323b1092],
308	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1215t1066r1323b1092],
309	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1334t1063r1560b1089],
310	7	CD	NUMBER	7	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1334t1063r1560b1089],
311	’”	NN	O	’”	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1334t1063r1560b1089],
312	”	CD	NUMBER	”	dep	313	SENT_12	[p1l1334t1063r1560b1089],
313	7Hamner	NN	O	7hamner	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1334t1063r1560b1089],
314	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1334t1063r1560b1089],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1334t1063r1560b1089],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1334t1063r1560b1089],

1	UNC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	UNC	nn	2	SENT_14	[p1l1334t1063r1560b1089],
2	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1568t1067r1666b1089],
3	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1675t1067r1709b1089],
4	Drug	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Drug	nn	6	SENT_14	[p1l1716t1067r1776b1094],
5	Safety	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Safety	nn	6	SENT_14	[p1l1785t1066r1864b1094],
6	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	prep_for	2	SENT_14	[p1l1871t1066r1989b1092],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1871t1066r1989b1092],

1	Research	NNP	O	Research	nn	3	SENT_15	[p1l359t1112r565b1150],
2	Triangle	NNP	O	Triangle	nn	3	SENT_15	[p1l585t1112r753b1159],
3	Park	NNP	O	Park	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l769t1112r875b1156],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l769t1112r875b1156],
5	North	NNP	LOCATION	North	nn	6	SENT_15	[p1l896t1112r1018b1150],
6	Carolina	NNP	LOCATION	Carolina	appos	3	SENT_15	[p1l1036t1111r1212b1150],

1	BACKGROUND	NN	O	background	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l361t1283r901b1332],
2	8	CD	NUMBER	8	num	1	SENT_16	[p1l925t1285r978b1332],
3	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l925t1285r978b1332],
4	AIMS	NNS	O	aim	dep	1	SENT_16	[p1l997t1283r1207b1332],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l997t1283r1207b1332],
6	Drug	NN	O	drug	nn	7	SENT_16	[p1l1274t1279r1705b1351],
7	—	NN	O	—	nsubj	8	SENT_16	[p1l1274t1279r1705b1351],
8	induced	VBD	O	induce	dep	1	SENT_16	[p1l1274t1279r1705b1351],
9	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	10	SENT_16	[p1l1767t1279r1898b1332],
10	injury	NN	O	injury	dobj	8	SENT_16	[p1l1960t1281r2143b1351],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_16	[p1l363t1368r565b1437],
12	DILI	NNP	LOCATION	DILI	nsubj	23	SENT_16	[p1l363t1368r565b1437],
13	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	12	SENT_16	[p1l363t1368r565b1437],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l363t1368r565b1437],
15	especially	RB	O	especially	amod	12	SENT_16	[p1l594t1368r883b1440],
16	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l907t1368r1057b1421],
17	antimicrobial	JJ	O	antimicrobial	amod	18	SENT_16	[p1l1084t1368r1498b1421],
18	agents	NNS	O	agent	prep_from	15	SENT_16	[p1l1524t1383r1733b1439],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1524t1383r1733b1439],
20	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	23	SENT_16	[p1l1761t1370r1805b1421],
21	an	DT	O	a	det	23	SENT_16	[p1l1833t1388r1906b1421],
22	important	JJ	O	important	amod	23	SENT_16	[p1l1932t1370r2139b1440, p1l362t1472r486b1510],
23	cause	NN	O	cause	rcmod	10	SENT_16	[p1l509t1477r672b1510],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l696t1456r766b1510],
25	serious	JJ	O	serious	amod	27	SENT_16	[p1l779t1459r991b1510],
26	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	27	SENT_16	[p1l1015t1456r1145b1510],
27	disease	NN	O	disease	prep_of	23	SENT_16	[p1l1168t1456r1392b1511],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1168t1456r1392b1511],

1	AmoXicillin	NNP	O	AmoXicillin	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1415t1456r2140b1510],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	3	SENT_17	[p1l1415t1456r2140b1510],
3	clavulanate	NN	O	clavulanate	dep	1	SENT_17	[p1l1415t1456r2140b1510],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	3	SENT_18	[p1l363t1546r496b1615],
2	AC	NN	ORGANIZATION	ac	nn	3	SENT_18	[p1l363t1546r496b1615],
3	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	7	SENT_18	[p1l363t1546r496b1615],
4	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	7	SENT_18	[p1l527t1548r571b1599],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_18	[p1l601t1566r633b1599],
6	leading	VBG	O	lead	amod	7	SENT_18	[p1l658t1546r882b1618],
7	cause	NN	O	cause	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l910t1566r1072b1599],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1101t1546r1171b1599],
9	idiosyncratic	JJ	O	idiosyncratic	amod	10	SENT_18	[p1l1188t1546r1579b1618],
10	DILI	NNP	O	DILI	prep_of	7	SENT_18	[p1l1608t1551r1766b1611],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1608t1551r1766b1611],
12	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1794t1546r1899b1599],
13	little	JJ	O	little	nsubjpass	15	SENT_18	[p1l1926t1546r2067b1599],
14	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	15	SENT_18	[p1l2095t1548r2139b1599],
15	understood	VBN	O	understand	conj_but	7	SENT_18	[p1l361t1636r716b1690],
16	about	IN	O	about	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l754t1636r932b1689],
17	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	18	SENT_18	[p1l970t1638r1185b1708],
18	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	prep_about	15	SENT_18	[p1l1224t1636r1630b1708],
19	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1667t1651r1726b1689],
20	this	DT	O	this	det	22	SENT_18	[p1l1767t1636r1879b1689],
21	adverse	JJ	O	adverse	amod	22	SENT_18	[p1l1919t1636r2140b1690],
22	reaction	NN	O	reaction	prep_to	15	SENT_18	[p1l362t1727r622b1777],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l362t1727r622b1777],

1	METHODS	NNS	O	method	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l655t1728r1057b1778],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l655t1728r1057b1778],
3	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	4	SENT_19	[p1l1088t1729r1183b1777],
4	performed	VBD	O	perform	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l1214t1724r1536b1796],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_19	[p1l1566t1745r1598b1777],
6	genome-Wide	JJ	MISC	genome-wide	amod	8	SENT_19	[p1l1626t1724r2029b1796],
7	association	NN	O	association	nn	8	SENT_19	[p1l2060t1745r2139b1777, p1l362t1816r639b1867],
8	study	NN	O	study	dobj	4	SENT_19	[p1l665t1814r833b1886],
9	using	VBG	O	use	xcomp	4	SENT_19	[p1l855t1816r1023b1886],
10	822,927	CD	NUMBER	822,927	num	17	SENT_19	[p1l1048t1818r1288b1879],
11	single	JJ	O	single	amod	17	SENT_19	[p1l1314t1814r1488b1886],
12	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	17	SENT_19	[p1l1514t1814r1835b1868],
13	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	nn	17	SENT_19	[p1l1860t1814r2139b1886, p1l361t1903r552b1975],
14	(	NN	O	(	nn	17	SENT_19	[p1l582t1903r756b1972],
15	SNP	NN	O	snp	nn	17	SENT_19	[p1l582t1903r756b1972],
16	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	17	SENT_19	[p1l582t1903r756b1972],
17	markers	NNS	O	marker	dobj	9	SENT_19	[p1l787t1903r1032b1956],
18	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1061t1903r1211b1956],
19	201	CD	NUMBER	201	number	21	SENT_19	[p1l1238t1907r1344b1956],
20	White	JJ	MISC	white	amod	21	SENT_19	[p1l1375t1903r1559b1956],
21	European	JJ	MISC	european	prep_from	17	SENT_19	[p1l1587t1908r1884b1975],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1911t1903r2025b1957],
23	US	NNP	LOCATION	US	nn	24	SENT_19	[p1l2051t1907r2138b1956],
24	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_from	17	SENT_19	[p1l362t2012r510b2044],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l536t1991r606b2044],
26	DILI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DILI	prep_of	17	SENT_19	[p1l619t1996r762b2044],
27	following	VBG	O	follow	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l786t1991r1077b2063],
28	AC	NN	O	ac	nn	29	SENT_19	[p1l1096t1996r1189b2044],
29	administration	NN	O	administration	prep_following	9	SENT_19	[p1l1215t1991r1674b2046],
30	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	32	SENT_19	[p1l1700t1992r2001b2060],
31	AC-DILI	NN	O	ac-dili	nn	32	SENT_19	[p1l1700t1992r2001b2060],
32	)	NN	O	)	dep	29	SENT_19	[p1l1700t1992r2001b2060],
33	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l2028t1991r2142b2046],
34	532	CD	NUMBER	532	num	36	SENT_19	[p1l362t2085r470b2134],
35	population	NN	O	population	nn	36	SENT_19	[p1l527t2081r869b2153],
36	controls	NNS	O	control	prep_following	9	SENT_19	[p1l925t2081r1189b2146],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l925t2081r1189b2146],
38	matched	VBN	O	match	partmod	36	SENT_19	[p1l1246t2081r1511b2135],
39	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1566t2081r1654b2134],
40	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	41	SENT_19	[p1l1708t2083r1923b2153],
41	background	NN	O	background	prep_for	38	SENT_19	[p1l1977t2081r2139b2134, p1l362t2171r600b2243],
42	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1977t2081r2139b2134, p1l362t2171r600b2243],

1	RESULTS	NNS	O	result	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l624t2175r966b2224],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l624t2175r966b2224],
3	AC	NN	O	ac	dep	1	SENT_20	[p1l986t2175r1240b2224],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l986t2175r1240b2224],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l986t2175r1240b2224],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l986t2175r1240b2224],

1	DILI	NNP	LOCATION	DILI	nsubjpass	3	SENT_22	[p1l986t2175r1240b2224],
2	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_22	[p1l1258t2191r1365b2224],
3	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1387t2171r1685b2225],
4	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1702t2171r1834b2224],
5	many	JJ	O	many	amod	6	SENT_22	[p1l1854t2191r2020b2243],
6	loci	NNS	O	locus	prep_with	3	SENT_22	[p1l2036t2171r2141b2224],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l361t2263r419b2313],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_22	[p1l448t2260r540b2313],
9	major	JJ	O	major	amod	11	SENT_22	[p1l569t2263r742b2332],
10	histocompatibility	NN	O	histocompatibility	nn	11	SENT_22	[p1l769t2260r1313b2332],
11	complex	NN	O	complex	prep_in	6	SENT_22	[p1l1340t2260r1599b2332],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1340t2260r1599b2332],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_23	[p1l1627t2260r1742b2313],
2	strongest	JJS	O	strongest	amod	3	SENT_23	[p1l1772t2276r2042b2332],
3	effect	NN	O	effect	nsubj	12	SENT_23	[p1l2070t2260r2139b2313, p1l362t2350r467b2403],
4	Was	VBD	O	be	cop	12	SENT_23	[p1l493t2370r600b2403],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l627t2350r759b2403],
6	an	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_23	[p1l788t2370r859b2403],
7	HLA	NN	O	hlum	nn	10	SENT_23	[p1l887t2355r1026b2402],
8	class	NN	O	class	nn	10	SENT_23	[p1l1053t2350r1185b2403],
9	II	CD	NUMBER	ii	num	10	SENT_23	[p1l1214t2355r1258b2402],
10	SNP	NN	O	snp	prep_with	12	SENT_23	[p1l1287t2354r1418b2403],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_23	[p1l1448t2350r1788b2419],
12	rs9274407	NN	O	rs9274407	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1448t2350r1788b2419],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1448t2350r1788b2419],
14	P	NN	O	p	appos	12	SENT_23	[p1l1814t2355r1857b2402],
15	=	JJ	O	=	advmod	21	SENT_23	[p1l1889t2370r1933b2387],
16	4.8	CD	NUMBER	4.8	dep	15	SENT_23	[p1l1969t2354r2053b2403],
17	X	NN	O	x	num	21	SENT_23	[p1l2090t2357r2133b2400],
18	10	CD	NUMBER	10	number	17	SENT_23	[p1l367t2438r554b2509],
19	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	number	17	SENT_23	[p1l367t2438r554b2509],
20	14	CD	NUMBER	14	number	17	SENT_23	[p1l367t2438r554b2509],
21	)	NN	O	)	rcmod	14	SENT_23	[p1l367t2438r554b2509],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l367t2438r554b2509],
23	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	24	SENT_23	[p1l576t2439r754b2493],
24	correlated	VBD	O	correlate	rcmod	12	SENT_23	[p1l777t2439r1070b2494],
25	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1089t2439r1221b2493],
26	rs3135388	NN	O	rs3135388	prep_with	24	SENT_23	[p1l1245t2444r1565b2505],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1245t2444r1565b2505],
28	a	DT	O	a	det	30	SENT_23	[p1l1589t2460r1621b2493],
29	tag	NN	O	tag	nn	30	SENT_23	[p1l1642t2455r1732b2512],
30	SNP	NN	O	snp	appos	26	SENT_23	[p1l1754t2444r1885b2493],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1907t2440r1976b2493],
32	HLADRB1	NN	O	hladrb1	prep_of	30	SENT_23	[p1l1985t2444r2139b2492, p1l358t2533r1054b2597],
33	*	CD	NUMBER	*	number	34	SENT_23	[p1l1985t2444r2139b2492, p1l358t2533r1054b2597],
34	1501	CD	DATE	1501	num	32	SENT_23	[p1l1985t2444r2139b2492, p1l358t2533r1054b2597],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1985t2444r2139b2492, p1l358t2533r1054b2597],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1985t2444r2139b2492, p1l358t2533r1054b2597],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1985t2444r2139b2492, p1l358t2533r1054b2597],

1	DQB1	NN	O	dqb1	nn	3	SENT_25	[p1l1985t2444r2139b2492, p1l358t2533r1054b2597],
2	*	CD	NUMBER	*	num	3	SENT_25	[p1l1985t2444r2139b2492, p1l358t2533r1054b2597],
3	0602	NN	DATE	0602	nsubj	7	SENT_25	[p1l1985t2444r2139b2492, p1l358t2533r1054b2597],
4	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	5	SENT_25	[p1l1083t2529r1203b2582],
5	was	VBD	O	be	rcmod	3	SENT_25	[p1l1227t2549r1334b2582],
6	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	5	SENT_25	[p1l1361t2529r1662b2601],
7	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1687t2529r1985b2583],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l2008t2529r2140b2582],
9	AC-DILI	NN	O	ac-dili	prep_with	7	SENT_25	[p1l359t2623r625b2672],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l359t2623r625b2672],

1	Conditioned	JJ	O	conditioned	ccomp	15	SENT_26	[p1l655t2618r1028b2673],
2	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1054t2638r1130b2671],
3	rs3135388	NN	O	rs3135388	prep_on	1	SENT_26	[p1l1157t2622r1477b2684],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1157t2622r1477b2684],
5	rs9274407	NN	O	rs9274407	nsubj	15	SENT_26	[p1l1506t2623r1812b2672],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	15	SENT_26	[p1l1838t2621r1881b2672],
7	still	RB	O	still	advmod	15	SENT_26	[p1l1909t2618r2015b2672],
8	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	amod	15	SENT_26	[p1l2042t2621r2139b2691, p1l361t2708r588b2761],
9	(	NN	O	(	nn	15	SENT_26	[p1l615t2708r675b2777],
10	P	NN	O	p	nn	15	SENT_26	[p1l615t2708r675b2777],
11	=	JJ	O	=	amod	15	SENT_26	[p1l705t2728r749b2745],
12	1.1	CD	NUMBER	1.1	num	15	SENT_26	[p1l788t2712r864b2761],
13	X	NN	O	x	nn	15	SENT_26	[p1l901t2715r945b2758],
14	10-4	CD	NUMBER	10-4	num	15	SENT_26	[p1l985t2707r1146b2777],
15	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l985t2707r1146b2777],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l985t2707r1146b2777],

1	An	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_27	[p1l1172t2713r1259b2761],
2	independent	JJ	O	independent	amod	3	SENT_27	[p1l1285t2708r1657b2780],
3	association	NN	O	association	nsubjpass	5	SENT_27	[p1l1683t2710r2008b2761],
4	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_27	[p1l2033t2728r2139b2761],
5	observed	VBN	O	observe	ccomp	17	SENT_27	[p1l362t2797r619b2852],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l641t2800r699b2850],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_27	[p1l722t2797r814b2851],
8	class	NN	O	class	nn	10	SENT_27	[p1l839t2798r970b2851],
9	I	CD	NUMBER	i	num	10	SENT_27	[p1l994t2803r1015b2850],
10	region	NN	O	region	prep_in	5	SENT_27	[p1l1039t2800r1225b2869],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_27	[p1l1250t2798r1590b2867],
12	rs2523822	NN	O	rs2523822	dep	10	SENT_27	[p1l1250t2798r1590b2867],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1250t2798r1590b2867],
14	P	NN	O	p	nsubj	17	SENT_27	[p1l1612t2802r1655b2850],
15	=	JJ	O	=	amod	14	SENT_27	[p1l1682t2817r1726b2834],
16	1.8	CD	NUMBER	1.8	tmod	15	SENT_27	[p1l1762t2802r1841b2851],
17	X	NN	O	x	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1872t2804r1915b2847],
18	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	19	SENT_27	[p1l1952t2796r2139b2867],
19	‘	NN	O	‘	dobj	17	SENT_27	[p1l1952t2796r2139b2867],
20	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	21	SENT_27	[p1l1952t2796r2139b2867],
21	°	CD	NUMBER	°	num	22	SENT_27	[p1l1952t2796r2139b2867],
22	)	NN	O	)	dep	19	SENT_27	[p1l1952t2796r2139b2867],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1952t2796r2139b2867],
24	related	JJ	O	related	amod	19	SENT_27	[p1l362t2887r561b2941],
25	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l590t2902r648b2940],
26	HLA-A	NN	O	hla-a	prep_to	24	SENT_27	[p1l676t2891r1054b2940],
27	*	CD	NUMBER	*	number	28	SENT_27	[p1l676t2891r1054b2940],
28	0201	CD	DATE	0201	num	26	SENT_27	[p1l676t2891r1054b2940],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l676t2891r1054b2940],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_28	[p1l1084t2887r1199b2940],
2	most	RBS	O	most	advmod	3	SENT_28	[p1l1229t2902r1378b2940],
3	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	amod	4	SENT_28	[p1l1407t2887r1714b2959],
4	class	NN	O	class	nsubj	9	SENT_28	[p1l1744t2887r1875b2940],
5	I	CD	NUMBER	i	dep	4	SENT_28	[p1l1905t2892r1927b2939],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1957t2887r2068b2941],
7	II	CD	NUMBER	ii	num	8	SENT_28	[p1l2096t2892r2140b2939],
8	SNPS	NNS	O	snp	conj_and	4	SENT_28	[p1l362t2981r518b3030],
9	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l545t2976r768b3031],
10	statistical	JJ	O	statistical	amod	11	SENT_28	[p1l793t2976r1070b3030],
11	interaction	NN	O	interaction	nn	16	SENT_28	[p1l1094t2979r1417b3030],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	13	SENT_28	[p1l1444t2977r1504b3046],
13	P	NN	O	p	dep	11	SENT_28	[p1l1444t2977r1504b3046],
14	=	JJ	O	=	amod	16	SENT_28	[p1l1533t2996r1577b3013],
15	.0015	CD	NUMBER	.0015	tmod	14	SENT_28	[p1l1611t2977r1803b3045],
16	)	NN	O	)	dobj	9	SENT_28	[p1l1611t2977r1803b3045],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1611t2977r1803b3045],

1	Highresolution	JJ	O	highresolution	amod	4	SENT_29	[p1l1831t2976r2139b3048, p1l361t3066r541b3119],
2	HLA	NN	O	hlum	nn	4	SENT_29	[p1l572t3071r711b3119],
3	genotyping	VBG	O	genotype	amod	4	SENT_29	[p1l741t3069r1073b3138],
4	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1106t3067r1233b3135],
5	177	CD	NUMBER	177	num	6	SENT_29	[p1l1106t3067r1233b3135],
6	cases	NNS	O	case	nsubj	10	SENT_29	[p1l1265t3086r1407b3119],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1440t3066r1551b3120],
8	219	CD	NUMBER	219	num	9	SENT_29	[p1l1581t3070r1687b3120],
9	controls	NNS	O	control	nsubj	10	SENT_29	[p1l1721t3066r1980b3135],
10	)	VBP	O	)	rcmod	4	SENT_29	[p1l1721t3066r1980b3135],
11	conﬁrmed	JJ	O	conﬁrmed	amod	12	SENT_29	[p1l2015t3086r2139b3119, p1l361t3154r557b3208],
12	associations	NNS	O	association	dobj	10	SENT_29	[p1l594t3157r945b3207],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l984t3155r1053b3207],
14	HLA-A	NN	O	hla-a	prep_of	12	SENT_29	[p1l1076t3159r1437b3207],
15	*	CD	NUMBER	*	num	14	SENT_29	[p1l1076t3159r1437b3207],
16	0201	CD	DATE	0201	number	17	SENT_29	[p1l1076t3159r1437b3207],
17	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_29	[p1l1482t3155r1541b3223],
18	P	NN	O	p	npadvmod	19	SENT_29	[p1l1482t3155r1541b3223],
19	=	JJ	O	=	amod	14	SENT_29	[p1l1582t3174r1626b3191],
20	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	21	SENT_29	[p1l1670t3159r1703b3207],
21	X	NN	O	x	amod	14	SENT_29	[p1l1749t3161r1792b3204],
22	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	23	SENT_29	[p1l1843t3153r1990b3223],
23	‘	NN	O	‘	dep	36	SENT_29	[p1l1843t3153r1990b3223],
24	6	CD	NUMBER	6	num	25	SENT_29	[p1l1843t3153r1990b3223],
25	)	NN	O	)	dep	23	SENT_29	[p1l1843t3153r1990b3223],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l2030t3154r2142b3208],
27	HLA-DQB1	NN	O	hla-dqb1	conj_and	23	SENT_29	[p1l358t3246r851b3310],
28	*	CD	NUMBER	*	num	27	SENT_29	[p1l358t3246r851b3310],
29	0602	CD	DATE	0602	number	30	SENT_29	[p1l358t3246r851b3310],
30	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	31	SENT_29	[p1l876t3242r936b3311],
31	P	NN	O	p	npadvmod	32	SENT_29	[p1l876t3242r936b3311],
32	=	JJ	O	=	amod	27	SENT_29	[p1l960t3262r1004b3279],
33	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	34	SENT_29	[p1l1033t3246r1064b3295],
34	X	NN	O	x	dep	36	SENT_29	[p1l1096t3249r1139b3292],
35	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	36	SENT_29	[p1l1174t3241r1344b3311],
36	’	NN	O	’	dep	39	SENT_29	[p1l1174t3241r1344b3311],
37	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	36	SENT_29	[p1l1174t3241r1344b3311],
38	°	CD	NUMBER	°	num	39	SENT_29	[p1l1174t3241r1344b3311],
39	)	NN	O	)	dep	10	SENT_29	[p1l1174t3241r1344b3311],
40	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1369t3242r1481b3296],
41	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	43	SENT_29	[p1l1502t3242r1639b3295],
42	interaction	NN	O	interaction	nn	43	SENT_29	[p1l1659t3244r1981b3295],
43	(	NN	O	(	dep	44	SENT_29	[p1l2005t3242r2022b3311],
44	=	JJ	O	=	rcmod	4	SENT_29	[p1l2089t3262r2133b3279],

1	E	NN	O	e	dep	2	SENT_30	[p1l73t2477r112b2512],
2	<	JJR	O	<	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l73t2515r112b2555],
3	rn	CD	NUMBER	rn	num	6	SENT_30	[p1l73t2558r112b2580],
4	W	NN	O	w	nn	6	SENT_30	[p1l73t2586r112b2618],
5	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l138t2323r179b2768],
6	IVNO	NNP	O	IVNO	dep	2	SENT_30	[p1l138t2323r179b2768],
7	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	6	SENT_30	[p1l138t2323r179b2768],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l138t2323r179b2768],

1	|	NN	O	|	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l138t2323r179b2768],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l138t2323r179b2768],

1	V1SNVH	NN	O	v1snvh	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l138t2323r179b2768],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l138t2323r179b2768],

1	I.	NN	O	i.	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l138t2323r179b2768],
2	GNV	NN	O	gnv	nn	3	SENT_33	[p1l205t2571r244b2693],
3	DISVE	NN	O	disve	dep	1	SENT_33	[p1l204t2400r245b2551],

1	.005	NN	NUMBER	.005	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l363t17r518b86],
2	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_34	[p2l363t17r518b86],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l363t17r518b86],

1	Additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	4	SENT_35	[p2l561t17r892b82],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l561t17r892b82],
3	population-dependent	JJ	O	population-dependent	amod	4	SENT_35	[p2l936t17r1599b89],
4	effects	NNS	O	effect	nsubjpass	6	SENT_35	[p2l1643t17r1826b70],
5	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_35	[p2l1869t36r2003b70],
6	observed	VBN	O	observe	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l2047t17r2140b70, p2l362t106r543b160],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l562t108r621b158],
8	HLA	NN	O	hlum	nn	9	SENT_35	[p2l641t111r780b158],
9	alleles	NNS	O	allele	prep_in	6	SENT_35	[p2l800t106r972b159],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l993t106r1124b159],
11	nominal	JJ	O	nominal	amod	12	SENT_35	[p2l1146t106r1395b159],
12	signiﬁcance	NN	O	signiﬁcance	prep_with	6	SENT_35	[p2l1416t106r1769b177],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1416t106r1769b177],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1792t111r1855b158],
2	an	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_36	[p2l1875t125r1946b159],
3	analysis	NN	O	analysis	prep_in	14	SENT_36	[p2l1967t106r2140b178, p2l362t196r431b247],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l472t194r541b247],
5	autoimmune-related	JJ	O	autoimmune-related	amod	6	SENT_36	[p2l570t194r1178b248],
6	genes	NNS	O	gene	prep_of	3	SENT_36	[p2l1216t214r1390b266],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1216t214r1390b266],
8	rs2476601	NN	O	rs2476601	appos	6	SENT_36	[p2l1432t198r1733b248],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1777t197r1835b247],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_36	[p2l1875t194r1967b247],
11	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	12	SENT_36	[p2l2007t214r2140b266],
12	PTPN22	NN	O	ptpn22	prep_in	8	SENT_36	[p2l358t288r596b337],
13	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	14	SENT_36	[p2l616t304r722b337],
14	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l744t284r1042b338],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_36	[p2l1063t284r1122b353],
16	P	NN	O	p	dobj	14	SENT_36	[p2l1063t284r1122b353],
17	=	JJ	O	=	amod	16	SENT_36	[p2l1145t304r1189b321],
18	1.3	CD	NUMBER	1.3	num	19	SENT_36	[p2l1222t288r1300b337],
19	X	NN	O	x	dep	17	SENT_36	[p2l1329t291r1372b334],
20	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	23	SENT_36	[p2l1405t283r1567b353],
21	‘	NN	O	‘	nn	23	SENT_36	[p2l1405t283r1567b353],
22	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	23	SENT_36	[p2l1405t283r1567b353],
23	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	14	SENT_36	[p2l1405t283r1567b353],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1405t283r1567b353],

1	CONCLUSIONS	NNS	O	conclusion	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1590t288r2138b338],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1590t288r2138b338],
3	Class	NN	O	class	nsubj	9	SENT_37	[p2l362t372r524b426],
4	I	CD	NUMBER	i	num	3	SENT_37	[p2l562t378r587b425],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l625t372r746b427],
6	II	CD	NUMBER	ii	num	8	SENT_37	[p2l781t378r835b425],
7	HLA	NN	O	hlum	nn	8	SENT_37	[p2l872t377r1024b425],
8	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	conj_and	3	SENT_37	[p2l1059t386r1373b445],
9	affect	VBP	O	affect	dep	1	SENT_37	[p2l1412t373r1587b426],
10	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	dobj	9	SENT_37	[p2l1624t372r2043b445],
11	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l2077t386r2140b426],
12	AC-DILI	NN	O	ac-dili	prep_to	9	SENT_37	[p2l359t466r651b528],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l359t466r651b528],
14	indicating	VBG	O	indicate	partmod	9	SENT_37	[p2l675t462r996b534],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_37	[p2l1020t462r1119b515],
16	importance	NN	O	importance	dobj	14	SENT_37	[p2l1143t465r1507b534],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1532t462r1608b515],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_37	[p2l1621t462r1720b515],
19	adaptive	JJ	O	adaptive	amod	21	SENT_37	[p2l1745t462r2010b534],
20	immune	JJ	O	immune	amod	21	SENT_37	[p2l2035t465r2139b514, p2l361t571r541b605],
21	response	NN	O	response	prep_of	16	SENT_37	[p2l582t571r860b624],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l900t554r966b604],
23	pathogenesis	NN	O	pathogenesis	prep_in	21	SENT_37	[p2l1004t551r1431b624],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1004t551r1431b624],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_38	[p2l1471t551r1595b605],
2	HLA	NN	O	hlum	nn	3	SENT_38	[p2l1636t556r1787b604],
3	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	nsubj	17	SENT_38	[p2l1825t565r2140b624],
4	identiﬁed	VBN	O	identiﬁed	partmod	3	SENT_38	[p2l360t640r666b694],
5	will	MD	O	will	aux	7	SENT_38	[p2l682t640r800b693],
6	be	VB	O	be	cop	7	SENT_38	[p2l816t640r891b693],
7	useful	JJ	O	useful	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l909t640r1104b693],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1121t643r1187b693],
9	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_in	7	SENT_38	[p2l1205t640r1424b694],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1445t640r1520b693],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_38	[p2l1528t640r1627b693],
12	pathogenesis	NN	O	pathogenesis	prep_of	9	SENT_38	[p2l1645t640r2056b712],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l2076t640r2152b693],
14	AC-DILI	NN	O	ac-dili	prep_of	12	SENT_38	[p2l359t734r633b783],
15	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l662t730r772b783],
16	have	VBP	O	have	aux	17	SENT_38	[p2l801t730r945b783],
17	limited	VBN	O	limit	conj_but	7	SENT_38	[p2l974t730r1203b784],
18	utility	NN	O	utility	dobj	17	SENT_38	[p2l1231t730r1423b802],
19	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1451t750r1513b783],
20	predictive	JJ	O	predictive	amod	23	SENT_38	[p2l1544t730r1855b802],
21	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1886t749r1956b783],
22	diagnostic	JJ	O	diagnostic	conj_or	20	SENT_38	[p2l1986t730r2139b802, p2l361t821r550b872],
23	biomarkers	NNS	O	biomarker	prep_as	18	SENT_38	[p2l570t818r935b872],
24	because	IN	O	because	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l956t818r1202b872],
25	of	IN	O	of	prepc_because_of	17	SENT_38	[p2l1224t818r1299b872],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_38	[p2l1309t818r1408b872],
27	low	JJ	O	low	amod	30	SENT_38	[p2l1429t818r1545b872],
28	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	30	SENT_38	[p2l1563t821r1809b890],
29	predictive	JJ	O	predictive	amod	30	SENT_38	[p2l1830t818r2141b890],
30	values	NNS	O	value	pobj	17	SENT_38	[p2l358t908r570b961],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l358t908r570b961],

1	Keywords	NNS	O	keyword	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l7t1001r347b1087],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l7t1001r347b1087],
3	Hepatotoxicity	NN	ORGANIZATION	hepatotoxicity	dep	1	SENT_39	[p2l443t1004r1004b1087],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l443t1004r1004b1087],
5	Genome-Wide	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genome-Wide	nn	7	SENT_39	[p2l1101t1001r1624b1065],
6	Association	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Association	nn	7	SENT_39	[p2l1715t1004r2141b1064],
7	Study	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Study	dep	3	SENT_39	[p2l12t1103r241b1189],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l12t1103r241b1189],
9	GWAS	NNP	O	GWAS	dep	1	SENT_39	[p2l277t1109r536b1181],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l277t1109r536b1181],
11	Pharmacogenomics	NNP	O	Pharmacogenomics	dep	9	SENT_39	[p2l571t1103r1305b1189],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l571t1103r1305b1189],

1	diosyncratic	JJ	O	diosyncratic	amod	3	SENT_40	[p2l109t1386r552b1473],
2	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	3	SENT_40	[p2l583t1387r739b1450],
3	toxicity	NN	O	toxicity	nsubjpass	11	SENT_40	[p2l771t1389r1044b1473],
4	because	IN	O	because	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1072t1387r1353b1450],
5	of	IN	O	of	prepc_because_of	3	SENT_40	[p2l1387t1387r1470b1450],
6	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_40	[p2l1491t1411r1530b1450],
7	prescribed	VBN	O	prescribe	amod	8	SENT_40	[p2l1560t1386r1937b1473],
8	drug	NN	O	drug	pobj	3	SENT_40	[p2l1970t1386r2142b1473],
9	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_40	[p2l108t1495r161b1556],
10	usually	RB	O	usually	advmod	11	SENT_40	[p2l224t1492r486b1578],
11	referred	VBN	O	refer	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l545t1492r829b1557],
12	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l889t1510r960b1556],
13	as	IN	O	as	amod	16	SENT_40	[p2l1024t1516r1092b1556],
14	drug-induced	JJ	O	drug-induced	amod	16	SENT_40	[p2l1155t1492r1651b1578],
15	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	16	SENT_40	[p2l1710t1492r1866b1556],
16	injury	NN	O	injury	prep_to	11	SENT_40	[p2l1924t1495r2143b1578],
17	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_40	[p2l13t1601r254b1683],
18	DILI	NNP	LOCATION	DILI	dep	16	SENT_40	[p2l13t1601r254b1683],
19	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	18	SENT_40	[p2l13t1601r254b1683],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l13t1601r254b1683],

1	Most	JJS	O	most	nsubj	3	SENT_41	[p2l300t1607r491b1664],
2	DILI	NNP	O	DILI	dep	1	SENT_41	[p2l536t1606r706b1663],
3	involves	VBZ	O	involve	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l751t1601r1042b1664],
4	reactions	NNS	O	reaction	dobj	3	SENT_41	[p2l1089t1603r1418b1664],
5	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	7	SENT_41	[p2l1465t1601r1614b1664],
6	appear	VBP	O	appear	cop	7	SENT_41	[p2l1659t1624r1904b1686],
7	unrelated	JJ	O	unrelated	rcmod	4	SENT_41	[p2l1948t1624r2139b1664, p2l10t1709r190b1773],
8	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l224t1728r295b1772],
9	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	10	SENT_41	[p2l333t1709r504b1795],
10	dose	NN	O	dose	prep_to	7	SENT_41	[p2l539t1709r701b1773],
11	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l737t1732r813b1772],
12	concentration	NN	O	concentration	conj_or	10	SENT_41	[p2l847t1712r1375b1772],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l847t1712r1375b1772],

1	Although	IN	O	although	mark	3	SENT_42	[p2l1410t1709r1761b1795],
2	comparatively	RB	O	comparatively	advmod	3	SENT_42	[p2l1797t1732r2139b1795, p2l11t1814r204b1900],
3	rare	JJ	O	rare	advcl	10	SENT_42	[p2l239t1837r395b1893],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l239t1837r395b1893],
5	DILI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DILI	nsubj	10	SENT_42	[p2l433t1820r604b1877],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	10	SENT_42	[p2l640t1817r693b1877],
7	a	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_42	[p2l732t1838r770b1877],
8	serious	JJ	O	serious	amod	10	SENT_42	[p2l805t1817r1059b1877],
9	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	10	SENT_42	[p2l1097t1814r1356b1877],
10	problem	NN	O	problem	dep	37	SENT_42	[p2l1392t1814r1700b1900],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1735t1814r1898b1877],
12	up	RB	O	up	advmod	27	SENT_42	[p2l1935t1837r2028b1900],
13	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l2067t1833r2138b1877],
14	10	CD	PERCENT	10	num	15	SENT_42	[p2l18t1926r154b1984],
15	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_to	12	SENT_42	[p2l18t1926r154b1984],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l193t1921r277b1984],
17	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	15	SENT_42	[p2l303t1945r481b1984],
18	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l519t1921r681b1983],
19	simultaneous	JJ	O	simultaneous	amod	21	SENT_42	[p2l721t1921r1213b1984],
20	severe	JJ	O	severe	amod	21	SENT_42	[p2l1254t1944r1466b1984],
21	elevations	NNS	O	elevation	prep_with	17	SENT_42	[p2l1505t1921r1865b1984],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1904t1923r1975b1983],
23	alanine	NN	O	alanine	nn	24	SENT_42	[p2l2013t1921r2139b1984, p2l11t2030r168b2090],
24	transaminase	NN	O	transaminase	prep_in	21	SENT_42	[p2l214t2030r700b2090],
25	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	27	SENT_42	[p2l747t2027r951b2109],
26	ALT	NN	O	alt	nn	27	SENT_42	[p2l747t2027r951b2109],
27	)	NN	O	)	prep_with	10	SENT_42	[p2l747t2027r951b2109],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1000t2027r1137b2091],
29	bilirubin	NN	O	bilirubin	prep_with	10	SENT_42	[p2l1178t2027r1501b2090],
30	developing	VBG	O	develop	partmod	10	SENT_42	[p2l1546t2027r1944b2113],
31	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	32	SENT_42	[p2l1986t2027r2142b2090],
32	failure	NN	O	failure	dobj	30	SENT_42	[p2l11t2133r293b2196],
33	}	CD	NUMBER	}	num	32	SENT_42	[p2l11t2133r293b2196],
34	A	DT	O	a	det	36	SENT_42	[p2l333t2139r390b2195],
35	prospective	JJ	O	prospective	amod	36	SENT_42	[p2l427t2136r840b2219],
36	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	37	SENT_42	[p2l881t2133r1083b2219],
37	estimated	VBD	O	estimate	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1120t2133r1476b2197],
38	the	DT	O	the	det	41	SENT_42	[p2l1515t2133r1628b2196],
39	standardized	JJ	O	standardized	amod	41	SENT_42	[p2l1669t2133r2142b2197],
40	incidence	NN	O	incidence	nn	41	SENT_42	[p2l10t2241r354b2305],
41	rate	NN	O	rate	dobj	37	SENT_42	[p2l387t2260r523b2304],
42	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l557t2241r640b2304],
43	symptomatic	JJ	O	symptomatic	amod	44	SENT_42	[p2l661t2244r1139b2327],
44	hepatic	JJ	O	hepatic	amod	47	SENT_42	[p2l1171t2241r1437b2327],
45	adverse	JJ	O	adverse	amod	47	SENT_42	[p2l1470t2241r1735b2305],
46	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	47	SENT_42	[p2l1768t2241r1940b2327],
47	reactions	NNS	O	reaction	prep_of	41	SENT_42	[p2l1972t2264r2139b2304, p2l12t2349r192b2410],
48	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l226t2365r294b2410],
49	8.1	CD	NUMBER	8.1	prep_at	37	SENT_42	[p2l326t2352r426b2410],
50	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l464t2369r580b2432],
51	100,000	CD	NUMBER	100,000	num	52	SENT_42	[p2l619t2352r898b2425],
52	people	NNS	O	people	prep_per	49	SENT_42	[p2l932t2346r1171b2432],
53	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1204t2349r1276b2409],
54	France	NNP	LOCATION	France	prep_in	52	SENT_42	[p2l1308t2351r1601b2410],
55	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1308t2351r1601b2410],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1633t2352r1710b2409],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_43	[p2l1743t2346r1856b2409],
3	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	4	SENT_43	[p2l1888t2346r2142b2411],
4	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	prep_in	13	SENT_43	[p2l12t2459r245b2532],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l12t2459r245b2532],
6	13	CD	PERCENT	13	num	7	SENT_43	[p2l305t2459r441b2517],
7	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nsubj	13	SENT_43	[p2l305t2459r441b2517],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l494t2454r577b2517],
9	acute	JJ	O	acute	amod	12	SENT_43	[p2l617t2472r808b2517],
10	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	12	SENT_43	[p2l858t2454r1014b2517],
11	failure	NN	O	failure	nn	12	SENT_43	[p2l1064t2454r1298b2517],
12	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	7	SENT_43	[p2l1350t2478r1527b2517],
13	are	VBP	O	be	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1581t2477r1686b2517],
14	because	IN	O	because	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1736t2454r2017b2517],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l2069t2454r2153b2517],
16	idiosyncratic	JJ	O	idiosyncratic	amod	17	SENT_43	[p2l10t2563r478b2649],
17	hepatotoxicity	NN	O	hepatotoxicity	prep_because_of	13	SENT_43	[p2l519t2563r1048b2649],
18	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1083t2563r1246b2626],
19	75	CD	PERCENT	75	num	20	SENT_43	[p2l1290t2568r1431b2627],
20	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_with	17	SENT_43	[p2l1290t2568r1431b2627],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1473t2563r1557b2626],
22	those	DT	O	those	nsubj	23	SENT_43	[p2l1586t2563r1780b2626],
23	dying	VBG	O	die	prepc_of	20	SENT_43	[p2l1822t2563r2025b2649],
24	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l2065t2586r2142b2626],
25	requiring	VBG	O	require	prepc_of	20	SENT_43	[p2l12t2704r351b2787],
26	emergency	NN	O	emergency	nn	28	SENT_43	[p2l384t2724r772b2787],
27	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	28	SENT_43	[p2l801t2701r957b2764],
28	transplantation	NN	O	transplantation	dobj	23	SENT_43	[p2l990t2701r1612b2787],
29	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l990t2701r1612b2787],

1	’	NN	O	’	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l990t2701r1612b2787],

1	AmoXicillin	NNP	O	AmoXicillin	nsubj	7	SENT_45	[p2l95t2806r964b2869],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	1	SENT_45	[p2l95t2806r964b2869],
3	clavulanate	JJ	O	clavulanate	amod	6	SENT_45	[p2l95t2806r964b2869],
4	(	NN	O	(	nn	6	SENT_45	[p2l1005t2807r1163b2889],
5	AC	NN	O	ac	nn	6	SENT_45	[p2l1005t2807r1163b2889],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_45	[p2l1005t2807r1163b2889],
7	is	VBZ	O	be	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1204t2809r1257b2869],
8	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1297t2830r1551b2892],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_45	[p2l1588t2806r1701b2869],
10	most	RBS	O	most	advmod	12	SENT_45	[p2l1739t2825r1923b2869],
11	commonly	RB	O	commonly	advmod	12	SENT_45	[p2l1960t2830r2139b2869, p2l11t2913r245b2998],
12	prescribed	VBN	O	prescribe	amod	13	SENT_45	[p2l277t2912r654b2998],
13	antimicrobials	NNS	O	antimicrobial	prep_among	7	SENT_45	[p2l688t2913r1215b2976],
14	worldwide	RB	O	worldwide	advmod	13	SENT_45	[p2l1250t2912r1647b2977],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1250t2912r1647b2977],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_46	[p2l1683t2913r1844b2976],
2	drug	NN	O	drug	nsubj	5	SENT_46	[p2l1881t2912r2053b2998],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	5	SENT_46	[p2l2086t2915r2139b2976],
4	generally	RB	O	generally	advmod	5	SENT_46	[p2l11t3019r339b3104],
5	well	RB	O	well	ccomp	22	SENT_46	[p2l369t3019r514b3082],
6	tolerated	VBD	O	tolerate	dep	5	SENT_46	[p2l548t3019r891b3097],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l548t3019r891b3097],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l927t3019r1080b3097],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l927t3019r1080b3097],
10	whereas	IN	O	whereas	mark	14	SENT_46	[p2l1114t3019r1403b3082],
11	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	12	SENT_46	[p2l1438t3019r1594b3082],
12	injury	NN	O	injury	nsubj	14	SENT_46	[p2l1626t3021r1844b3104],
13	can	MD	O	can	aux	14	SENT_46	[p2l1877t3042r2000b3082],
14	occur	VB	O	occur	conj_and	6	SENT_46	[p2l2035t3043r2139b3082, p2l11t3148r128b3188],
15	rarely	RB	O	rarely	advmod	14	SENT_46	[p2l167t3125r386b3211],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l167t3125r386b3211],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_46	[p2l427t3125r540b3188],
18	overall	JJ	O	overall	amod	20	SENT_46	[p2l581t3125r822b3188],
19	risk	NN	O	risk	nn	20	SENT_46	[p2l861t3125r995b3188],
20	benefit	NN	O	benefit	nsubj	22	SENT_46	[p2l1032t3125r1283b3188],
21	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	22	SENT_46	[p2l1321t3128r1374b3188],
22	favorable	JJ	O	favorable	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1415t3125r1765b3188],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1415t3125r1765b3188],

1	DILI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DILI	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1807t3131r1978b3188],
2	following	VBG	O	follow	dep	1	SENT_47	[p2l2018t3125r2138b3188, p2l10t3230r258b3316],
3	AC	NN	O	ac	nn	4	SENT_47	[p2l280t3236r391b3294],
4	administration	NN	O	administration	pobj	2	SENT_47	[p2l420t3230r970b3295],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_47	[p2l999t3231r1381b3313],
6	AC-DILI	NN	O	ac-dili	nn	7	SENT_47	[p2l999t3231r1381b3313],
7	)	NN	O	)	tmod	4	SENT_47	[p2l999t3231r1381b3313],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l999t3231r1381b3313],
9	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	10	SENT_47	[p2l1407t3230r1627b3293],
10	appears	VBZ	O	appear	rcmod	7	SENT_47	[p2l1655t3253r1932b3316],
11	to	TO	O	to	aux	12	SENT_47	[p2l1960t3249r2032b3293],
12	be	VB	O	be	xcomp	10	SENT_47	[p2l2058t3230r2140b3293],

1	Abbreviations	NNS	O	abbreviation	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l76t3483r488b3532],
2	used	VBN	O	use	partmod	1	SENT_48	[p2l508t3484r649b3532],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l666t3483r716b3531],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	5	SENT_48	[p2l737t3483r845b3532],
5	paper	NN	O	paper	prep_in	2	SENT_48	[p2l861t3494r1049b3543],
6	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l861t3494r1049b3543],
7	AC	NN	O	ac	dep	5	SENT_48	[p2l1068t3483r1164b3541],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1068t3483r1164b3541],
9	amoxicillin-clavulanate	NN	O	amoxicillin-clavulanate	appos	7	SENT_48	[p2l1186t3484r1886b3541],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1186t3484r1886b3541],
11	AC-DILI	NNP	O	AC-DILI	nn	13	SENT_48	[p2l1906t3483r2138b3541],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1906t3483r2138b3541],
13	DILI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DILI	dep	7	SENT_48	[p2l13t3570r122b3618],
14	following	VBG	O	follow	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l152t3569r423b3630],
15	AC	NN	O	ac	nn	16	SENT_48	[p2l447t3570r529b3618],
16	administration	NN	O	administration	prep_following	13	SENT_48	[p2l558t3570r1008b3627],
17	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l558t3570r1008b3627],
18	ADME	NNP	O	ADME	dep	13	SENT_48	[p2l1037t3570r1232b3627],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1037t3570r1232b3627],
20	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	21	SENT_48	[p2l1264t3570r1397b3630],
21	absorption	NN	O	absorption	dep	13	SENT_48	[p2l1424t3570r1756b3629],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1424t3570r1756b3629],
23	distribution	NN	O	distribution	conj_and	18	SENT_48	[p2l1786t3570r2138b3627],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1786t3570r2138b3627],
25	metabolism	NN	O	metabolism	dep	13	SENT_48	[p2l12t3656r382b3714],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l12t3656r382b3714],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l419t3656r526b3705],
28	excretion	NN	O	excretion	conj_and	18	SENT_48	[p2l563t3656r850b3714],
29	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l563t3656r850b3714],
30	ALP	NNP	O	ALP	dep	18	SENT_48	[p2l885t3656r1018b3714],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l885t3656r1018b3714],
32	alkaline	NN	O	alkaline	nn	33	SENT_48	[p2l1055t3656r1290b3705],
33	phosphatase	NN	O	phosphatase	appos	30	SENT_48	[p2l1328t3656r1725b3715],
34	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1328t3656r1725b3715],
35	ALT	NNP	O	ALT	dep	18	SENT_48	[p2l1760t3656r1884b3714],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1760t3656r1884b3714],
37	alanine	NN	O	alanine	nn	38	SENT_48	[p2l1921t3656r2140b3705],
38	transaminase	NN	O	transaminase	appos	35	SENT_48	[p2l9t3742r436b3799],
39	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l9t3742r436b3799],
40	AST	NNP	ORGANIZATION	AST	dep	18	SENT_48	[p2l468t3741r597b3799],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l468t3741r597b3799],
42	aspartate	NN	O	aspartate	nn	43	SENT_48	[p2l632t3744r916b3801],
43	aminotransferase	NN	O	aminotransferase	appos	40	SENT_48	[p2l949t3741r1494b3799],
44	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l949t3741r1494b3799],
45	CI	NN	O	ci	dep	18	SENT_48	[p2l1528t3741r1599b3799],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1528t3741r1599b3799],
47	confidence	NN	O	confidence	nn	48	SENT_48	[p2l1633t3741r1956b3790],
48	interval	NN	O	interval	appos	45	SENT_48	[p2l1991t3742r2142b3790, p3l9t21r107b78],
49	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1991t3742r2142b3790, p3l9t21r107b78],

1	CIOMS	NNP	LOCATION	CIOMS	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l134t21r346b78],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l134t21r346b78],
3	Council	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Council	appos	1	SENT_49	[p3l373t21r588b69],
4	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l613t20r694b69],
5	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	International	nn	6	SENT_49	[p3l720t21r1096b69],
6	Organizations	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Organizations	prep_for	3	SENT_49	[p3l1124t21r1532b81],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1556t20r1613b69],
8	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	9	SENT_49	[p3l1639t21r1865b69],
9	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	prep_of	6	SENT_49	[p3l1890t20r2138b78],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1890t20r2138b78],
11	DILI	NNP	LOCATION	DILI	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l13t107r140b165],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l13t107r140b165],
13	drug-induced	JJ	O	drug-induced	amod	15	SENT_49	[p3l168t107r553b167],
14	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	15	SENT_49	[p3l583t107r704b155],
15	injury	NN	O	injury	appos	11	SENT_49	[p3l731t107r904b168],
16	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l731t107r904b168],
17	DILIN	NNP	LOCATION	DILIN	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l935t107r1108b165],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l935t107r1108b165],
19	drug-induced	JJ	O	drug-induced	amod	22	SENT_49	[p3l1136t107r1520b167],
20	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	22	SENT_49	[p3l1551t107r1672b155],
21	injury	NN	O	injury	nn	22	SENT_49	[p3l1698t107r1858b168],
22	network	NN	O	network	appos	17	SENT_49	[p3l1885t107r2138b165],
23	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1885t107r2138b165],
24	LD	NNP	O	LD	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l13t193r102b250],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l13t193r102b250],
26	linkage	NN	O	linkage	nn	27	SENT_49	[p3l148t193r363b252],
27	disequilibrium	NN	O	disequilibrium	appos	24	SENT_49	[p3l405t193r844b252],
28	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l405t193r844b252],
29	MHC	NN	O	mhc	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l891t192r1041b250],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l891t192r1041b250],
31	major	JJ	O	major	amod	33	SENT_49	[p3l1087t193r1259b254],
32	histocompatibility	NN	O	histocompatibility	nn	33	SENT_49	[p3l1301t193r1833b252],
33	complex	NN	O	complex	appos	29	SENT_49	[p3l1873t193r2138b252],
34	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1873t193r2138b252],
35	NPV	NNP	O	NPV	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l13t279r147b336],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l13t279r147b336],
37	negative	JJ	O	negative	amod	39	SENT_49	[p3l188t279r439b339],
38	predictive	JJ	O	predictive	amod	39	SENT_49	[p3l479t279r766b338],
39	value	NN	O	value	appos	35	SENT_49	[p3l801t279r975b336],
40	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l801t279r975b336],
41	OR	NN	O	or	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l1015t278r1116b336],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1015t278r1116b336],
43	odds	NNS	O	odds	nn	44	SENT_49	[p3l1155t279r1297b327],
44	ratio	NN	O	ratio	appos	41	SENT_49	[p3l1335t279r1483b336],
45	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1335t279r1483b336],
46	PBC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	PBC	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l1524t279r1658b336],
47	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1524t279r1658b336],
48	primary	JJ	O	primary	amod	50	SENT_49	[p3l1700t279r1927b339],
49	biliary	JJ	O	biliary	amod	50	SENT_49	[p3l1965t279r2142b339],
50	cirrhosis	NN	O	cirrhosis	appos	46	SENT_49	[p3l10t365r274b423],
51	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l10t365r274b423],
52	POPRES	NN	LOCATION	popre	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l308t365r570b423],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l308t365r570b423],
54	Population	NNP	O	Population	nn	56	SENT_49	[p3l604t365r920b424],
55	Reference	NNP	O	Reference	nn	56	SENT_49	[p3l955t365r1257b414],
56	Sample	NNP	O	Sample	appos	52	SENT_49	[p3l1285t365r1529b424],
57	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1285t365r1529b424],
58	Q-Q	NNP	O	Q-Q	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l1562t365r1680b423],
59	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1562t365r1680b423],
60	quanti	FW	O	quanti	nn	62	SENT_49	[p3l1712t365r2142b424, p3l9t451r115b508],
61	|	FW	O	|	nn	62	SENT_49	[p3l1712t365r2142b424, p3l9t451r115b508],
62	equantile	NN	O	equantile	appos	58	SENT_49	[p3l1712t365r2142b424, p3l9t451r115b508],
63	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1712t365r2142b424, p3l9t451r115b508],
64	SNP	NN	ORGANIZATION	snp	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l141t450r282b508],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l141t450r282b508],
66	single	JJ	O	single	amod	68	SENT_49	[p3l309t451r483b510],
67	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	68	SENT_49	[p3l512t451r820b499],
68	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	appos	64	SENT_49	[p3l848t451r1288b510],
69	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l848t451r1288b510],
70	ULN	NNP	O	ULN	dep	3	SENT_49	[p3l1318t451r1450b508],
71	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1318t451r1450b508],
72	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	73	SENT_49	[p3l1481t462r1649b510],
73	limit	NN	O	limit	appos	70	SENT_49	[p3l1676t451r1805b499],
74	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1831t450r1888b499],
75	normal	JJ	O	normal	prep_of	73	SENT_49	[p3l1915t451r2138b499],
76	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1915t451r2138b499],

1	©	RB	O	©	dep	2	SENT_50	[p3l678t542r721b585],
2	2011	CD	DATE	2011	dep	3	SENT_50	[p3l743t536r896b585],
3	by	IN	O	by	dep	8	SENT_50	[p3l919t537r980b597],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_50	[p3l999t537r1088b585],
5	AGA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	AGA	nn	6	SENT_50	[p3l1108t536r1232b585],
6	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	pobj	3	SENT_50	[p3l1255t537r1474b585],
7	doi	FW	O	doi	dep	6	SENT_50	[p3l552t708r1600b770],
8	:10.1053	CD	NUMBER	:10.1053	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l552t708r1600b770],
9	/	:	O	/	punct	8	SENT_50	[p3l552t708r1600b770],
10	j.	NN	O	j.	nn	11	SENT_50	[p3l552t708r1600b770],
11	gastro	NN	O	gastro	dep	8	SENT_50	[p3l552t708r1600b770],
12	.2011.04.001	CD	NUMBER	.2011.04.001	dep	11	SENT_50	[p3l552t708r1600b770],

1	July	NNP	DATE	July	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l8t803r120b862],
2	2011	CD	DATE	2011	dep	1	SENT_51	[p3l147t802r309b851],

1	primarily	RB	O	primarily	advmod	11	SENT_52	[p3l10t998r352b1085],
2	due	JJ	O	due	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l391t998r523b1064],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l565t1017r637b1062],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_52	[p3l680t998r794b1062],
5	clavulanate	JJ	O	clavulanate	amod	7	SENT_52	[p3l836t998r1248b1062],
6	component	NN	O	component	nn	7	SENT_52	[p3l1291t1003r1764b1085],
7	,4	NN	O	,4	prep_due_to	11	SENT_52	[p3l1291t1003r1764b1085],
8	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	11	SENT_52	[p3l1804t1001r1858b1062],
9	an	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_52	[p3l1901t1022r1988b1062],
10	important	JJ	O	important	amod	11	SENT_52	[p3l2028t1001r2148b1062, p3l10t1122r290b1190],
11	cause	NN	O	cause	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l326t1127r522b1167],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l560t1103r644b1167],
13	idiosyncratic	JJ	O	idiosyncratic	prep_of	11	SENT_52	[p3l668t1103r1138b1190],
14	DILI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DILI	nsubj	11	SENT_52	[p3l1175t1109r1347b1167],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1383t1106r1455b1167],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_52	[p3l1492t1103r1606b1167],
17	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	18	SENT_52	[p3l1642t1103r1896b1169],
18	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	prep_in	14	SENT_52	[p3l1933t1109r2148b1167],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l11t1208r148b1274],
20	Europe	NNP	LOCATION	Europe	conj_and	14	SENT_52	[p3l199t1213r577b1295],
21	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	num	20	SENT_52	[p3l199t1213r577b1295],
22	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	23	SENT_52	[p3l199t1213r577b1295],
23	7	CD	NUMBER	7	dep	20	SENT_52	[p3l199t1213r577b1295],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l628t1208r766b1274],
25	represents	VBZ	O	represent	conj_and	11	SENT_52	[p3l817t1227r1187b1295],
26	17	CD	PERCENT	17	num	27	SENT_52	[p3l1248t1213r1385b1273],
27	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dobj	25	SENT_52	[p3l1248t1213r1385b1273],
28	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1438t1208r1522b1272],
29	all	DT	O	all	det	30	SENT_52	[p3l1562t1208r1647b1272],
30	DILI	NNP	O	DILI	prep_of	27	SENT_52	[p3l1699t1208r2151b1274],
31	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	33	SENT_52	[p3l1699t1208r2151b1274],
32	related	JJ	O	related	amod	33	SENT_52	[p3l1699t1208r2151b1274],
33	hospitalizations	NNS	O	hospitalization	nsubj	25	SENT_52	[p3l10t1313r697b1400],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l10t1313r697b1400],

1	“	NN	O	“	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l10t1313r697b1400],
2	Whereas	IN	O	whereas	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l734t1313r1044b1377],
3	most	JJS	O	most	amod	4	SENT_53	[p3l1084t1332r1268b1377],
4	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_whereas	1	SENT_53	[p3l1305t1316r1598b1400],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1635t1313r1799b1377],
6	AC	NN	O	ac	prep_with	1	SENT_53	[p3l1834t1319r2150b1377],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1834t1319r2150b1377],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1834t1319r2150b1377],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1834t1319r2150b1377],

1	DlLI	RB	O	dlli	advmod	2	SENT_55	[p3l1834t1319r2150b1377],
2	make	VB	O	make	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l11t1418r207b1482],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_55	[p3l239t1442r278b1482],
4	full	JJ	O	full	amod	5	SENT_55	[p3l307t1418r432b1482],
5	recovery	NN	O	recovery	dobj	2	SENT_55	[p3l463t1422r858b1505],
6	,59	CD	NUMBER	,59	num	7	SENT_55	[p3l463t1422r858b1505],
7	cases	NNS	O	case	nsubjpass	20	SENT_55	[p3l891t1442r1070b1482],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1103t1418r1187b1482],
9	acute	JJ	O	acute	amod	11	SENT_55	[p3l1206t1437r1399b1482],
10	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	11	SENT_55	[p3l1430t1418r1586b1482],
11	failure	NN	O	failure	prep_of	7	SENT_55	[p3l1616t1418r1851b1482],
12	leading	VBG	O	lead	partmod	11	SENT_55	[p3l1882t1418r2151b1505],
13	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l11t1542r83b1587],
14	death	NN	O	death	nn	17	SENT_55	[p3l132t1523r336b1589],
15	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l384t1546r460b1587],
16	liver	NN	O	liver	conj_or	14	SENT_55	[p3l504t1523r661b1587],
17	transplantation	NN	O	transplantation	prep_to	12	SENT_55	[p3l706t1523r1282b1610],
18	have	VBP	O	have	aux	20	SENT_55	[p3l1328t1523r1492b1587],
19	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_55	[p3l1537t1523r1708b1587],
20	reported	VBN	O	report	dep	2	SENT_55	[p3l1755t1523r2149b1610],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1755t1523r2149b1610],

1	”	NN	O	”	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1755t1523r2149b1610],
2	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_56	[p3l8t1628r150b1692],
3	mechanism	NN	O	mechanism	dep	1	SENT_56	[p3l186t1628r607b1692],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l643t1628r727b1692],
5	AC	NN	O	ac	prep_of	3	SENT_56	[p3l746t1634r1062b1692],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l746t1634r1062b1692],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l746t1634r1062b1692],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l746t1634r1062b1692],

1	DlLl	NN	O	dlll	nsubj	3	SENT_58	[p3l746t1634r1062b1692],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	3	SENT_58	[p3l1097t1631r1150b1692],
3	unknown	JJ	O	unknown	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1187t1628r1556b1692],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1187t1628r1556b1692],

1	Three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	3	SENT_59	[p3l1592t1628r1804b1692],
2	previous	JJ	O	previous	amod	3	SENT_59	[p3l1839t1631r2148b1715],
3	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	9	SENT_59	[p3l11t1733r266b1799],
4	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l300t1733r480b1797],
5	Northwestern	NNP	MISC	Northwestern	nn	6	SENT_59	[p3l511t1733r1022b1798],
6	Europe11	NN	O	europe11	prep_from	3	SENT_59	[p3l1054t1738r1474b1820],
7	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	number	8	SENT_59	[p3l1054t1738r1474b1820],
8	13	CD	NUMBER	13	num	6	SENT_59	[p3l1054t1738r1474b1820],
9	reported	VBD	O	report	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1509t1733r1822b1820],
10	an	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_59	[p3l1853t1757r1940b1797],
11	association	NN	O	association	dobj	9	SENT_59	[p3l1972t1757r2149b1797, p3l11t1841r263b1902],
12	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l318t1838r617b1902],
13	AC-DILI	NN	O	ac-dili	prep_between	11	SENT_59	[p3l670t1844r986b1902],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1043t1838r1180b1904],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_59	[p3l1235t1838r1349b1902],
16	HLA	NN	O	hlum	nn	20	SENT_59	[p3l1406t1844r1576b1902],
17	class	NN	O	class	nn	20	SENT_59	[p3l1631t1838r1796b1902],
18	II	CD	NUMBER	ii	num	20	SENT_59	[p3l1853t1844r1908b1902],
19	allele	NN	O	allele	nn	20	SENT_59	[p3l1965t1838r2149b1902],
20	DRB1	NN	O	drb1	dobj	9	SENT_59	[p3l7t1948r445b2022],
21	*	CD	NUMBER	*	number	22	SENT_59	[p3l7t1948r445b2022],
22	1501	CD	DATE	1501	dep	20	SENT_59	[p3l7t1948r445b2022],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l7t1948r445b2022],
24	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l487t1943r651b2007],
25	odds	NNS	O	odds	nn	26	SENT_59	[p3l694t1943r868b2009],
26	ratios	NNS	O	ratio	prep_with	9	SENT_59	[p3l912t1946r1116b2007],
27	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	29	SENT_59	[p3l1162t1944r1332b2026],
28	OR	NN	O	or	nn	29	SENT_59	[p3l1162t1944r1332b2026],
29	)	NN	O	)	dep	26	SENT_59	[p3l1162t1944r1332b2026],
30	ranging	VBG	O	range	partmod	26	SENT_59	[p3l1379t1946r1663b2030],
31	between	IN	O	between	quantmod	32	SENT_59	[p3l1702t1943r2002b2007],
32	2.6	CD	NUMBER	2.6	dobj	30	SENT_59	[p3l2043t1948r2148b2007],
33	and	CC	NUMBER	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l11t2048r148b2114],
34	10	CD	NUMBER	10	conj_and	32	SENT_59	[p3l205t2053r301b2112],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l205t2053r301b2112],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_60	[p3l352t2054r408b2112],
2	further	JJ	O	further	amod	3	SENT_60	[p3l458t2048r719b2112],
3	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	10	SENT_60	[p3l769t2048r971b2135],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1020t2048r1104b2112],
5	27	CD	NUMBER	27	num	7	SENT_60	[p3l1142t2054r1230b2113],
6	Spanish	JJ	MISC	spanish	amod	7	SENT_60	[p3l1282t2048r1573b2135],
7	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	3	SENT_60	[p3l1625t2072r1803b2112],
8	did	VBD	O	do	aux	10	SENT_60	[p3l1857t2048r1975b2114],
9	not	RB	O	not	neg	10	SENT_60	[p3l2025t2067r2150b2112],
10	observe	VB	O	observe	dep	42	SENT_60	[p3l11t2153r282b2217],
11	a	DT	O	a	det	13	SENT_60	[p3l326t2177r365b2217],
12	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	amod	13	SENT_60	[p3l406t2153r790b2240],
13	association	NN	O	association	dobj	10	SENT_60	[p3l832t2156r1241b2217],
14	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1282t2153r1445b2217],
15	DRB1	NN	O	drb1	prep_with	10	SENT_60	[p3l1485t2158r1822b2217],
16	*	CD	NUMBER	*	number	17	SENT_60	[p3l1485t2158r1822b2217],
17	15	CD	NUMBER	15	num	15	SENT_60	[p3l1485t2158r1822b2217],
18	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1862t2153r1989b2217],
19	did	VBD	O	do	dep	42	SENT_60	[p3l2032t2153r2151b2219],
20	report	VB	O	report	ccomp	19	SENT_60	[p3l12t2277r238b2345],
21	a	DT	O	a	det	24	SENT_60	[p3l266t2282r305b2322],
22	signiﬁcantly	RB	O	signiﬁcantly	advmod	23	SENT_60	[p3l331t2258r782b2345],
23	higher	JJR	O	higher	amod	24	SENT_60	[p3l807t2258r1044b2345],
24	frequency	NN	O	frequency	dobj	20	SENT_60	[p3l1072t2258r1433b2345],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1459t2258r1543b2322],
26	DQB1	NN	O	dqb1	prep_of	24	SENT_60	[p3l1556t2264r1765b2340],
27	*	CD	NUMBER	*	number	28	SENT_60	[p3l1782t2263r1983b2322],
28	06.14	CD	NUMBER	06.14	num	30	SENT_60	[p3l1782t2263r1983b2322],
29	The	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_60	[p3l2008t2258r2149b2322],
30	differences	NNS	O	difference	dep	20	SENT_60	[p3l11t2363r405b2429],
31	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l446t2366r517b2427],
32	ﬁndings	NNS	O	ﬁndings	prep_in	30	SENT_60	[p3l557t2363r855b2450],
33	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l895t2363r1194b2427],
34	the	DT	O	the	det	35	SENT_60	[p3l1235t2363r1348b2427],
35	Spanish	JJ	MISC	spanish	prep_between	32	SENT_60	[p3l1390t2363r1681b2450],
36	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1722t2363r1859b2429],
37	Northwestern	NNP	MISC	Northwestern	nn	39	SENT_60	[p3l1897t2363r2148b2427, p3l9t2487r291b2532],
38	European	JJ	MISC	european	amod	39	SENT_60	[p3l342t2474r699b2555],
39	studies	NNS	O	study	conj_and	35	SENT_60	[p3l751t2468r1005b2534],
40	may	MD	O	may	aux	42	SENT_60	[p3l1059t2492r1212b2555],
41	be	VB	O	be	cop	42	SENT_60	[p3l1259t2468r1341b2532],
42	due	JJ	O	due	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1393t2468r1525b2534],
43	to	TO	O	to	aux	44	SENT_60	[p3l1578t2487r1649b2532],
44	use	VB	O	use	xcomp	42	SENT_60	[p3l1702t2492r1820b2532],
45	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1873t2468r1957b2532],
46	lowresolution	JJ	O	lowresolution	amod	47	SENT_60	[p3l1995t2468r2148b2532, p3l12t2574r387b2638],
47	genotyping	NN	O	genotyping	prep_of	44	SENT_60	[p3l453t2577r884b2661],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l453t2577r884b2661],
49	population-speciﬁc	NN	O	population-speciﬁc	nn	50	SENT_60	[p3l951t2574r1659b2661],
50	linkage	NN	O	linkage	appos	47	SENT_60	[p3l1724t2574r2148b2661],
51	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	53	SENT_60	[p3l1724t2574r2148b2661],
52	dis	NN	O	di	nn	53	SENT_60	[p3l1724t2574r2148b2661],
53	—	NN	O	—	nsubj	42	SENT_60	[p3l1724t2574r2148b2661],

1	equilibrium	NN	O	equilibrium	nn	2	SENT_61	[p3l11t2715r446b2802],
2	patterns	NNS	O	pattern	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l494t2734r815b2802],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l494t2734r815b2802],
4	population	NN	O	population	nn	5	SENT_61	[p3l865t2715r1277b2802],
5	stratiﬁcation	NN	O	stratiﬁcation	conj_or	2	SENT_61	[p3l1325t2715r1816b2794],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1325t2715r1816b2794],
7	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1866t2738r1943b2779],
8	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1991t2734r2062b2779],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_61	[p3l2114t2739r2152b2779],
10	larger	JJR	O	larger	amod	11	SENT_61	[p3l10t2856r220b2943],
11	proportion	NN	O	proportion	prep_to	15	SENT_61	[p3l257t2859r664b2943],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l703t2856r787b2920],
13	hepatocellular	JJ	O	hepatocellular	amod	14	SENT_61	[p3l813t2856r1339b2943],
14	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	11	SENT_61	[p3l1377t2880r1555b2920],
15	in	IN	O	in	conj_or	2	SENT_61	[p3l1594t2859r1666b2920],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_61	[p3l1705t2856r1818b2920],
17	Spanish	JJ	MISC	spanish	amod	18	SENT_61	[p3l1858t2856r2150b2943],
18	study	NN	O	study	pobj	15	SENT_61	[p3l11t2961r292b3048],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l11t2961r292b3048],

1	”	NN	O	”	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l11t2961r292b3048],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_63	[p3l97t3072r212b3130],
2	conducted	VBD	O	conduct	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l241t3066r628b3132],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_63	[p3l655t3090r694b3130],
4	genome-wide	JJ	O	genome-wide	amod	9	SENT_63	[p3l719t3066r1204b3153],
5	association	NN	O	association	nn	9	SENT_63	[p3l1233t3069r1642b3130],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	9	SENT_63	[p3l1672t3066r1918b3150],
7	GWA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GWA	nn	9	SENT_63	[p3l1672t3066r1918b3150],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	9	SENT_63	[p3l1672t3066r1918b3150],
9	study	NN	O	study	dobj	2	SENT_63	[p3l1951t3066r2153b3153],
10	to	TO	O	to	aux	11	SENT_63	[p3l11t3191r83b3236],
11	investigate	VB	O	investigate	xcomp	2	SENT_63	[p3l126t3175r517b3259],
12	whether	IN	O	whether	complm	17	SENT_63	[p3l558t3172r858b3236],
13	additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	16	SENT_63	[p3l899t3172r1277b3238],
14	common	JJ	O	common	amod	16	SENT_63	[p3l1319t3196r1648b3236],
15	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	16	SENT_63	[p3l1690t3175r1949b3259],
16	variants	NNS	O	variant	nsubj	17	SENT_63	[p3l1988t3175r2148b3236, p3l11t3296r162b3341],
17	affect	VBP	O	affect	ccomp	11	SENT_63	[p3l211t3277r413b3341],
18	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	dobj	17	SENT_63	[p3l461t3277r949b3364],
19	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l994t3296r1065b3341],
20	AC	NN	O	ac	prep_to	17	SENT_63	[p3l1112t3283r1444b3341],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1112t3283r1444b3341],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1112t3283r1444b3341],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1112t3283r1444b3341],

1	DILI	NNP	LOCATION	DILI	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1112t3283r1444b3341],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1112t3283r1444b3341],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_66	[p3l1492t3283r1548b3341],
2	group	NN	O	group	nsubj	6	SENT_66	[p3l1594t3300r1811b3364],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1862t3277r1946b3341],
4	wellphenotyped	JJ	O	wellphenotyped	amod	5	SENT_66	[p3l1979t3277r2148b3341, p3l10t3382r449b3469],
5	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	2	SENT_66	[p3l492t3406r670b3446],
6	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l718t3382r790b3466],
7	n	NN	O	n	nsubjpass	16	SENT_66	[p3l718t3382r790b3466],
8	=	JJ	O	=	dep	16	SENT_66	[p3l841t3406r894b3427],
9	201	CD	NUMBER	201	num	10	SENT_66	[p3l946t3383r1103b3465],
10	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	16	SENT_66	[p3l946t3383r1103b3465],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1150t3382r1313b3446],
12	high	JJ	O	high	amod	14	SENT_66	[p3l1358t3382r1523b3469],
13	causality	NN	O	causality	nn	14	SENT_66	[p3l1568t3382r1889b3469],
14	scores	NNS	O	score	prep_with	10	SENT_66	[p3l1931t3405r2148b3446],
15	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_66	[p3l9t3511r174b3551],
16	assembled	VBN	O	assemble	xcomp	6	SENT_66	[p3l218t3487r595b3553],
17	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l636t3487r817b3551],
18	several	JJ	O	several	amod	20	SENT_66	[p3l859t3487r1101b3551],
19	multicenter	JJ	O	multicenter	amod	20	SENT_66	[p3l1143t3487r1573b3551],
20	collections	NNS	O	collection	prep_from	16	SENT_66	[p3l1615t3487r2005b3551],
21	together	RB	O	together	advmod	16	SENT_66	[p3l2050t3506r2148b3551, p4l11t27r242b114],

1	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_67	[p4l268t27r431b91],
2	532	CD	NUMBER	532	num	6	SENT_67	[p4l462t32r592b91],
3	genetically	RB	O	genetically	advmod	4	SENT_67	[p4l625t27r1015b114],
4	matched	VBN	O	match	amod	6	SENT_67	[p4l1042t27r1361b93],
5	population	NN	O	population	nn	6	SENT_67	[p4l1389t27r1800b114],
6	controls	NNS	O	control	pobj	1	SENT_67	[p4l1830t27r2147b91],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p4l1830t27r2147b91],

1	Our	PRP$	O	we	poss	2	SENT_68	[p4l12t138r160b196],
2	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	3	SENT_68	[p4l189t132r390b219],
3	conﬁrms	VBZ	O	conﬁrms	_	0	SENT_68	[p4l418t132r740b196],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_68	[p4l772t132r885b196],
5	DRB1	NN	O	drb1	dobj	3	SENT_68	[p4l912t138r1114b196],
6	*	CD	NUMBER	*	number	7	SENT_68	[p4l1132t137r1326b196],
7	1501	CD	DATE	1501	num	8	SENT_68	[p4l1132t137r1326b196],
8	association	NN	O	association	dep	5	SENT_68	[p4l1362t135r1771b196],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_68	[p4l1801t132r1938b198],
10	identiﬁes	NNS	O	identiﬁes	dobj	3	SENT_68	[p4l1966t132r2148b198, p4l11t237r183b301],
11	additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	13	SENT_68	[p4l219t237r597b303],
12	HLA	NN	O	hlum	nn	13	SENT_68	[p4l630t243r801b301],
13	class	NN	O	class	dep	10	SENT_68	[p4l833t237r998b301],
14	I	CD	NUMBER	i	nn	17	SENT_68	[p4l1032t243r1058b301],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_68	[p4l1092t237r1229b303],
16	II	CD	NUMBER	ii	nn	17	SENT_68	[p4l1261t243r1316b301],
17	associations	NNS	O	association	dep	10	SENT_68	[p4l1350t240r1809b301],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p4l1350t240r1809b301],

1	Materials	NNPS	O	Materials	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l279t462r690b534],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l728t463r892b534],
3	Methods	NNS	O	method	conj_and	1	SENT_69	[p4l937t463r1326b534],

1	Case	NNP	O	Case	_	0	SENT_70	[p4l278t579r453b644],
2	Recruitment	NN	O	recruitment	dep	1	SENT_70	[p4l483t577r984b644],

1	Cases	NNS	O	case	nsubj	2	SENT_71	[p4l277t694r475b752],
2	(	VBP	O	(	dep	22	SENT_71	[p4l510t689r582b771],
3	n	NN	O	n	nsubj	13	SENT_71	[p4l510t689r582b771],
4	=	JJ	O	=	dep	13	SENT_71	[p4l620t712r673b733],
5	211	CD	NUMBER	211	num	6	SENT_71	[p4l712t689r870b772],
6	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	8	SENT_71	[p4l712t689r870b772],
7	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_71	[p4l902t712r1068b752],
8	recruited	VBN	O	recruit	dep	13	SENT_71	[p4l1100t688r1429b754],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_71	[p4l1458t691r1530b752],
10	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	12	SENT_71	[p4l1560t694r1602b752],
11	separate	JJ	O	separate	amod	12	SENT_71	[p4l1633t707r1932b775],
12	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_in	8	SENT_71	[p4l1963t688r2148b754, p4l10t796r101b857],
13	(	VBP	O	(	xcomp	2	SENT_71	[p4l155t793r621b877],
14	DILIGEN	NNP	O	DILIGEN	dobj	13	SENT_71	[p4l155t793r621b877],
15	,16	CD	NUMBER	,16	num	18	SENT_71	[p4l155t793r621b877],
16	Spanish	JJ	MISC	spanish	amod	18	SENT_71	[p4l672t793r964b880],
17	DILI	NNP	O	DILI	nn	18	SENT_71	[p4l1015t799r1186b857],
18	Registry	NN	O	registry	nsubj	13	SENT_71	[p4l1236t796r1583b880],
19	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	num	21	SENT_71	[p4l1236t796r1583b880],
20	Drug	NN	O	drug	nn	21	SENT_71	[p4l1634t793r2151b880],
21	—	NN	O	—	nsubj	22	SENT_71	[p4l1634t793r2151b880],
22	induced	VBD	O	induce	_	0	SENT_71	[p4l1634t793r2151b880],
23	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	24	SENT_71	[p4l10t898r166b962],
24	injury	NN	O	injury	iobj	22	SENT_71	[p4l199t901r419b985],
25	network	NN	O	network	nn	27	SENT_71	[p4l451t898r754b962],
26	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	27	SENT_71	[p4l794t898r1136b981],
27	DILIN	NNP	O	DILIN	dobj	22	SENT_71	[p4l794t898r1136b981],
28	]	CD	NUMBER	]	number	29	SENT_71	[p4l794t898r1136b981],
29	,7	CD	NUMBER	,7	dep	27	SENT_71	[p4l794t898r1136b981],
30	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_71	[p4l1172t898r1309b964],
31	EUDRAGENE17	NN	O	eudragene17	nn	32	SENT_71	[p4l1343t899r1962b981],
32	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	27	SENT_71	[p4l1343t899r1962b981],
33	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	34	SENT_71	[p4l2001t898r2151b962],
34	used	VBD	O	use	rcmod	32	SENT_71	[p4l11t1004r179b1070],
35	similar	JJ	O	similar	amod	37	SENT_71	[p4l218t1004r471b1068],
36	inclusion	NN	O	inclusion	nn	37	SENT_71	[p4l508t1004r850b1068],
37	criteria	NNS	O	criterion	dobj	34	SENT_71	[p4l889t1007r1162b1068],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p4l889t1007r1162b1068],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	2	SENT_72	[p4l1202t1004r1306b1068],
2	participants	NNS	O	participant	nsubj	3	SENT_72	[p4l1344t1007r1785b1091],
3	provided	VBD	O	provide	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l1826t1004r2151b1091],
4	written	VBN	O	write	amod	6	SENT_72	[p4l9t1112r275b1173],
5	informed	VBN	O	inform	amod	6	SENT_72	[p4l313t1109r657b1175],
6	consent	NN	O	consent	dobj	3	SENT_72	[p4l695t1128r998b1188],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l695t1128r998b1188],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l1039t1109r1176b1175],
9	each	DT	O	each	det	10	SENT_72	[p4l1214t1109r1375b1173],
10	study	NN	O	study	nsubjpass	13	SENT_72	[p4l1416t1109r1618b1196],
11	had	VBD	O	have	aux	13	SENT_72	[p4l1654t1109r1792b1175],
12	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_72	[p4l1828t1109r1999b1173],
13	approved	VBN	O	approve	conj_and	3	SENT_72	[p4l2039t1132r2148b1196, p4l10t1215r262b1302],
14	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l293t1215r380b1302],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_72	[p4l411t1215r525b1279],
16	appropriate	JJ	O	appropriate	amod	19	SENT_72	[p4l559t1218r989b1302],
17	ethical	JJ	O	ethical	amod	19	SENT_72	[p4l1024t1215r1266b1279],
18	review	NN	O	review	nn	19	SENT_72	[p4l1300t1218r1530b1279],
19	boards	NNS	O	board	agent	13	SENT_72	[p4l1558t1215r1824b1281],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l1558t1215r1824b1281],

1	DILIGEN	NNP	O	DILIGEN	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l278t1324r611b1385],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l278t1324r611b1385],

1	Between	IN	O	between	dep	9	SENT_74	[p4l664t1326r968b1384],
2	October	NNP	DATE	October	pobj	1	SENT_74	[p4l1007t1320r1305b1384],
3	2004	CD	DATE	2004	num	2	SENT_74	[p4l1341t1326r1520b1384],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l1558t1320r1695b1386],
5	April	NNP	DATE	April	conj_and	2	SENT_74	[p4l1728t1320r1914b1407],
6	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	5	SENT_74	[p4l1951t1326r2148b1400],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l1951t1326r2148b1400],
8	78	CD	NUMBER	78	num	9	SENT_74	[p4l13t1431r96b1490],
9	cases	NNS	O	case	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l149t1449r327b1489],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l379t1425r463b1489],
11	AC	NN	O	ac	prep_of	9	SENT_74	[p4l498t1431r813b1489],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l498t1431r813b1489],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l498t1431r813b1489],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l498t1431r813b1489],

1	DILI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DILI	nsubjpass	12	SENT_76	[p4l498t1431r813b1489],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l865t1425r949b1489],
3	European	NNP	MISC	European	nn	4	SENT_76	[p4l987t1431r1343b1512],
4	origin	NN	O	origin	prep_of	1	SENT_76	[p4l1394t1428r1613b1512],
5	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1663t1425r1843b1489],
6	centers	NNS	O	center	prep_from	4	SENT_76	[p4l1894t1444r2149b1489],
7	throughout	IN	O	throughout	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l11t1530r443b1617],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_76	[p4l467t1530r581b1594],
9	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	10	SENT_76	[p4l605t1530r859b1596],
10	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	prep_throughout	6	SENT_76	[p4l882t1530r1227b1617],
11	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	12	SENT_76	[p4l1249t1553r1414b1594],
12	collected	VBN	O	collect	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1439t1530r1777b1596],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1439t1530r1777b1596],

1	Inclusion	NN	O	inclusion	nn	2	SENT_77	[p4l1804t1530r2150b1594],
2	criteria	NNS	O	criterion	nsubjpass	4	SENT_77	[p4l11t1638r271b1699],
3	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_77	[p4l312t1658r477b1699],
4	suspected	VBN	O	suspect	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l524t1635r881b1722],
5	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	6	SENT_77	[p4l924t1635r1081b1699],
6	injury	NN	O	injury	dobj	4	SENT_77	[p4l1124t1638r1344b1722],
7	because	IN	O	because	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1385t1635r1668b1699],
8	of	IN	O	of	prepc_because_of	4	SENT_77	[p4l1715t1635r1799b1699],
9	AC	NN	O	ac	pobj	4	SENT_77	[p4l1829t1641r1940b1699],
10	with	IN	O	with	prep	4	SENT_77	[p4l1986t1635r2149b1699],
11	either	CC	O	either	dep	10	SENT_77	[p4l11t1740r222b1804],
12	(	NN	O	(	conj	10	SENT_77	[p4l265t1741r355b1824],
13	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	12	SENT_77	[p4l265t1741r355b1824],
14	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	17	SENT_77	[p4l265t1741r355b1824],
15	clinically	RB	O	clinically	advmod	16	SENT_77	[p4l402t1740r728b1827],
16	apparent	JJ	O	apparent	amod	17	SENT_77	[p4l768t1759r1095b1827],
17	jaundice	NN	O	jaundice	npadvmod	10	SENT_77	[p4l1130t1740r1445b1827],
18	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1488t1764r1565b1804],
19	bilirubin	NN	O	bilirubin	dep	20	SENT_77	[p4l1604t1740r1928b1804],
20	>	JJR	O	>	npadvmod	10	SENT_77	[p4l1974t1746r2150b1804],
21	2.4	CD	NUMBER	2.4	num	23	SENT_77	[p4l1974t1746r2150b1804],
22	mg/dL	NN	O	mg/dl	nn	23	SENT_77	[p4l11t1845r259b1932],
23	(	NN	O	(	dep	20	SENT_77	[p4l290t1845r484b1929],
24	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l290t1845r484b1929],
25	exclusion	NN	O	exclusion	prep_after	10	SENT_77	[p4l513t1845r857b1909],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l887t1845r971b1909],
27	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	25	SENT_77	[p4l989t1869r1167b1909],
28	because	IN	O	because	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1197t1845r1480b1909],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1511t1845r1595b1909],
30	hemolysis	NN	O	hemolysis	nn	31	SENT_77	[p4l1612t1845r2021b1932],
31	)	NN	O	)	prep_because_of	27	SENT_77	[p4l1612t1845r2021b1932],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1612t1845r2021b1932],
33	(	NN	O	(	dep	40	SENT_77	[p4l2055t1846r2146b1929],
34	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	35	SENT_77	[p4l2055t1846r2146b1929],
35	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	33	SENT_77	[p4l2055t1846r2146b1929],
36	ALT	NNP	O	ALT	dep	35	SENT_77	[p4l8t1956r168b2014],
37	>	JJR	O	>	amod	38	SENT_77	[p4l212t1955r381b2014],
38	5X	NN	O	5x	dep	40	SENT_77	[p4l212t1955r381b2014],
39	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	40	SENT_77	[p4l422t1973r638b2037],
40	limit	NN	O	limit	dep	52	SENT_77	[p4l677t1950r854b2014],
41	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l895t1950r979b2014],
42	normal	JJ	O	normal	amod	45	SENT_77	[p4l1008t1950r1275b2014],
43	(	NN	O	(	nn	45	SENT_77	[p4l1318t1950r1566b2034],
44	ULN	NN	O	uln	nn	45	SENT_77	[p4l1318t1950r1566b2034],
45	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	40	SENT_77	[p4l1318t1950r1566b2034],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1318t1950r1566b2034],
47	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1609t1973r1686b2014],
48	(	NN	O	(	nn	51	SENT_77	[p4l1728t1951r1818b2034],
49	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	51	SENT_77	[p4l1728t1951r1818b2034],
50	)	NN	O	)	nn	51	SENT_77	[p4l1728t1951r1818b2034],
51	alkaline	NN	O	alkaline	conj_or	45	SENT_77	[p4l1864t1950r2149b2014],
52	phosphatase	NN	O	phosphatase	dep	54	SENT_77	[p4l11t2055r472b2142],
53	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	52	SENT_77	[p4l509t2056r708b2138],
54	ALP	NN	O	alp	dep	58	SENT_77	[p4l509t2056r708b2138],
55	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	54	SENT_77	[p4l509t2056r708b2138],
56	>	JJR	O	>	amod	58	SENT_77	[p4l750t2061r919b2119],
57	2X	NN	O	2x	nn	58	SENT_77	[p4l750t2061r919b2119],
58	ULN	NN	O	uln	dep	25	SENT_77	[p4l953t2061r1132b2120],
59	plus	CC	O	plus	prep	58	SENT_77	[p4l1165t2055r1318b2142],
60	bilirubin	NN	O	bilirubin	dep	59	SENT_77	[p4l1353t2055r1677b2119],
61	above	IN	O	above	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1711t2055r1918b2119],
62	ULN	NNP	O	ULN	prep_above	60	SENT_77	[p4l1953t2061r2147b2120],
63	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1953t2061r2147b2120],
