1	I	PRP	O	I	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l554t35r573b63],

1	‘	NN	O	‘	nn	2	SENT_2	[p1l200t49r303b100],
2	u	NN	O	u	dep	10	SENT_2	[p1l200t49r303b100],
3	o	NN	O	o	dep	2	SENT_2	[p1l435t54r459b102],
4	an	DT	O	a	dep	3	SENT_2	[p1l554t54r758b124],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l554t54r758b124],
6	HUMAN	NNP	O	HUMAN	nn	8	SENT_2	[p1l166t154r329b181],
7	GEN	NNP	O	GEN	nn	8	SENT_2	[p1l352t154r439b181],
8	ETIC	NNP	O	ETIC	dep	3	SENT_2	[p1l448t154r544b181],
9	STUDY	NN	O	study	dep	10	SENT_2	[p1l566t154r710b181],
10	doi	FW	O	doi	dep	14	SENT_2	[p1l1479t129r1953b186],
11	:10.1111	CD	NUMBER	:10.1111	dep	10	SENT_2	[p1l1479t129r1953b186],
12	/	:	O	/	punct	14	SENT_2	[p1l1479t129r1953b186],
13	j.1369-1600	CD	DURATION	j.1369-1600	num	14	SENT_2	[p1l1479t129r1953b186],
14	.2011.0039	CD	NUMBER	.2011.0039	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1479t129r1953b186],

1	U1	NN	O	u1	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1958t160r1970b181],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1974t167r1994b181],

1	X	NN	O	x	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1974t167r1994b181],

1	Genome-wide	JJ	O	genome-wide	amod	3	SENT_5	[p1l166t269r626b319],
2	significant	JJ	O	significant	amod	3	SENT_5	[p1l654t269r983b334],
3	association	NN	O	association	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1010t269r1367b319],
4	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1398t269r1672b319],
5	alcohol	NN	O	alcohol	nn	6	SENT_5	[p1l1702t269r1932b319],
6	dependence	NN	O	dependence	prep_between	3	SENT_5	[p1l165t359r559b424],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l586t359r700b409],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_5	[p1l730t374r766b409],
9	variant	NN	O	variant	prep_between	3	SENT_5	[p1l789t359r1020b409],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1048t359r1101b408],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_5	[p1l1129t359r1235b409],
12	ADH	NN	O	adh	nn	14	SENT_5	[p1l1259t359r1413b408],
13	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	14	SENT_5	[p1l1439t374r1592b424],
14	cluster	NN	O	cluster	prep_in	3	SENT_5	[p1l1620t359r1844b409],

1	Josef	NNP	PERSON	Josef	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l162t504r256b547],
2	Frank	NNP	PERSON	Frank	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l274t499r404b543],
3	‘	NNP	PERSON	‘	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l274t499r404b543],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l274t499r404b543],
5	Sven	NNP	PERSON	Sven	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l421t504r505b537],
6	Cichon	NNP	PERSON	Cichon	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l526t499r720b543],
7	"	``	O	"	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l526t499r720b543],
8	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l526t499r720b543],
9	"	``	O	"	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l526t499r720b543],
10	‘	NN	O	‘	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l526t499r720b543],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l526t499r720b543],
12	jens	VBZ	PERSON	jen	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l734t504r812b547],
13	Treut	NNP	PERSON	Treut	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l832t499r1026b543],
14	|	NNP	O	|	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l832t499r1026b543],
15	ein	NN	O	ein	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l832t499r1026b543],
16	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l832t499r1026b543],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l832t499r1026b543],
18	Monika	NNP	PERSON	Monika	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1045t504r1181b537],
19	Ridinger5	NNP	PERSON	Ridinger5	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1202t499r1384b547],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1202t499r1384b547],
21	Manuel	NNP	PERSON	Manuel	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1402t504r1534b537],
22	Mattheisen	NNP	PERSON	Mattheisen	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1558t499r1835b543],
23	"	``	O	"	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1558t499r1835b543],
24	"	``	O	"	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1558t499r1835b543],
25	7	CD	NUMBER	7	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1558t499r1835b543],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1558t499r1835b543],
27	Per	IN	PERSON	per	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l166t558r226b590],
28	Hoffmann	NNP	PERSON	Hoffmann	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l247t553r476b597],
29	”	NNP	O	”	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l247t553r476b597],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l247t553r476b597],
31	Stefan	NNP	PERSON	Stefan	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l493t558r609b590],
32	Herms	NNP	PERSON	Herms	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l633t553r799b597],
33	“	NNP	O	“	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l633t553r799b597],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l633t553r799b597],
35	Norbert	NNP	PERSON	Norbert	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l817t558r967b590],
36	Wodarzs	NNP	PERSON	Wodarzs	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l987t553r1156b597],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l987t553r1156b597],
38	Michael	NNP	PERSON	Michael	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1175t558r1314b590],
39	Soyka	NNP	PERSON	Soyka	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1336t553r1491b600],
40	”	NN	O	”	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1336t553r1491b600],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1336t553r1491b600],
42	Peter	NNP	PERSON	Peter	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1509t558r1609b590],
43	Zill	NNP	PERSON	Zill	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1627t553r1710b597],
44	’	NNP	O	’	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1627t553r1710b597],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1627t553r1710b597],
46	Wolfgang	NNP	PERSON	Wolfgang	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l163t620r339b663],
47	Maier	NNP	PERSON	Maier	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l360t615r502b659],
48	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l360t615r502b659],
49	°	NN	O	°	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l360t615r502b659],
50	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l360t615r502b659],
51	Rainald	NN	O	rainald	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l520t620r657b653],
52	M6ssner	NN	O	m6ssner	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l681t615r874b659],
53	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l681t615r874b659],
54	°	RB	O	°	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l681t615r874b659],
55	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l681t615r874b659],
56	Wolfgang	NNP	PERSON	Wolfgang	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l890t620r1065b663],
57	Gaebel	NNP	PERSON	Gaebel	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1085t615r1250b659],
58	"	``	O	"	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1085t615r1250b659],
59	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1085t615r1250b659],
60	Norbert	NNP	PERSON	Norbert	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1269t620r1419b653],
61	Dahmen	NNP	PERSON	Dahmen	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1441t615r1634b659],
62	"	``	O	"	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1441t615r1634b659],
63	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1441t615r1634b659],
64	Norbert	NNP	PERSON	Norbert	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l166t679r316b711],
65	Scherbaum	NNP	PERSON	Scherbaum	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l337t674r586b717],
66	”	NN	O	”	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l337t674r586b717],
67	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l337t674r586b717],
68	Christine	NNP	PERSON	Christine	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l603t678r772b711],
69	Schma	NNP	PERSON	Schma	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l793t674r952b717],
70	|	NN	O	|	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l793t674r952b717],
71	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l793t674r952b717],
72	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l793t674r952b717],
73	Michael	NNP	PERSON	Michael	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l970t679r1109b711],
74	Steffens	NNP	PERSON	Steffens	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1131t674r1305b717],
75	‘	NNP	O	‘	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1131t674r1305b717],
76	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1131t674r1305b717],
77	Susanne	NNP	PERSON	Susanne	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1322t678r1474b711],
78	Lucae	NNP	PERSON	Lucae	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1496t674r1642b717],
79	"	``	O	"	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1496t674r1642b717],
80	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1496t674r1642b717],
81	Marcus	NNP	PERSON	Marcus	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1660t679r1791b711],
82	lsing	VBG	O	lsing	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1813t674r1938b721],
83	”	NN	O	”	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1813t674r1938b721],
84	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1813t674r1938b721],
85	Bertram	NNP	PERSON	Bertram	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l166t741r323b773],
86	Miiller-Myhsok	NNP	PERSON	Miiller-Myhsok	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l346t736r664b783],
87	"	``	O	"	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l346t736r664b783],
88	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l346t736r664b783],
89	Markus	NNP	PERSON	Markus	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l682t741r818b773],
90	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l840t741r881b773],
91	Niithen	NNP	PERSON	Niithen	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l904t736r1088b780],
92	”	NN	O	”	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l904t736r1088b780],
93	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l904t736r1088b780],
94	Karl	NNP	PERSON	Karl	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1105t741r1180b773],
95	Mann	NNP	PERSON	Mann	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1204t736r1343b780],
96	”	NNP	O	”	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1204t736r1343b780],
97	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1204t736r1343b780],
98	Falk	NNP	PERSON	Falk	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1362t741r1436b773],
99	Kiefer	NNP	PERSON	Kiefer	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1456t736r1594b773],
100	”	NNP	O	”	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1456t736r1594b773],
101	&	CC	O	&	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1615t740r1640b773],
102	Marcella	NNP	PERSON	Marcella	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l166t800r322b832],
103	Rietsche	NNP	PERSON	Rietsche	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l343t795r522b832],
104	|	NN	O	|	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l343t795r522b832],
105	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l343t795r522b832],
106	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l165t870r306b897],
107	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l315t870r340b891],
108	Genetic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetic	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l345t870r433b891],
109	Epidemiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Epidemiology	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l443t870r594b897],
110	in	IN	ORGANIZATION	in	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l603t870r620b890],
111	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l631t870r744b897],
112	Central	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Central	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l752t870r834b891],
113	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l846t870r934b891],
114	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l943t870r968b891],
115	Mental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mental	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l974t870r1048b891],
116	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1059t870r1137b893],
117	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1059t870r1137b893],
118	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1145t870r1258b897],
119	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1266t870r1291b891],
120	Heidelberg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heidelberg	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1297t870r1425b897],
121	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1297t870r1425b897],
122	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1433t867r1551b897],
123	‘	NNP	O	‘	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1433t867r1551b897],
124	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1433t867r1551b897],
125	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1560t870r1701b897],
126	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1709t870r1734b891],
127	Genomics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genomics	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1740t870r1858b893],
128	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1740t870r1858b893],
129	Life	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Life	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1866t870r1903b891],
130	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	&	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1912t870r1929b891],
131	Brain	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Brain	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1939t870r1994b891],
132	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l164t908r245b932],
133	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l164t908r245b932],
134	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l256t908r368b936],
135	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l379t908r404b930],
136	Bonn	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bonn	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l414t909r475b932],
137	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l414t909r475b932],
138	Germanyl	NNP	O	Germanyl	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l486t905r604b936],
139	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l486t905r604b936],
140	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l615t908r703b930],
141	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l716t908r741b930],
142	Human	JJ	ORGANIZATION	human	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l750t908r831b930],
143	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l844t908r946b932],
144	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l844t908r946b932],
145	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l957t908r1070b936],
146	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1081t908r1106b929],
147	Bonn	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bonn	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1115t909r1177b932],
148	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1115t909r1177b932],
149	Germany3	NN	O	germany3	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1188t905r1306b936],
150	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1188t905r1306b936],
151	Institute	NNP	O	Institute	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1317t908r1405b930],
152	of	IN	O	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1417t908r1442b930],
153	Neuroscience	NNP	O	Neuroscience	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1452t909r1607b930],
154	and	CC	O	and	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1619t908r1659b929],
155	Medicine	NNP	O	Medicine	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1673t908r1773b930],
156	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1786t908r1882b936],
157	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1786t908r1882b936],
158	NM	NN	O	nm	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1786t908r1882b936],
159	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1786t908r1882b936],
160	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1786t908r1882b936],
161	)	NN	O	)	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1786t908r1882b936],
162	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1786t908r1882b936],
163	Research	NNP	O	Research	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1893t909r1993b930],
164	Centerjuelich	NNP	O	Centerjuelich	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l164t947r328b974],
165	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l164t947r328b974],
166	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l337t944r455b975],
167	‘	NNP	O	‘	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l337t944r455b975],
168	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l337t944r455b975],
169	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l465t948r606b975],
170	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l616t947r641b969],
171	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l649t947r762b975],
172	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l772t947r884b975],
173	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l895t947r978b969],
174	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l990t947r1070b969],
175	Regensburg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Regensburg	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1080t948r1215b975],
176	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1080t948r1215b975],
177	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1225t947r1337b975],
178	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1347t947r1372b969],
179	Regensburg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Regensburg	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1380t947r1515b975],
180	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1380t947r1515b975],
181	Germany5	NN	O	germany5	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1524t944r1642b975],
182	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1524t944r1642b975],
183	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1652t948r1740b969],
184	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1750t947r1783b968],
185	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1793t947r1876b969],
186	Biometry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biometry	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1889t947r1994b975],
187	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1889t947r1994b975],
188	Informatics	NNP	O	Informatics	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l165t987r292b1010],
189	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l165t987r292b1010],
190	and	CC	O	and	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l300t987r339b1008],
191	Epidemiology	NNP	O	Epidemiology	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l351t987r503b1014],
192	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l351t987r503b1014],
193	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l511t987r624b1014],
194	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l632t987r657b1008],
195	Bonn	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bonn	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l664t987r726b1010],
196	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l664t987r726b1010],
197	Germanyé	NNP	O	Germanyé	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l734t984r852b1014],
198	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l734t984r852b1014],
199	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l861t987r1002b1014],
200	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1011t987r1036b1008],
201	Biostatistics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biostatistics	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1043t987r1175b1010],
202	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1043t987r1175b1010],
203	Harvard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Harvard	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1184t987r1275b1008],
204	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1285t987r1360b1008],
205	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1370t987r1395b1008],
206	Public	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Public	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1402t987r1466b1008],
207	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1477t987r1555b1010],
208	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1477t987r1555b1010],
209	MA	NNP	LOCATION	MA	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1564t987r1608b1010],
210	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1564t987r1608b1010],
211	USA7	NN	O	usa7	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1616t984r1681b1010],
212	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1616t984r1681b1010],
213	Private	JJ	ORGANIZATION	private	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1690t987r1766b1008],
214	Hospital	NN	ORGANIZATION	hospital	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1777t987r1867b1014],
215	Meiringen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Meiringen	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1879t987r1994b1014],
216	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1879t987r1994b1014],
217	Switzerlanda	NNP	O	Switzerlanda	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l164t1022r308b1049],
218	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l164t1022r308b1049],
219	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l317t1026r458b1053],
220	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l466t1025r491b1047],
221	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l498t1025r611b1053],
222	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l619t1025r732b1053],
223	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l740t1025r765b1047],
224	Munich	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Munich	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l772t1025r857b1049],
225	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l772t1025r857b1049],
226	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l865t1022r983b1053],
227	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l865t1022r983b1053],
228	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l865t1022r983b1053],
229	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l865t1022r983b1053],
230	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l991t1026r1133b1053],
231	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1141t1025r1166b1046],
232	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1173t1025r1286b1053],
233	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1294t1025r1407b1053],
234	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1415t1025r1440b1046],
235	Bonn	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bonn	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1447t1026r1508b1049],
236	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1447t1026r1508b1049],
237	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1516t1022r1644b1053],
238	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1516t1022r1644b1053],
239	°	NN	O	°	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1516t1022r1644b1053],
240	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1516t1022r1644b1053],
241	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1652t1026r1793b1053],
242	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1802t1025r1827b1046],
243	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1834t1025r1946b1053],
244	and	CC	O	and	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1954t1025r1994b1047],
245	Psychotherapy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychotherapy	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l165t1065r330b1092],
246	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l339t1064r451b1092],
247	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l460t1064r485b1085],
248	Dusseldorf	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dusseldorf	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l492t1064r617b1088],
249	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l492t1064r617b1088],
250	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l626t1061r736b1092],
251	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l626t1061r736b1092],
252	l	NN	O	l	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l744t1061r753b1088],
253	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l744t1061r753b1088],
254	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l762t1064r904b1092],
255	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l913t1064r937b1086],
256	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l945t1064r1058b1092],
257	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1067t1064r1179b1092],
258	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1188t1064r1213b1085],
259	Mainz	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mainz	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1220t1065r1288b1088],
260	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1220t1065r1288b1088],
261	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1297t1061r1424b1092],
262	”	NNP	O	”	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1297t1061r1424b1092],
263	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1297t1061r1424b1092],
264	Addiction	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Addiction	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1432t1064r1541b1086],
265	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1553t1064r1653b1086],
266	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1664t1064r1737b1092],
267	at	IN	O	at	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1747t1067r1768b1086],
268	the	DT	O	the	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1775t1065r1812b1086],
269	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1823t1065r1964b1092],
270	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l1973t1064r1998b1085],
271	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l165t1103r278b1131],
272	and	CC	O	and	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l294t1103r333b1125],
273	Psychotherapy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychotherapy	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l353t1103r517b1131],
274	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l534t1103r646b1131],
275	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	276	SENT_6	[p1l663t1103r688b1125],
276	Duisburg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Duisburg	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l702t1103r880b1131],
277	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l702t1103r880b1131],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l702t1103r880b1131],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l702t1103r880b1131],

1	Essen	NNP	LOCATION	Essen	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l702t1103r880b1131],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l702t1103r880b1131],
3	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	appos	1	SENT_8	[p1l896t1100r1023b1131],
4	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l896t1100r1023b1131],
5	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	3	SENT_8	[p1l896t1100r1023b1131],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l896t1100r1023b1131],
7	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	appos	1	SENT_8	[p1l1040t1104r1181b1131],
8	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1198t1103r1223b1124],
9	Psychiatric	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatric	nn	10	SENT_8	[p1l1237t1104r1353b1131],
10	Pharmacogenetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmacogenetics	prep_of	7	SENT_8	[p1l1372t1103r1579b1131],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1372t1103r1579b1131],
12	Ma	NNP	O	Ma	appos	1	SENT_8	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],
13	>	JJR	O	>	npadvmod	14	SENT_8	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],
14	<	JJR	O	<	amod	12	SENT_8	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],
15	»	CD	NUMBER	»	num	16	SENT_8	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],
16	Plancl	NN	O	plancl	dep	1	SENT_8	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],
17	<	JJR	O	<	dep	16	SENT_8	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],

1	|	NN	O	|	nn	2	SENT_10	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],
2	nstitute	NN	O	nstitute	nsubj	12	SENT_10	[p1l1596t1103r1823b1125],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1841t1103r1865b1125],
4	Psychiatry	NNP	O	Psychiatry	nn	6	SENT_10	[p1l1880t1103r1994b1131],
5	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	nn	6	SENT_10	[p1l164t1140r292b1170],
6	”	NNP	O	”	prep_of	2	SENT_10	[p1l164t1140r292b1170],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l164t1140r292b1170],
8	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	appos	6	SENT_10	[p1l306t1143r447b1170],
9	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l461t1143r486b1164],
10	Molecular	JJ	ORGANIZATION	molecular	amod	11	SENT_10	[p1l498t1143r609b1164],
11	Psychology	NN	ORGANIZATION	psychology	prep_of	8	SENT_10	[p1l622t1143r747b1170],
12	Ma	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ma	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],
13	>	JJR	O	>	nsubj	14	SENT_10	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],
14	<	JJR	O	<	xcomp	12	SENT_10	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],

1	Plancl	NN	O	plancl	dep	2	SENT_12	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],
2	<	JJR	O	<	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],

1	lnstitute	NN	O	lnstitute	nsubj	12	SENT_14	[p1l761t1143r988b1164],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1003t1143r1027b1164],
3	Psychiatry	NNP	O	Psychiatry	nn	5	SENT_14	[p1l1039t1143r1153b1170],
4	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	nn	5	SENT_14	[p1l1166t1140r1294b1170],
5	“	NNP	O	“	prep_of	1	SENT_14	[p1l1166t1140r1294b1170],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1166t1140r1294b1170],
7	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	appos	5	SENT_14	[p1l1308t1143r1449b1170],
8	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1463t1143r1487b1164],
9	Statistical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Statistical	nn	10	SENT_14	[p1l1498t1143r1599b1164],
10	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	prep_of	7	SENT_14	[p1l1615t1143r1718b1166],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1615t1143r1718b1166],
12	Ma	NNP	O	Ma	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],
13	>	JJR	O	>	nsubj	17	SENT_14	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],
14	<	JJR	O	<	amod	13	SENT_14	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],
15	»	CD	NUMBER	»	num	16	SENT_14	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],
16	Plancl	NN	O	plancl	npadvmod	17	SENT_14	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],
17	<	JJR	O	<	xcomp	12	SENT_14	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],

1	lnstitute	NN	O	lnstitute	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1732t1143r1958b1164],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1973t1143r1998b1164],
3	Psychiatry	NNP	O	Psychiatry	nn	4	SENT_16	[p1l165t1182r279b1209],
4	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	prep_of	1	SENT_16	[p1l289t1179r452b1209],
5	"	``	O	"	punct	6	SENT_16	[p1l289t1179r452b1209],
6	’	NN	O	’	dep	1	SENT_16	[p1l289t1179r452b1209],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l289t1179r452b1209],
8	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	1	SENT_16	[p1l465t1182r607b1209],
9	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l617t1182r642b1203],
10	Addictive	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Addictive	nn	11	SENT_16	[p1l647t1182r753b1203],
11	Behavior	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Behavior	prep_of	6	SENT_16	[p1l766t1182r864b1203],
12	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l873t1182r912b1203],
13	Addiction	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Addiction	nn	14	SENT_16	[p1l922t1182r1031b1203],
14	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	prep_of	6	SENT_16	[p1l1044t1182r1150b1205],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1044t1182r1150b1205],
16	Central	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Central	nn	17	SENT_16	[p1l1160t1182r1242b1203],
17	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	appos	11	SENT_16	[p1l1255t1182r1343b1203],
18	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1355t1182r1379b1203],
19	Mental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mental	nn	20	SENT_16	[p1l1388t1182r1462b1203],
20	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	prep_of	17	SENT_16	[p1l1476t1182r1553b1205],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1476t1182r1553b1205],
22	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	20	SENT_16	[p1l1563t1182r1676b1209],
23	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1686t1182r1711b1203],
24	Heidelberg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heidelberg	nn	26	SENT_16	[p1l1720t1182r1848b1209],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1720t1182r1848b1209],
26	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	prep_of	22	SENT_16	[p1l1858t1179r1981b1209],
27	"	''	O	"	punct	22	SENT_16	[p1l1858t1179r1981b1209],

1	ABSTRACT	NN	O	abstract	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l163t1363r397b1390],

1	Alcohol	NN	O	alcohol	nn	2	SENT_18	[p1l164t1465r286b1492],
2	dependence	NN	O	dependence	nsubj	10	SENT_18	[p1l300t1465r483b1499],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_18	[p1l499t1465r570b1499],
4	AD	NN	O	ad	nn	5	SENT_18	[p1l499t1465r570b1499],
5	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_18	[p1l499t1465r570b1499],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	10	SENT_18	[p1l586t1467r608b1492],
7	an	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_18	[p1l624t1474r662b1492],
8	important	JJ	O	important	amod	10	SENT_18	[p1l677t1467r835b1499],
9	contributory	JJ	O	contributory	amod	10	SENT_18	[p1l850t1465r1049b1499],
10	factor	NN	O	factor	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1063t1465r1153b1492],
11	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1168t1468r1197b1492],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_18	[p1l1212t1465r1261b1492],
13	global	JJ	O	global	amod	14	SENT_18	[p1l1276t1465r1370b1499],
14	burden	NN	O	burden	prep_to	10	SENT_18	[p1l1383t1465r1496b1492],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1510t1465r1541b1492],
16	disease	NN	O	disease	prep_of	14	SENT_18	[p1l1557t1465r1673b1492],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1557t1465r1673b1492],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_19	[p1l1688t1465r1746b1492],
2	etiology	NN	O	etiology	nsubj	5	SENT_19	[p1l1761t1465r1884b1499],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1899t1465r1929b1492],
4	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_of	2	SENT_19	[p1l1945t1466r1994b1492],
5	involves	VBZ	O	involve	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l164t1513r288b1540],
6	both	CC	O	both	prep	5	SENT_19	[p1l300t1513r371b1540],
7	environmental	JJ	O	environmental	amod	10	SENT_19	[p1l383t1513r614b1540],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l627t1513r685b1540],
9	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	10	SENT_19	[p1l697t1515r807b1547],
10	factors	NNS	O	factor	dep	6	SENT_19	[p1l820t1513r933b1544],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l820t1513r933b1544],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l948t1513r1006b1540],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_19	[p1l1018t1513r1067b1540],
14	disorder	NN	O	disorder	nsubj	15	SENT_19	[p1l1080t1513r1205b1540],
15	has	VBZ	O	have	conj_and	5	SENT_19	[p1l1217t1513r1271b1540],
16	a	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_19	[p1l1284t1522r1301b1540],
17	heritability	NN	O	heritability	dobj	15	SENT_19	[p1l1313t1513r1484b1547],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1497t1513r1527b1540],
19	around	IN	O	around	amod	21	SENT_19	[p1l1542t1513r1655b1540],
20	50	CD	PERCENT	50	num	21	SENT_19	[p1l1670t1514r1746b1541],
21	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_of	17	SENT_19	[p1l1670t1514r1746b1541],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1670t1514r1746b1541],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_20	[p1l1758t1513r1817b1540],
2	aim	NN	O	aim	nsubj	7	SENT_20	[p1l1831t1515r1889b1540],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1901t1513r1931b1540],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_20	[p1l1945t1513r1994b1540],
5	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	6	SENT_20	[p1l164t1564r278b1595],
6	study	NN	O	study	prep_of	2	SENT_20	[p1l288t1561r373b1595],
7	was	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l382t1570r442b1588],
8	to	TO	O	to	aux	9	SENT_20	[p1l452t1564r481b1588],
9	identify	VB	O	identify	xcomp	7	SENT_20	[p1l492t1561r609b1595],
10	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	nn	11	SENT_20	[p1l619t1561r822b1595],
11	genes	NNS	O	gene	dobj	9	SENT_20	[p1l832t1570r918b1595],
12	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l928t1561r970b1588],
13	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_for	11	SENT_20	[p1l980t1562r1029b1588],
14	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1039t1561r1075b1595],
15	performing	VBG	O	perform	prepc_by	9	SENT_20	[p1l1085t1561r1259b1595],
16	a	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_20	[p1l1270t1570r1287b1588],
17	genome	NN	O	genome	nn	21	SENT_20	[p1l1297t1561r1505b1595],
18	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	21	SENT_20	[p1l1297t1561r1505b1595],
19	wide	JJ	O	wide	amod	21	SENT_20	[p1l1297t1561r1505b1595],
20	association	NN	O	association	nn	21	SENT_20	[p1l1517t1563r1689b1588],
21	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	24	SENT_20	[p1l1700t1561r1784b1595],
22	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	24	SENT_20	[p1l1795t1561r1925b1595],
23	GWAS	NN	O	gwa	nn	24	SENT_20	[p1l1795t1561r1925b1595],
24	)	NN	O	)	xcomp	15	SENT_20	[p1l1795t1561r1925b1595],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1795t1561r1925b1595],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_21	[p1l1935t1561r1994b1588],
2	sample	NN	O	sample	nsubj	3	SENT_21	[p1l164t1609r273b1643],
3	comprised	VBN	O	comprise	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l282t1609r442b1643],
4	1333	CD	DATE	1333	num	6	SENT_21	[p1l453t1610r534b1637],
5	male	JJ	O	male	amod	6	SENT_21	[p1l545t1609r621b1637],
6	in-patients	NNS	O	in-patient	dobj	3	SENT_21	[p1l630t1611r797b1643],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l806t1609r877b1637],
8	severe	JJ	O	severe	amod	9	SENT_21	[p1l887t1618r981b1637],
9	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_with	6	SENT_21	[p1l991t1610r1040b1636],
10	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1050t1609r1204b1643],
11	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	3	SENT_21	[p1l1213t1612r1243b1637],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_21	[p1l1252t1609r1301b1637],
13	Diagnostic	JJ	MISC	diagnostic	amod	16	SENT_21	[p1l1310t1611r1475b1643],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1485t1609r1543b1637],
15	Statistical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	statistical	conj_and	13	SENT_21	[p1l1553t1609r1705b1637],
16	Manual	NN	ORGANIZATION	manual	pobj	3	SENT_21	[p1l1713t1609r1835b1637],
17	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1844t1609r1874b1637],
18	Mental	JJ	ORGANIZATION	mental	amod	19	SENT_21	[p1l1885t1609r1995b1637],
19	Disorders	NNS	ORGANIZATION	disorder	prep_of	16	SENT_21	[p1l163t1657r318b1688],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l163t1657r318b1688],
21	4th	JJ	ORDINAL	4th	amod	22	SENT_21	[p1l328t1657r382b1685],
22	edition	NN	O	edition	conj_and	19	SENT_21	[p1l390t1657r505b1688],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l390t1657r505b1688],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l515t1657r573b1685],
25	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	26	SENT_21	[p1l582t1658r599b1684],
26	1	CD	NUMBER	1	conj_and	19	SENT_21	[p1l606t1658r620b1684],
27	68	CD	NUMBER	68	num	28	SENT_21	[p1l627t1658r665b1685],
28	controls	NNS	O	control	dep	26	SENT_21	[p1l675t1657r809b1685],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l675t1657r809b1685],

1	These	DT	O	these	nsubj	2	SENT_22	[p1l817t1657r907b1685],
2	included	VBD	O	include	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l915t1657r1049b1685],
3	48	CD	NUMBER	48	number	4	SENT_22	[p1l1057t1658r1097b1685],
4	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	5	SENT_22	[p1l1104t1658r1120b1685],
5	patients	NNS	O	patient	dobj	2	SENT_22	[p1l1128t1659r1252b1691],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1261t1657r1319b1685],
7	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	8	SENT_22	[p1l1330t1658r1345b1684],
8	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dobj	2	SENT_22	[p1l1351t1658r1367b1685],
9	58	CD	NUMBER	58	num	10	SENT_22	[p1l1373t1658r1411b1685],
10	controls	NNS	O	control	dep	8	SENT_22	[p1l1421t1657r1547b1685],
11	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1555t1657r1629b1685],
12	a	DT	O	a	det	15	SENT_22	[p1l1637t1666r1654b1685],
13	previous	JJ	O	previous	amod	15	SENT_22	[p1l1661t1659r1794b1691],
14	GWAS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GWAS	nn	15	SENT_22	[p1l1803t1658r1901b1685],
15	study	NN	O	study	prep_from	2	SENT_22	[p1l1910t1657r1995b1691],
16	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l163t1705r200b1739],
17	our	PRP$	O	we	poss	18	SENT_22	[p1l214t1714r267b1733],
18	group	NN	O	group	prep_by	2	SENT_22	[p1l281t1714r380b1739],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l281t1714r380b1739],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	2	SENT_23	[p1l396t1705r441b1732],
2	individuals	NNS	O	individual	nsubj	3	SENT_23	[p1l454t1705r625b1733],
3	were	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l639t1714r712b1733],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l727t1705r757b1733],
5	German	JJ	MISC	german	amod	6	SENT_23	[p1l773t1706r899b1733],
6	descent	NN	O	descent	prep_of	3	SENT_23	[p1l913t1705r1037b1733],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l913t1705r1037b1733],

1	Single-marker	JJ	O	single-marker	amod	2	SENT_24	[p1l1053t1705r1272b1739],
2	tests	NNS	O	test	nsubjpass	20	SENT_24	[p1l1286t1708r1354b1733],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1369t1705r1427b1733],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_24	[p1l1441t1714r1458b1733],
5	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	7	SENT_24	[p1l1471t1705r1618b1739],
6	score-based	JJ	O	score-based	amod	7	SENT_24	[p1l1632t1705r1813b1733],
7	analysis	NN	O	analysis	conj_and	2	SENT_24	[p1l1827t1705r1950b1739],
8	to	TO	O	to	aux	9	SENT_24	[p1l1965t1708r1994b1733],
9	assess	VB	O	assess	infmod	7	SENT_24	[p1l165t1763r256b1782],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_24	[p1l268t1754r317b1782],
11	combined	JJ	O	combined	amod	12	SENT_24	[p1l329t1754r481b1782],
12	contribution	NN	O	contribution	dobj	9	SENT_24	[p1l493t1754r689b1782],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l701t1754r731b1782],
14	multiple	JJ	O	multiple	amod	15	SENT_24	[p1l744t1754r873b1788],
15	markers	NNS	O	marker	prep_of	12	SENT_24	[p1l884t1754r1012b1782],
16	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1024t1754r1095b1781],
17	small	JJ	O	small	amod	18	SENT_24	[p1l1107t1754r1190b1782],
18	effects	NNS	O	effect	prep_with	9	SENT_24	[p1l1201t1754r1295b1782],
19	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_24	[p1l1307t1763r1381b1782],
20	performed	VBN	O	perform	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1392t1754r1560b1788],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1392t1754r1560b1788],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_25	[p1l1572t1754r1631b1782],
2	single	JJ	O	single	amod	4	SENT_25	[p1l1643t1754r1732b1788],
3	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	4	SENT_25	[p1l1744t1754r1906b1782],
4	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	nsubj	24	SENT_25	[p1l1917t1754r1994b1788, p1l164t1802r325b1836],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_25	[p1l335t1802r423b1836],
6	SNP	NN	ORGANIZATION	snp	dep	4	SENT_25	[p1l335t1802r423b1836],
7	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	8	SENT_25	[p1l335t1802r423b1836],
8	rs1	NN	O	rs1	dep	4	SENT_25	[p1l434t1803r481b1830],
9	78989	CD	NUMBER	78989	number	10	SENT_25	[p1l489t1803r591b1830],
10	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	8	SENT_25	[p1l598t1803r623b1833],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l598t1803r623b1833],
12	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	14	SENT_25	[p1l635t1802r731b1830],
13	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	14	SENT_25	[p1l741t1804r763b1830],
14	located	JJ	O	located	rcmod	4	SENT_25	[p1l774t1802r885b1830],
15	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l894t1802r1024b1830],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_25	[p1l1034t1802r1083b1830],
17	ADH	NNP	O	ADH	nn	18	SENT_25	[p1l1093t1803r1169b1829],
18	1B	NN	O	1b	prep_between	14	SENT_25	[p1l1171t1803r1212b1829],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1223t1802r1282b1830],
20	ADH	NN	O	adh	nn	22	SENT_25	[p1l1291t1803r1367b1829],
21	1C	NN	O	1c	nn	22	SENT_25	[p1l1370t1803r1409b1830],
22	genes	NNS	O	gene	conj_and	18	SENT_25	[p1l1419t1811r1513b1836],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1419t1811r1513b1836],
24	achieved	VBD	O	achieve	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1526t1802r1661b1830],
25	genome	NN	O	genome	dep	33	SENT_25	[p1l1672t1802r1879b1836],
26	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	25	SENT_25	[p1l1672t1802r1879b1836],
27	wide	JJ	O	wide	amod	30	SENT_25	[p1l1672t1802r1879b1836],
28	signiﬁcance	NN	O	signiﬁcance	nn	30	SENT_25	[p1l1890t1802r1994b1836, p1l164t1859r253b1878],
29	[	NN	O	[	nn	30	SENT_25	[p1l272t1850r304b1884],
30	P	NN	O	p	dep	25	SENT_25	[p1l272t1850r304b1884],
31	=	JJ	O	=	dep	33	SENT_25	[p1l313t1862r334b1872],
32	1.2	CD	NUMBER	1.2	num	33	SENT_25	[p1l347t1852r394b1878],
33	7E	NN	O	7e	dep	38	SENT_25	[p1l401t1852r485b1881],
34	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	35	SENT_25	[p1l401t1852r485b1881],
35	8	CD	NUMBER	8	dep	33	SENT_25	[p1l401t1852r485b1881],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l401t1852r485b1881],
37	odds	NNS	O	odds	appos	35	SENT_25	[p1l504t1850r574b1878],
38	ratio	NN	O	ratio	dep	40	SENT_25	[p1l590t1853r663b1878],
39	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	38	SENT_25	[p1l681t1850r782b1884],
40	OR	NN	O	or	dep	44	SENT_25	[p1l681t1850r782b1884],
41	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	40	SENT_25	[p1l681t1850r782b1884],
42	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l681t1850r782b1884],
43	1.46	CD	NUMBER	1.46	num	44	SENT_25	[p1l795t1850r886b1884],
44	]	NN	O	]	dep	24	SENT_25	[p1l795t1850r886b1884],
45	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l795t1850r886b1884],

1	Other	JJ	O	other	amod	2	SENT_26	[p1l905t1850r993b1878],
2	markers	NNS	O	marker	nsubjpass	8	SENT_26	[p1l1009t1850r1136b1878],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1153t1850r1227b1878],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	5	SENT_26	[p1l1243t1850r1299b1878],
5	region	NN	O	region	prep_from	2	SENT_26	[p1l1315t1853r1416b1884],
6	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_26	[p1l1432t1859r1505b1878],
7	also	RB	O	also	advmod	8	SENT_26	[p1l1523t1850r1582b1878],
8	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1600t1850r1759b1878],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1774t1850r1846b1878],
10	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_with	8	SENT_26	[p1l1861t1852r1917b1881],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1861t1852r1917b1881],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1937t1850r1995b1878],
13	conditional	JJ	O	conditional	amod	14	SENT_26	[p1l164t1898r341b1926],
14	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	nsubj	15	SENT_26	[p1l353t1898r483b1932],
15	indicated	VBD	O	indicate	conj_and	8	SENT_26	[p1l495t1898r638b1926],
16	that	IN	O	that	complm	18	SENT_26	[p1l649t1898r712b1925],
17	these	DT	O	these	nsubj	18	SENT_26	[p1l723t1898r803b1926],
18	made	VBN	O	make	ccomp	15	SENT_26	[p1l815t1898r899b1926],
19	a	DT	O	a	det	22	SENT_26	[p1l912t1907r929b1925],
20	partially	RB	O	partially	advmod	21	SENT_26	[p1l939t1898r1070b1932],
21	independent	JJ	O	independent	amod	22	SENT_26	[p1l1081t1898r1275b1932],
22	contribution	NN	O	contribution	dobj	18	SENT_26	[p1l1286t1898r1490b1926],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1286t1898r1490b1926],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_27	[p1l1502t1898r1561b1926],
2	SNP	NN	O	snp	nn	3	SENT_27	[p1l1572t1899r1638b1926],
3	rs1	NN	O	rs1	nsubj	25	SENT_27	[p1l1649t1899r1696b1926],
4	78989	CD	NUMBER	78989	num	5	SENT_27	[p1l1704t1899r1806b1926],
5	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	3	SENT_27	[p1l1813t1899r1827b1925],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	25	SENT_27	[p1l1841t1900r1864b1926],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1875t1900r1906b1925],
8	complete	JJ	O	complete	amod	10	SENT_27	[p1l1917t1907r1994b1926, p1l164t1946r237b1980],
9	linkage	NN	O	linkage	nn	10	SENT_27	[p1l250t1946r363b1980],
10	disequilibrium	NN	O	disequilibrium	prep_in	25	SENT_27	[p1l377t1946r602b1980],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l615t1946r686b1973],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_27	[p1l699t1946r748b1973],
13	functional	JJ	O	functional	amod	18	SENT_27	[p1l762t1946r923b1974],
14	Arg2	NN	O	arg2	nn	18	SENT_27	[p1l935t1947r1014b1980],
15	72Gln	NN	O	72gln	nn	18	SENT_27	[p1l1021t1946r1116b1974],
16	variant	JJ	O	variant	amod	18	SENT_27	[p1l1129t1948r1242b1973],
17	(	NN	O	(	nn	18	SENT_27	[p1l1257t1946r1289b1980],
18	P	NN	O	p	prep_with	25	SENT_27	[p1l1257t1946r1289b1980],
19	=	JJ	O	=	advmod	22	SENT_27	[p1l1299t1958r1319b1968],
20	1.24	CD	NUMBER	1.24	num	21	SENT_27	[p1l1332t1947r1471b1977],
21	E	NN	O	e	dep	19	SENT_27	[p1l1332t1947r1471b1977],
22	—	NN	O	—	rcmod	18	SENT_27	[p1l1332t1947r1471b1977],
23	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	22	SENT_27	[p1l1332t1947r1471b1977],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1332t1947r1471b1977],
25	OR	NN	O	or	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1487t1947r1534b1974],
26	=	JJ	O	=	dep	25	SENT_27	[p1l1544t1958r1564b1968],
27	1.31	CD	NUMBER	1.31	num	28	SENT_27	[p1l1578t1946r1659b1980],
28	)	NN	O	)	dobj	26	SENT_27	[p1l1578t1946r1659b1980],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1675t1946r1705b1974],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_27	[p1l1720t1946r1769b1973],
31	ADH	NNP	O	ADH	nn	33	SENT_27	[p1l1782t1947r1858b1973],
32	1C	NN	O	1c	nn	33	SENT_27	[p1l1861t1947r1901b1974],
33	gene	NN	O	gene	prep_of	28	SENT_27	[p1l1914t1955r1992b1980],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1914t1955r1992b1980],
35	which	WDT	O	which	nsubjpass	38	SENT_27	[p1l164t1994r260b2022],
36	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	38	SENT_27	[p1l274t1994r328b2021],
37	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	38	SENT_27	[p1l342t1994r416b2022],
38	reported	VBN	O	report	rcmod	33	SENT_27	[p1l430t1994r562b2028],
39	to	TO	O	to	aux	40	SENT_27	[p1l576t1997r605b2022],
40	modify	VB	O	modify	xcomp	38	SENT_27	[p1l620t1994r727b2028],
41	the	DT	O	the	det	42	SENT_27	[p1l741t1994r790b2022],
42	rate	NN	O	rate	dobj	40	SENT_27	[p1l804t1997r865b2021],
43	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l880t1994r910b2021],
44	ethanol	NN	O	ethanol	nn	45	SENT_27	[p1l926t1994r1046b2021],
45	oxidation	NN	O	oxidation	prep_of	42	SENT_27	[p1l1060t1994r1205b2021],
46	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1219t1997r1249b2021],
47	acetaldehyde	NN	O	acetaldehyde	prep_to	45	SENT_27	[p1l1265t1994r1465b2028],
48	in	FW	O	in	nn	49	SENT_27	[p1l1480t1996r1508b2021],
49	vitro	FW	O	vitro	advmod	40	SENT_27	[p1l1523t1996r1597b2021],
50	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1523t1996r1597b2021],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_28	[p1l1613t1995r1639b2021],
2	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	4	SENT_28	[p1l1652t1994r1799b2028],
3	score-based	JJ	O	score-based	amod	4	SENT_28	[p1l1814t1994r1995b2022],
4	approach	NN	O	approach	nsubj	5	SENT_28	[p1l165t2042r311b2076],
5	produced	VBD	O	produce	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l320t2042r465b2076],
6	a	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_28	[p1l475t2051r492b2069],
7	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	amod	10	SENT_28	[p1l502t2042r664b2076],
8	result	NN	O	result	nn	10	SENT_28	[p1l672t2042r761b2070],
9	(	NN	O	(	nn	10	SENT_28	[p1l771t2042r803b2076],
10	P	NN	O	p	nsubj	11	SENT_28	[p1l771t2042r803b2076],
11	=	JJ	O	=	ccomp	5	SENT_28	[p1l813t2054r833b2064],
12	9.66	CD	NUMBER	9.66	num	13	SENT_28	[p1l845t2042r997b2076],
13	E	NN	O	e	iobj	11	SENT_28	[p1l845t2042r997b2076],
14	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	16	SENT_28	[p1l845t2042r997b2076],
15	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	16	SENT_28	[p1l845t2042r997b2076],
16	)	NN	O	)	dobj	11	SENT_28	[p1l845t2042r997b2076],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l845t2042r997b2076],

1	This	DT	O	this	nsubj	5	SENT_29	[p1l1007t2042r1073b2070],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	5	SENT_29	[p1l1083t2044r1105b2070],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_29	[p1l1115t2042r1164b2070],
4	ﬁrst	JJ	O	ﬁrst	amod	5	SENT_29	[p1l1173t2042r1233b2070],
5	GWAS	NN	O	gwa	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1243t2043r1340b2070],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1351t2042r1381b2070],
7	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_of	5	SENT_29	[p1l1392t2044r1441b2069],
8	to	TO	O	to	aux	9	SENT_29	[p1l1451t2046r1480b2070],
9	provide	VB	O	provide	dep	5	SENT_29	[p1l1489t2042r1605b2076],
10	genome-wide	JJ	O	genome-wide	amod	12	SENT_29	[p1l1615t2042r1823b2076],
11	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	amod	12	SENT_29	[p1l1833t2042r1995b2076],
12	support	NN	O	support	dobj	9	SENT_29	[p1l164t2093r284b2124],
13	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l296t2090r338b2117],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_29	[p1l350t2090r399b2117],
15	role	NN	O	role	prep_for	9	SENT_29	[p1l411t2090r469b2117],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l482t2090r513b2117],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_29	[p1l526t2090r575b2117],
18	ADH	NN	O	adh	nn	20	SENT_29	[p1l587t2091r663b2117],
19	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	20	SENT_29	[p1l674t2099r745b2124],
20	cluster	NN	O	cluster	prep_of	15	SENT_29	[p1l758t2090r862b2117],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l875t2090r933b2117],
22	to	TO	O	to	aux	23	SENT_29	[p1l945t2093r974b2117],
23	suggest	VB	O	suggest	conj_and	9	SENT_29	[p1l987t2093r1102b2124],
24	a	DT	O	a	det	26	SENT_29	[p1l1115t2099r1132b2117],
25	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	26	SENT_29	[p1l1143t2090r1290b2124],
26	component	NN	O	component	dobj	23	SENT_29	[p1l1302t2094r1479b2124],
27	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1491t2093r1520b2117],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_29	[p1l1533t2090r1582b2117],
29	etiology	NN	O	etiology	prep_to	23	SENT_29	[p1l1594t2090r1717b2124],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1729t2090r1759b2117],
31	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_of	29	SENT_29	[p1l1773t2091r1828b2117],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1773t2091r1828b2117],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_30	[p1l1841t2090r1899b2117],
2	latter	JJ	O	latter	amod	3	SENT_30	[p1l1912t2090r1995b2117],
3	result	NN	O	result	nsubj	5	SENT_30	[p1l163t2138r252b2165],
4	may	MD	O	may	aux	5	SENT_30	[p1l262t2147r330b2172],
5	indicate	VB	O	indicate	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l340t2138r464b2165],
6	that	IN	O	that	advmod	7	SENT_30	[p1l475t2138r538b2165],
7	many	JJ	O	many	dep	13	SENT_30	[p1l549t2147r638b2172],
8	more	JJR	O	more	amod	11	SENT_30	[p1l648t2147r728b2165],
9	AD	NN	O	ad	nn	11	SENT_30	[p1l739t2139r789b2165],
10	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	nn	11	SENT_30	[p1l800t2138r1003b2172],
11	genes	NNS	O	gene	nsubj	13	SENT_30	[p1l1014t2147r1100b2172],
12	still	RB	O	still	advmod	13	SENT_30	[p1l1112t2138r1166b2165],
13	await	VBP	O	await	ccomp	5	SENT_30	[p1l1178t2140r1262b2165],
14	identiﬁcation	NN	O	identiﬁcation	dobj	13	SENT_30	[p1l1273t2138r1486b2165],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1273t2138r1486b2165],

1	Keywords	NNPS	O	Keywords	nn	2	SENT_31	[p1l166t2226r352b2260],
2	Alcohol	NNP	O	Alcohol	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l394t2225r516b2252],
3	dehydrogenase	NN	O	dehydrogenase	dep	2	SENT_31	[p1l535t2225r774b2259],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l535t2225r774b2259],
5	alcohol	NN	O	alcohol	nn	6	SENT_31	[p1l796t2225r909b2252],
6	dependence	NN	O	dependence	appos	3	SENT_31	[p1l928t2225r1119b2259],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l928t2225r1119b2259],
8	alcohol	NN	O	alcohol	nn	9	SENT_31	[p1l1141t2225r1255b2252],
9	metabolism	NN	O	metabolism	appos	3	SENT_31	[p1l1273t2225r1461b2256],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1273t2225r1461b2256],
11	genome	NN	O	genome	appos	3	SENT_31	[p1l1483t2225r1699b2259],
12	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	11	SENT_31	[p1l1483t2225r1699b2259],
13	wide	JJ	O	wide	amod	18	SENT_31	[p1l1483t2225r1699b2259],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1483t2225r1699b2259],
15	GWAS	NN	O	gwa	dep	18	SENT_31	[p1l1720t2226r1827b2256],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1720t2226r1827b2256],
17	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	18	SENT_31	[p1l1848t2225r1994b2259],
18	variation	NN	O	variation	dep	11	SENT_31	[p1l164t2274r313b2299],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l164t2274r313b2299],

1	Correspondence	NN	O	correspondence	nsubj	31	SENT_32	[p1l165t2365r340b2392],
2	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l354t2368r381b2387],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l354t2368r381b2387],
4	Marcella	NNP	PERSON	Marcella	nn	5	SENT_32	[p1l395t2365r500b2387],
5	Rietschel	NNP	PERSON	Rietschel	prep_to	1	SENT_32	[p1l513t2365r629b2390],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l513t2365r629b2390],
7	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	appos	5	SENT_32	[p1l643t2366r790b2392],
8	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l803t2365r827b2387],
9	Genetic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetic	nn	10	SENT_32	[p1l841t2366r932b2387],
10	Epidemiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Epidemiology	prep_of	7	SENT_32	[p1l945t2365r1107b2392],
11	in	IN	ORGANIZATION	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1121t2367r1144b2387],
12	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	prep_in	10	SENT_32	[p1l1157t2365r1288b2392],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1157t2365r1288b2392],
14	Central	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Central	nn	15	SENT_32	[p1l1304t2365r1392b2387],
15	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	appos	5	SENT_32	[p1l1405t2366r1507b2387],
16	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1521t2365r1544b2387],
17	Mental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mental	nn	22	SENT_32	[p1l1558t2365r1644b2387],
18	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	22	SENT_32	[p1l1657t2365r1738b2387],
19	Mannheim	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mannheim	nn	22	SENT_32	[p1l1751t2365r1885b2387],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	22	SENT_32	[p1l1899t2365r1993b2392],
21	CIMH	NN	O	cimh	nn	22	SENT_32	[p1l1899t2365r1993b2392],
22	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	15	SENT_32	[p1l1899t2365r1993b2392],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1899t2365r1993b2392],
24	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	22	SENT_32	[p1l164t2404r287b2430],
25	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l296t2403r320b2424],
26	Heidelberg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heidelberg	prep_of	24	SENT_32	[p1l329t2403r464b2430],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l329t2403r464b2430],
28	IS	VBZ	O	be	cop	31	SENT_32	[p1l473t2404r506b2430],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l473t2404r506b2430],
30	68159	CD	NUMBER	68159	num	31	SENT_32	[p1l517t2404r598b2425],
31	Mannheim	NNP	O	Mannheim	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l608t2403r748b2427],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l608t2403r748b2427],
33	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	appos	31	SENT_32	[p1l758t2404r872b2430],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l758t2404r872b2430],

1	E	NN	O	e	nn	3	SENT_33	[p1l882t2403r966b2424],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	3	SENT_33	[p1l882t2403r966b2424],
3	mail	NN	O	mail	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l882t2403r966b2424],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l882t2403r966b2424],
5	marcella.rietschel@zi—mannheim.de	NN	O	marcella.rietschel@zi—mannheim.de	dep	3	SENT_33	[p1l975t2403r1417b2431],

1	INTRODUCTION	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l166t2562r515b2588],
2	addicted	VBN	O	addict	amod	1	SENT_34	[p1l1110t2561r1248b2588],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l1110t2561r1248b2588],

1	Elucidation	NN	O	elucidation	nsubj	6	SENT_35	[p1l1265t2561r1442b2588],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1458t2561r1488b2588],
3	this	DT	O	this	det	4	SENT_35	[p1l1506t2561r1562b2588],
4	point	NN	O	point	prep_of	1	SENT_35	[p1l1578t2563r1659b2595],
5	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	6	SENT_35	[p1l1674t2563r1697b2588],
6	important	JJ	O	important	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1713t2563r1872b2595],
7	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1887t2561r1929b2588],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_35	[p1l1945t2561r1994b2588],
9	development	NN	O	development	prep_for	6	SENT_35	[p1l1109t2609r1308b2643],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1332t2609r1362b2636],
11	successful	JJ	O	successful	amod	12	SENT_35	[p1l1388t2609r1543b2636],
12	prevention	NN	O	prevention	prep_of	9	SENT_35	[p1l1566t2611r1734b2643],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1758t2609r1816b2636],
14	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nn	16	SENT_35	[p1l1840t2612r1994b2636],
15	Alcohol	NN	O	alcohol	nn	16	SENT_35	[p1l164t2657r286b2684],
16	dependence	NN	O	dependence	conj_and	12	SENT_35	[p1l299t2657r482b2691],
17	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	19	SENT_35	[p1l497t2657r567b2691],
18	AD	NN	O	ad	nn	19	SENT_35	[p1l497t2657r567b2691],
19	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	25	SENT_35	[p1l497t2657r567b2691],
20	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	25	SENT_35	[p1l582t2659r605b2684],
21	a	DT	O	a	det	25	SENT_35	[p1l619t2666r636b2684],
22	common	JJ	O	common	amod	25	SENT_35	[p1l650t2666r787b2684],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l801t2657r860b2684],
24	debilitating	JJ	O	debilitating	amod	25	SENT_35	[p1l873t2657r1049b2691],
25	strategies	NNS	O	strategy	ccomp	6	SENT_35	[p1l1110t2659r1256b2691],
26	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1267t2657r1309b2684],
27	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_for	25	SENT_35	[p1l1320t2658r1375b2684],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1320t2658r1375b2684],

1	Previous	JJ	O	previous	amod	2	SENT_36	[p1l1388t2659r1523b2684],
2	research	NN	O	research	nsubj	25	SENT_36	[p1l1534t2657r1668b2684],
3	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	4	SENT_36	[p1l1679t2657r1732b2684],
4	shown	VBN	O	show	rcmod	2	SENT_36	[p1l1744t2657r1847b2684],
5	that	IN	O	that	complm	8	SENT_36	[p1l1858t2657r1922b2684],
6	sus	FW	O	sus	nn	8	SENT_36	[p1l1933t2666r1994b2684],
7	—	FW	O	—	nn	8	SENT_36	[p1l1933t2666r1994b2684],
8	disorder	NN	O	disorder	dep	4	SENT_36	[p1l164t2705r294b2736],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l164t2705r294b2736],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l316t2705r374b2733],
11	ranks	VBZ	O	rank	conj_and	4	SENT_36	[p1l392t2705r479b2733],
12	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l500t2714r608b2739],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_36	[p1l627t2705r676b2733],
14	leading	VBG	O	lead	amod	15	SENT_36	[p1l695t2705r809b2739],
15	causes	NNS	O	cause	prep_among	11	SENT_36	[p1l828t2714r929b2733],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l949t2705r979b2733],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_36	[p1l1000t2705r1049b2733],
18	ceptibility	NN	O	ceptibility	prep_of	15	SENT_36	[p1l1109t2705r1262b2739],
19	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1272t2708r1301b2733],
20	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_to	18	SENT_36	[p1l1311t2706r1360b2732],
21	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	23	SENT_36	[p1l1370t2707r1393b2733],
22	partly	RB	O	partly	advmod	23	SENT_36	[p1l1403t2705r1495b2739],
23	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1506t2707r1616b2739],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1627t2705r1685b2733],
25	has	VBZ	O	have	conj_and	23	SENT_36	[p1l1694t2705r1748b2733],
26	a	DT	O	a	det	27	SENT_36	[p1l1759t2714r1776b2732],
27	heritability	NN	O	heritability	dobj	25	SENT_36	[p1l1786t2705r1957b2739],
28	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1967t2705r1997b2733],
29	global	JJ	O	global	amod	30	SENT_36	[p1l164t2754r258b2788],
30	burden	NN	O	burden	prep_of	27	SENT_36	[p1l278t2754r390b2782],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l411t2754r442b2782],
32	disease	NN	O	disease	prep_of	30	SENT_36	[p1l464t2754r573b2782],
33	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	32	SENT_36	[p1l595t2754r701b2788],
34	World	NNP	ORGANIZATION	World	nn	36	SENT_36	[p1l595t2754r701b2788],
35	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	36	SENT_36	[p1l721t2754r826b2782],
36	Organization	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Organization	dep	40	SENT_36	[p1l847t2755r1049b2788],
37	40-60	CD	PERCENT	40-60	num	38	SENT_36	[p1l1109t2755r1242b2782],
38	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	36	SENT_36	[p1l1109t2755r1242b2782],
39	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	40	SENT_36	[p1l1257t2754r1365b2788],
40	Enoch	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Enoch	dep	27	SENT_36	[p1l1257t2754r1365b2788],
41	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	&	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1377t2755r1400b2782],
42	Goldman	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Goldman	dep	27	SENT_36	[p1l1413t2754r1555b2782],
43	2002	CD	DATE	2002	num	44	SENT_36	[p1l1569t2754r1673b2788],
44	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	40	SENT_36	[p1l1569t2754r1673b2788],
45	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1569t2754r1673b2788],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_37	[p1l1686t2754r1745b2782],
2	introduction	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1758t2754r1954b2782],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1967t2754r1997b2782],
4	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	5	SENT_37	[p1l165t2803r270b2837],
5	)	CD	NUMBER	)	prep_of	2	SENT_37	[p1l165t2803r270b2837],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l165t2803r270b2837],

1	Despite	IN	O	despite	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l282t2805r394b2837],
2	extensive	JJ	O	extensive	amod	3	SENT_38	[p1l405t2805r547b2831],
3	research	NN	O	research	prep_despite	7	SENT_38	[p1l557t2803r699b2834],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l557t2803r699b2834],
5	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	7	SENT_38	[p1l711t2805r732b2831],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	7	SENT_38	[p1l743t2805r765b2831],
7	unclear	JJ	O	unclear	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l776t2803r895b2831],
8	why	WRB	O	why	advmod	27	SENT_38	[p1l906t2803r971b2837],
9	only	RB	O	only	advmod	12	SENT_38	[p1l982t2803r1049b2837],
10	high-density	JJ	O	high-density	amod	12	SENT_38	[p1l1109t2803r1305b2837],
11	single	JJ	O	single	amod	12	SENT_38	[p1l1314t2803r1403b2837],
12	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nsubj	27	SENT_38	[p1l1411t2803r1573b2831],
13	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	nn	18	SENT_38	[p1l1581t2803r1808b2837],
14	(	NN	O	(	nn	18	SENT_38	[p1l1817t2803r1904b2837],
15	SNP	NN	O	snp	nn	18	SENT_38	[p1l1817t2803r1904b2837],
16	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	18	SENT_38	[p1l1817t2803r1904b2837],
17	chips	NNS	O	chip	nn	18	SENT_38	[p1l1914t2803r1994b2837],
18	aproportion	NN	O	aproportion	nsubj	25	SENT_38	[p1l165t2854r359b2886],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l368t2852r399b2880],
20	all	DT	O	all	det	21	SENT_38	[p1l410t2852r447b2879],
21	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_of	18	SENT_38	[p1l456t2852r627b2880],
22	exposed	VBN	O	expose	partmod	21	SENT_38	[p1l637t2852r759b2886],
23	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l768t2855r798b2880],
24	alcohol	NN	O	alcohol	prep_to	22	SENT_38	[p1l808t2852r922b2880],
25	become	VBP	O	become	rcmod	12	SENT_38	[p1l930t2852r1049b2880],
26	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	27	SENT_38	[p1l1109t2852r1163b2880],
27	enabled	VBN	O	enable	advcl	7	SENT_38	[p1l1185t2852r1305b2880],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_38	[p1l1326t2852r1375b2880],
29	systematic	JJ	O	systematic	amod	30	SENT_38	[p1l1397t2854r1560b2886],
30	investigation	NN	O	investigation	dobj	27	SENT_38	[p1l1582t2854r1781b2886],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1803t2852r1833b2880],
32	common	JJ	O	common	prep_of	30	SENT_38	[p1l1857t2861r1994b2880],

1	©	NN	O	©	dep	12	SENT_39	[p1l164t2959r185b2980],
2	201	CD	NUMBER	201	number	3	SENT_39	[p1l194t2959r241b2980],
3	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	1	SENT_39	[p1l247t2959r258b2980],
4	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_39	[p1l267t2958r313b2980],
5	Authors	NNPS	O	Authors	dep	3	SENT_39	[p1l322t2958r427b2983],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l322t2958r427b2983],
7	Addiction	NN	ORGANIZATION	addiction	nn	8	SENT_39	[p1l437t2958r556b2980],
8	Biology	NN	ORGANIZATION	biology	appos	3	SENT_39	[p1l564t2958r655b2985],
9	©	NN	O	©	dep	12	SENT_39	[p1l663t2959r684b2980],
10	201	CD	NUMBER	201	num	9	SENT_39	[p1l693t2959r740b2980],
11	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	12	SENT_39	[p1l746t2959r757b2980],
12	Society	NNP	O	Society	dep	25	SENT_39	[p1l768t2959r854b2985],
13	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l863t2958r895b2980],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_39	[p1l904t2958r942b2980],
15	Study	NN	ORGANIZATION	study	prep_for	12	SENT_39	[p1l951t2958r1020b2985],
16	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1029t2958r1053b2980],
17	Addiction	NN	ORGANIZATION	addiction	nn	19	SENT_39	[p1l1062t2958r1181b2980],
18	Addiction	NN	ORGANIZATION	addiction	nn	19	SENT_39	[p1l1611t2958r1719b2980],
19	Biology	NN	ORGANIZATION	biology	prep_of	15	SENT_39	[p1l1728t2958r1821b2985],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1728t2958r1821b2985],
21	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	22	SENT_39	[p1l1833t2959r1844b2980],
22	7	CD	NUMBER	7	appos	19	SENT_39	[p1l1850t2959r1869b2983],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1850t2959r1869b2983],
24	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	25	SENT_39	[p1l1882t2959r1893b2980],
25	71-180	CD	NUMBER	71-180	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1899t2959r1994b2980],

1	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	4	SENT_40	[p1l15t3169r49b3231],
2	72	CD	NUMBER	72	num	4	SENT_40	[p1l69t3169r156b3234],
3	Iosef	NNP	PERSON	Iosef	nn	4	SENT_40	[p1l342t3166r517b3248],
4	Frank	NNP	PERSON	Frank	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l544t3166r748b3232],
5	et	FW	O	et	nn	6	SENT_40	[p1l773t3174r833b3232],
6	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	4	SENT_40	[p1l860t3166r936b3232],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l860t3166r936b3232],

1	variation	NN	O	variation	nsubj	15	SENT_41	[p1l7t3435r349b3495],
2	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l380t3435r453b3494],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_41	[p1l483t3429r602b3495],
4	human	JJ	O	human	amod	5	SENT_41	[p1l633t3429r910b3495],
5	genome	NN	O	genome	prep_in	1	SENT_41	[p1l941t3451r1253b3511],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l941t3451r1253b3511],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1290t3429r1431b3495],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_41	[p1l1463t3451r1503b3494],
9	large	JJ	O	large	amod	10	SENT_41	[p1l1534t3429r1719b3511],
10	number	NN	O	number	conj_and	5	SENT_41	[p1l1750t3429r2048b3495],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l2080t3429r2153b3495],
12	genome-wide	JJ	O	genome-wide	amod	14	SENT_41	[p1l8t3546r511b3628],
13	association	NN	O	association	nn	14	SENT_41	[p1l570t3552r987b3612],
14	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	10	SENT_41	[p1l1045t3546r1301b3612],
15	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1362t3546r1653b3627],
16	GWAS	NN	O	gwa	nn	17	SENT_41	[p1l1362t3546r1653b3627],
17	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	27	SENT_41	[p1l1362t3546r1653b3627],
18	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1713t3546r1814b3612],
19	a	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_41	[p1l1873t3568r1914b3611],
20	wide	JJ	O	wide	amod	21	SENT_41	[p1l1969t3546r2144b3612],
21	range	NN	O	range	prep_for	17	SENT_41	[p1l7t3685r221b3744],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l254t3663r326b3729],
23	complex	JJ	O	complex	amod	24	SENT_41	[p1l362t3663r676b3744],
24	disorders	NNS	O	disorder	prep_of	21	SENT_41	[p1l707t3663r1045b3729],
25	have	VBP	O	have	aux	27	SENT_41	[p1l1077t3663r1251b3729],
26	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	27	SENT_41	[p1l1282t3663r1460b3729],
27	published	VBN	O	publish	ccomp	15	SENT_41	[p1l1490t3663r1854b3744],
28	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1885t3671r1955b3729],
29	date	NN	O	date	prep_to	27	SENT_41	[p1l1988t3663r2145b3729],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	2	SENT_42	[p2l11t25r355b106],
2	Hindorff	NNP	O	Hindorff	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l11t25r355b106],
3	et	FW	O	et	nn	4	SENT_42	[p2l389t33r449b91],
4	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	2	SENT_42	[p2l476t25r555b91],
5	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	6	SENT_42	[p2l603t25r856b106],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	4	SENT_42	[p2l603t25r856b106],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l603t25r856b106],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_43	[p2l897t25r1114b91],
2	investigations	NNS	O	investigation	nsubj	4	SENT_43	[p2l1156t31r1670b106],
3	have	VBP	O	have	aux	4	SENT_43	[p2l1712t25r1886b91],
4	implicated	VBN	O	implicate	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1928t25r2145b106, p2l8t142r206b208],
5	new	JJ	O	new	amod	6	SENT_43	[p2l235t164r395b208],
6	variants	NNS	O	variant	dobj	4	SENT_43	[p2l423t148r750b216],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l423t148r750b216],
8	genes	NNS	O	gene	dobj	4	SENT_43	[p2l785t164r992b223],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1025t142r1165b208],
10	pathways	NNS	O	pathway	dobj	4	SENT_43	[p2l1193t142r1573b223],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1193t142r1573b223],

1	However	RB	O	however	advmod	6	SENT_44	[p2l1607t146r1948b216],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1607t146r1948b216],
3	they	PRP	O	they	nsubj	6	SENT_44	[p2l1982t142r2146b223],
4	have	VBP	O	have	aux	6	SENT_44	[p2l7t259r181b325],
5	also	RB	O	also	advmod	6	SENT_44	[p2l230t259r373b325],
6	demonstrated	VBN	O	demonstrate	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l420t259r937b325],
7	that	IN	O	that	complm	11	SENT_44	[p2l982t259r1135b324],
8	sample	NN	O	sample	nn	9	SENT_44	[p2l1182t259r1443b340],
9	size	NN	O	size	nsubj	11	SENT_44	[p2l1490t265r1621b325],
10	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	11	SENT_44	[p2l1667t265r1721b325],
11	crucial	JJ	O	crucial	ccomp	6	SENT_44	[p2l1768t259r2028b325],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l2073t265r2145b324],
13	detecting	VBG	O	detect	prepc_in	11	SENT_44	[p2l8t377r352b458],
14	ﬁndings	NNS	O	ﬁndings	dobj	13	SENT_44	[p2l379t377r678b458],
15	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l707t377r878b442],
16	genome-wide	JJ	O	genome-wide	amod	17	SENT_44	[p2l907t377r1409b458],
17	signiﬁcance	NN	O	signiﬁcance	prep_with	13	SENT_44	[p2l1439t377r1880b458],
18	due	JJ	O	due	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1910t377r2044b442],
19	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l2073t385r2144b442],
20	a	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_44	[p2l10t517r51b560],
21	combination	NN	O	combination	prep_due_to	13	SENT_44	[p2l91t495r568b561],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l609t495r682b561],
23	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	24	SENT_44	[p2l726t503r862b561],
24	effects	NNS	O	effect	prep_of	21	SENT_44	[p2l904t495r1151b561],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l904t495r1151b561],

1	First	RB	ORDINAL	first	advmod	14	SENT_45	[p2l1195t499r1382b569],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1195t499r1382b569],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_45	[p2l1427t495r1545b561],
4	effects	NNS	O	effect	nsubj	14	SENT_45	[p2l1586t495r1814b561],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1857t495r1930b561],
6	individual	JJ	O	individual	amod	10	SENT_45	[p2l1974t495r2145b561, p2l7t612r243b677],
7	(	NN	O	(	nn	10	SENT_45	[p2l269t612r654b693],
8	common	JJ	O	common	amod	10	SENT_45	[p2l269t612r654b693],
9	)	NN	O	)	nn	10	SENT_45	[p2l269t612r654b693],
10	variants	NNS	O	variant	prep_of	4	SENT_45	[p2l681t617r988b677],
11	are	VBP	O	be	cop	14	SENT_45	[p2l1016t634r1131b677],
12	typically	RB	O	typically	advmod	14	SENT_45	[p2l1156t612r1475b693],
13	rather	RB	O	rather	advmod	14	SENT_45	[p2l1498t612r1733b677],
14	small	JJ	O	small	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1758t612r1956b677],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1983t612r2141b686],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1983t612r2141b686],
17	second	JJ	ORDINAL	second	nsubj	37	SENT_45	[p2l9t729r283b803],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l9t729r283b803],
19	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l319t750r393b794],
20	a	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_45	[p2l425t751r466b794],
21	consequence	NN	O	consequence	prep_as	37	SENT_45	[p2l495t749r978b810],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1009t729r1082b794],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_45	[p2l1114t729r1232b794],
24	large	JJ	O	large	amod	25	SENT_45	[p2l1262t729r1447b810],
25	number	NN	O	number	prep_of	21	SENT_45	[p2l1476t729r1775b794],
26	of	IN	O	of	prep	25	SENT_45	[p2l1805t729r1878b794],
27	simultaneously	RB	O	simultaneously	pcomp	26	SENT_45	[p2l1912t729r2145b794, p2l7t846r373b927],
28	investigated	VBN	O	investigate	partmod	21	SENT_45	[p2l399t846r844b927],
29	markers	NNS	O	marker	dobj	28	SENT_45	[p2l868t846r1176b911],
30	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1203t868r1298b911],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_45	[p2l1323t846r1441b911],
32	arrays	NNS	O	array	prep_on	28	SENT_45	[p2l1470t868r1725b927],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1470t868r1725b927],
34	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_45	[p2l1755t846r1874b911],
35	singlemarker	NN	O	singlemarker	nn	36	SENT_45	[p2l1901t846r2145b927, p2l7t963r279b1028],
36	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	nsubj	37	SENT_45	[p2l338t963r654b1044],
37	have	VBP	O	have	ccomp	14	SENT_45	[p2l713t963r886b1028],
38	to	TO	O	to	aux	40	SENT_45	[p2l945t970r1015b1028],
39	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	40	SENT_45	[p2l1073t963r1156b1028],
40	corrected	VBN	O	correct	xcomp	37	SENT_45	[p2l1215t963r1567b1028],
41	for	IN	O	for	prep	40	SENT_45	[p2l1625t963r1726b1028],
42	the	DT	O	the	det	44	SENT_45	[p2l1783t963r1901b1028],
43	large	JJ	O	large	amod	44	SENT_45	[p2l1959t963r2144b1044],
44	number	NN	O	number	dep	48	SENT_45	[p2l7t1079r306b1145],
45	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l338t1079r411b1145],
46	tests	NNS	O	test	prep_of	44	SENT_45	[p2l447t1087r611b1145],
47	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	48	SENT_45	[p2l647t1079r866b1161],
48	Yang	NNP	PERSON	Yang	dep	52	SENT_45	[p2l647t1079r866b1161],
49	et	FW	O	et	nn	50	SENT_45	[p2l899t1087r959b1145],
50	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	48	SENT_45	[p2l986t1079r1065b1145],
51	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	52	SENT_45	[p2l1104t1079r1357b1161],
52	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	41	SENT_45	[p2l1104t1079r1357b1161],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1104t1079r1357b1161],
54	allowing	VBG	O	allow	conj_and	14	SENT_45	[p2l1396t1079r1718b1161],
55	only	RB	O	only	advmod	57	SENT_45	[p2l1752t1079r1914b1161],
56	those	DT	O	those	det	57	SENT_45	[p2l1945t1079r2144b1145],
57	markers	NNS	O	marker	dobj	54	SENT_45	[p2l7t1196r314b1262],
58	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l344t1196r516b1262],
59	the	DT	O	the	det	61	SENT_45	[p2l544t1196r662b1262],
60	strongest	JJS	O	strongest	amod	61	SENT_45	[p2l694t1204r1036b1278],
61	effects	NNS	O	effect	prep_with	57	SENT_45	[p2l1065t1196r1292b1262],
62	to	TO	O	to	aux	63	SENT_45	[p2l1323t1204r1393b1262],
63	surpass	VB	O	surpass	xcomp	54	SENT_45	[p2l1425t1218r1704b1278],
64	the	DT	O	the	det	65	SENT_45	[p2l1735t1196r1852b1262],
65	level	NN	O	level	dobj	63	SENT_45	[p2l1883t1196r2050b1262],
66	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l2080t1196r2153b1262],
67	genome-wide	JJ	O	genome-wide	amod	68	SENT_45	[p2l9t1313r511b1395],
68	signiﬁcance	NN	O	signiﬁcance	prep_of	65	SENT_45	[p2l540t1313r998b1395],
69	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l540t1313r998b1395],

1	Recently	RB	DATE	recently	advmod	42	SENT_46	[p2l128t1430r457b1511],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l128t1430r457b1511],
3	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	4	SENT_46	[p2l484t1452r586b1496],
4	reported	VBD	O	report	parataxis	42	SENT_46	[p2l609t1430r927b1512],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_46	[p2l952t1452r992b1495],
6	GWAS	NN	O	gwa	nsubj	36	SENT_46	[p2l1016t1433r1252b1496],
7	conducted	VBN	O	conduct	partmod	6	SENT_46	[p2l1277t1430r1668b1496],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1690t1436r1763b1495],
9	48	CD	NUMBER	48	number	10	SENT_46	[p2l1787t1432r1882b1496],
10	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	12	SENT_46	[p2l1900t1434r1938b1498],
11	male	JJ	O	male	amod	12	SENT_46	[p2l1963t1430r2144b1496],
12	in-patients	NNS	O	in-patient	prep_in	7	SENT_46	[p2l7t1553r410b1629],
13	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l435t1547r606b1612],
14	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_with	12	SENT_46	[p2l629t1550r748b1612],
15	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l776t1547r1147b1629],
16	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	7	SENT_46	[p2l1171t1555r1242b1613],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_46	[p2l1267t1547r1386b1613],
18	Diagnostic	JJ	MISC	diagnostic	amod	21	SENT_46	[p2l1409t1552r1806b1629],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1834t1547r1974b1613],
20	Statistical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	statistical	conj_and	18	SENT_46	[p2l1999t1550r2145b1613, p2l7t1664r255b1730],
21	Manual	NN	ORGANIZATION	manual	pobj	7	SENT_46	[p2l273t1664r567b1730],
22	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l588t1664r661b1730],
23	Mental	JJ	ORGANIZATION	mental	amod	24	SENT_46	[p2l684t1664r949b1730],
24	Disorders	NNS	ORGANIZATION	disorder	prep_of	21	SENT_46	[p2l967t1664r1339b1738],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l967t1664r1339b1738],
26	4th	JJ	ORDINAL	4th	amod	30	SENT_46	[p2l1365t1664r1496b1730],
27	edition	NN	O	edition	nn	30	SENT_46	[p2l1516t1664r1774b1730],
28	(	NN	O	(	nn	30	SENT_46	[p2l1797t1664r2141b1745],
29	DSM-IV	NN	O	dsm-iv	nn	30	SENT_46	[p2l1797t1664r2141b1745],
30	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	21	SENT_46	[p2l1797t1664r2141b1745],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l10t1781r150b1847],
32	1358	CD	DATE	1358	num	35	SENT_46	[p2l203t1783r398b1847],
33	population-based	JJ	O	population-based	amod	35	SENT_46	[p2l449t1781r1102b1863],
34	control	NN	O	control	nn	35	SENT_46	[p2l1149t1781r1418b1847],
35	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_of	21	SENT_46	[p2l1465t1781r1877b1847],
36	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	4	SENT_46	[p2l1929t1781r2056b1862],
37	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1929t1781r2056b1862],
38	a	DT	O	a	det	40	SENT_46	[p2l2105t1803r2146b1846],
39	detailed	JJ	O	detailed	amod	40	SENT_46	[p2l8t1898r300b1964],
40	description	NN	O	description	prep_for	36	SENT_46	[p2l320t1898r752b1979],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l320t1898r752b1979],
42	see	VB	O	see	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l779t1920r888b1964],
43	Treutlein	NNP	O	Treutlein	nsubj	45	SENT_46	[p2l906t1898r1253b1964],
44	et	FW	O	et	nn	45	SENT_46	[p2l1273t1906r1334b1964],
45	al.	FW	O	al.	xcomp	42	SENT_46	[p2l1360t1898r1439b1964],
46	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	47	SENT_46	[p2l1467t1898r1719b1979],
47	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	45	SENT_46	[p2l1467t1898r1719b1979],
48	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1467t1898r1719b1979],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1743t1902r1822b1963],
2	brief	NN	O	brief	prep_in	6	SENT_47	[p2l1841t1898r2025b1972],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1841t1898r2025b1972],
4	no	DT	O	no	det	5	SENT_47	[p2l2050t1920r2144b1964],
5	marker	NN	O	marker	nsubj	6	SENT_47	[p2l7t2015r279b2081],
6	surpassed	VBD	O	surpass	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l312t2015r679b2096],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_47	[p2l710t2015r828b2081],
8	threshold	NN	O	threshold	dobj	6	SENT_47	[p2l860t2015r1218b2081],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1249t2015r1322b2081],
10	genome-wide	JJ	O	genome-wide	amod	11	SENT_47	[p2l1359t2015r1861b2096],
11	signiﬁcance	NN	O	signiﬁcance	prep_of	8	SENT_47	[p2l1894t2015r2145b2096, p2l8t2154r241b2198],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1894t2015r2145b2096, p2l8t2154r241b2198],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l264t2136r343b2197],
2	a	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_48	[p2l365t2154r405b2197],
3	subsequent	JJ	O	subsequent	prep_in	22	SENT_48	[p2l425t2132r851b2213],
4	follow	VBP	O	follow	rcmod	3	SENT_48	[p2l870t2132r1224b2213],
5	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dobj	4	SENT_48	[p2l870t2132r1224b2213],
6	up	IN	O	up	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l870t2132r1224b2213],
7	study	NN	O	study	prep_up	4	SENT_48	[p2l1244t2132r1449b2213],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1468t2132r1541b2198],
9	an	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_48	[p2l1566t2154r1659b2197],
10	independent	JJ	O	independent	amod	11	SENT_48	[p2l1678t2132r2146b2213],
11	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_of	7	SENT_48	[p2l9t2250r270b2331],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l304t2250r377b2315],
13	1024	CD	DATE	1024	num	16	SENT_48	[p2l421t2252r619b2316],
14	male	JJ	O	male	amod	16	SENT_48	[p2l653t2250r835b2315],
15	AD	NN	O	ad	nn	16	SENT_48	[p2l867t2253r986b2315],
16	in-patients	NNS	O	in-patient	prep_of	11	SENT_48	[p2l1020t2255r1422b2331],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1458t2250r1598b2315],
18	996	CD	NUMBER	996	num	19	SENT_48	[p2l1633t2253r1781b2316],
19	controls	NNS	O	control	prep_of	11	SENT_48	[p2l1818t2250r2140b2324],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1818t2250r2140b2324],
21	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	22	SENT_48	[p2l7t2389r109b2432],
22	genotyped	VBD	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l131t2367r519b2448],
23	the	DT	O	the	quantmod	25	SENT_48	[p2l539t2367r656b2432],
24	12	CD	NUMBER	12	number	25	SENT_48	[p2l685t2369r773b2431],
25	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	28	SENT_48	[p2l790t2370r825b2431],
26	top	JJ	O	top	amod	28	SENT_48	[p2l853t2375r970b2448],
27	SN	NNP	O	SN	nn	28	SENT_48	[p2l992t2370r1098b2434],
28	Ps	NNPS	O	Ps	dobj	22	SENT_48	[p2l1101t2371r1184b2432],
29	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1205t2367r1382b2432],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_48	[p2l1402t2367r1520b2432],
31	GWAS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GWAS	prep_from	22	SENT_48	[p2l1543t2370r1778b2433],
32	as	RB	O	as	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1803t2389r1877b2432],
33	well	RB	O	well	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1898t2367r2048b2432],
34	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l2070t2389r2144b2432],
35	an	DT	O	a	det	40	SENT_48	[p2l10t2506r103b2549],
36	additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	40	SENT_48	[p2l124t2484r503b2549],
37	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	38	SENT_48	[p2l529t2487r563b2548],
38	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	40	SENT_48	[p2l578t2487r618b2550],
39	SN	NN	O	sn	nn	40	SENT_48	[p2l644t2487r750b2551],
40	Ps	NN	O	p	conj_and	31	SENT_48	[p2l753t2488r836b2549],
41	suggested	VBN	O	suggest	partmod	40	SENT_48	[p2l858t2484r1221b2565],
42	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1239t2484r1327b2565],
43	combining	VBG	O	combine	agent	41	SENT_48	[p2l1346t2484r1748b2565],
44	the	DT	O	the	det	45	SENT_48	[p2l1767t2484r1886b2549],
45	GWAS	NN	O	gwa	nsubj	46	SENT_48	[p2l1908t2487r2143b2550],
46	results	VBZ	O	result	ccomp	43	SENT_48	[p2l7t2601r253b2666],
47	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l285t2601r457b2666],
48	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	50	SENT_48	[p2l489t2623r661b2682],
49	expression	NN	O	expression	nn	50	SENT_48	[p2l693t2606r1088b2682],
50	data	NNS	O	datum	prep_with	46	SENT_48	[p2l1120t2601r1282b2666],
51	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1313t2601r1490b2666],
52	rats	NNS	O	rat	prep_from	46	SENT_48	[p2l1520t2608r1659b2666],
53	subjected	VBN	O	subject	partmod	52	SENT_48	[p2l1693t2601r2043b2682],
54	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l2073t2608r2144b2666],
55	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	57	SENT_48	[p2l8t2718r294b2783],
56	alcohol	NN	O	alcohol	nn	57	SENT_48	[p2l326t2718r599b2783],
57	exposure	NN	O	exposure	prep_to	53	SENT_48	[p2l628t2740r981b2799],
58	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l628t2740r981b2799],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1014t2721r1093b2782],
2	a	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_49	[p2l1124t2740r1165b2783],
3	combined	JJ	O	combined	amod	4	SENT_49	[p2l1194t2718r1561b2783],
4	analysis	NN	O	analysis	prep_in	14	SENT_49	[p2l1592t2718r1890b2799],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1921t2718r1994b2783],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_49	[p2l2026t2718r2144b2783],
7	GWAS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GWAS	prep_of	4	SENT_49	[p2l8t2837r244b2900],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l281t2835r422b2900],
9	follow-up	JJ	O	follow-up	amod	10	SENT_49	[p2l453t2835r807b2916],
10	data	NNS	O	datum	conj_and	7	SENT_49	[p2l841t2835r1022b2909],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l841t2835r1022b2909],
12	two	CD	NUMBER	two	npadvmod	13	SENT_49	[p2l1060t2842r1196b2900],
13	tightly	RB	O	tightly	advmod	14	SENT_49	[p2l1230t2835r1475b2916],
14	linked	VBN	O	link	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1508t2835r1734b2900],
15	intergenic	JJ	O	intergenic	amod	16	SENT_49	[p2l1766t2840r2144b2916],
16	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	nsubj	17	SENT_49	[p2l8t2955r201b3019],
17	located	JJ	O	located	xcomp	14	SENT_49	[p2l255t2951r523b3017],
18	close	RB	O	close	advmod	17	SENT_49	[p2l576t2951r757b3017],
19	to	TO	O	to	dep	28	SENT_49	[p2l811t2959r882b3017],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_49	[p2l936t2951r1054b3017],
21	peroxisomal	JJ	O	peroxisomal	amod	27	SENT_49	[p2l1108t2951r1565b3033],
22	trans2enoylCoA	NN	O	trans2enoylcoa	nn	27	SENT_49	[p2l1621t2951r2145b3033, p2l9t3071r167b3134],
23	reductase	NN	O	reductase	nn	27	SENT_49	[p2l233t3068r595b3134],
24	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	27	SENT_49	[p2l667t3068r931b3150],
25	PECR	NN	O	pecr	nn	27	SENT_49	[p2l667t3068r931b3150],
26	)	NN	O	)	nn	27	SENT_49	[p2l667t3068r931b3150],
27	gene	NN	O	gene	nsubj	28	SENT_49	[p2l1004t3090r1176b3150],
28	achieved	VBD	O	achieve	ccomp	17	SENT_49	[p2l1247t3068r1574b3134],
29	genome-wide	JJ	O	genome-wide	amod	30	SENT_49	[p2l1642t3068r2144b3150],
30	signiﬁcance	NN	O	signiﬁcance	dobj	28	SENT_49	[p2l9t3185r468b3267],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l9t3185r468b3267],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_50	[p2l128t3302r269b3368],
2	aims	NNS	O	aim	nsubj	10	SENT_50	[p2l298t3308r471b3368],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l499t3302r572b3368],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_50	[p2l601t3302r719b3368],
5	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	6	SENT_50	[p2l744t3310r1021b3384],
6	study	NN	O	study	prep_of	2	SENT_50	[p2l1047t3302r1251b3384],
7	were	VBD	O	be	cop	10	SENT_50	[p2l1276t3324r1453b3368],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	9	SENT_50	[p2l1483t3302r1583b3384],
9	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	10	SENT_50	[p2l1483t3302r1583b3384],
10	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1483t3302r1583b3384],
11	to	TO	O	to	aux	12	SENT_50	[p2l1613t3310r1683b3368],
12	enlarge	VB	O	enlarge	xcomp	10	SENT_50	[p2l1711t3302r1988b3384],
13	our	PRP$	O	we	poss	16	SENT_50	[p2l2016t3324r2145b3368],
14	previous	JJ	O	previous	amod	16	SENT_50	[p2l7t3425r327b3501],
15	GWAS	NNS	O	gwa	nn	16	SENT_50	[p2l357t3422r592b3485],
16	sample	NN	O	sample	dobj	12	SENT_50	[p2l623t3419r883b3501],
17	in	IN	O	in	mark	20	SENT_50	[p2l912t3425r984b3484],
18	order	NN	O	order	dep	20	SENT_50	[p2l1012t3419r1211b3485],
19	to	TO	O	to	aux	20	SENT_50	[p2l1237t3427r1307b3485],
20	increase	VB	O	increase	purpcl	12	SENT_50	[p2l1336t3425r1645b3485],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_50	[p2l1673t3419r1791b3485],
22	power	NN	O	power	dobj	20	SENT_50	[p2l1818t3441r2047b3501],
23	to	TO	O	to	aux	24	SENT_50	[p2l2073t3427r2144b3485],
24	detect	VB	O	detect	infmod	22	SENT_50	[p2l8t3536r230b3602],
25	new	JJ	O	new	amod	27	SENT_50	[p2l253t3558r413b3602],
26	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	nn	27	SENT_50	[p2l436t3536r926b3618],
27	genes	NNS	O	gene	dobj	24	SENT_50	[p2l951t3558r1158b3618],
28	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1181t3536r1269b3617],
29	raising	VBG	O	raise	prepc_by	24	SENT_50	[p2l1290t3542r1549b3618],
30	them	PRP	O	they	dobj	29	SENT_50	[p2l1572t3536r1768b3602],
31	above	IN	O	above	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1792t3536r2002b3602],
32	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_50	[p2l2026t3536r2144b3602],
33	threshold	NN	O	threshold	prep_above	29	SENT_50	[p2l7t3653r365b3719],
34	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l388t3653r460b3719],
35	genome-wide	JJ	O	genome-wide	amod	36	SENT_50	[p2l488t3653r990b3735],
36	signiﬁcance	NN	O	signiﬁcance	prep_of	33	SENT_50	[p2l1015t3653r1456b3735],
37	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1482t3653r1622b3719],
38	(	NN	O	(	prep_of	33	SENT_50	[p2l1647t3653r1747b3734],
39	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	40	SENT_50	[p2l1647t3653r1747b3734],
40	)	NN	O	)	dep	33	SENT_50	[p2l1647t3653r1747b3734],
41	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1774t3661r1844b3719],
42	test	NN	O	test	prep_to	40	SENT_50	[p2l1868t3661r2017b3727],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1868t3661r2017b3727],
44	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l2044t3653r2146b3719],
45	the	DT	O	the	det	47	SENT_50	[p3l7t24r126b90],
46	ﬁrst	JJ	O	ﬁrst	amod	47	SENT_50	[p3l142t24r287b90],
47	time	NN	O	time	prep_for	33	SENT_50	[p3l303t29r486b98],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l303t29r486b98],
49	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l507t24r609b90],
50	the	DT	O	the	det	51	SENT_50	[p3l625t24r743b90],
51	presence	NN	O	presence	prep_for	33	SENT_50	[p3l761t46r1087b105],
52	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l1106t24r1179b90],
53	a	DT	O	a	det	55	SENT_50	[p3l1202t46r1243b89],
54	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	55	SENT_50	[p3l1259t24r1612b105],
55	component	NN	O	component	prep_of	51	SENT_50	[p3l1631t32r2056b105],
56	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l2073t32r2144b90],
57	the	DT	O	the	det	58	SENT_50	[p3l7t141r126b207],
58	development	NN	O	development	prep_to	29	SENT_50	[p3l147t141r626b222],
59	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l647t141r720b207],
60	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_of	58	SENT_50	[p3l743t144r876b207],
61	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l743t144r876b207],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_51	[p3l901t144r963b206],
2	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	3	SENT_51	[p3l981t141r1335b222],
3	component	NN	O	component	nsubjpass	5	SENT_51	[p3l1357t149r1782b222],
4	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_51	[p3l1802t146r1855b207],
5	deﬁned	VBN	O	deﬁned	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l1877t141r2146b207],
6	as	IN	O	as	mark	16	SENT_51	[p3l9t280r84b324],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_51	[p3l100t258r218b324],
8	presence	NN	O	presence	nsubj	16	SENT_51	[p3l233t280r560b339],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l577t258r650b324],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_51	[p3l671t280r712b323],
11	multitude	NN	O	multitude	prep_of	8	SENT_51	[p3l726t258r1095b324],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l1111t258r1184b324],
13	small	JJ	O	small	amod	15	SENT_51	[p3l1204t258r1403b324],
14	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	15	SENT_51	[p3l1419t264r1685b339],
15	effects	NNS	O	effect	prep_of	11	SENT_51	[p3l1702t258r1929b324],
16	(	VBP	O	(	advcl	5	SENT_51	[p3l1949t258r2146b339],
17	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l1949t258r2146b339],
18	individual	JJ	O	individual	amod	20	SENT_51	[p3l7t376r387b441],
19	effect	NN	O	effect	nn	20	SENT_51	[p3l409t376r604b441],
20	sizes	NNS	O	size	prep_with	16	SENT_51	[p3l628t381r793b441],
21	below	IN	O	below	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l816t376r1038b441],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_51	[p3l1060t376r1178b441],
23	threshold	NN	O	threshold	prep_below	16	SENT_51	[p3l1202t376r1560b441],
24	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l1582t376r1683b441],
25	detection	NN	O	detection	prep_for	23	SENT_51	[p3l1707t376r2051b441],
26	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l2077t384r2145b441],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_51	[p3l7t493r126b558],
28	level	NN	O	level	prep_at	16	SENT_51	[p3l157t493r325b558],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l356t493r429b558],
30	single	JJ	O	single	amod	31	SENT_51	[p3l464t493r678b574],
31	markers	NNS	O	marker	prep_of	28	SENT_51	[p3l709t493r1016b558],
32	within	IN	O	within	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l1047t493r1295b558],
33	a	DT	O	a	det	35	SENT_51	[p3l1328t515r1369b558],
34	GWAS	NNP	O	GWAS	nn	35	SENT_51	[p3l1400t493r1686b574],
35	)	NN	O	)	prep_within	16	SENT_51	[p3l1400t493r1686b574],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l1400t493r1686b574],
37	being	VBG	O	be	auxpass	38	SENT_51	[p3l1720t493r1927b574],
38	measured	VBN	O	measure	xcomp	16	SENT_51	[p3l1957t515r2145b558, p3l9t610r214b675],
39	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l239t632r313b675],
40	a	DT	O	a	det	42	SENT_51	[p3l341t632r382b675],
41	summed	VBN	O	sum	amod	42	SENT_51	[p3l407t610r727b675],
42	effect	NN	O	effect	prep_as	38	SENT_51	[p3l751t610r963b675],
43	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l751t610r963b675],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_52	[p3l988t610r1131b675],
2	latter	JJ	O	latter	amod	3	SENT_52	[p3l1155t610r1355b675],
3	method	NN	O	method	nsubjpass	7	SENT_52	[p3l1378t610r1665b675],
4	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	7	SENT_52	[p3l1689t610r1818b675],
5	recently	RB	DATE	recently	advmod	7	SENT_52	[p3l1842t610r2146b691],
6	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_52	[p3l6t727r184b792],
7	applied	VBN	O	apply	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l211t727r477b808],
8	successfully	RB	O	successfully	advmod	7	SENT_52	[p3l503t727r944b808],
9	to	TO	O	to	aux	10	SENT_52	[p3l969t734r1039b792],
10	test	VB	O	test	xcomp	7	SENT_52	[p3l1065t734r1196b792],
11	for	IN	O	for	prep	10	SENT_52	[p3l1221t727r1322b792],
12	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_52	[p3l1349t748r1390b792],
13	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	14	SENT_52	[p3l1414t727r1768b808],
14	contribution	NN	O	contribution	dep	21	SENT_52	[p3l1794t727r2145b792, p3l7t849r156b909],
15	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l186t851r257b909],
16	schizophrenia	NN	O	schizophrenia	nn	19	SENT_52	[p3l291t844r818b925],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l851t844r991b909],
18	bipolar	JJ	O	bipolar	nn	19	SENT_52	[p3l1020t844r1284b925],
19	disorder	NN	O	disorder	prep_to	14	SENT_52	[p3l1315t844r1618b909],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	21	SENT_52	[p3l1653t843r1943b925],
21	Purcell	NNP	PERSON	Purcell	dep	25	SENT_52	[p3l1653t843r1943b925],
22	et	FW	O	et	nn	23	SENT_52	[p3l1975t852r2035b909],
23	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	21	SENT_52	[p3l2061t844r2140b909],
24	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	25	SENT_52	[p3l10t961r262b1042],
25	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	11	SENT_52	[p3l10t961r262b1042],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l10t961r262b1042],

1	For	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l300t964r423b1026],
2	a	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_53	[p3l458t983r499b1026],
3	detailed	JJ	O	detailed	amod	4	SENT_53	[p3l533t961r825b1026],
4	explanation	NN	O	explanation	prep_for	9	SENT_53	[p3l859t961r1305b1042],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1340t961r1413b1026],
6	this	DT	O	this	det	7	SENT_53	[p3l1451t961r1586b1026],
7	approach	NN	O	approach	prep_of	4	SENT_53	[p3l1624t961r1994b1042],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1624t961r1994b1042],
9	see	VB	O	see	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l2034t982r2144b1026],
10	Purcell	NNP	PERSON	Purcell	nsubj	11	SENT_53	[p3l7t1078r273b1143],
11	et	FW	O	et	xcomp	9	SENT_53	[p3l293t1086r353b1143],
12	al.	FW	O	al.	nn	13	SENT_53	[p3l380t1077r459b1143],
13	(	FW	O	(	dep	11	SENT_53	[p3l488t1077r769b1159],
14	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	15	SENT_53	[p3l488t1077r769b1159],
15	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	11	SENT_53	[p3l488t1077r769b1159],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l488t1077r769b1159],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l793t1082r872b1142],
2	simple	JJ	O	simple	amod	3	SENT_54	[p3l894t1078r1132b1159],
3	terms	NNS	O	term	prep_in	9	SENT_54	[p3l1154t1085r1384b1152],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1154t1085r1384b1152],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_54	[p3l1409t1078r1527b1143],
6	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	8	SENT_54	[p3l1548t1078r1902b1159],
7	scorebased	JJ	O	scorebased	amod	8	SENT_54	[p3l1924t1100r2145b1143, p3l6t1194r218b1260],
8	approach	NN	O	approach	nsubj	9	SENT_54	[p3l243t1194r596b1276],
9	uses	VBZ	O	use	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l618t1216r776b1260],
10	information	NN	O	information	dobj	9	SENT_54	[p3l801t1194r1251b1260],
11	concerning	VBG	O	concern	partmod	10	SENT_54	[p3l1274t1200r1703b1276],
12	association	NN	O	association	nn	13	SENT_54	[p3l1728t1200r2145b1260],
13	ﬁndings	NNS	O	ﬁndings	dobj	11	SENT_54	[p3l7t1311r305b1393],
14	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l327t1311r428b1377],
15	several	JJ	O	several	quantmod	16	SENT_54	[p3l450t1311r708b1377],
16	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	17	SENT_54	[p3l737t1314r829b1377],
17	ooo	NN	O	ooo	prep_for	13	SENT_54	[p3l860t1315r1010b1377],
18	SN	NNP	O	SN	nn	19	SENT_54	[p3l1035t1315r1141b1378],
19	Ps	NNP	O	Ps	dep	11	SENT_54	[p3l1144t1316r1226b1377],
20	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1249t1311r1426b1377],
21	a	DT	O	a	det	23	SENT_54	[p3l1448t1333r1490b1376],
22	discovery	NN	O	discovery	nn	23	SENT_54	[p3l1511t1311r1862b1393],
23	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_from	11	SENT_54	[p3l1883t1311r2144b1393],
24	to	TO	O	to	aux	25	SENT_54	[p3l7t1436r78b1494],
25	calculate	VB	O	calculate	xcomp	11	SENT_54	[p3l119t1428r456b1494],
26	a	DT	O	a	det	28	SENT_54	[p3l499t1450r540b1493],
27	summary	NN	O	summary	nn	28	SENT_54	[p3l581t1450r943b1510],
28	score	NN	NUMBER	score	dobj	25	SENT_54	[p3l983t1450r1175b1494],
29	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1215t1428r1316b1494],
30	each	DT	O	each	det	31	SENT_54	[p3l1357t1428r1532b1494],
31	individual	NN	O	individual	prep_for	25	SENT_54	[p3l1572t1428r1951b1494],
32	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1990t1434r2063b1493],
33	a	DT	O	a	det	35	SENT_54	[p3l2105t1450r2146b1493],
34	target	NN	O	target	nn	35	SENT_54	[p3l7t1553r228b1627],
35	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_in	31	SENT_54	[p3l254t1545r532b1627],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l254t1545r532b1627],

1	Subsequent	JJ	O	subsequent	amod	2	SENT_55	[p3l563t1545r1000b1627],
2	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	nsubjpass	4	SENT_55	[p3l1026t1545r1341b1626],
3	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_55	[p3l1369t1567r1484b1611],
4	performed	VBN	O	perform	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1509t1545r1895b1627],
5	to	TO	O	to	aux	6	SENT_55	[p3l1919t1553r1989b1611],
6	test	VB	O	test	xcomp	4	SENT_55	[p3l2015t1553r2146b1611],
7	whether	IN	O	whether	complm	14	SENT_55	[p3l7t1662r321b1728],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_55	[p3l365t1662r482b1728],
9	cases	NNS	O	case	nsubj	14	SENT_55	[p3l528t1684r719b1728],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l765t1668r837b1727],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_55	[p3l881t1662r999b1728],
12	target	NN	O	target	nn	13	SENT_55	[p3l1044t1670r1265b1744],
13	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_in	9	SENT_55	[p3l1310t1662r1571b1744],
14	have	VBP	O	have	ccomp	6	SENT_55	[p3l1615t1662r1789b1728],
15	different	JJ	O	different	amod	16	SENT_55	[p3l1835t1662r2145b1728],
16	scores	NNS	O	score	dobj	14	SENT_55	[p3l9t1801r234b1845],
17	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l256t1779r434b1845],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_55	[p3l454t1779r572b1845],
19	controls	NNS	O	control	prep_from	14	SENT_55	[p3l594t1779r897b1845],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l919t1785r992b1844],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_55	[p3l1013t1779r1131b1845],
22	target	NN	O	target	nn	23	SENT_55	[p3l1153t1787r1374b1861],
23	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_in	19	SENT_55	[p3l1396t1779r1675b1861],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1396t1779r1675b1861],

1	Therefore	RB	O	therefore	advmod	6	SENT_56	[p3l1697t1779r2076b1853],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1697t1779r2076b1853],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_56	[p3l2105t1801r2146b1844],
4	GWAS	NNP	O	GWAS	nsubj	6	SENT_56	[p3l8t1899r244b1962],
5	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	6	SENT_56	[p3l268t1902r321b1962],
6	ﬁrst	JJ	O	ﬁrst	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l343t1896r487b1962],
7	carried	VBD	O	carry	ccomp	6	SENT_56	[p3l509t1896r775b1962],
8	out	RP	O	out	prt	7	SENT_56	[p3l796t1904r920b1962],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l941t1902r1014b1961],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_56	[p3l1037t1918r1078b1961],
11	discovery	NN	O	discovery	nn	12	SENT_56	[p3l1099t1896r1450b1977],
12	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_in	7	SENT_56	[p3l1472t1896r1751b1977],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1472t1896r1751b1977],

1	Following	VBG	O	follow	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1776t1896r2145b1977],
2	this	DT	O	this	det	3	SENT_57	[p3l7t2013r143b2079],
3	step	NN	O	step	prep_following	16	SENT_57	[p3l181t2021r343b2094],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l181t2021r343b2094],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_57	[p3l384t2013r502b2079],
6	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	7	SENT_57	[p3l537t2013r891b2094],
7	score	NN	NUMBER	score	nsubjpass	16	SENT_57	[p3l929t2035r1120b2079],
8	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1156t2013r1257b2079],
9	each	DT	O	each	det	10	SENT_57	[p3l1293t2013r1469b2079],
10	individual	NN	O	individual	prep_for	7	SENT_57	[p3l1504t2013r1883b2079],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1918t2018r1991b2078],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_57	[p3l2026t2013r2144b2079],
13	target	NN	O	target	nn	14	SENT_57	[p3l7t2138r228b2211],
14	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_in	10	SENT_57	[p3l268t2130r528b2211],
15	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_57	[p3l568t2136r621b2196],
16	calculated	VBN	O	calculate	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l661t2130r1045b2196],
17	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1082t2130r1170b2211],
18	counting	VBG	O	count	agent	16	SENT_57	[p3l1208t2136r1548b2211],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_57	[p3l1586t2130r1704b2196],
20	number	NN	O	number	nsubj	24	SENT_57	[p3l1743t2130r2041b2196],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l2080t2130r2153b2196],
22	reference	NN	O	reference	nn	23	SENT_57	[p3l6t2247r352b2313],
23	alleles	NNS	O	allele	prep_of	20	SENT_57	[p3l384t2247r610b2313],
24	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	18	SENT_57	[p3l644t2247r791b2329],
25	e.g.	FW	O	e.g.	dobj	24	SENT_57	[p3l644t2247r791b2329],
26	risk	NN	O	risk	nn	27	SENT_57	[p3l825t2247r962b2313],
27	alleles	NNS	O	allele	dep	25	SENT_57	[p3l993t2247r1218b2313],
28	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1250t2269r1327b2313],
29	minor	JJ	O	minor	amod	31	SENT_57	[p3l1355t2253r1585b2313],
30	alleles	NNS	O	allele	nn	31	SENT_57	[p3l1616t2247r1868b2328],
31	)	NN	O	)	conj_or	25	SENT_57	[p3l1616t2247r1868b2328],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1902t2247r1975b2313],
33	this	DT	O	this	det	34	SENT_57	[p3l2008t2247r2144b2313],
34	subject	NN	O	subject	prep_of	31	SENT_57	[p3l8t2364r271b2446],
35	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l323t2386r417b2430],
36	any	DT	O	any	prep_on	24	SENT_57	[p3l470t2386r607b2445],
37	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l658t2364r731b2430],
38	the	DT	O	the	prep_of	36	SENT_57	[p3l786t2364r904b2430],
39	included	VBN	O	include	partmod	38	SENT_57	[p3l956t2364r1279b2430],
40	loci	NNS	O	locus	dobj	39	SENT_57	[p3l1329t2364r1478b2430],
41	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1329t2364r1478b2430],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_58	[p3l1530t2364r1689b2430],
2	number	NN	O	number	nsubjpass	4	SENT_58	[p3l1741t2364r2040b2430],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_58	[p3l2090t2370r2144b2430],
4	weighted	VBN	O	weight	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l7t2481r348b2563],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l365t2481r452b2562],
6	multiplication	NN	O	multiplication	agent	4	SENT_58	[p3l470t2481r1000b2563],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1018t2481r1190b2546],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_58	[p3l1207t2481r1325b2547],
9	log	NN	O	log	nn	12	SENT_58	[p3l1344t2481r1627b2563],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_58	[p3l1344t2481r1627b2563],
11	OR	NN	O	or	nn	12	SENT_58	[p3l1344t2481r1627b2563],
12	)	NN	O	)	prep_with	4	SENT_58	[p3l1344t2481r1627b2563],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1650t2481r1723b2547],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_58	[p3l1745t2481r1863b2547],
15	respective	JJ	O	respective	amod	16	SENT_58	[p3l1881t2503r2145b2563, p3l7t2603r137b2664],
16	marker	NN	O	marker	prep_of	12	SENT_58	[p3l153t2598r425b2664],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l441t2603r513b2663],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_58	[p3l529t2598r647b2664],
19	discovery	NN	O	discovery	nn	20	SENT_58	[p3l663t2598r1014b2679],
20	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_in	16	SENT_58	[p3l1031t2598r1309b2679],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1031t2598r1309b2679],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_59	[p3l1326t2598r1468b2664],
2	sum	NN	O	sum	nsubjpass	12	SENT_59	[p3l1486t2620r1644b2664],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1660t2598r1733b2664],
4	all	DT	O	all	prep_of	2	SENT_59	[p3l1754t2598r1843b2663],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1858t2598r1931b2664],
6	these	DT	O	these	det	7	SENT_59	[p3l1951t2598r2144b2664],
7	products	NNS	O	product	prep_of	4	SENT_59	[p3l6t2715r333b2796],
8	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_59	[p3l359t2721r412b2781],
9	then	RB	O	then	advmod	10	SENT_59	[p3l438t2715r610b2781],
10	calculated	VBN	O	calculate	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l635t2715r1020b2781],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1046t2715r1186b2781],
12	divided	VBN	O	divide	conj_and	10	SENT_59	[p3l1211t2715r1478b2781],
13	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1501t2715r1588b2796],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_59	[p3l1613t2715r1730b2781],
15	number	NN	O	number	agent	10	SENT_59	[p3l1756t2715r2054b2781],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l2080t2715r2153b2781],
17	included	VBN	O	include	prepc_of	15	SENT_59	[p3l7t2832r330b2898],
18	loci	NNS	O	locus	dobj	17	SENT_59	[p3l364t2832r513b2898],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l364t2832r513b2898],

1	Finally	RB	O	finally	advmod	12	SENT_60	[p3l552t2832r815b2913],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l552t2832r815b2913],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_60	[p3l854t2832r973b2898],
4	association	NN	O	association	nsubjpass	12	SENT_60	[p3l1010t2837r1427b2898],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1463t2832r1536b2898],
6	this	DT	O	this	det	7	SENT_60	[p3l1574t2832r1710b2898],
7	score	NN	NUMBER	score	prep_of	4	SENT_60	[p3l1748t2854r1939b2898],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1974t2832r2146b2897],
9	disease	NN	O	disease	nn	10	SENT_60	[p3l8t2950r269b3015],
10	status	NN	O	status	prep_with	7	SENT_60	[p3l290t2957r510b3015],
11	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	12	SENT_60	[p3l530t2955r584b3015],
12	tested	VBN	O	test	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l604t2950r822b3015],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l840t2955r912b3014],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_60	[p3l931t2950r1049b3015],
15	target	NN	O	target	nn	16	SENT_60	[p3l1069t2958r1290b3031],
16	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_in	12	SENT_60	[p3l1310t2950r1571b3031],
17	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1590t2950r1677b3031],
18	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	19	SENT_60	[p3l1695t2955r1778b3015],
19	inclusion	NN	O	inclusion	agent	12	SENT_60	[p3l1799t2950r2145b3015],
20	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l9t3089r83b3132],
21	a	DT	O	a	det	22	SENT_60	[p3l106t3089r147b3132],
22	predictor	NN	O	predictor	prep_as	12	SENT_60	[p3l165t3067r505b3148],
23	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l524t3072r597b3132],
24	a	DT	O	a	det	27	SENT_60	[p3l618t3089r659b3132],
25	logistic	JJ	O	logistic	amod	27	SENT_60	[p3l678t3067r939b3148],
26	regression	NN	O	regression	nn	27	SENT_60	[p3l959t3072r1347b3148],
27	model	NN	O	model	prep_in	22	SENT_60	[p3l1366t3067r1613b3132],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1366t3067r1613b3132],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_61	[p3l1633t3067r1775b3132],
2	ﬁnding	NN	O	ﬁnding	nsubj	13	SENT_61	[p3l1795t3067r2059b3148],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l2080t3067r2153b3132],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_61	[p3l7t3184r125b3249],
5	presence	NN	O	presence	prep_of	2	SENT_61	[p3l147t3206r474b3265],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l498t3184r571b3249],
7	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_61	[p3l599t3206r640b3249],
8	polygenic	JJ	O	polygenic	amod	9	SENT_61	[p3l661t3184r1015b3265],
9	component	NN	O	component	prep_of	5	SENT_61	[p3l1039t3192r1464b3265],
10	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1486t3192r1556b3249],
11	AD	NN	O	ad	prep_to	9	SENT_61	[p3l1579t3187r1698b3248],
12	would	MD	O	would	aux	13	SENT_61	[p3l1720t3184r1951b3249],
13	indicate	VB	O	indicate	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1973t3184r2145b3249, p3l8t3309r158b3366],
14	that	IN	O	that	complm	24	SENT_61	[p3l183t3301r336b3366],
15	many	JJ	O	many	amod	19	SENT_61	[p3l360t3323r575b3382],
16	more	JJR	O	more	dep	15	SENT_61	[p3l598t3323r791b3366],
17	individual	JJ	O	individual	amod	19	SENT_61	[p3l816t3301r1195b3366],
18	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	19	SENT_61	[p3l1220t3306r1486b3382],
19	variants	NNS	O	variant	nsubj	24	SENT_61	[p3l1510t3306r1818b3366],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1845t3301r1917b3366],
21	small	JJ	O	small	amod	22	SENT_61	[p3l1946t3301r2146b3366],
22	effect	NN	O	effect	prep_of	19	SENT_61	[p3l8t3418r202b3483],
23	still	RB	O	still	advmod	24	SENT_61	[p3l226t3418r355b3483],
24	await	VBP	O	await	ccomp	13	SENT_61	[p3l380t3423r583b3483],
25	detection	NN	O	detection	dobj	24	SENT_61	[p3l606t3418r969b3483],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l606t3418r969b3483],

1	MATERIALS	NNS	O	material	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l12t3664r594b3727],
2	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l634t3664r864b3727],
3	METHODS	NNS	O	method	conj_and	1	SENT_62	[p3l921t3664r1438b3727],

1	Subject	JJ	O	subject	amod	2	SENT_63	[p4l8t76r283b158],
2	recruitment	NN	O	recruitment	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l309t82r759b142],

1	For	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l6t269r128b330],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_64	[p4l147t264r266b330],
3	purposes	NNS	O	purpose	prep_for	17	SENT_64	[p4l286t286r619b346],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l641t264r714b330],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_64	[p4l738t264r856b330],
6	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	7	SENT_64	[p4l876t272r1152b346],
7	study	NN	O	study	prep_of	3	SENT_64	[p4l1173t264r1383b345],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1173t264r1383b345],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_64	[p4l1408t264r1526b330],
10	sample	NN	O	sample	nsubj	17	SENT_64	[p4l1549t264r1809b346],
11	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1830t264r2007b330],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_64	[p4l2026t264r2144b330],
13	previous	JJ	O	previous	amod	14	SENT_64	[p4l6t386r327b462],
14	GWAS	NNP	O	GWAS	prep_from	10	SENT_64	[p4l370t383r605b446],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	14	SENT_64	[p4l651t380r1171b462],
16	subsequently	RB	O	subsequently	advmod	17	SENT_64	[p4l651t380r1171b462],
17	referred	VBN	O	refer	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1210t380r1508b446],
18	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1547t388r1618b446],
19	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1661t402r1735b446],
20	‘	NN	O	‘	nn	21	SENT_64	[p4l1782t380r2141b461],
21	GWAS1	NN	O	gwas1	prep_as	25	SENT_64	[p4l1782t380r2141b461],
22	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	23	SENT_64	[p4l1782t380r2141b461],
23	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	25	SENT_64	[p4l1782t380r2141b461],
24	was	VBD	O	be	cop	25	SENT_64	[p4l7t518r150b562],
25	enlarged	JJ	O	enlarged	prepc_to	17	SENT_64	[p4l203t496r528b578],
26	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l577t496r665b577],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_64	[p4l715t496r834b562],
28	inclusion	NN	O	inclusion	prep_by	25	SENT_64	[p4l885t496r1232b562],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1284t496r1357b562],
30	an	DT	O	a	det	33	SENT_64	[p4l1414t518r1507b561],
31	additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	33	SENT_64	[p4l1561t496r1939b562],
32	900	CD	NUMBER	900	num	33	SENT_64	[p4l1993t499r2142b562],
33	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_of	28	SENT_64	[p4l6t618r304b693],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l344t612r483b678],
35	the	DT	O	the	det	37	SENT_64	[p4l519t612r638b678],
36	GWAS	NNP	O	GWAS	nn	37	SENT_64	[p4l676t615r912b678],
37	data	NNS	O	datum	nsubj	44	SENT_64	[p4l952t612r1114b678],
38	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1152t612r1225b678],
39	a	DT	O	a	det	43	SENT_64	[p4l1267t634r1308b677],
40	further	JJ	O	further	amod	43	SENT_64	[p4l1344t612r1612b678],
41	862	CD	NUMBER	862	num	43	SENT_64	[p4l1654t615r1797b678],
42	German	JJ	MISC	german	amod	43	SENT_64	[p4l1841t615r2145b678],
43	controls	NNS	O	control	prep_of	37	SENT_64	[p4l8t728r310b794],
44	(	VBP	O	(	prepc_to	17	SENT_64	[p4l359t728r879b809],
45	subsequently	RB	O	subsequently	advmod	44	SENT_64	[p4l359t728r879b809],
46	referred	VBN	O	refer	dep	44	SENT_64	[p4l922t728r1219b794],
47	to	TO	O	to	xcomp	46	SENT_64	[p4l1262t736r1333b794],
48	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1381t750r1455b794],
49	‘	NN	O	‘	nn	50	SENT_64	[p4l1504t728r1886b809],
50	GWAS2	NN	O	gwas2	prep_as	46	SENT_64	[p4l1504t728r1886b809],
51	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	52	SENT_64	[p4l1504t728r1886b809],
52	)	NN	O	)	dep	50	SENT_64	[p4l1504t728r1886b809],
53	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1504t728r1886b809],

1	Thus	RB	O	thus	advmod	16	SENT_65	[p4l1932t728r2140b802],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1932t728r2140b802],
3	when	WRB	O	when	advmod	13	SENT_65	[p4l7t844r215b910],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l253t849r325b909],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_65	[p4l362t844r481b910],
6	text	NN	O	text	prep_in	13	SENT_65	[p4l518t852r659b910],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_65	[p4l695t844r813b910],
8	‘	NN	O	‘	nsubjpass	13	SENT_65	[p4l856t844r1150b925],
9	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	11	SENT_65	[p4l856t844r1150b925],
10	study	NN	O	study	nn	11	SENT_65	[p4l1189t844r1410b925],
11	’	NN	O	’	dep	8	SENT_65	[p4l1189t844r1410b925],
12	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_65	[p4l1452t849r1506b910],
13	mentioned	VBN	O	mention	advcl	16	SENT_65	[p4l1544t844r1966b918],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1544t844r1966b918],
15	this	DT	O	this	nsubj	16	SENT_65	[p4l2008t844r2144b910],
16	refers	VBZ	O	refer	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l6t961r214b1026],
17	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l241t969r312b1026],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_65	[p4l340t961r458b1026],
19	pooled	JJ	O	pooled	amod	20	SENT_65	[p4l484t961r731b1042],
20	GWAS1	NN	O	gwas1	prep_to	16	SENT_65	[p4l758t964r1041b1027],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1077t961r1217b1026],
22	GWAS2	NN	O	gwas2	nn	23	SENT_65	[p4l1244t964r1528b1027],
23	data	NNS	O	datum	prep_to	16	SENT_65	[p4l1562t961r1743b1026],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1562t961r1743b1026],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	2	SENT_66	[p4l127t1077r236b1141],
2	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	9	SENT_66	[p4l272t1082r569b1158],
3	were	VBD	O	be	cop	4	SENT_66	[p4l607t1099r784b1142],
4	male	JJ	O	male	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l821t1077r1003b1142],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l1043t1077r1183b1142],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l1220t1077r1293b1142],
7	self	NN	O	self	nn	8	SENT_66	[p4l1335t1077r1803b1158],
8	—	NN	O	—	prep_of	9	SENT_66	[p4l1335t1077r1803b1158],
9	reported	VBD	O	report	conj_and	4	SENT_66	[p4l1335t1077r1803b1158],
10	German	JJ	MISC	german	amod	11	SENT_66	[p4l1841t1080r2145b1143],
11	ancestry	NN	O	ancestry	dobj	9	SENT_66	[p4l9t1201r336b1274],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l9t1201r336b1274],
