1	nature	NN	O	nature	nn	2	SENT_1	[p1l6t75r138b106],
2	Vol	NN	O	vol	dep	9	SENT_1	[p1l1462t73r1507b98],
3	452	CD	NUMBER	452	num	4	SENT_1	[p1l1518t70r1601b104],
4	|	NN	O	|	dep	2	SENT_1	[p1l1518t70r1601b104],
5	3	CD	DATE	3	dep	4	SENT_1	[p1l1518t70r1601b104],
6	April	NNP	DATE	April	tmod	4	SENT_1	[p1l1612t73r1677b104],
7	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	6	SENT_1	[p1l1689t70r1772b104],
8	|	NNP	O	|	dep	9	SENT_1	[p1l1689t70r1772b104],
9	doi	FW	O	doi	dep	12	SENT_1	[p1l6t122r383b150],
10	:10.1038	CD	NUMBER	:10.1038	dep	9	SENT_1	[p1l6t122r383b150],
11	/	:	O	/	punct	12	SENT_1	[p1l6t122r383b150],
12	nature06846	CD	NUMBER	nature06846	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l6t122r383b150],

1	LETTERS	NNS	O	letter	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l14t225r508b319],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_3	[p1l6t442r70b512],
2	variant	NN	O	variant	nsubj	3	SENT_3	[p1l96t440r384b513],
3	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l413t439r842b513],
4	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l872t439r1046b512],
5	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	6	SENT_3	[p1l1080t440r1399b513],
6	dependence	NN	O	dependence	prep_with	3	SENT_3	[p1l1429t439r1936b530],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1429t439r1936b530],
8	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	9	SENT_3	[p1l1969t439r2140b530],
9	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_with	3	SENT_3	[p1l7t569r271b621],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l299t547r443b621],
11	peripheral	JJ	O	peripheral	amod	13	SENT_3	[p1l477t547r884b638],
12	arterial	JJ	O	arterial	amod	13	SENT_3	[p1l916t547r1207b621],
13	disease	NN	O	disease	conj_and	6	SENT_3	[p1l1240t547r1542b621],

1	Thorgeir	NNP	O	Thorgeir	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t694r169b736],
2	E.	NNP	O	E.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l185t696r212b728],
3	Thorgeirsson1	NNP	O	Thorgeirsson1	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l228t688r527b736],
4	*	NNP	O	*	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l228t688r527b736],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l228t688r527b736],
6	Frank	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Frank	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l545t694r647b728],
7	Ge	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ge	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l662t688r823b734],
8	|	VBD	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l662t688r823b734],
9	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l662t688r823b734],
10	er1	NN	O	er1	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l662t688r823b734],
11	*	NN	O	*	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l662t688r823b734],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l662t688r823b734],
13	Patrick	NNP	PERSON	Patrick	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l841t694r969b728],
14	Su	NNP	O	Su	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l984t688r1147b734],
15	|	VBD	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l984t688r1147b734],
16	em1	NN	O	em1	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l984t688r1147b734],
17	*	NN	O	*	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l984t688r1147b734],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l984t688r1147b734],
19	Thorunn	NNP	O	Thorunn	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1163t694r1323b728],
20	Rafnar1	NN	O	rafnar1	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1342t688r1512b734],
21	*	NN	O	*	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1342t688r1512b734],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1342t688r1512b734],
23	Anna	NNP	PERSON	Anna	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1527t696r1625b728],
24	Wiste	NNP	PERSON	Wiste	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1642t688r1805b734],
25	”	NN	O	”	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1642t688r1805b734],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1642t688r1805b734],
27	Kristinn	NNP	PERSON	Kristinn	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1821t696r1963b728],
28	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1982t696r2010b728],
29	Magnussonl	NNP	PERSON	Magnussonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t741r251b790],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l6t741r251b790],
31	Andrei	NNP	PERSON	Andrei	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l266t748r392b782],
32	Manolescul	NNP	PERSON	Manolescul	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l410t741r643b787],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l410t741r643b787],
34	Gudmar	NNP	PERSON	Gudmar	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l659t748r813b782],
35	Thorleifssonl	NNP	PERSON	Thorleifssonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l827t741r1090b788],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l827t741r1090b788],
37	Hreinn	NNP	PERSON	Hreinn	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1107t749r1231b782],
38	Stefanssonl	NNP	PERSON	Stefanssonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1248t741r1481b787],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1248t741r1481b787],
40	Andres	NNP	PERSON	Andres	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1497t748r1633b782],
41	lngasonl	NN	O	lngasonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1650t741r1822b790],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1650t741r1822b790],
43	Simon	NNP	PERSON	Simon	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1838t749r1952b782],
44	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1970t749r2006b781],
45	Staceyl	NNP	PERSON	Staceyl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t795r155b844],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l6t795r155b844],
47	Jon	NNP	PERSON	Jon	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l171t803r232b836],
48	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l248t803r282b835],
49	Bergthorssonl	NNP	PERSON	Bergthorssonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l300t795r576b844],
50	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l300t795r576b844],
51	Steinunn	NNP	PERSON	Steinunn	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l593t803r756b836],
52	Thorlaciusl	NNP	PERSON	Thorlaciusl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l773t795r998b841],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l773t795r998b841],
54	Julius	NNP	PERSON	Julius	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1014t802r1119b836],
55	Gudmundssonl	NNP	PERSON	Gudmundssonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1134t795r1436b841],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1134t795r1436b841],
57	Thorlakur	NNP	PERSON	Thorlakur	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1451t802r1637b836],
58	Jonssonl	NNP	PERSON	Jonssonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1651t795r1828b841],
59	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1651t795r1828b841],
60	Margret	NNP	PERSON	Margret	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1845t803r1997b844],
61	Jakobsdottir1	NNP	PERSON	Jakobsdottir1	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t849r366b895],
62	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l6t849r366b895],
63	Jona	NNP	PERSON	Jona	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t849r366b895],
64	Saemundsdottirl	NNP	PERSON	Saemundsdottirl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l383t849r711b895],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l383t849r711b895],
66	O	NNP	O	O	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l727t849r1053b895],
67	|	VBD	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l727t849r1053b895],
68	ofO	NN	O	ofo	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l727t849r1053b895],
69	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l727t849r1053b895],
70	afsdottir1	NN	O	afsdottir1	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l727t849r1053b895],
71	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l727t849r1053b895],
72	Larus	NNP	PERSON	Larus	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1071t857r1171b890],
73	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1185t857r1209b890],
74	Gudmundssonl	NNP	PERSON	Gudmundssonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1226t849r1527b895],
75	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1226t849r1527b895],
76	Gyda	NNP	PERSON	Gyda	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1544t856r1640b898],
77	Bjornsdottirl	NNP	PERSON	Bjornsdottirl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1658t849r1906b898],
78	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1658t849r1906b898],
79	Kristleifur	NNP	PERSON	Kristleifur	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1922t856r2107b890],
80	Kristjanssonl	NNP	PERSON	Kristjanssonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t903r263b951],
81	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l6t903r263b951],
82	Halla	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Halla	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l281t910r373b943],
83	Sku	NNP	O	Sku	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l391t903r622b949],
84	|	NNP	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l391t903r622b949],
85	adottir3	NN	O	adottir3	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l391t903r622b949],
86	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l391t903r622b949],
87	Helgi	NNP	PERSON	Helgi	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l640t910r733b951],
88	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l748t911r772b943],
89	|	NNP	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l791t903r977b949],
90	saksson4	NN	O	saksson4	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l791t903r977b949],
91	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l791t903r977b949],
92	Tomas	NNP	PERSON	Tomas	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l992t911r1121b943],
93	Gudbjartssons	NNP	PERSON	Gudbjartssons	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1137t903r1417b951],
94	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1137t903r1417b951],
95	Gregory	NNP	PERSON	Gregory	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1434t911r1587b951],
96	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1601t911r1635b943],
97	Joness	NNP	PERSON	Joness	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1650t903r1782b949],
98	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1650t903r1782b949],
99	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	Thomas	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1797t910r1951b943],
100	Mue	NNP	PERSON	Mue	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1962t903r2133b949],
101	|	VBZ	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1962t903r2133b949],
102	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1962t903r2133b949],
103	er9	NN	O	er9	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1962t903r2133b949],
104	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1962t903r2133b949],
105	Anders	NNP	PERSON	Anders	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t963r142b996],
106	Gottsaterlo	NNP	PERSON	Gottsaterlo	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l154t956r376b1002],
107	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l154t956r376b1002],
108	Andrea	NNP	PERSON	Andrea	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l387t963r525b996],
109	Flex	NNP	PERSON	Flex	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l539t956r653b1002],
110	“	NNP	O	“	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l539t956r653b1002],
111	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l539t956r653b1002],
112	Katja	NNP	PERSON	Katja	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l666t964r759b1004],
113	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l773t964r805b996],
114	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l819t964r854b996],
115	Aben12	NN	PERSON	aben12	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l866t956r1050b1002],
116	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l866t956r1050b1002],
117	13	CD	NUMBER	13	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l866t956r1050b1002],
118	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l866t956r1050b1002],
119	Femmie	NNP	O	Femmie	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1063t964r1210b996],
120	de	IN	O	de	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1221t963r1265b996],
121	Vegt	NNP	O	Vegt	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1275t956r1407b1004],
122	”	NNP	O	”	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1275t956r1407b1004],
123	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1275t956r1407b1004],
124	Peter	NNP	PERSON	Peter	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1420t964r1517b996],
125	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1529t964r1555b996],
126	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1566t964r1604b996],
127	Mulders	NNP	PERSON	Mulders	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1617t956r1815b1002],
128	”	NNP	O	”	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1617t956r1815b1002],
129	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1617t956r1815b1002],
130	Dolores	NNP	PERSON	Dolores	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1831t963r1976b996],
131	|	NNP	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1993t956r2096b1002],
132	s	VBZ	O	s	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1993t956r2096b1002],
133	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1993t956r2096b1002],
134	a15	NN	O	a15	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1993t956r2096b1002],
135	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1993t956r2096b1002],
136	Maria	NNP	PERSON	Maria	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t1017r114b1049],
137	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l129t1017r153b1049],
138	Vidal	NNP	PERSON	Vidal	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l169t1009r309b1055],
139	”	NNP	O	”	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l169t1009r309b1055],
140	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l169t1009r309b1055],
141	Laura	NNP	PERSON	Laura	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l327t1017r428b1049],
142	Asin16	NNP	PERSON	Asin16	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l444t1009r570b1055],
143	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l444t1009r570b1055],
144	Berta	NNP	PERSON	Berta	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l588t1017r683b1049],
145	Saez	NNP	PERSON	Saez	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l700t1009r828b1055],
146	”	NNP	O	”	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l700t1009r828b1055],
147	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l700t1009r828b1055],
148	Laura	NNP	PERSON	Laura	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l846t1017r947b1049],
149	Murillo	NNP	PERSON	Murillo	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l964t1009r1141b1055],
150	”	NNP	O	”	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l964t1009r1141b1055],
151	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l964t1009r1141b1055],
152	Thorsteinn	NNP	PERSON	Thorsteinn	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1156t1016r1361b1049],
153	B	NNP	O	B	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1380t1009r1560b1055],
154	|	VBD	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1380t1009r1560b1055],
155	onda	FW	O	onda	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1380t1009r1560b1055],
156	|	FW	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1380t1009r1560b1055],
157	19	CD	NUMBER	19	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1380t1009r1560b1055],
158	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1380t1009r1560b1055],
159	Halldor	NNP	PERSON	Halldor	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1575t1016r1713b1049],
160	Ko	NNP	PERSON	Ko	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1729t1009r1983b1055],
161	|	VBD	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1729t1009r1983b1055],
162	beinsson6	CD	NUMBER	beinsson6	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1729t1009r1983b1055],
163	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1729t1009r1983b1055],
164	Jon	NNP	PERSON	Jon	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1998t1017r2060b1049],
165	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l2077t1017r2114b1050],
166	Stefanssons	NNP	PERSON	Stefanssons	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t1062r239b1108],
167	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l6t1062r239b1108],
168	lngunn	NN	O	lngunn	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l257t1070r383b1110],
169	Hansdottirzo	NNP	PERSON	Hansdottirzo	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l401t1062r644b1108],
170	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l401t1062r644b1108],
171	Valgerdur	NNP	PERSON	Valgerdur	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l659t1069r849b1110],
172	Runarsdottirzo	NNP	PERSON	Runarsdottirzo	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l865t1062r1142b1108],
173	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l865t1062r1142b1108],
174	Roberto	NNP	PERSON	Roberto	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1160t1069r1307b1102],
175	Pola	NNP	PERSON	Pola	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1325t1062r1485b1108],
176	“’	CD	NUMBER	“’	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1325t1062r1485b1108],
177	21	CD	NUMBER	21	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1325t1062r1485b1108],
178	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1325t1062r1485b1108],
179	Bengt	NNP	PERSON	Bengt	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1501t1070r1606b1110],
180	Lindbladlo	NNP	PERSON	Lindbladlo	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1623t1062r1824b1108],
181	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1623t1062r1824b1108],
182	Andre	NNP	PERSON	Andre	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1840t1069r1956b1102],
183	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1972t1070r2018b1102],
184	van	NNP	PERSON	van	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l2034t1079r2098b1102],
185	Rijs	NNP	PERSON	Rijs	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t1115r75b1164],
186	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l6t1115r75b1164],
187	Benjamin	NNP	PERSON	Benjamin	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l93t1123r264b1164],
188	Dieplingerg	NNP	PERSON	Dieplingerg	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l282t1115r501b1164],
189	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l282t1115r501b1164],
190	Meinhard	NNP	PERSON	Meinhard	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l518t1122r699b1156],
191	Ha	NNP	PERSON	Ha	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l718t1115r940b1164],
192	|	VBD	O	|	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l718t1115r940b1164],
193	tmayer9	CD	NUMBER	tmayer9	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l718t1115r940b1164],
194	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l718t1115r940b1164],
195	Jose	NNP	PERSON	Jose	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l955t1124r1037b1156],
196	I.	NNP	PERSON	I.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1054t1124r1070b1155],
197	Mayordomo15	NNP	PERSON	Mayordomo15	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1088t1115r1444b1164],
198	’	VBD	O	’	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1088t1115r1444b1164],
199	16	CD	NUMBER	16	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1088t1115r1444b1164],
200	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1088t1115r1444b1164],
201	17	CD	NUMBER	17	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1088t1115r1444b1164],
202	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1088t1115r1444b1164],
203	Lambertus	NNP	O	Lambertus	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1460t1122r1659b1156],
204	A.	NNP	O	A.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1674t1124r1711b1156],
205	Kiemeney12	NNP	O	Kiemeney12	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1730t1116r2039b1164],
206	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1730t1116r2039b1164],
207	13	CD	NUMBER	13	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1730t1116r2039b1164],
208	’	NN	O	’	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1730t1116r2039b1164],
209	14	CD	NUMBER	14	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1730t1116r2039b1164],
210	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1730t1116r2039b1164],
211	Stefan	NNP	PERSON	Stefan	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t1176r123b1209],
212	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l141t1177r168b1209],
213	Matthiassonzz	NNP	PERSON	Matthiassonzz	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l186t1169r464b1215],
214	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l186t1169r464b1215],
215	Hogni	NNP	O	Hogni	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l482t1177r590b1217],
216	Oskarsson	NNP	O	Oskarsson	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l607t1169r849b1215],
217	”	NN	O	”	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l607t1169r849b1215],
218	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l607t1169r849b1215],
219	Thorarinn	NNP	PERSON	Thorarinn	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l864t1175r1051b1209],
220	Tyrfingssonzo	NNP	PERSON	Tyrfingssonzo	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1067t1169r1333b1217],
221	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1067t1169r1333b1217],
222	Daniel	NNP	PERSON	Daniel	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1349t1176r1466b1209],
223	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1485t1177r1511b1209],
224	Gudbjartssonl	NNP	PERSON	Gudbjartssonl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1528t1169r1808b1217],
225	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1528t1169r1808b1217],
226	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	Jeffrey	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1823t1176r1951b1217],
227	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1967t1177r1997b1209],
228	Gulcherl	NNP	PERSON	Gulcherl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l6t1223r281b1295],
229	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l6t1223r281b1295],
230	Steinn	NNP	PERSON	Steinn	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l307t1235r490b1287],
231	Jonsson7	NNP	PERSON	Jonsson7	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l515t1223r796b1295],
232	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l515t1223r796b1295],
233	Unnur	NNP	O	Unnur	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l824t1236r1008b1287],
234	Thorsteinsdottir1	NN	O	thorsteinsdottir1	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1030t1223r1626b1295],
235	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1030t1223r1626b1295],
236	22	CD	NUMBER	22	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1030t1223r1626b1295],
237	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1030t1223r1626b1295],
238	Augustine	NNP	PERSON	Augustine	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1650t1235r1956b1299],
239	Kongl	NNP	PERSON	Kongl	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l1983t1223r2154b1299],
240	&	CC	O	&	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l9t1326r70b1392],
241	Kari	NNP	PERSON	Kari	dep	242	SENT_4	[p1l101t1327r246b1392],
242	Stefanssonmz	NNP	PERSON	Stefanssonmz	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l280t1311r819b1392],

1	Smoking	NN	O	smoking	nsubj	5	SENT_5	[p1l9t1545r299b1619],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	5	SENT_5	[p1l321t1547r371b1601],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_5	[p1l395t1565r430b1601],
4	leading	VBG	O	lead	amod	5	SENT_5	[p1l451t1545r691b1619],
5	cause	NN	O	cause	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l714t1565r888b1601],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l913t1545r983b1601],
7	preventable	JJ	O	preventable	amod	8	SENT_5	[p1l999t1545r1381b1618],
8	death	NN	O	death	prep_of	5	SENT_5	[p1l1407t1545r1604b1611],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1407t1545r1604b1611],
10	causing	VBG	O	cause	partmod	5	SENT_5	[p1l1630t1547r1876b1619],
11	about	IN	O	about	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1899t1545r2086b1601],
12	5	CD	NUMBER	5	number	13	SENT_5	[p1l2110t1551r2142b1601],
13	million	CD	NUMBER	million	num	15	SENT_5	[p1l8t1634r246b1691],
14	premature	JJ	O	premature	amod	15	SENT_5	[p1l282t1644r624b1707],
15	deaths	NNS	O	death	prep_about	10	SENT_5	[p1l662t1634r871b1691],
16	worldwide	JJ	O	worldwide	amod	18	SENT_5	[p1l906t1634r1251b1691],
17	each	DT	SET	each	det	18	SENT_5	[p1l1289t1634r1433b1691],
18	year	NN	SET	year	tmod	10	SENT_5	[p1l1466t1632r1684b1709],
19	”	RB	O	”	advmod	5	SENT_5	[p1l1466t1632r1684b1709],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1466t1632r1684b1709],

1	Evidence	NN	O	evidence	dep	13	SENT_6	[p1l1723t1634r2013b1691],
2	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l2050t1634r2146b1691],
3	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	4	SENT_6	[p1l9t1725r239b1798],
4	inﬂuence	NN	O	inﬂuence	prep_for	1	SENT_6	[p1l259t1723r560b1780],
5	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l582t1743r664b1780],
6	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	7	SENT_6	[p1l685t1723r965b1798],
7	behaviour	NN	O	behaviour	prep_on	4	SENT_6	[p1l982t1723r1314b1780],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1334t1723r1454b1780],
9	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	prep_on	4	SENT_6	[p1l1472t1725r1739b1780],
10	dependence	NN	O	dependence	dep	13	SENT_6	[p1l1761t1723r2144b1796],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_6	[p1l12t1810r252b1881],
12	ND	NN	ORGANIZATION	nd	nn	13	SENT_6	[p1l12t1810r252b1881],
13	)	NN	O	)	dep	15	SENT_6	[p1l12t1810r252b1881],
14	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	13	SENT_6	[p1l12t1810r252b1881],
15	‘	NN	O	‘	dep	18	SENT_6	[p1l12t1810r252b1881],
16	8	CD	NUMBER	8	num	15	SENT_6	[p1l12t1810r252b1881],
17	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	18	SENT_6	[p1l278t1812r386b1869],
18	prompted	VBN	O	prompt	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l412t1812r738b1886],
19	a	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_6	[p1l765t1832r799b1869],
20	search	NN	O	search	dobj	18	SENT_6	[p1l826t1812r1031b1869],
21	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1058t1812r1154b1869],
22	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	nn	23	SENT_6	[p1l1182t1812r1618b1887],
23	genes	NNS	O	gene	prep_for	20	SENT_6	[p1l1643t1832r1838b1887],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1643t1832r1838b1887],

1	Furthermore	RB	O	furthermore	advmod	3	SENT_7	[p1l1869t1812r2143b1869, p1l8t1921r195b1967],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1869t1812r2143b1869, p1l8t1921r195b1967],
3	assessing	VBG	O	assess	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l238t1903r533b1975],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_7	[p1l570t1901r672b1957],
5	impact	NN	O	impact	dobj	3	SENT_7	[p1l712t1903r937b1974],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l977t1901r1047b1957],
7	sequence	NN	O	sequence	nn	8	SENT_7	[p1l1081t1921r1374b1974],
8	variants	NNS	O	variant	prep_of	5	SENT_7	[p1l1412t1903r1674b1957],
9	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1716t1921r1798b1957],
10	smokingrelated	JJ	O	smokingrelated	amod	11	SENT_7	[p1l1838t1901r2142b1975, p1l8t1990r233b2046],
11	diseases	NNS	O	disease	prep_on	3	SENT_7	[p1l261t1990r518b2046],
12	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	13	SENT_7	[p1l547t1992r597b2046],
13	important	JJ	O	important	dep	3	SENT_7	[p1l625t1992r959b2063],
14	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l986t2000r1050b2046],
15	public	JJ	O	public	amod	19	SENT_7	[p1l1077t1990r1284b2063],
16	health9	NN	O	health9	nn	19	SENT_7	[p1l1310t1987r1617b2046],
17	’	NN	O	’	nn	19	SENT_7	[p1l1310t1987r1617b2046],
18	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	19	SENT_7	[p1l1310t1987r1617b2046],
19	°	NN	O	°	prep_to	13	SENT_7	[p1l1310t1987r1617b2046],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1310t1987r1617b2046],

1	Smoking	NN	O	smoking	nsubj	6	SENT_8	[p1l1649t1990r1938b2064],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	6	SENT_8	[p1l1965t1992r2015b2046],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_8	[p1l2043t1990r2145b2046],
4	major	JJ	O	major	amod	6	SENT_8	[p1l8t2081r202b2153],
5	risk	NN	O	risk	nn	6	SENT_8	[p1l226t2079r350b2136],
6	factor	NN	O	factor	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l372t2079r564b2136],
7	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l587t2079r683b2136],
8	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	9	SENT_8	[p1l705t2079r853b2154],
9	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_for	6	SENT_8	[p1l876t2099r1087b2136],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_8	[p1l1114t2077r1380b2147],
11	LC	NN	O	lc	dep	9	SENT_8	[p1l1114t2077r1380b2147],
12	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	13	SENT_8	[p1l1114t2077r1380b2147],
13	”‘	CD	NUMBER	”‘	num	14	SENT_8	[p1l1114t2077r1380b2147],
14	”	NN	O	”	dep	11	SENT_8	[p1l1114t2077r1380b2147],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1405t2079r1527b2136],
16	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	17	SENT_8	[p1l1549t2081r1600b2136],
17	one	CD	NUMBER	one	conj_and	6	SENT_8	[p1l1625t2099r1740b2136],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1766t2079r1836b2136],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_8	[p1l1852t2079r1954b2136],
20	main	JJ	O	main	amod	21	SENT_8	[p1l1978t2081r2145b2136],
21	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_of	17	SENT_8	[p1l8t2168r133b2225],
22	factors	NNS	O	factor	dep	29	SENT_8	[p1l168t2168r388b2225],
23	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l426t2168r522b2225],
24	peripheral	JJ	O	peripheral	amod	26	SENT_8	[p1l557t2168r896b2241],
25	arterial	JJ	O	arterial	amod	26	SENT_8	[p1l934t2168r1171b2225],
26	disease	NN	O	disease	prep_for	22	SENT_8	[p1l1208t2168r1435b2225],
27	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	28	SENT_8	[p1l1478t2166r1823b2237],
28	PAD	NN	O	pad	dep	29	SENT_8	[p1l1478t2166r1823b2237],
29	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	17	SENT_8	[p1l1478t2166r1823b2237],
30	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	number	31	SENT_8	[p1l1478t2166r1823b2237],
31	5	CD	NUMBER	5	dep	29	SENT_8	[p1l1478t2166r1823b2237],
32	“	NN	O	“	dep	31	SENT_8	[p1l1478t2166r1823b2237],
33	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	32	SENT_8	[p1l1478t2166r1823b2237],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1478t2166r1823b2237],

1	Here	RB	O	here	advmod	3	SENT_9	[p1l1863t2173r2021b2225],
2	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	3	SENT_9	[p1l2056t2188r2144b2225],
3	identify	VBP	O	identify	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l8t2257r264b2331],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	13	SENT_9	[p1l284t2277r318b2314],
5	common	JJ	O	common	amod	13	SENT_9	[p1l339t2277r627b2314],
6	Variant	JJ	O	variant	amod	13	SENT_9	[p1l646t2259r879b2314],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l901t2259r966b2313],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_9	[p1l988t2257r1089b2314],
9	nicotinic	JJ	O	nicotinic	amod	10	SENT_9	[p1l1111t2259r1401b2314],
10	acetylcholine	NN	O	acetylcholine	prep_in	6	SENT_9	[p1l1423t2257r1850b2332],
11	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nn	13	SENT_9	[p1l1873t2267r2146b2330],
12	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	13	SENT_9	[p1l9t2366r156b2421],
13	cluster	NN	O	cluster	dobj	3	SENT_9	[p1l191t2346r410b2403],
14	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l444t2366r526b2403],
15	chromosome	NN	O	chromosome	nn	16	SENT_9	[p1l561t2346r984b2403],
16	15q24	NN	O	15q24	prep_on	13	SENT_9	[p1l1024t2352r1211b2420],
17	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1244t2346r1391b2403],
18	an	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_9	[p1l1426t2366r1503b2403],
19	effect	NN	O	effect	prep_with	3	SENT_9	[p1l1538t2346r1714b2403],
20	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1749t2366r1831b2403],
21	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	22	SENT_9	[p1l1866t2346r2147b2421],
22	quantity	NN	O	quantity	prep_on	19	SENT_9	[p1l9t2437r301b2509],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l9t2437r301b2509],
24	ND	NN	ORGANIZATION	nd	prep_on	19	SENT_9	[p1l340t2439r452b2491],
25	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l493t2435r614b2492],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_9	[p1l651t2435r753b2491],
27	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_on	19	SENT_9	[p1l791t2435r916b2491],
28	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l952t2435r1022b2491],
29	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	31	SENT_9	[p1l1053t2445r1172b2491],
30	smoking-related	JJ	O	smoking-related	amod	31	SENT_9	[p1l1212t2435r1746b2509],
31	diseases	NNS	O	disease	prep_of	27	SENT_9	[p1l1784t2435r2041b2492],
32	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l2080t2437r2145b2491],
33	populations	NNS	O	population	prep_in	31	SENT_9	[p1l7t2524r397b2597],
34	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l433t2523r503b2580],
35	European	JJ	MISC	european	amod	36	SENT_9	[p1l530t2528r845b2597],
36	descent	NN	O	descent	prep_of	33	SENT_9	[p1l879t2524r1138b2580],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l879t2524r1138b2580],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_10	[p1l1175t2524r1299b2580],
2	Variant	JJ	O	variant	nsubj	3	SENT_10	[p1l1331t2526r1564b2580],
3	has	VBZ	O	have	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1597t2523r1705b2580],
4	an	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_10	[p1l1740t2543r1817b2580],
5	effect	NN	O	effect	dobj	3	SENT_10	[p1l1852t2523r2028b2580],
6	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l2063t2543r2145b2580],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_10	[p1l7t2613r109b2670],
8	number	NN	O	number	prep_on	5	SENT_10	[p1l125t2613r385b2670],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l400t2613r470b2670],
10	cigarettes	NNS	O	cigarette	prep_of	8	SENT_10	[p1l479t2615r788b2688],
11	smoked	VBD	O	smoke	partmod	10	SENT_10	[p1l806t2613r1058b2670],
12	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1071t2632r1179b2686],
13	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	11	SENT_10	[p1l1194t2613r1310b2688],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1322t2615r1387b2669],
15	our	PRP$	O	we	poss	16	SENT_10	[p1l1403t2633r1516b2670],
16	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_in	11	SENT_10	[p1l1532t2613r1759b2686],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1776t2613r1846b2670],
18	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_of	16	SENT_10	[p1l1855t2613r2141b2670],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1855t2613r2141b2670],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_11	[p1l8t2702r131b2759],
2	same	JJ	O	same	amod	3	SENT_11	[p1l158t2722r320b2759],
3	variant	NN	O	variant	nsubjpass	5	SENT_11	[p1l343t2704r576b2759],
4	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_11	[p1l599t2722r720b2759],
5	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l746t2702r1077b2759],
6	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1099t2702r1247b2759],
7	ND	NN	ORGANIZATION	nd	prep_with	5	SENT_11	[p1l1270t2707r1383b2759],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1409t2704r1475b2758],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	13	SENT_11	[p1l1500t2722r1534b2759],
10	previous	JJ	O	previous	amod	13	SENT_11	[p1l1557t2704r1837b2775],
11	genomewide	JJ	O	genomewide	amod	13	SENT_11	[p1l1864t2722r2143b2777, p1l6t2790r160b2847],
12	association	NN	O	association	nn	13	SENT_11	[p1l220t2793r581b2847],
13	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	5	SENT_11	[p1l641t2791r820b2865],
14	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	15	SENT_11	[p1l876t2791r1006b2847],
15	used	VBD	O	use	rcmod	13	SENT_11	[p1l1065t2791r1214b2847],
16	low-quantity	JJ	O	low-quantity	amod	17	SENT_11	[p1l1271t2791r1695b2865],
17	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	dobj	15	SENT_11	[p1l1752t2791r2021b2847],
18	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l2082t2810r2145b2847],
19	controlsls	NNS	O	controlsl	prep_as	15	SENT_11	[p1l9t2878r404b2946],
20	”	RB	O	”	advmod	15	SENT_11	[p1l9t2878r404b2946],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l9t2878r404b2946],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l428t2880r549b2937],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l568t2880r715b2937],
24	a	DT	O	a	det	26	SENT_11	[p1l738t2900r772b2937],
25	similar	JJ	O	similar	amod	26	SENT_11	[p1l793t2880r1022b2937],
26	approach	NN	O	approach	prep_with	28	SENT_11	[p1l1044t2880r1347b2954],
27	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	28	SENT_11	[p1l1367t2900r1455b2937],
28	observe	VBP	O	observe	conj_and	5	SENT_11	[p1l1479t2880r1725b2937],
29	a	DT	O	a	det	32	SENT_11	[p1l1749t2900r1783b2937],
30	highly	RB	O	highly	advmod	31	SENT_11	[p1l1802t2880r2011b2955],
31	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	amod	32	SENT_11	[p1l2031t2882r2143b2955, p1l8t2969r261b3025],
32	association	NN	O	association	dobj	28	SENT_11	[p1l293t2971r654b3025],
33	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l682t2969r830b3026],
34	ND	NN	O	nd	prep_with	32	SENT_11	[p1l859t2973r991b3025],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l859t2973r991b3025],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_12	[p1l1022t2972r1074b3025],
2	comparison	NN	O	comparison	nsubj	13	SENT_12	[p1l1105t2971r1490b3042],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1521t2969r1591b3025],
4	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	2	SENT_12	[p1l1615t2989r1776b3025],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1809t2969r1878b3025],
6	LC	NN	O	lc	prep_of	4	SENT_12	[p1l1902t2972r1994b3026],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l2025t2969r2146b3026],
8	PAD	NN	O	pad	prep_of	4	SENT_12	[p1l9t3062r160b3114],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l184t3058r331b3115],
10	population	NN	O	population	nn	11	SENT_12	[p1l354t3058r714b3131],
11	controls	NNS	O	control	prep_with	6	SENT_12	[p1l739t3058r1005b3115],
12	each	DT	O	each	dep	13	SENT_12	[p1l1031t3058r1175b3115],
13	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1200t3058r1444b3115],
14	that	IN	O	that	complm	17	SENT_12	[p1l1467t3058r1597b3115],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_12	[p1l1620t3058r1722b3115],
16	variant	JJ	O	variant	nsubj	17	SENT_12	[p1l1744t3060r1978b3115],
17	confers	VBZ	O	confer	ccomp	13	SENT_12	[p1l2002t3078r2143b3115, p1l8t3147r126b3204],
18	risk	NN	O	risk	dobj	17	SENT_12	[p1l155t3147r279b3204],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l306t3147r377b3204],
20	LC	NN	O	lc	prep_of	18	SENT_12	[p1l398t3150r490b3204],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l518t3147r639b3204],
22	PAD	NN	O	pad	prep_of	18	SENT_12	[p1l667t3151r837b3204],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l667t3151r837b3204],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_13	[p1l868t3147r991b3204],
2	findings	NNS	O	finding	nsubj	3	SENT_13	[p1l1019t3147r1286b3222],
3	provide	VBP	O	provide	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1314t3147r1563b3220],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_13	[p1l1593t3167r1627b3204],
5	case	NN	O	case	nn	6	SENT_13	[p1l1655t3167r1786b3204],
6	study	NN	O	study	dobj	3	SENT_13	[p1l1816t3147r1994b3222],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l2020t3147r2090b3204],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	13	SENT_13	[p1l2112t3167r2146b3204],
9	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	13	SENT_13	[p1l9t3238r620b3311],
10	—	NN	O	—	nn	13	SENT_13	[p1l9t3238r620b3311],
11	environment	NN	O	environment	nn	13	SENT_13	[p1l9t3238r620b3311],
12	interaction	NN	O	interaction	nn	13	SENT_13	[p1l643t3234r1070b3302],
13	”	NN	O	”	prep_of	6	SENT_13	[p1l643t3234r1070b3302],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l643t3234r1070b3302],
15	highlighting	VBG	O	highlight	partmod	3	SENT_13	[p1l1093t3236r1498b3311],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_13	[p1l1519t3236r1621b3293],
17	role	NN	O	role	dobj	15	SENT_13	[p1l1643t3236r1769b3293],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1792t3236r1863b3293],
19	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	20	SENT_13	[p1l1878t3238r2144b3293],
20	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_of	17	SENT_13	[p1l9t3324r318b3381],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l341t3327r405b3381],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_13	[p1l427t3325r529b3381],
23	pathology	NN	O	pathology	prep_in	15	SENT_13	[p1l552t3324r880b3399],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l901t3324r971b3381],
25	other	JJ	O	other	amod	27	SENT_13	[p1l988t3325r1161b3381],
26	serious	JJ	O	serious	amod	27	SENT_13	[p1l1184t3327r1414b3381],
27	diseases	NNS	O	disease	prep_of	23	SENT_13	[p1l1438t3325r1713b3381],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1438t3325r1713b3381],

1	To	TO	O	to	aux	2	SENT_14	[p1l87t3417r171b3471],
2	perform	VB	O	perform	purpcl	20	SENT_14	[p1l194t3414r451b3488],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_14	[p1l475t3435r506b3471],
4	genome	NN	O	genome	nn	7	SENT_14	[p1l528t3414r952b3489],
5	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	7	SENT_14	[p1l528t3414r952b3489],
6	wide	JJ	O	wide	amod	7	SENT_14	[p1l528t3414r952b3489],
7	association	NN	O	association	dobj	2	SENT_14	[p1l976t3416r1321b3471],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_14	[p1l1348t3415r1574b3483],
9	GWA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GWA	nn	11	SENT_14	[p1l1348t3415r1574b3483],
10	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	11	SENT_14	[p1l1348t3415r1574b3483],
11	study	NN	O	study	dep	7	SENT_14	[p1l1603t3414r1774b3489],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1793t3414r1862b3471],
13	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	14	SENT_14	[p1l1877t3414r2145b3489],
14	quantity	NN	O	quantity	prep_of	11	SENT_14	[p1l9t3505r274b3577],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_14	[p1l295t3503r460b3571],
16	SQ	NN	O	sq	nn	17	SENT_14	[p1l295t3503r460b3571],
17	)	NN	O	)	dep	11	SENT_14	[p1l295t3503r460b3571],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l295t3503r460b3571],
19	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	20	SENT_14	[p1l480t3523r564b3559],
20	used	VBD	O	use	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l585t3503r727b3560],
21	questionnaire	NN	O	questionnaire	nn	22	SENT_14	[p1l748t3505r1176b3577],
22	data	NNS	O	datum	dobj	20	SENT_14	[p1l1197t3503r1329b3560],
23	limited	VBN	O	limit	partmod	22	SENT_14	[p1l1347t3503r1572b3560],
24	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1591t3514r1652b3559],
25	basic	JJ	O	basic	amod	26	SENT_14	[p1l1672t3503r1827b3559],
26	questions	NNS	O	question	prep_to	23	SENT_14	[p1l1848t3505r2144b3576],
27	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l9t3612r89b3648],
28	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	29	SENT_14	[p1l125t3592r394b3666],
29	behaviour	NN	O	behaviour	prep_on	23	SENT_14	[p1l427t3592r745b3648],
30	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	32	SENT_14	[p1l780t3592r903b3648],
31	were	VBD	O	be	cop	32	SENT_14	[p1l936t3612r1082b3648],
32	available	JJ	O	available	rcmod	29	SENT_14	[p1l1119t3592r1387b3648],
33	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1424t3591r1514b3648],
34	a	DT	O	a	det	36	SENT_14	[p1l1550t3612r1581b3648],
35	large	JJ	O	large	amod	36	SENT_14	[p1l1615t3592r1764b3666],
36	number	NN	O	number	prep_for	32	SENT_14	[p1l1800t3592r2048b3648],
37	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l2085t3591r2153b3648],
38	lifetime	NN	O	lifetime	nn	39	SENT_14	[p1l7t3681r245b3737],
39	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_of	36	SENT_14	[p1l263t3681r535b3737],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l263t3681r535b3737],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_15	[p1l555t3681r674b3737],
2	GWA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GWA	nsubj	3	SENT_15	[p1l692t3684r870b3738],
3	scan	VB	O	scan	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l886t3701r1019b3737],
4	comprises	VBZ	O	comprise	ccomp	3	SENT_15	[p1l1037t3683r1350b3754],
5	10,995	CD	NUMBER	10,995	num	7	SENT_15	[p1l1375t3686r1569b3746],
6	Icelandic	JJ	MISC	icelandic	amod	7	SENT_15	[p1l1589t3681r1870b3738],
7	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	dobj	4	SENT_15	[p1l1887t3681r2144b3737],
8	who	WP	O	who	nsubjpass	11	SENT_15	[p2l7t15r139b72],
9	had	VBD	O	have	aux	11	SENT_15	[p2l157t15r273b72],
10	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_15	[p2l287t15r434b72],
11	assayed	VBN	O	assay	rcmod	7	SENT_15	[p2l451t15r682b90],
12	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l697t15r836b72],
13	Inﬁnium	NNP	O	Inﬁnium	nn	16	SENT_15	[p2l853t15r1133b72],
14	HumanHap300	NNP	O	HumanHap300	nn	16	SENT_15	[p2l1151t20r1640b89],
15	SNP	NN	O	snp	nn	16	SENT_15	[p2l1660t19r1794b72],
16	chips	NNS	O	chip	prep_with	11	SENT_15	[p2l1813t15r1973b89],
17	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1991t15r2144b72],
18	Illumina	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Illumina	prep_from	11	SENT_15	[p2l9t104r291b161],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l9t104r291b161],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_16	[p2l316t107r368b160],
2	set	NN	O	set	nsubj	7	SENT_16	[p2l390t115r472b161],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l495t104r564b161],
4	306,207	CD	NUMBER	306,207	num	6	SENT_16	[p2l580t109r819b169],
5	single-nucleotide	JJ	O	single-nucleotide	amod	6	SENT_16	[p2l844t104r1379b179],
6	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	prep_of	2	SENT_16	[p2l1402t104r1897b178],
7	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1925t104r2139b173],
8	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	nsubj	10	SENT_16	[p2l1925t104r2139b173],
9	)	JJ	O	)	dep	10	SENT_16	[p2l1925t104r2139b173],
10	fulﬁlling	VBG	O	fulﬁlling	xcomp	7	SENT_16	[p2l9t193r275b268],
11	our	PRP$	O	we	poss	13	SENT_16	[p2l311t214r420b250],
12	quality	NN	O	quality	nn	13	SENT_16	[p2l456t193r673b268],
13	criteria	NNS	O	criterion	nsubjpass	15	SENT_16	[p2l707t195r928b250],
14	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	15	SENT_16	[p2l962t214r1075b250],
15	tested	VBN	O	test	ccomp	10	SENT_16	[p2l1112t193r1309b250],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1112t193r1309b250],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_17	[p2l1346t198r1452b250],
2	focused	VBD	O	focus	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1489t193r1727b250],
3	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1764t214r1844b250],
4	cigarette	NN	O	cigarette	nn	5	SENT_17	[p2l1881t195r2144b268],
5	smoking	NN	O	smoking	prep_on	2	SENT_17	[p2l9t283r294b358],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l9t283r294b358],
7	with	IN	O	with	mark	9	SENT_17	[p2l324t283r464b340],
8	SQ	NN	O	sq	nsubj	9	SENT_17	[p2l493t286r585b352],
9	reported	VBD	O	report	advcl	2	SENT_17	[p2l615t283r884b357],
10	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l913t303r971b340],
11	cigarettes	NNS	O	cigarette	prep_as	9	SENT_17	[p2l1001t285r1293b358],
12	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1322t303r1424b357],
13	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	11	SENT_17	[p2l1453t283r1576b358],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1453t283r1576b358],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	3	SENT_18	[p2l1605t283r1695b340],
2	SQ	NN	O	sq	nn	3	SENT_18	[p2l1725t286r1817b352],
3	data	NNS	O	datum	nsubjpass	5	SENT_18	[p2l1846t283r1978b340],
4	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_18	[p2l2005t303r2151b340],
5	clustered	VBN	O	cluster	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l9t373r289b431],
6	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l320t375r444b431],
7	categories	NNS	O	category	nsubj	8	SENT_18	[p2l477t375r785b449],
8	(	VBP	O	(	prepc_into	5	SENT_18	[p2l821t373r936b443],
9	see	VB	O	see	xcomp	8	SENT_18	[p2l821t373r936b443],
10	Supplementary	NNP	O	Supplementary	nn	12	SENT_18	[p2l967t373r1447b449],
11	Information	NNP	O	Information	nn	12	SENT_18	[p2l1475t373r1886b443],
12	)	NNP	O	)	dobj	9	SENT_18	[p2l1475t373r1886b443],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l1923t373r2039b431],
14	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	15	SENT_18	[p2l2066t394r2151b431],
15	refer	VBP	O	refer	prepc_into	5	SENT_18	[p2l9t463r152b521],
16	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l171t474r232b520],
17	them	PRP	O	they	prep_to	15	SENT_18	[p2l254t463r416b520],
18	as	IN	O	as	mark	22	SENT_18	[p2l438t484r495b520],
19	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	num	21	SENT_18	[p2l518t462r629b532],
20	SQ	NN	O	sq	nn	21	SENT_18	[p2l518t462r629b532],
21	levels	NNS	O	level	nsubj	22	SENT_18	[p2l650t463r852b521],
22	’	VBP	O	’	advcl	15	SENT_18	[p2l650t463r852b521],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l650t463r852b521],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_19	[p2l875t463r995b520],
2	SQ	NN	O	sq	nn	3	SENT_19	[p2l1017t466r1109b532],
3	levels	NNS	O	level	nsubj	5	SENT_19	[p2l1129t463r1295b521],
4	were	VBD	O	be	cop	5	SENT_19	[p2l1315t484r1461b520],
5	o	NN	O	o	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1483t469r1515b521],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_19	[p2l1542t463r1715b532],
7	1-10	CD	NUMBER	1-10	num	8	SENT_19	[p2l1542t463r1715b532],
8	cigarettes	NNS	O	cigarette	dep	5	SENT_19	[p2l1738t465r2029b539],
9	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l2051t483r2152b538],
10	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	8	SENT_19	[p2l9t553r163b629],
11	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	10	SENT_19	[p2l9t553r163b629],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l9t553r163b629],
13	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	14	SENT_19	[p2l208t559r230b610],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	conj_and	5	SENT_19	[p2l277t553r536b623],
15	11-20	CD	NUMBER	11-20	num	16	SENT_19	[p2l277t553r536b623],
16	)	NN	O	)	dep	14	SENT_19	[p2l277t553r536b623],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l277t553r536b623],
18	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	19	SENT_19	[p2l575t559r607b610],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	conj_and	5	SENT_19	[p2l651t553r887b623],
20	21-30	CD	NUMBER	21-30	num	21	SENT_19	[p2l651t553r887b623],
21	)	NN	O	)	dep	19	SENT_19	[p2l651t553r887b623],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l930t553r1045b611],
23	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	24	SENT_19	[p2l1083t559r1113b611],
24	(	NN	O	(	conj_and	5	SENT_19	[p2l1158t553r1249b623],
25	31	CD	NUMBER	31	num	28	SENT_19	[p2l1158t553r1249b623],
26	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1293t574r1359b611],
27	more	JJR	O	more	num	28	SENT_19	[p2l1395t554r1604b623],
28	)	NN	O	)	dep	24	SENT_19	[p2l1395t554r1604b623],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1395t554r1604b623],

1	Each	DT	O	each	det	2	SENT_20	[p2l1644t553r1794b611],
2	increment	NN	O	increment	nsubj	3	SENT_20	[p2l1831t555r2151b611],
3	represents	VBZ	O	represent	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l9t654r325b718],
4	an	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_20	[p2l352t664r425b701],
5	increase	NN	O	increase	dobj	3	SENT_20	[p2l449t645r699b701],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l724t645r785b700],
7	SQ	NN	O	sq	prep_in	5	SENT_20	[p2l811t647r902b712],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l929t643r998b701],
9	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	10	SENT_20	[p2l1020t649r1084b701],
10	cigarettes	NNS	O	cigarette	prep_of	7	SENT_20	[p2l1111t645r1402b719],
11	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1427t663r1529b718],
12	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	10	SENT_20	[p2l1553t643r1676b719],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1553t643r1676b719],

1	Allele	NN	O	allele	nn	2	SENT_21	[p2l1702t643r1876b701],
2	T	NN	O	t	nsubjpass	10	SENT_21	[p2l1901t646r1946b700],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1970t643r2040b701],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_21	[p2l2055t643r2151b701],
5	SNP	NN	ORGANIZATION	snp	nn	6	SENT_21	[p2l9t736r144b790],
6	rs1051730	NN	O	rs1051730	prep_of	2	SENT_21	[p2l189t738r505b790],
7	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_21	[p2l548t753r662b790],
8	most	RBS	O	most	advmod	9	SENT_21	[p2l706t744r861b790],
9	strongly	RB	O	strongly	advmod	10	SENT_21	[p2l905t733r1160b808],
10	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1201t733r1516b790],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1557t733r1697b790],
12	SQ	NN	O	sq	prep_with	10	SENT_21	[p2l1741t736r1851b802],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1741t736r1851b802],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1897t733r2012b790],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_21	[p2l2055t733r2151b790],
16	association	NN	O	association	nsubj	21	SENT_21	[p2l9t825r355b880],
17	was	VBD	O	be	cop	21	SENT_21	[p2l372t843r485b880],
18	highly	RB	O	highly	advmod	19	SENT_21	[p2l504t822r702b898],
19	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	amod	21	SENT_21	[p2l718t822r1042b898],
20	(	NN	O	(	nn	21	SENT_21	[p2l1066t823r1137b892],
21	P	NN	O	p	conj_and	10	SENT_21	[p2l1066t823r1137b892],
22	=	JJ	O	=	amod	21	SENT_21	[p2l1155t844r1202b862],
23	5	CD	NUMBER	5	tmod	22	SENT_21	[p2l1228t829r1259b880],
24	x	CC	O	x	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1287t842r1322b877],
25	10	CD	NUMBER	10	conj_and	10	SENT_21	[p2l1351t825r1460b880],
26	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1351t825r1460b880],
27	16	CD	DATE	16	num	28	SENT_21	[p2l1474t810r1569b892],
28	)	NN	O	)	dep	25	SENT_21	[p2l1474t810r1569b892],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1474t810r1569b892],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_22	[p2l1590t822r1709b880],
2	SNP	NN	O	snp	nsubj	3	SENT_22	[p2l1729t826r1864b880],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1884t825r1929b880],
4	within	IN	O	within	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1947t823r2151b880],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_22	[p2l7t913r104b970],
6	CHRNA3	NN	O	chrna3	nn	7	SENT_22	[p2l132t916r427b971],
7	gene	NN	O	gene	nsubj	14	SENT_22	[p2l448t933r589b988],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l612t915r672b970],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_22	[p2l696t933r727b970],
10	linkage	NN	O	linkage	nn	12	SENT_22	[p2l748t913r971b988],
11	disequilibrium	NN	O	disequilibrium	nn	12	SENT_22	[p2l994t913r1457b987],
12	block	NN	O	block	prep_in	7	SENT_22	[p2l1478t913r1652b970],
13	also	RB	O	also	advmod	14	SENT_22	[p2l1673t913r1790b970],
14	containing	VBG	O	contain	prepc_within	3	SENT_22	[p2l1815t915r2152b988],
15	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	17	SENT_22	[p2l8t1014r120b1060],
16	other	JJ	O	other	amod	17	SENT_22	[p2l142t1003r303b1060],
17	genes	NNS	O	gene	dobj	14	SENT_22	[p2l322t1023r503b1078],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l322t1023r503b1078],
19	CHRNA5	NN	O	chrna5	appos	17	SENT_22	[p2l529t1006r821b1060],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l836t1003r949b1060],
21	CHRNB4	NN	O	chrnb4	conj_and	19	SENT_22	[p2l974t1006r1271b1069],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l974t1006r1271b1069],
23	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	24	SENT_22	[p2l1292t1003r1412b1060],
24	encode	VBP	O	encode	rcmod	17	SENT_22	[p2l1432t1003r1647b1060],
25	nicotinic	JJ	O	nicotinic	amod	27	SENT_22	[p2l1666t1005r1934b1060],
26	acetylcholine	NN	O	acetylcholine	nn	27	SENT_22	[p2l1954t1003r2148b1078, p2l9t1093r230b1151],
27	receptors	NNS	O	receptor	nsubj	28	SENT_22	[p2l266t1104r545b1168],
28	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	24	SENT_22	[p2l585t1093r702b1163],
29	ref	NN	O	ref	dobj	28	SENT_22	[p2l585t1093r702b1163],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l585t1093r702b1163],

1	18	CD	NUMBER	18	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l748t1093r855b1162],
2	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_23	[p2l748t1093r855b1162],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l748t1093r855b1162],

1	Six	CD	NUMBER	six	num	3	SENT_24	[p2l895t1095r986b1151],
2	other	JJ	O	other	amod	3	SENT_24	[p2l1021t1093r1182b1150],
3	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	dep	7	SENT_24	[p2l1218t1096r1378b1151],
4	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1415t1114r1494b1150],
5	chromosome	NN	O	chromosome	nn	6	SENT_24	[p2l1530t1093r1932b1151],
6	15q24	NN	O	15q24	prep_on	3	SENT_24	[p2l1975t1099r2151b1168],
7	passed	VBD	O	pass	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l8t1182r207b1256],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_24	[p2l250t1182r344b1239],
9	threshold	NN	O	threshold	nsubj	17	SENT_24	[p2l388t1182r678b1239],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l722t1182r790b1239],
11	genome	NN	O	genome	nn	16	SENT_24	[p2l826t1182r1240b1257],
12	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	16	SENT_24	[p2l826t1182r1240b1257],
13	wide	JJ	O	wide	amod	16	SENT_24	[p2l826t1182r1240b1257],
14	signiﬁcance	NN	O	signiﬁcance	nn	16	SENT_24	[p2l1284t1182r1637b1257],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_24	[p2l1687t1182r1823b1251],
16	P	NN	O	p	prep_of	9	SENT_24	[p2l1687t1182r1823b1251],
17	<	JJR	O	<	xcomp	7	SENT_24	[p2l1687t1182r1823b1251],
18	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	21	SENT_24	[p2l1843t1188r1875b1239],
19	X	NN	O	x	nn	21	SENT_24	[p2l1902t1202r1937b1236],
20	10-7	CD	NUMBER	10-7	num	21	SENT_24	[p2l1965t1170r2149b1251],
21	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	7	SENT_24	[p2l1965t1170r2149b1251],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1965t1170r2149b1251],
23	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l6t1272r113b1330],
24	they	PRP	O	they	nsubjpass	27	SENT_24	[p2l149t1272r285b1347],
25	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	27	SENT_24	[p2l320t1293r411b1330],
26	all	DT	O	all	advmod	27	SENT_24	[p2l450t1272r520b1330],
27	correlated	VBN	O	correlate	conj_but	7	SENT_24	[p2l559t1272r870b1330],
28	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l905t1272r1045b1330],
29	rs1051730	NN	O	rs1051730	nn	31	SENT_24	[p2l1083t1278r1396b1330],
30	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	31	SENT_24	[p2l1440t1260r1516b1342],
31	r2	NN	O	r2	prep_with	27	SENT_24	[p2l1440t1260r1516b1342],
32	=	JJ	O	=	amod	35	SENT_24	[p2l1541t1294r1588b1312],
33	0.14-0	CD	NUMBER	0.14-0	number	34	SENT_24	[p2l1612t1272r1954b1342],
34	.93	CD	NUMBER	.93	num	35	SENT_24	[p2l1612t1272r1954b1342],
35	)	NN	O	)	dep	27	SENT_24	[p2l1612t1272r1954b1342],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1612t1272r1954b1342],

1	After	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1993t1272r2152b1330],
2	correction	NN	O	correction	prep_after	11	SENT_25	[p2l9t1364r329b1419],
3	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l357t1362r448b1419],
4	rs1051730	NN	O	rs1051730	prep_for	2	SENT_25	[p2l475t1367r807b1427],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l475t1367r807b1427],
6	none	NN	O	none	nsubj	11	SENT_25	[p2l837t1382r992b1419],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1022t1362r1091b1419],
8	these	DT	O	these	det	10	SENT_25	[p2l1110t1362r1266b1419],
9	six	CD	NUMBER	six	num	10	SENT_25	[p2l1295t1364r1380b1419],
10	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	prep_of	6	SENT_25	[p2l1406t1365r1569b1419],
11	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1599t1362r1833b1419],
12	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_25	[p2l1862t1382r1893b1419],
13	P	NN	O	p	nn	14	SENT_25	[p2l1922t1366r1967b1418],
14	value	NN	O	value	nsubj	18	SENT_25	[p2l1988t1362r2151b1419],
15	below	IN	O	below	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l6t1451r194b1509],
16	10-3	CD	NUMBER	10-3	num	17	SENT_25	[p2l229t1439r369b1509],
17	(	CD	NUMBER	(	prep_below	14	SENT_25	[p2l406t1452r521b1521],
18	see	VBP	O	see	ccomp	11	SENT_25	[p2l406t1452r521b1521],
19	Supplementary	NNP	O	Supplementary	nn	20	SENT_25	[p2l553t1451r1028b1527],
20	Table	NNP	O	Table	nsubj	22	SENT_25	[p2l1055t1451r1226b1509],
21	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	22	SENT_25	[p2l1264t1451r1337b1521],
22	)	CD	NUMBER	)	xcomp	18	SENT_25	[p2l1264t1451r1337b1521],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1264t1451r1337b1521],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_26	[p2l1368t1455r1420b1508],
2	quantile	JJ	O	quantile	amod	5	SENT_26	[p2l1450t1451r1997b1526],
3	—	NN	O	—	nn	5	SENT_26	[p2l1450t1451r1997b1526],
4	quantile	NN	O	quantile	nn	5	SENT_26	[p2l1450t1451r1997b1526],
5	plot	NN	O	plot	nsubj	9	SENT_26	[p2l2028t1451r2152b1526],
6	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l8t1542r98b1599],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_26	[p2l125t1542r222b1599],
8	GWA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GWA	prep_for	5	SENT_26	[p2l251t1545r429b1600],
9	scan	VB	O	scan	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l457t1562r590b1599],
10	(	RB	O	(	advmod	11	SENT_26	[p2l622t1542r737b1611],
11	see	VB	O	see	xcomp	9	SENT_26	[p2l622t1542r737b1611],
12	Supplementary	NNP	O	Supplementary	nn	13	SENT_26	[p2l767t1542r1242b1617],
13	Fig	NNP	O	Fig	dobj	11	SENT_26	[p2l1268t1544r1376b1618],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1268t1544r1376b1618],

1	1a	NN	O	1a	nn	2	SENT_27	[p2l1415t1542r1501b1611],
2	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	3	SENT_27	[p2l1415t1542r1501b1611],
3	shows	VBZ	O	show	dep	31	SENT_27	[p2l1536t1542r1722b1599],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_27	[p2l1750t1542r1847b1599],
5	observed	VBN	O	observe	amod	6	SENT_27	[p2l1876t1542r2152b1600],
6	excess	NN	O	excess	dobj	3	SENT_27	[p2l9t1653r194b1690],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l215t1632r284b1690],
8	signals	NNS	O	signal	prep_of	6	SENT_27	[p2l295t1632r516b1708],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l295t1632r516b1708],
10	whereas	IN	O	whereas	mark	27	SENT_27	[p2l536t1632r783b1690],
11	a	DT	O	a	det	15	SENT_27	[p2l805t1653r836b1690],
12	quantile	JJ	O	quantile	amod	15	SENT_27	[p2l856t1632r1403b1707],
13	—	NN	O	—	nn	15	SENT_27	[p2l856t1632r1403b1707],
14	quantile	NN	O	quantile	nn	15	SENT_27	[p2l856t1632r1403b1707],
15	plot	NN	O	plot	nsubj	27	SENT_27	[p2l1422t1632r1546b1707],
16	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1566t1632r1705b1690],
17	removing	VBG	O	remove	prepc_after	15	SENT_27	[p2l1725t1634r2024b1708],
18	182	CD	NUMBER	182	num	19	SENT_27	[p2l2049t1638r2150b1690],
19	markers	NNS	O	marker	npadvmod	20	SENT_27	[p2l8t1722r259b1780],
20	located	JJ	O	located	acomp	17	SENT_27	[p2l288t1722r511b1780],
21	within	IN	O	within	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l539t1722r742b1780],
22	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	23	SENT_27	[p2l777t1728r799b1779],
23	megabase	NN	O	megabase	prep_within	17	SENT_27	[p2l835t1722r1133b1798],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1164t1722r1232b1780],
25	rs1051730	NN	O	rs1051730	prep_of	23	SENT_27	[p2l1253t1728r1567b1780],
26	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	27	SENT_27	[p2l1598t1724r1643b1780],
27	consistent	JJ	O	consistent	advcl	3	SENT_27	[p2l1674t1724r1986b1780],
28	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l2013t1722r2151b1780],
29	noise	NN	O	noise	prep_with	27	SENT_27	[p2l8t1814r170b1869],
30	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	29	SENT_27	[p2l193t1812r308b1881],
31	see	VBP	O	see	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l193t1812r308b1881],
32	Supplementary	NNP	O	Supplementary	nn	33	SENT_27	[p2l327t1812r803b1887],
33	Fig	NNP	O	Fig	nsubj	31	SENT_27	[p2l819t1814r928b1887],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l819t1814r928b1887],

1	lb	NN	O	lb	nn	2	SENT_28	[p2l957t1812r1070b1881],
2	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	18	SENT_28	[p2l957t1812r1070b1881],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l957t1812r1070b1881],
4	illustrating	VBG	O	illustrate	partmod	18	SENT_28	[p2l1091t1812r1429b1887],
5	that	IN	O	that	advmod	4	SENT_28	[p2l1447t1812r1569b1869],
6	all	DT	O	all	dep	5	SENT_28	[p2l1589t1812r1658b1869],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1678t1811r1746b1869],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_28	[p2l1756t1812r1852b1869],
9	strongest	JJS	O	strongest	amod	10	SENT_28	[p2l1872t1823r2152b1887],
10	signals	NNS	O	signal	prep_of	4	SENT_28	[p2l9t1902r213b1978],
11	standing	VBG	O	stand	partmod	10	SENT_28	[p2l250t1902r516b1978],
12	out	RP	O	out	prt	11	SENT_28	[p2l553t1914r657b1960],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l693t1904r753b1959],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_28	[p2l789t1902r885b1960],
15	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	nn	16	SENT_28	[p2l921t1902r1042b1960],
16	plot	NN	O	plot	prep_in	11	SENT_28	[p2l1077t1902r1201b1977],
17	are	VBP	O	be	cop	18	SENT_28	[p2l1238t1923r1329b1960],
18	located	JJ	O	located	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1365t1902r1588b1960],
19	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1625t1923r1705b1960],
20	chromosome	NN	O	chromosome	nn	21	SENT_28	[p2l1741t1902r2152b1960],
21	15q24	NN	O	15q24	prep_on	18	SENT_28	[p2l15t1997r211b2066],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l15t1997r211b2066],

1	An	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_29	[p2l244t1995r336b2049],
2	additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	4	SENT_29	[p2l370t1992r687b2049],
3	2,950	CD	NUMBER	2,950	num	4	SENT_29	[p2l720t1997r883b2058],
4	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	nsubjpass	8	SENT_29	[p2l918t1992r1174b2049],
5	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1207t1992r1360b2049],
6	Iceland	NNP	LOCATION	Iceland	prep_from	4	SENT_29	[p2l1394t1992r1619b2049],
7	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_29	[p2l1650t2012r1795b2049],
8	genotyped	VBN	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1829t1992r2152b2067],
9	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l8t2082r98b2139],
10	rs1051730	NN	O	rs1051730	prep_for	8	SENT_29	[p2l117t2088r449b2148],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l117t2088r449b2148],
12	giving	VBG	O	give	xcomp	8	SENT_29	[p2l471t2084r661b2158],
13	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_29	[p2l680t2103r711b2139],
14	total	NN	O	total	iobj	12	SENT_29	[p2l730t2082r871b2139],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l891t2082r960b2139],
16	13,945	CD	NUMBER	13,945	num	17	SENT_29	[p2l977t2088r1171b2148],
17	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_of	14	SENT_29	[p2l1194t2082r1450b2139],
18	(	RB	O	(	dep	19	SENT_29	[p2l1474t2082r1670b2152],
19	Table	NNP	O	Table	dep	17	SENT_29	[p2l1474t2082r1670b2152],
20	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	21	SENT_29	[p2l1696t2082r1748b2152],
21	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	19	SENT_29	[p2l1696t2082r1748b2152],
22	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1771t2082r1910b2139],
23	a	DT	O	a	det	24	SENT_29	[p2l1930t2103r1962b2139],
24	mean	NN	O	mean	prep_with	17	SENT_29	[p2l1981t2103r2151b2139],
25	variant	JJ	O	variant	amod	26	SENT_29	[p2l6t2174r227b2229],
26	frequency	NN	O	frequency	dobj	12	SENT_29	[p2l250t2172r558b2247],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l580t2172r649b2229],
28	34.7	CD	PERCENT	34.7	num	29	SENT_29	[p2l665t2177r875b2238],
29	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_of	26	SENT_29	[p2l665t2177r875b2238],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l665t2177r875b2238],
31	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	35	SENT_29	[p2l898t2172r1087b2229],
32	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	35	SENT_29	[p2l1111t2174r1156b2229],
33	not	RB	O	not	neg	35	SENT_29	[p2l1180t2183r1286b2229],
34	signiﬁcantly	RB	O	signiﬁcantly	advmod	35	SENT_29	[p2l1310t2172r1689b2247],
35	different	JJ	O	different	rcmod	29	SENT_29	[p2l1710t2172r1975b2229],
36	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1999t2172r2152b2229],
37	the	DT	O	the	det	38	SENT_29	[p2l7t2262r104b2320],
38	frequency	NN	O	frequency	prep_from	35	SENT_29	[p2l123t2262r430b2338],
39	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l447t2262r516b2320],
40	34.4	CD	PERCENT	34.4	num	41	SENT_29	[p2l527t2267r718b2322],
41	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_of	38	SENT_29	[p2l527t2267r718b2322],
42	observed	VBN	O	observe	partmod	41	SENT_29	[p2l740t2262r1016b2320],
43	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1034t2264r1094b2319],
44	4,203	CD	NUMBER	4,203	num	45	SENT_29	[p2l1113t2268r1276b2329],
45	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_in	42	SENT_29	[p2l1298t2262r1641b2320],
46	who	WP	O	who	nsubjpass	48	SENT_29	[p2l1659t2262r1792b2320],
47	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	48	SENT_29	[p2l1810t2283r1956b2320],
48	genotyped	VBN	O	genotype	dep	35	SENT_29	[p2l1975t2283r2149b2338, p2l7t2352r181b2427],
49	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l201t2352r316b2409],
50	who	WP	O	who	dep	51	SENT_29	[p2l335t2352r468b2409],
51	reported	VBD	O	report	dep	35	SENT_29	[p2l490t2352r757b2427],
52	never	RB	O	never	neg	51	SENT_29	[p2l777t2373r946b2409],
53	having	VBG	O	have	aux	54	SENT_29	[p2l965t2352r1175b2428],
54	smoked	VBN	O	smoke	xcomp	51	SENT_29	[p2l1195t2352r1437b2409],
55	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	56	SENT_29	[p2l1461t2352r1634b2421],
56	odds	NNS	O	odds	xcomp	54	SENT_29	[p2l1461t2352r1634b2421],
57	ratio	NN	O	ratio	nn	59	SENT_29	[p2l1655t2354r1799b2409],
58	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	59	SENT_29	[p2l1826t2352r1979b2422],
59	OR	NN	O	or	dep	56	SENT_29	[p2l1826t2352r1979b2422],
60	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	61	SENT_29	[p2l1826t2352r1979b2422],
61	1.01	CD	NUMBER	1.01	num	66	SENT_29	[p2l2012t2358r2150b2418],
62	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l2012t2358r2150b2418],
63	95	CD	PERCENT	95	number	64	SENT_29	[p2l9t2446r145b2500],
64	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	66	SENT_29	[p2l9t2446r145b2500],
65	conﬁdence	NN	O	conﬁdence	nn	66	SENT_29	[p2l177t2441r513b2498],
66	interval	NN	O	interval	dep	56	SENT_29	[p2l543t2441r779b2498],
67	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	69	SENT_29	[p2l812t2442r935b2510],
68	CI	NN	O	ci	nn	69	SENT_29	[p2l812t2442r935b2510],
69	)	NN	O	)	dep	66	SENT_29	[p2l812t2442r935b2510],
70	0.96-1	CD	NUMBER	0.96-1	num	71	SENT_29	[p2l970t2447r1285b2507],
71	.07	CD	NUMBER	.07	nsubj	51	SENT_29	[p2l970t2447r1285b2507],
72	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l970t2447r1285b2507],
73	P	NN	O	p	appos	71	SENT_29	[p2l1317t2446r1427b2497],
74	=	JJ	O	=	amod	76	SENT_29	[p2l1317t2446r1427b2497],
75	0.60	CD	NUMBER	0.60	tmod	74	SENT_29	[p2l1451t2442r1624b2510],
76	)	NN	O	)	dep	73	SENT_29	[p2l1451t2442r1624b2510],
77	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1451t2442r1624b2510],

1	Indeed	RB	O	indeed	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1656t2441r1886b2507],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1656t2441r1886b2507],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_30	[p2l1917t2441r2014b2498],
4	frequency	NN	O	frequency	appos	1	SENT_30	[p2l2042t2441r2148b2498, p2l9t2552r234b2607],

1	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l252t2531r321b2589],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_31	[p2l332t2531r429b2589],
3	variant	NN	O	variant	prep_of	11	SENT_31	[p2l448t2533r667b2589],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l689t2533r749b2588],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_31	[p2l770t2531r867b2589],
6	3,627	CD	NUMBER	3,627	num	10	SENT_31	[p2l889t2536r1052b2598],
7	low	JJ	O	low	amod	10	SENT_31	[p2l1073t2531r1479b2607],
8	—	NN	O	—	nn	10	SENT_31	[p2l1073t2531r1479b2607],
9	quantity	NN	O	quantity	nn	10	SENT_31	[p2l1073t2531r1479b2607],
10	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_in	3	SENT_31	[p2l1498t2531r1753b2589],
11	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1780t2531r1876b2600],
12	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	15	SENT_31	[p2l1780t2531r1876b2600],
13	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1899t2552r1965b2589],
14	fewer	JJR	O	fewer	conj_or	12	SENT_31	[p2l1985t2531r2152b2589],
15	cigarettes	NNS	O	cigarette	nsubj	21	SENT_31	[p2l9t2623r298b2696],
16	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l322t2640r423b2695],
17	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	15	SENT_31	[p2l447t2621r577b2696],
18	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	17	SENT_31	[p2l447t2621r577b2696],
19	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	21	SENT_31	[p2l608t2623r652b2678],
20	signiﬁcantly	RB	O	signiﬁcantly	advmod	21	SENT_31	[p2l677t2620r1056b2696],
21	less	JJR	O	less	ccomp	11	SENT_31	[p2l1076t2621r1180b2678],
22	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1205t2621r1345b2678],
23	that	DT	O	that	prep_than	21	SENT_31	[p2l1368t2621r1490b2678],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1515t2623r1575b2677],
25	those	DT	O	those	prep_in	23	SENT_31	[p2l1598t2620r1763b2678],
26	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	29	SENT_31	[p2l1785t2621r1918b2678],
27	do	VBP	O	do	aux	29	SENT_31	[p2l1944t2621r2021b2678],
28	not	RB	O	not	neg	29	SENT_31	[p2l2047t2632r2153b2678],
29	smoke	VB	O	smoke	rcmod	25	SENT_31	[p2l9t2710r209b2768],
30	(	JJ	O	(	amod	36	SENT_31	[p2l236t2711r368b2780],
31	OR	NN	O	or	tmod	30	SENT_31	[p2l236t2711r368b2780],
32	0.83	CD	NUMBER	0.83	num	31	SENT_31	[p2l388t2716r532b2777],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l388t2716r532b2777],
34	95	CD	PERCENT	95	number	35	SENT_31	[p2l558t2716r694b2770],
35	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	31	SENT_31	[p2l558t2716r694b2770],
36	CI	NN	O	ci	dobj	29	SENT_31	[p2l718t2714r791b2768],
37	0.78-0	CD	NUMBER	0.78-0	num	38	SENT_31	[p2l814t2716r1129b2777],
38	.90	CD	NUMBER	.90	nsubj	11	SENT_31	[p2l814t2716r1129b2777],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l814t2716r1129b2777],
40	P	NN	O	p	appos	38	SENT_31	[p2l1154t2715r1199b2767],
41	=	JJ	O	=	amod	40	SENT_31	[p2l1216t2732r1263b2750],
42	4.5	CD	NUMBER	4.5	tmod	41	SENT_31	[p2l1287t2717r1376b2768],
43	x	CC	O	x	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1403t2730r1438b2765],
44	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	45	SENT_31	[p2l1467t2698r1654b2780],
45	‘	NN	O	‘	appos	38	SENT_31	[p2l1467t2698r1654b2780],
46	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	47	SENT_31	[p2l1467t2698r1654b2780],
47	)	NN	O	)	dep	45	SENT_31	[p2l1467t2698r1654b2780],
48	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1467t2698r1654b2780],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_32	[p2l1679t2710r1799b2768],
2	increase	NN	O	increase	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1821t2713r2068b2768],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l2091t2713r2152b2767],
4	ldeCODE	NNP	O	ldeCODE	nn	5	SENT_32	[p2l7t2813r118b2840],
5	Genetics	NNP	O	Genetics	prep_in	2	SENT_32	[p2l128t2819r237b2843],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l128t2819r237b2843],
7	101	CD	NUMBER	101	num	10	SENT_32	[p2l247t2819r282b2840],
8	Reykjavik	NNP	LOCATION	Reykjavik	nn	10	SENT_32	[p2l294t2819r409b2845],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l294t2819r409b2845],
10	Iceland	NNP	LOCATION	Iceland	appos	5	SENT_32	[p2l421t2819r509b2840],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l421t2819r509b2840],

1	2Department	NN	O	2department	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l520t2813r675b2845],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l685t2819r707b2840],
3	Psychiatry	NNP	O	Psychiatry	nn	6	SENT_33	[p2l718t2819r839b2845],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l849t2819r891b2840],
5	Behavioral	NNP	O	Behavioral	nn	6	SENT_33	[p2l903t2819r1023b2840],
6	Sciences	NNPS	O	Sciences	prep_of	1	SENT_33	[p2l1035t2819r1142b2843],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1035t2819r1142b2843],
8	Emory	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Emory	nn	9	SENT_33	[p2l1154t2819r1228b2845],
9	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	1	SENT_33	[p2l1238t2819r1363b2845],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1238t2819r1363b2845],
11	Atlanta	NNP	LOCATION	Atlanta	appos	1	SENT_33	[p2l1373t2819r1466b2843],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1373t2819r1466b2843],
13	GA	NNP	O	GA	appos	1	SENT_33	[p2l1477t2819r1514b2840],
14	30322	CD	NUMBER	30322	num	13	SENT_33	[p2l1524t2819r1606b2843],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1524t2819r1606b2843],
16	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	appos	1	SENT_33	[p2l1617t2819r1674b2840],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1617t2819r1674b2840],

1	3Department	NN	O	3department	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1684t2813r1839b2845],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1850t2819r1872b2840],
3	Medical	NNP	MISC	Medical	nn	4	SENT_34	[p2l1882t2819r1975b2840],
4	Oncology	NNP	MISC	Oncology	prep_of	1	SENT_34	[p2l1986t2818r2104b2845],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1986t2818r2104b2845],
6	4Department	NN	O	4department	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l6t2846r164b2878],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l174t2851r196b2873],
8	Pathology	NN	O	pathology	prep_of	6	SENT_34	[p2l207t2851r329b2878],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l207t2851r329b2878],
10	‘	SYM	O	‘	dep	6	SENT_34	[p2l339t2846r495b2878],
11	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l339t2846r495b2878],
12	’D	NN	O	’d	nn	13	SENT_34	[p2l339t2846r495b2878],
13	epartment	NN	O	epartment	dep	6	SENT_34	[p2l339t2846r495b2878],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l506t2851r528b2873],
15	Cardiothoracic	JJ	O	cardiothoracic	amod	16	SENT_34	[p2l537t2851r713b2873],
16	Surgery	NN	O	surgery	prep_of	13	SENT_34	[p2l724t2852r820b2878],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l724t2852r820b2878],
18	6Department	NN	O	6department	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l830t2846r987b2878],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l997t2851r1019b2873],
20	General	NNP	O	General	nn	22	SENT_34	[p2l1029t2851r1120b2873],
21	Adult	NN	O	adult	nn	22	SENT_34	[p2l1131t2851r1195b2873],
22	Psychiatry	NNP	O	Psychiatry	prep_of	18	SENT_34	[p2l1207t2851r1334b2878],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1207t2851r1334b2878],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1345t2851r1386b2873],
25	7Department	NN	O	7department	prep_of	18	SENT_34	[p2l1397t2846r1553b2878],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1563t2851r1586b2873],
27	Medicine	NNP	MISC	Medicine	prep_of	25	SENT_34	[p2l1596t2851r1711b2877],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1596t2851r1711b2877],
29	Landspitali	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Landspitali	nn	31	SENT_34	[p2l1723t2851r1849b2878],
30	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	31	SENT_34	[p2l1860t2852r1980b2878],
31	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l1991t2851r2094b2878],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1991t2851r2094b2878],
33	101	CD	NUMBER	101	num	34	SENT_34	[p2l2104t2852r2139b2873],
34	Reykjavik	NNP	LOCATION	Reykjavik	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l6t2885r121b2911],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l6t2885r121b2911],
36	Iceland	NNP	LOCATION	Iceland	nn	38	SENT_34	[p2l142t2885r225b2906],
37	.8	NNP	NUMBER	.8	nn	38	SENT_34	[p2l239t2880r409b2911],
38	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l239t2880r409b2911],
39	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l430t2885r452b2906],
40	Surgery	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Surgery	prep_of	38	SENT_34	[p2l471t2885r567b2911],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l471t2885r567b2911],
42	Dunedin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dunedin	nn	43	SENT_34	[p2l589t2885r686b2906],
43	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l708t2885r785b2906],
44	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l806t2885r828b2906],
45	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	prep_of	43	SENT_34	[p2l848t2885r963b2910],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l848t2885r963b2910],
47	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l984t2886r1103b2911],
48	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1123t2885r1146b2906],
49	Otago	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Otago	prep_of	47	SENT_34	[p2l1165t2885r1244b2911],
50	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1165t2885r1244b2911],
51	Dunedin	NNP	LOCATION	Dunedin	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l1265t2885r1363b2906],
52	9054	CD	NUMBER	9054	num	51	SENT_34	[p2l1384t2886r1455b2910],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1384t2886r1455b2910],
54	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	57	SENT_34	[p2l1476t2886r1529b2906],
55	Zealand	NNP	LOCATION	Zealand	nn	57	SENT_34	[p2l1549t2885r1643b2906],
56	.9	NNP	NUMBER	.9	nn	57	SENT_34	[p2l1657t2880r1827b2911],
57	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l1657t2880r1827b2911],
58	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1847t2885r1869b2906],
59	Laboratory	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Laboratory	nn	60	SENT_34	[p2l1890t2885r2018b2911],
60	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	prep_of	57	SENT_34	[p2l2039t2885r2154b2910],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l2039t2885r2154b2910],
62	Konventhospital	NNP	PERSON	Konventhospital	nn	64	SENT_34	[p2l6t2918r198b2944],
63	Barmherzige	NNP	PERSON	Barmherzige	nn	64	SENT_34	[p2l209t2917r358b2944],
64	Brueder	NNP	PERSON	Brueder	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l368t2917r465b2943],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l368t2917r465b2943],
66	4020	CD	NUMBER	4020	num	69	SENT_34	[p2l475t2918r541b2939],
67	Linz	NNP	LOCATION	Linz	nn	69	SENT_34	[p2l552t2918r603b2943],
68	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l552t2918r603b2943],
69	Austria	NNP	LOCATION	Austria	appos	1	SENT_34	[p2l612t2918r704b2939],
70	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l612t2918r704b2939],

1	l	NN	O	l	nn	3	SENT_35	[p2l712t2912r814b2939],
2	°	CD	NUMBER	°	num	3	SENT_35	[p2l712t2912r814b2939],
3	Center	NNP	O	Center	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l712t2912r814b2939],
4	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l822t2917r854b2939],
5	Vascular	JJ	O	vascular	amod	6	SENT_35	[p2l863t2917r968b2939],
6	Diseases	NNS	O	disease	prep_for	3	SENT_35	[p2l978t2918r1087b2943],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l978t2918r1087b2943],
8	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	9	SENT_35	[p2l1099t2918r1218b2944],
9	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	appos	3	SENT_35	[p2l1228t2917r1331b2944],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1228t2917r1331b2944],
11	MAS	NNP	O	MAS	appos	3	SENT_35	[p2l1342t2918r1406b2942],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1342t2918r1406b2942],
13	205	CD	NUMBER	205	number	14	SENT_35	[p2l1416t2918r1462b2939],
14	02	CD	NUMBER	02	appos	11	SENT_35	[p2l1472t2918r1502b2939],
15	Malmo	NNP	LOCATION	Malmo	dep	14	SENT_35	[p2l1513t2917r1602b2943],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1513t2917r1602b2943],
17	Sweden	NNP	LOCATION	Sweden	appos	11	SENT_35	[p2l1612t2917r1710b2939],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1612t2917r1710b2939],
19	"	''	O	"	punct	3	SENT_35	[p2l1719t2912r1864b2944],

1	Laboratory	NN	O	laboratory	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1719t2912r1864b2944],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1874t2917r1896b2939],
3	Vascular	JJ	ORGANIZATION	vascular	amod	4	SENT_36	[p2l1904t2917r2009b2939],
4	Biology	NN	ORGANIZATION	biology	prep_of	1	SENT_36	[p2l2019t2917r2104b2944],
5	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l2113t2917r2154b2939],
6	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	prep_of	1	SENT_36	[p2l6t2951r115b2976],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l6t2951r115b2976],
8	A.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	A.	nn	11	SENT_36	[p2l125t2951r148b2972],
9	Gemelli	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Gemelli	nn	11	SENT_36	[p2l158t2950r248b2972],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	11	SENT_36	[p2l259t2951r378b2977],
11	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	appos	1	SENT_36	[p2l391t2950r494b2977],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l391t2950r494b2977],
13	Universita	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universita	nn	18	SENT_36	[p2l507t2951r626b2972],
14	Cattolica	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cattolica	nn	18	SENT_36	[p2l639t2950r744b2972],
15	del	NNP	ORGANIZATION	del	nn	18	SENT_36	[p2l756t2950r789b2972],
16	Sacro	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sacro	nn	18	SENT_36	[p2l802t2951r867b2972],
17	Cuore	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cuore	nn	18	SENT_36	[p2l879t2951r950b2972],
18	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	appos	1	SENT_36	[p2l962t2950r1039b2972],
19	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1051t2950r1073b2972],
20	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	prep_of	18	SENT_36	[p2l1085t2950r1200b2975],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1085t2950r1200b2975],
22	00168	CD	NUMBER	00168	num	25	SENT_36	[p2l1212t2951r1288b2972],
23	Rome	NNP	LOCATION	Rome	nn	25	SENT_36	[p2l1302t2951r1374b2976],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1302t2951r1374b2976],
25	Italy	NNP	LOCATION	Italy	appos	1	SENT_36	[p2l1388t2950r1442b2977],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1388t2950r1442b2977],

1	l2Department	NN	O	l2department	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1453t2945r1618b2977],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1629t2950r1652b2972],
3	Epidemiology	NNP	O	Epidemiology	prep_of	1	SENT_37	[p2l1664t2950r1823b2977],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1834t2950r1876b2972],
5	Biostatistics	NNP	O	Biostatistics	prep_of	1	SENT_37	[p2l1889t2951r2038b2976],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1889t2951r2038b2976],
7	Radboud	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Radboud	nn	11	SENT_37	[p2l2052t2950r2154b2972],
8	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	11	SENT_37	[p2l6t2984r125b3010],
9	Nijmegen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nijmegen	nn	11	SENT_37	[p2l136t2984r248b3010],
10	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	11	SENT_37	[p2l6t3017r99b3038],
11	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	appos	1	SENT_37	[p2l117t3017r202b3041],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l117t3017r202b3041],
13	6500	CD	NUMBER	6500	num	15	SENT_37	[p2l221t3017r285b3038],
14	HB	NNP	ORGANIZATION	HB	nn	15	SENT_37	[p2l305t3017r337b3038],
15	Nijmegen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nijmegen	appos	1	SENT_37	[p2l356t3017r474b3043],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l356t3017r474b3043],
17	The	DT	LOCATION	the	det	18	SENT_37	[p2l492t3016r536b3038],
18	Netherlands	NNP	LOCATION	Netherlands	appos	1	SENT_37	[p2l555t3017r705b3038],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l555t3017r705b3038],

1	l3Comprehensive	JJ	O	l3comprehensive	amod	4	SENT_38	[p2l723t3011r929b3043],
2	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	4	SENT_38	[p2l947t3017r1030b3038],
3	Center	NNP	O	Center	nn	4	SENT_38	[p2l1048t3017r1128b3038],
4	East	NNP	O	East	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1146t3017r1199b3041],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1146t3017r1199b3041],
6	6501	CD	NUMBER	6501	num	8	SENT_38	[p2l1218t3017r1273b3038],
7	BG	NNP	ORGANIZATION	BG	nn	8	SENT_38	[p2l1293t3017r1325b3038],
8	Nijmegen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nijmegen	appos	4	SENT_38	[p2l1345t3017r1463b3043],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1345t3017r1463b3043],
10	The	DT	LOCATION	the	det	11	SENT_38	[p2l1481t3017r1525b3038],
11	Netherlands	NNP	LOCATION	Netherlands	appos	8	SENT_38	[p2l1544t3017r1694b3038],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1544t3017r1694b3038],

1	“	NNP	O	“	nn	2	SENT_39	[p2l1711t3011r1877b3043],
2	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1711t3011r1877b3043],
3	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1895t3017r1917b3038],
4	Urology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Urology	prep_of	2	SENT_39	[p2l1934t3017r2032b3043],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1934t3017r2032b3043],
6	Radboud	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Radboud	nn	10	SENT_39	[p2l2051t3017r2154b3038],
7	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	10	SENT_39	[p2l6t3050r126b3076],
8	Nijmegen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nijmegen	nn	10	SENT_39	[p2l6t3082r117b3108],
9	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	10	SENT_39	[p2l133t3081r227b3103],
10	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	appos	2	SENT_39	[p2l243t3082r328b3107],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l243t3082r328b3107],
12	6525	CD	NUMBER	6525	num	14	SENT_39	[p2l343t3082r403b3103],
13	GA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GA	nn	14	SENT_39	[p2l419t3082r456b3103],
14	Nijmegen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nijmegen	appos	2	SENT_39	[p2l472t3082r590b3108],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l472t3082r590b3108],
16	The	DT	LOCATION	the	det	17	SENT_39	[p2l606t3081r650b3103],
17	Netherlands	NNP	LOCATION	Netherlands	appos	2	SENT_39	[p2l666t3081r816b3103],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l666t3081r816b3103],

1	l5Division	NN	O	l5division	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l831t3076r945b3103],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l960t3081r983b3103],
3	Medical	NNP	O	Medical	nn	4	SENT_40	[p2l997t3081r1090b3103],
4	Oncology	NNP	O	Oncology	prep_of	1	SENT_40	[p2l1107t3081r1226b3108],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1107t3081r1226b3108],
6	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	7	SENT_40	[p2l1242t3082r1361b3108],
7	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	appos	1	SENT_40	[p2l1377t3081r1481b3108],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1377t3081r1481b3108],
9	5009	CD	NUMBER	5009	num	12	SENT_40	[p2l1496t3082r1560b3103],
10	Zaragoza	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Zaragoza	nn	12	SENT_40	[p2l1576t3082r1692b3108],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1576t3082r1692b3108],
12	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	1	SENT_40	[p2l1708t3082r1777b3108],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1708t3082r1777b3108],

1	“	NN	O	“	nn	3	SENT_41	[p2l1787t3076r2004b3108],
2	Nanotechnology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nanotechnology	nn	3	SENT_41	[p2l1787t3076r2004b3108],
3	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l2020t3082r2117b3103],
4	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l2132t3081r2154b3103],
5	Aragon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Aragon	prep_of	3	SENT_41	[p2l6t3115r98b3141],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l6t3115r98b3141],
7	5009	CD	NUMBER	5009	num	10	SENT_41	[p2l112t3115r176b3136],
8	Zaragoza	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Zaragoza	nn	10	SENT_41	[p2l190t3115r306b3141],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l190t3115r306b3141],
10	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	5	SENT_41	[p2l319t3115r388b3141],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l319t3115r388b3141],
12	"	''	O	"	punct	3	SENT_41	[p2l401t3109r498b3136],

1	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	3	SENT_42	[p2l401t3109r498b3136],
2	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	nn	3	SENT_42	[p2l512t3115r601b3136],
3	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l616t3115r718b3140],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l616t3115r718b3140],
5	5009	CD	NUMBER	5009	num	8	SENT_42	[p2l732t3115r796b3136],
6	Zaragoza	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Zaragoza	nn	8	SENT_42	[p2l810t3115r926b3141],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l810t3115r926b3141],
8	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	3	SENT_42	[p2l939t3115r1008b3141],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l939t3115r1008b3141],

1	“	NNP	O	“	nn	2	SENT_43	[p2l1021t3109r1135b3136],
2	Division	NNP	O	Division	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1021t3109r1135b3136],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1148t3115r1170b3136],
4	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	5	SENT_43	[p2l1183t3115r1276b3136],
5	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	prep_of	2	SENT_43	[p2l1290t3115r1409b3141],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1290t3115r1409b3141],
7	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	nn	9	SENT_43	[p2l1423t3115r1520b3141],
8	Reina	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Reina	nn	9	SENT_43	[p2l1535t3115r1597b3136],
9	Sofia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sofia	appos	2	SENT_43	[p2l1610t3115r1673b3140],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1610t3115r1673b3140],
11	31500	CD	NUMBER	31500	num	12	SENT_43	[p2l1686t3115r1760b3136],
12	Tudela	NN	O	tudelum	appos	2	SENT_43	[p2l1772t3114r1859b3140],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1772t3114r1859b3140],
14	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	2	SENT_43	[p2l1872t3115r1945b3141],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1872t3115r1945b3141],

1	l9Department	NN	O	l9department	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1954t3109r2119b3141],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l2132t3115r2154b3136],
3	Lung	NN	O	lung	nn	4	SENT_44	[p2l6t3148r61b3174],
4	Disease	NN	O	disease	prep_of	1	SENT_44	[p2l76t3148r173b3173],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l76t3148r173b3173],
6	Primary	JJ	ORGANIZATION	primary	amod	9	SENT_44	[p2l189t3148r279b3174],
7	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	9	SENT_44	[p2l295t3147r371b3169],
8	Care	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Care	nn	9	SENT_44	[p2l387t3148r441b3169],
9	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	appos	1	SENT_44	[p2l456t3148r541b3173],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l456t3148r541b3173],
11	101	CD	NUMBER	101	num	14	SENT_44	[p2l555t3148r590b3169],
12	Reykjavik	NNP	LOCATION	Reykjavik	nn	14	SENT_44	[p2l607t3147r723b3174],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l607t3147r723b3174],
14	Iceland	NNP	LOCATION	Iceland	appos	1	SENT_44	[p2l739t3147r828b3169],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l739t3147r828b3169],

1	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	2	SENT_45	[p2l838t3142r935b3174],
2	°	CD	NUMBER	°	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l838t3142r935b3174],
3	Vogur	NNP	O	Vogur	nn	7	SENT_45	[p2l838t3142r935b3174],
4	SAA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	SAA	nn	7	SENT_45	[p2l949t3148r1001b3169],
5	Addiction	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Addiction	nn	7	SENT_45	[p2l1016t3147r1131b3169],
6	Treatment	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Treatment	nn	7	SENT_45	[p2l1145t3148r1271b3169],
7	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	2	SENT_45	[p2l1286t3148r1371b3173],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1286t3148r1371b3173],
9	112	CD	NUMBER	112	appos	7	SENT_45	[p2l1385t3148r1419b3169],
10	Reykjavik	NNP	LOCATION	Reykjavik	dep	2	SENT_45	[p2l1435t3147r1551b3174],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1435t3147r1551b3174],
12	Iceland	NNP	LOCATION	Iceland	appos	10	SENT_45	[p2l1567t3142r1745b3169],
13	.21	CD	NUMBER	.21	num	12	SENT_45	[p2l1567t3142r1745b3169],
14	OASI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	OASI	nn	15	SENT_45	[p2l1567t3142r1745b3169],
15	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	2	SENT_45	[p2l1763t3148r1859b3169],
16	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1874t3147r1906b3169],
17	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	prep_for	15	SENT_45	[p2l1921t3147r2027b3169],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l2042t3147r2084b3169],
19	Care	NNP	O	Care	prep_for	15	SENT_45	[p2l2099t3148r2154b3169],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	22	SENT_45	[p2l6t3180r108b3206],
21	IRCCS	NN	O	ircc	nn	22	SENT_45	[p2l6t3180r108b3206],
22	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_45	[p2l6t3180r108b3206],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l6t3180r108b3206],
24	94018	CD	NUMBER	94018	num	25	SENT_45	[p2l118t3181r194b3202],
25	Troina	NNP	O	Troina	appos	22	SENT_45	[p2l203t3181r278b3202],
26	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	25	SENT_45	[p2l292t3180r353b3206],
27	EN	IN	O	en	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l292t3180r353b3206],
28	)	CD	NUMBER	)	prep_en	25	SENT_45	[p2l292t3180r353b3206],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l292t3180r353b3206],
30	Italy	NNP	LOCATION	Italy	appos	2	SENT_45	[p2l365t3180r419b3207],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l365t3180r419b3207],

1	22School	NN	O	22school	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l429t3175r530b3202],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l541t3180r563b3202],
3	Medicine	NNP	MISC	Medicine	prep_of	1	SENT_46	[p2l573t3180r688b3206],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l573t3180r688b3206],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	1	SENT_46	[p2l700t3181r819b3207],
6	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l829t3180r851b3202],
7	Iceland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Iceland	prep_of	5	SENT_46	[p2l862t3180r951b3206],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l862t3180r951b3206],
9	101	CD	NUMBER	101	num	12	SENT_46	[p2l961t3181r996b3202],
10	Reykjavik	NNP	LOCATION	Reykjavik	nn	12	SENT_46	[p2l1009t3180r1124b3207],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1009t3180r1124b3207],
12	Iceland	NNP	LOCATION	Iceland	appos	1	SENT_46	[p2l1136t3180r1225b3202],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1136t3180r1225b3202],

1	23Therapeia	NN	O	23therapeium	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1235t3175r1383b3207],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1235t3175r1383b3207],
3	101	CD	NUMBER	101	num	6	SENT_47	[p2l1393t3181r1428b3202],
4	Reykjavik	NNP	LOCATION	Reykjavik	nn	6	SENT_47	[p2l1441t3180r1556b3207],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1441t3180r1556b3207],
6	Iceland	NNP	LOCATION	Iceland	appos	1	SENT_47	[p2l1568t3180r1657b3202],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1568t3180r1657b3202],

1	©	RB	O	©	amod	6	SENT_49	[p2l847t3307r932b3329],
2	2008	CD	DATE	2008	tmod	1	SENT_49	[p2l847t3307r932b3329],
3	Nature	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nature	nn	6	SENT_49	[p2l950t3307r1039b3329],
4	Publishing	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Publishing	nn	6	SENT_49	[p2l1046t3307r1192b3335],
5	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	nn	6	SENT_49	[p2l1199t3307r1285b3335],
6	NATURE	NNP	ORGANIZATION	NATURE	nsubj	7	SENT_49	[p2l6t3361r184b3395],
7	|	VBD	O	|	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l6t3361r184b3395],
8	Vol	NNP	O	Vol	nn	9	SENT_49	[p2l6t3361r184b3395],
9	452l3	NNP	O	452l3	dobj	7	SENT_49	[p2l196t3361r279b3395],
10	April	NNP	DATE	April	tmod	7	SENT_49	[p2l290t3364r353b3394],
11	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	10	SENT_49	[p2l366t3365r440b3389],

1	LETTERS	NNS	O	letter	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l6t3419r178b3449],

1	Table	NNP	O	Table	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l6t3527r85b3552],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	1	SENT_51	[p2l97t3528r108b3551],
3	I	PRP	O	I	dep	1	SENT_51	[p2l121t3524r123b3558],
4	Genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	5	SENT_51	[p2l135t3528r272b3557],
5	status	NN	O	status	dep	3	SENT_51	[p2l282t3529r370b3552],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l380t3527r431b3552],
7	SQ	NN	O	sq	nn	8	SENT_51	[p2l442t3528r482b3556],
8	level	NN	O	level	dep	3	SENT_51	[p2l494t3527r558b3552],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l569t3527r597b3552],
10	13,945	CD	NUMBER	13,945	num	12	SENT_51	[p2l606t3528r703b3556],
11	Icelandic	JJ	MISC	icelandic	amod	12	SENT_51	[p2l714t3527r837b3552],
12	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_of	5	SENT_51	[p2l848t3527r967b3552],
13	Parameter	NNP	O	Parameter	nn	14	SENT_51	[p2l6t3578r122b3598],
14	Genotype	NN	O	genotype	dep	22	SENT_51	[p2l818t3578r926b3602],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l935t3577r957b3597],
16	rsl05l730	NN	O	rsl05l730	nn	19	SENT_51	[p2l966t3578r1086b3598],
17	Total	JJ	O	total	amod	19	SENT_51	[p2l1458t3577r1515b3598],
18	n	NN	O	n	nn	19	SENT_51	[p2l1525t3584r1536b3597],
19	(	NN	O	(	prep_of	14	SENT_51	[p2l1546t3577r1678b3602],
20	frequency	NN	O	frequency	dep	22	SENT_51	[p2l1546t3577r1678b3602],
21	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	20	SENT_51	[p2l1546t3577r1678b3602],
22	Frequency	NN	O	frequency	dep	5	SENT_51	[p2l1841t3578r1956b3602],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1964t3577r1986b3598],
24	T	NN	O	t	nn	25	SENT_51	[p2l1994t3578r2009b3597],
25	allele	NN	O	allele	prep_of	22	SENT_51	[p2l2017t3577r2075b3597],

1	GG	NNS	O	gg	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l783t3640r817b3660],
2	GT	NN	O	gt	nn	3	SENT_52	[p2l1065t3640r1098b3660],
3	TT	NN	O	tt	dep	1	SENT_52	[p2l1346t3640r1377b3660],

1	Cigarettes	NNS	O	cigarette	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l6t36r137b64],
2	per	IN	O	per	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l148t43r188b64],
3	day	NN	DURATION	day	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l198t36r242b64],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l254t36r301b63],
5	SQ	NN	O	sq	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l254t36r301b63],
6	level	NN	O	level	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l314t36r381b61],
7	)	NN	O	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l314t36r381b61],
8	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l40t71r53b93],
9	to	TO	O	to	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l63t72r88b93],
10	10	CD	NUMBER	10	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l100t71r130b93],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l141t70r179b96],
12	o	NN	O	o	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l141t70r179b96],
13	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l141t70r179b96],
14	1,743	CD	NUMBER	1,743	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l652t71r721b97],
15	1,558	CD	NUMBER	1,558	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l932t71r1002b97],
16	326	CD	NUMBER	326	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1224t71r1271b94],
17	3,627	CD	NUMBER	3,627	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1482t71r1553b97],
18	(	NN	O	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1565t70r1660b96],
19	0.260	CD	NUMBER	0.260	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1565t70r1660b96],
20	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1565t70r1660b96],
21	0.305	CD	NUMBER	0.305	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1924t71r1995b93],
22	11	CD	NUMBER	11	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l40t106r70b128],
23	to	TO	O	to	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l80t107r105b128],
24	20	CD	NUMBER	20	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l115t106r146b128],
25	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l158t105r195b131],
26	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l158t105r195b131],
27	)	NN	O	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l158t105r195b131],
28	2,727	CD	NUMBER	2,727	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l651t106r722b132],
29	2,865	CD	NUMBER	2,865	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l931t106r1003b132],
30	810	CD	NUMBER	810	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1224t106r1272b128],
31	6,402	CD	NUMBER	6,402	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1482t106r1554b132],
32	(	NN	O	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1565t105r1660b131],
33	0.459	CD	NUMBER	0.459	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1565t105r1660b131],
34	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1565t105r1660b131],
35	0.350	CD	NUMBER	0.350	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1925t106r1996b128],
36	21	CD	NUMBER	21	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l39t141r70b163],
37	to	TO	O	to	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l80t142r105b163],
38	30	CD	NUMBER	30	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l115t141r146b163],
39	(	NN	O	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l158t140r196b166],
40	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l158t140r196b166],
41	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l158t140r196b166],
42	1,145	CD	NUMBER	1,145	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l652t141r722b167],
43	1,416	CD	NUMBER	1,416	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l933t141r1003b167],
44	427	CD	NUMBER	427	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1223t141r1271b163],
45	2,988	CD	NUMBER	2,988	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1482t141r1554b167],
46	(	NN	O	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1565t140r1660b166],
47	0,214	CD	NUMBER	0,214	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1565t140r1660b166],
48	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1565t140r1660b166],
49	0.380	CD	NUMBER	0.380	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1925t141r1996b163],
50	31	CD	NUMBER	31	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l39t176r70b198],
51	and	CC	O	and	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l81t175r125b198],
52	more	JJR	O	more	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l138t182r202b198],
53	(	NN	O	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l213t175r251b201],
54	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l213t175r251b201],
55	)	NN	O	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l213t175r251b201],
56	341 448 139 928	CD	NUMBER	341 448 139 928	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1494t176r1542b198],[p3l662t176r710b198],
57	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1554t175r1649b201],
58	0.067	CD	NUMBER	0.067	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1554t175r1649b201],
59	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1554t175r1649b201],
60	0.391	CD	NUMBER	0.391	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1925t176r1996b198],
61	All	DT	O	all	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l2007t175r2039b198],
62	levels	NNS	O	level	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l2052t175r2121b198],
63	(	VBP	O	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l6t210r155b239],
64	frequency	NN	O	frequency	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l6t210r155b239],
65	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l6t210r155b239],
66	/	:	O	/	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l470t211r541b238],
67	,956	CD	NUMBER	,956	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l470t211r541b238],
68	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l552t210r647b236],
69	0.427	CD	NUMBER	0.427	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l552t210r647b236],
70	)	NN	O	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l552t210r647b236],
71	6,287	CD	NUMBER	6,287	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l750t211r821b237],
72	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l833t210r928b236],
73	0.451	CD	NUMBER	0.451	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l833t210r928b236],
74	)	NN	O	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l833t210r928b236],
75	1,702	CD	NUMBER	1,702	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1032t211r1102b237],
76	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1114t210r1209b236],
77	0.122	CD	NUMBER	0.122	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1114t210r1209b236],
78	)	NN	O	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1114t210r1209b236],
79	13,945	CD	NUMBER	13,945	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1347t211r1434b237],
80	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1446t210r1541b236],
81	1.000	CD	NUMBER	1.000	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1446t210r1541b236],
82	)	NN	O	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1446t210r1541b236],
83	0.347	CD	NUMBER	0.347	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1797t211r1868b234],
84	Mean	NN	O	mean	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1878t211r1949b234],
85	SQ	NN	O	sq	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1961t211r1996b238],
86	level	NN	O	level	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l2009t211r2063b234],
87	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l6t245r86b271],
88	mean	NN	O	mean	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l6t245r86b271],
89	i	FW	O	i	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l97t248r116b267],
90	s.d.	FW	O	s.d.	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l126t245r179b271],
91	)	FW	O	)	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l126t245r179b271],
92	1.01	CD	NUMBER	1.01	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l413t246r466b268],
93	i	FW	O	i	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l476t248r495b267],
94	0.85	CD	NUMBER	0.85	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l505t246r560b268],
95	1.12	CD	NUMBER	1.12	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l693t246r747b268],
96	i	FW	O	i	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l757t248r776b267],
97	0.86	CD	NUMBER	0.86	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l786t246r841b268],
98	1.22	CD	NUMBER	1.22	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l974t246r1027b268],
99	i	FW	O	i	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1037t248r1056b267],
100	0.85	CD	NUMBER	0.85	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1066t246r1121b268],
101	1.09	CD	NUMBER	1.09	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1298t246r1351b268],
102	i	FW	O	i	dep	103	SENT_53	[p3l1361t248r1380b267],
103	0.86	CD	NUMBER	0.86	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1390t246r1445b268],

1	frequency	NN	O	frequency	nsubj	4	SENT_54	[p3l8t418r316b493],
2	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l344t418r599b475],
3	levels	NNS	O	level	prep_between	1	SENT_54	[p3l632t418r796b475],
4	varies	VBZ	O	vary	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l828t420r1023b484],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l828t420r1023b484],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1059t418r1174b475],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_54	[p3l1207t418r1303b475],
8	largest	JJS	O	largest	amod	9	SENT_54	[p3l1335t418r1536b493],
9	increase	NN	O	increase	nsubj	20	SENT_54	[p3l1569t420r1816b475],
10	(	CD	PERCENT	(	num	12	SENT_54	[p3l1854t418r2059b487],
11	4.5	CD	PERCENT	4.5	num	12	SENT_54	[p3l1854t418r2059b487],
12	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nsubjpass	15	SENT_54	[p3l1854t418r2059b487],
13	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	12	SENT_54	[p3l1854t418r2059b487],
14	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	15	SENT_54	[p3l2099t420r2143b475],
15	observed	VBN	O	observe	rcmod	9	SENT_54	[p3l8t507r283b564],
16	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l311t507r567b564],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_54	[p3l597t507r693b564],
18	lowest	JJS	O	lowest	amod	19	SENT_54	[p3l722t507r918b564],
19	levels	NNS	O	level	prep_between	15	SENT_54	[p3l947t507r1111b564],
20	(	VBP	O	(	conj_and	4	SENT_54	[p3l1146t507r1204b576],
21	o	NN	O	o	dobj	20	SENT_54	[p3l1146t507r1204b576],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1237t507r1351b564],
23	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	24	SENT_54	[p3l1388t507r1462b576],
24	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	21	SENT_54	[p3l1388t507r1462b576],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1388t507r1462b576],
26	whereas	IN	O	whereas	mark	33	SENT_54	[p3l1492t507r1740b564],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_54	[p3l1770t507r1866b564],
28	increase	NN	O	increase	nsubj	33	SENT_54	[p3l1897t509r2144b564],
29	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l6t596r262b652],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_54	[p3l283t596r380b652],
31	highest	JJS	O	highest	amod	32	SENT_54	[p3l402t596r624b670],
32	levels	NNS	O	level	prep_between	28	SENT_54	[p3l646t596r810b652],
33	(	VBP	O	(	advcl	20	SENT_54	[p3l838t596r895b664],
34	2	CD	NUMBER	2	nsubj	41	SENT_54	[p3l838t596r895b664],
35	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l921t596r1035b652],
36	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	37	SENT_54	[p3l1060t596r1117b664],
37	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	34	SENT_54	[p3l1060t596r1117b664],
38	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	41	SENT_54	[p3l1145t598r1190b652],
39	only	RB	O	only	quantmod	40	SENT_54	[p3l1215t596r1351b670],
40	1.1	CD	PERCENT	1.1	num	41	SENT_54	[p3l1378t601r1543b654],
41	%	NN	PERCENT	%	ccomp	33	SENT_54	[p3l1378t601r1543b654],
42	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1378t601r1543b654],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1569t600r1635b652],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_55	[p3l1657t596r1753b652],
3	context	NN	O	context	prep_in	25	SENT_55	[p3l1777t607r2007b652],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l2030t596r2098b653],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_55	[p3l2114t616r2145b652],
6	case	NN	O	case	prep_of	3	SENT_55	[p3l9t685r388b741],
7	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	10	SENT_55	[p3l9t685r388b741],
8	control	NN	O	control	nn	10	SENT_55	[p3l9t685r388b741],
9	LC	NN	O	lc	nn	10	SENT_55	[p3l419t688r509b742],
10	study	NN	O	study	dep	6	SENT_55	[p3l541t685r724b759],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l541t685r724b759],
12	an	DT	O	a	det	15	SENT_55	[p3l759t705r831b741],
13	additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	15	SENT_55	[p3l864t685r1179b741],
14	523	CD	NUMBER	523	num	15	SENT_55	[p3l1213t690r1318b741],
15	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	nsubjpass	25	SENT_55	[p3l1352t684r1607b741],
16	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1639t684r1792b741],
17	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	prep_from	15	SENT_55	[p3l1825t687r1997b758],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l2030t685r2144b741],
19	1,375	CD	NUMBER	1,375	num	20	SENT_55	[p3l14t780r170b840],
20	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	nsubjpass	25	SENT_55	[p3l192t774r446b831],
21	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l466t774r618b831],
22	The	DT	LOCATION	the	det	23	SENT_55	[p3l637t774r756b831],
23	Netherlands	NNPS	LOCATION	Netherlands	prep_from	20	SENT_55	[p3l774t774r1152b831],
24	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	25	SENT_55	[p3l1169t795r1314b831],
25	genotyped	VBN	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1334t774r1671b849],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1334t774r1671b849],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_56	[p3l1690t779r1797b831],
2	performed	VBD	O	perform	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1814t774r2145b848],
3	multiple	JJ	O	multiple	amod	5	SENT_56	[p3l8t863r269b937],
4	regression	NN	O	regression	nn	5	SENT_56	[p3l304t865r617b938],
5	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	dobj	2	SENT_56	[p3l653t863r900b938],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l938t863r1006b920],
7	SQ	NN	O	sq	nn	8	SENT_56	[p3l1034t867r1125b931],
8	data	NNS	O	datum	prep_of	5	SENT_56	[p3l1162t863r1292b920],
9	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1327t863r1480b920],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_56	[p3l1515t863r1611b920],
11	three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	12	SENT_56	[p3l1645t863r1802b920],
12	countries	NNS	O	country	prep_from	2	SENT_56	[p3l1838t865r2142b929],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1838t865r2142b929],
14	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l6t952r145b1009],
15	adjustment	NN	O	adjustment	prep_with	2	SENT_56	[p3l178t952r527b1027],
16	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l559t952r649b1009],
17	sex	NN	O	sex	prep_for	15	SENT_56	[p3l681t973r776b1009],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l808t952r922b1009],
19	year	NN	DURATION	year	prep_for	15	SENT_56	[p3l952t973r1083b1027],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1115t952r1184b1009],
21	birth	NN	O	birth	nn	23	SENT_56	[p3l1206t952r1360b1009],
22	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	23	SENT_56	[p3l1396t952r1591b1021],
23	Table	NNP	O	Table	prep_of	17	SENT_56	[p3l1396t952r1591b1021],
24	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	25	SENT_56	[p3l1624t952r1703b1021],
25	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	23	SENT_56	[p3l1624t952r1703b1021],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1624t952r1703b1021],

1	Results	NNS	O	result	nsubj	8	SENT_57	[p3l1739t952r1957b1009],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1991t952r2144b1009],
3	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	prep_from	1	SENT_57	[p3l9t1043r181b1115],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l207t1041r321b1098],
5	The	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_57	[p3l345t1041r464b1098],
6	Netherlands	NNP	LOCATION	Netherlands	nsubj	8	SENT_57	[p3l488t1041r867b1098],
7	combined	VBN	O	combine	partmod	6	SENT_57	[p3l893t1041r1204b1098],
8	gave	VBD	O	give	dep	45	SENT_57	[p3l1229t1061r1364b1116],
9	an	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_57	[p3l1389t1061r1463b1098],
10	estimated	JJ	O	estimated	amod	11	SENT_57	[p3l1488t1041r1786b1098],
11	increase	NN	O	increase	nsubj	16	SENT_57	[p3l1811t1043r2058b1098],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l2084t1041r2153b1098],
13	0.074	CD	NUMBER	0.074	num	15	SENT_57	[p3l8t1135r172b1186],
14	SQ	NN	O	sq	nn	15	SENT_57	[p3l196t1133r287b1198],
15	units	NNS	O	unit	prep_of	11	SENT_57	[p3l311t1132r464b1186],
16	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	8	SENT_57	[p3l491t1130r561b1198],
17	P	NN	O	p	dobj	16	SENT_57	[p3l491t1130r561b1198],
18	=	JJ	O	=	advmod	16	SENT_57	[p3l579t1151r626b1169],
19	0.012	CD	NUMBER	0.012	num	20	SENT_57	[p3l651t1130r839b1198],
20	)	NN	O	)	dep	18	SENT_57	[p3l651t1130r839b1198],
21	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l866t1130r956b1186],
22	each	DT	O	each	det	23	SENT_57	[p3l978t1130r1116b1186],
23	copy	NN	O	copy	prep_for	18	SENT_57	[p3l1138t1150r1286b1204],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1307t1130r1375b1186],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_57	[p3l1388t1130r1484b1186],
26	variant	NN	O	variant	prep_of	23	SENT_57	[p3l1504t1132r1739b1195],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1504t1132r1739b1195],
28	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	34	SENT_57	[p3l1762t1130r1950b1186],
29	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	34	SENT_57	[p3l1972t1132r2017b1186],
30	not	RB	O	not	neg	34	SENT_57	[p3l2040t1141r2145b1186],
31	signiﬁcantly	RB	O	signiﬁcantly	advmod	32	SENT_57	[p3l8t1218r386b1293],
32	different	JJ	O	different	amod	34	SENT_57	[p3l405t1218r669b1275],
33	(	NN	O	(	nn	34	SENT_57	[p3l695t1219r765b1287],
34	P	NN	O	p	rcmod	26	SENT_57	[p3l695t1219r765b1287],
35	=	JJ	O	=	advmod	34	SENT_57	[p3l783t1240r830b1258],
36	0.45	CD	NUMBER	0.45	num	37	SENT_57	[p3l855t1219r1006b1287],
37	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	35	SENT_57	[p3l855t1219r1006b1287],
38	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1033t1218r1186b1275],
39	the	DT	O	the	det	40	SENT_57	[p3l1208t1219r1304b1275],
40	estimate	NN	O	estimate	prep_from	34	SENT_57	[p3l1326t1221r1583b1275],
41	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1605t1218r1674b1275],
42	0.098	CD	NUMBER	0.098	num	44	SENT_57	[p3l1688t1224r1850b1275],
43	SQ	NN	O	sq	nn	44	SENT_57	[p3l1875t1222r1967b1287],
44	units	NNS	O	unit	prep_of	40	SENT_57	[p3l1990t1221r2144b1275],
45	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l12t1309r83b1378],
46	P	NN	O	p	nsubj	47	SENT_57	[p3l12t1309r83b1378],
47	=	JJ	O	=	xcomp	45	SENT_57	[p3l100t1330r147b1348],
48	10-18	CD	NUMBER	10-18	num	49	SENT_57	[p3l178t1296r371b1378],
49	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	45	SENT_57	[p3l178t1296r371b1378],
50	based	VBN	O	base	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l398t1308r573b1366],
51	on	IN	O	on	prepc_based_on	49	SENT_57	[p3l597t1329r676b1366],
52	the	DT	O	the	det	54	SENT_57	[p3l699t1309r796b1366],
53	Icelandic	JJ	MISC	icelandic	amod	54	SENT_57	[p3l820t1308r1098b1366],
54	data	NNS	O	datum	pobj	49	SENT_57	[p3l1121t1309r1267b1366],
55	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1121t1309r1267b1366],

1	Combining	VBG	O	combine	partmod	11	SENT_58	[p3l1295t1309r1649b1384],
2	all	DT	O	all	det	3	SENT_58	[p3l1673t1308r1743b1366],
3	results	NNS	O	result	dobj	1	SENT_58	[p3l1766t1309r1981b1375],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1766t1309r1981b1375],
5	each	DT	O	each	det	6	SENT_58	[p3l2007t1308r2144b1366],
6	copy	NN	O	copy	nsubjpass	11	SENT_58	[p3l8t1418r157b1473],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l178t1398r247b1455],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_58	[p3l260t1398r356b1455],
9	variant	NN	O	variant	prep_of	6	SENT_58	[p3l377t1400r597b1455],
10	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_58	[p3l617t1419r730b1455],
11	estimated	VBN	O	estimate	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l754t1398r1052b1455],
12	to	TO	O	to	aux	13	SENT_58	[p3l1075t1409r1136b1455],
13	increase	VB	O	increase	xcomp	11	SENT_58	[p3l1161t1400r1408b1455],
14	SQ	NN	O	sq	nn	15	SENT_58	[p3l1432t1402r1524b1466],
15	level	NN	O	level	iobj	13	SENT_58	[p3l1546t1398r1684b1455],
16	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1705t1398r1782b1473],
17	0.095	CD	NUMBER	0.095	num	18	SENT_58	[p3l1802t1404r1964b1455],
18	units	NNS	O	unit	prep_by	15	SENT_58	[p3l1990t1400r2143b1455],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_58	[p3l12t1487r83b1556],
20	P	NN	O	p	npadvmod	21	SENT_58	[p3l12t1487r83b1556],
21	=	JJ	O	=	amod	18	SENT_58	[p3l100t1509r147b1527],
22	6	CD	NUMBER	6	num	23	SENT_58	[p3l172t1492r204b1545],
23	X	NN	O	x	dobj	13	SENT_58	[p3l231t1507r265b1542],
24	10-20	CD	NUMBER	10-20	num	25	SENT_58	[p3l294t1475r510b1556],
25	)	NN	O	)	tmod	13	SENT_58	[p3l294t1475r510b1556],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l294t1475r510b1556],
27	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	28	SENT_58	[p3l529t1487r718b1545],
28	corresponds	VBZ	O	correspond	rcmod	25	SENT_58	[p3l739t1487r1117b1562],
29	to	TO	O	to	aux	30	SENT_58	[p3l1136t1499r1198b1545],
30	about	IN	O	about	xcomp	28	SENT_58	[p3l1220t1487r1398b1545],
31	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	32	SENT_58	[p3l1418t1508r1530b1545],
32	cigarette	NN	O	cigarette	xcomp	30	SENT_58	[p3l1550t1489r1812b1563],
33	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1831t1508r1932b1562],
34	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	32	SENT_58	[p3l1951t1487r2073b1563],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1951t1487r2073b1563],
