1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_1	[p1l491t186r596b247],
2	NEW	NNP	O	NEW	nn	3	SENT_1	[p1l643t173r952b249],
3	ENGLAND	NNP	LOCATION	ENGLAND	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l999t172r1657b249],

1	JOURNAL	NN	O	journal	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l331t297r948b400],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l997t304r1077b392],
3	MEDICINE	NNP	O	MEDICINE	prep_of	1	SENT_2	[p1l1113t297r1816b374],

1	ESTABLISHED	VBN	O	establish	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l355t487r568b505],
2	IN	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l582t487r618b505],
3	1812	CD	DATE	1812	prep_in	1	SENT_3	[p1l633t487r703b505],

1	JULY	NN	DATE	july	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l936t481r1034b513],
2	14	CD	DATE	14	num	1	SENT_4	[p1l1048t480r1104b510],
3	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1048t480r1104b510],
4	2005	CD	DATE	2005	appos	1	SENT_4	[p1l1119t481r1215b506],

1	VOL	NNP	O	VOL	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1549t487r1617b505],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1549t487r1617b505],

1	353	CD	NUMBER	353	num	2	SENT_6	[p1l1627t487r1679b506],
2	NO.	NN	O	no.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1720t487r1775b505],
3	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	2	SENT_6	[p1l1786t487r1800b504],

1	Erlotinib	NNP	O	Erlotinib	nsubj	4	SENT_7	[p1l196t595r455b650],
2	in	IN	O	in	prep	1	SENT_7	[p1l473t596r530b649],
3	Previously	RB	DATE	previously	pcomp	2	SENT_7	[p1l546t595r848b665],
4	Treated	VBN	O	treat	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l860t595r1081b650],
5	N	NN	O	n	dobj	4	SENT_7	[p1l1097t600r1149b650],
6	on	IN	O	on	prep	4	SENT_7	[p1l1152t595r1573b650],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1152t595r1573b650],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1152t595r1573b650],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1152t595r1573b650],

1	Small-Cell	JJ	O	small-cell	amod	3	SENT_9	[p1l1152t595r1573b650],
2	Lung	NN	O	lung	nn	3	SENT_9	[p1l1589t600r1742b665],
3	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1757t599r1964b650],

1	Frances	NNP	PERSON	Frances	nn	3	SENT_10	[p1l215t732r340b760],
2	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	3	SENT_10	[p1l353t731r385b760],
3	Shepherd	NNP	PERSON	Shepherd	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l400t729r570b769],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l400t729r570b769],
5	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l587t732r762b769],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l587t732r762b769],
7	José	NNP	PERSON	José	nn	9	SENT_10	[p1l587t732r762b769],
8	Rodrigues	NNP	PERSON	Rodrigues	nn	9	SENT_10	[p1l777t729r945b770],
9	Pereira	NNP	PERSON	Pereira	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l962t732r1085b766],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l962t732r1085b766],
11	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l1103t732r1193b766],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1103t732r1193b766],
13	Tudor	NNP	PERSON	Tudor	nn	14	SENT_10	[p1l1206t729r1305b760],
14	Ciuleanu	NNP	PERSON	Ciuleanu	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l1317t729r1475b766],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1317t729r1475b766],
16	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l1492t732r1582b766],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1492t732r1582b766],
18	Eng	NNP	PERSON	Eng	nn	20	SENT_10	[p1l1599t732r1661b770],
19	Huat	NNP	PERSON	Huat	nn	20	SENT_10	[p1l1675t732r1758b760],
20	Tan	NNP	PERSON	Tan	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l1768t732r1836b766],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1768t732r1836b766],
22	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l1854t732r1944b766],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1854t732r1944b766],
24	Vera	NNP	PERSON	Vera	nn	25	SENT_10	[p1l208t781r281b809],
25	Hirsh	NNP	PERSON	Hirsh	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l297t778r398b815],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l297t778r398b815],
27	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l415t781r505b815],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l415t781r505b815],
29	Sumitra	NNP	PERSON	Sumitra	nn	30	SENT_10	[p1l520t780r653b809],
30	Thongprasert	NNP	PERSON	Thongprasert	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l665t778r904b819],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l665t778r904b819],
32	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l922t781r1012b815],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l922t781r1012b815],
34	Daniel	NNP	PERSON	Daniel	nn	35	SENT_10	[p1l1029t778r1130b809],
35	Campos	NNP	PERSON	Campos	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l1143t780r1288b818],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1143t780r1288b818],
37	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l1304t781r1393b815],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1304t781r1393b815],
39	Savitree	NNP	PERSON	Savitree	nn	40	SENT_10	[p1l1407t780r1537b809],
40	Maoleekoonpiroj	NNP	PERSON	Maoleekoonpiroj	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l1552t778r1842b819],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1552t778r1842b819],
42	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l1858t781r1946b815],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1858t781r1946b815],
44	Michael	NNP	PERSON	Michael	nn	45	SENT_10	[p1l200t827r325b858],
45	Smylie	NNP	PERSON	Smylie	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l339t827r454b868],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l339t827r454b868],
47	M.B.	NNP	LOCATION	M.B.	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l469t830r552b864],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l469t830r552b864],
49	Ch	NNP	O	Ch	appos	3	SENT_10	[p1l565t827r660b864],
50	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l565t827r660b864],

1	B.	NNP	O	B.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l565t827r660b864],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l565t827r660b864],
3	Renato	NNP	PERSON	Renato	nn	4	SENT_11	[p1l675t830r791b858],
4	Martins	NNP	PERSON	Martins	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l807t830r945b864],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l807t830r945b864],
6	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l962t830r1052b864],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l962t830r1052b864],
8	Maximiliano	NNP	PERSON	Maximiliano	nn	10	SENT_11	[p1l1069t827r1277b858],
9	van	NNP	PERSON	van	nn	10	SENT_11	[p1l1289t838r1346b858],
10	Kooten	NNP	PERSON	Kooten	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l1364t830r1490b864],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1364t830r1490b864],
12	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l1507t830r1597b864],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1507t830r1597b864],
14	Mircea	NNP	PERSON	Mircea	nn	15	SENT_11	[p1l1615t830r1727b858],
15	Dediu	NNP	PERSON	Dediu	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l1743t827r1851b864],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1743t827r1851b864],
17	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l1868t830r1958b864],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1868t830r1958b864],
19	Brian	NNP	PERSON	Brian	nn	20	SENT_11	[p1l220t879r304b907],
20	Findlay	NNP	PERSON	Findlay	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l322t876r445b917],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l322t876r445b917],
22	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l462t879r553b913],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l462t879r553b913],
24	Dongsheng	NNP	PERSON	Dongsheng	nn	25	SENT_11	[p1l570t876r765b917],
25	Tu	NNP	PERSON	Tu	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l775t879r823b913],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l775t879r823b913],
27	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l840t876r940b913],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l840t876r940b913],
29	Diannejohnston	NNP	PERSON	Diannejohnston	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l957t876r1250b916],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l957t876r1250b916],
31	Andrea	NNP	PERSON	Andrea	nn	32	SENT_11	[p1l1264t876r1384b907],
32	Bezjak	NNP	PERSON	Bezjak	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l1401t876r1516b917],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1401t876r1516b917],
34	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l1533t879r1623b913],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1533t879r1623b913],
36	Gary	NNP	PERSON	Gary	nn	39	SENT_11	[p1l1638t878r1716b917],
37	Clark	NNP	PERSON	Clark	nn	39	SENT_11	[p1l1728t876r1822b913],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1728t876r1822b913],
39	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	1	SENT_11	[p1l1839t876r1938b913],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1839t876r1938b913],

1	Pedro	NNP	PERSON	Pedro	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l504t925r599b956],
2	Santabarbara	NNP	PERSON	Santabarbara	nn	6	SENT_12	[p1l613t925r847b962],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l613t925r847b962],
4	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	6	SENT_12	[p1l865t928r955b962],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l865t928r955b962],
6	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	dep	1	SENT_12	[p1l972t925r1071b962],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l972t925r1071b962],
8	and	CC	O	and	prep	6	SENT_12	[p1l1086t925r1146b956],
9	Lesley	NNP	PERSON	Lesley	nn	14	SENT_12	[p1l1163t925r1263b966],
10	Seymour	NNP	PERSON	Seymour	nn	14	SENT_12	[p1l1276t927r1430b966],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1276t927r1430b966],
12	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	14	SENT_12	[p1l1447t928r1538b962],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1447t928r1538b962],
14	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	dep	8	SENT_12	[p1l1555t925r1654b962],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1555t925r1654b962],
16	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l522t974r569b1005],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_12	[p1l579t974r632b1005],
18	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	21	SENT_12	[p1l647t974r789b1005],
19	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	21	SENT_12	[p1l804t977r920b1005],
20	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	nn	21	SENT_12	[p1l935t977r1074b1006],
21	ofCanada	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ofCanada	prep_for	14	SENT_12	[p1l1087t974r1255b1005],
22	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	prep	14	SENT_12	[p1l1269t974r1390b1005],
23	Trials	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Trials	nn	24	SENT_12	[p1l1404t974r1492b1005],
24	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	dep	22	SENT_12	[p1l1506t977r1635b1015],
25	"	``	O	"	punct	14	SENT_12	[p1l1506t977r1635b1015],
26	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1506t977r1635b1015],
27	~	FW	O	~	nn	28	SENT_12	[p1l1506t977r1635b1015],
28	‘	FW	O	‘	amod	6	SENT_12	[p1l1506t977r1635b1015],

1	ABSTRACT	NN	O	abstract	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l967t1116r1185b1139],

1	BACKG	NNP	O	BACKG	nsubj	5	SENT_14	[p1l93t1239r196b1259],
2	no	DT	O	no	det	4	SENT_14	[p1l204t1239r244b1259],
3	u	NN	O	u	nn	4	SENT_14	[p1l251t1239r268b1259],
4	N	NN	O	n	dep	1	SENT_14	[p1l277t1239r294b1259],
5	D	NN	O	d	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l303t1239r321b1259],
6	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	7	SENT_14	[p1l90t1276r143b1304],
7	conducted	VBD	O	conduct	ccomp	5	SENT_14	[p1l158t1273r333b1304],
8	a	DT	O	a	dobj	7	SENT_14	[p1l348t1283r365b1304],
9	randomized	VBN	O	randomize	partmod	8	SENT_14	[p1l379t1273r593b1310],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l379t1273r593b1310],
11	placebo	NN	O	placebo	nn	12	SENT_14	[p1l609t1273r939b1312],
12	—	NN	O	—	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l609t1273r939b1312],
13	controlled	VBN	O	control	partmod	12	SENT_14	[p1l609t1273r939b1312],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l609t1273r939b1312],
15	double-blind	JJ	O	double-blind	amod	16	SENT_14	[p1l956t1273r1175b1304],
16	trial	NN	O	trial	dobj	13	SENT_14	[p1l1190t1273r1257b1304],
17	to	TO	O	to	aux	18	SENT_14	[p1l1272t1279r1303b1304],
18	determine	VB	O	determine	infmod	16	SENT_14	[p1l1319t1273r1490b1304],
19	whether	IN	O	whether	complm	27	SENT_14	[p1l90t1323r229b1354],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_14	[p1l237t1323r288b1353],
21	epidermal	JJ	O	epidermal	amod	26	SENT_14	[p1l298t1323r466b1362],
22	growth	NN	O	growth	nn	26	SENT_14	[p1l475t1323r595b1362],
23	factor	NN	O	factor	nn	26	SENT_14	[p1l604t1323r702b1353],
24	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nn	26	SENT_14	[p1l710t1329r850b1362],
25	inhibitor	NN	O	inhibitor	nn	26	SENT_14	[p1l857t1323r1007b1354],
26	erlotinib	NN	O	erlotinib	nsubj	27	SENT_14	[p1l1015t1323r1157b1353],
27	prolongs	VBZ	O	prolong	ccomp	18	SENT_14	[p1l1167t1323r1317b1362],
28	survival	NN	O	survival	dobj	27	SENT_14	[p1l1328t1323r1451b1354],
29	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1459t1323r1491b1353],
30	non	JJ	O	non	amod	36	SENT_14	[p1l92t1373r337b1404],
31	—	JJ	O	—	amod	36	SENT_14	[p1l92t1373r337b1404],
32	small	JJ	O	small	amod	36	SENT_14	[p1l92t1373r337b1404],
33	—	NN	O	—	nn	36	SENT_14	[p1l92t1373r337b1404],
34	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	36	SENT_14	[p1l92t1373r337b1404],
35	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	36	SENT_14	[p1l346t1373r421b1412],
36	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_in	28	SENT_14	[p1l430t1383r536b1403],
37	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l545t1373r620b1403],
38	the	DT	O	the	det	39	SENT_14	[p1l628t1373r679b1403],
39	failure	NN	O	failure	prep_after	27	SENT_14	[p1l688t1373r793b1404],
40	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l803t1373r842b1403],
41	ﬁrst-line	NN	O	ﬁrst-line	nn	44	SENT_14	[p1l844t1373r984b1403],
42	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l994t1383r1029b1404],
43	second-line	JJ	O	second-line	conj_or	41	SENT_14	[p1l1038t1373r1228b1403],
44	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_of	39	SENT_14	[p1l1237t1373r1478b1412],
45	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1237t1373r1478b1412],

1	M	NN	O	m	dep	7	SENT_15	[p1l95t1479r115b1498],
2	ET	NNP	O	ET	nn	3	SENT_15	[p1l124t1479r157b1498],
3	H	NNP	O	H	dep	1	SENT_15	[p1l163t1479r181b1498],
4	o	NN	O	o	nn	5	SENT_15	[p1l189t1478r210b1498],
5	D	NN	O	d	dep	7	SENT_15	[p1l216t1479r234b1498],
6	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	7	SENT_15	[p1l239t1478r254b1498],
7	Patients	NNS	O	patient	dep	30	SENT_15	[p1l91t1519r222b1549],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l235t1519r310b1550],
9	stage	NN	O	stage	nn	10	SENT_15	[p1l324t1525r410b1558],
10	IIIB	NN	O	iiib	prep_with	7	SENT_15	[p1l423t1521r484b1549],
11	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l499t1528r534b1549],
12	IV	CD	NUMBER	iv	num	17	SENT_15	[p1l545t1521r582b1549],
13	non	JJ	O	non	amod	17	SENT_15	[p1l594t1518r845b1549],
14	—	JJ	O	—	amod	17	SENT_15	[p1l594t1518r845b1549],
15	small	JJ	O	small	amod	17	SENT_15	[p1l594t1518r845b1549],
16	—	NN	O	—	nn	17	SENT_15	[p1l594t1518r845b1549],
17	cell	NN	O	cell	prep_with	7	SENT_15	[p1l594t1518r845b1549],
18	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	19	SENT_15	[p1l857t1518r934b1558],
19	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nsubj	30	SENT_15	[p1l946t1529r1062b1556],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l946t1529r1062b1556],
21	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1076t1519r1150b1549],
22	performance	NN	O	performance	nn	23	SENT_15	[p1l1163t1518r1378b1558],
23	status	NN	O	status	prep_with	19	SENT_15	[p1l1392t1525r1490b1549],
24	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l92t1568r173b1599],
25	o	NN	O	o	prep_from	23	SENT_15	[p1l183t1571r201b1599],
26	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l211t1575r242b1599],
27	3	CD	NUMBER	3	prep_to	25	SENT_15	[p1l252t1571r279b1606],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l252t1571r279b1606],
29	were	VBD	O	be	cop	30	SENT_15	[p1l288t1579r366b1600],
30	eligible	JJ	O	eligible	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l375t1569r494b1608],
31	if	IN	O	if	mark	34	SENT_15	[p1l502t1568r531b1599],
32	they	PRP	O	they	nsubj	34	SENT_15	[p1l533t1569r601b1608],
33	had	VBD	O	have	aux	34	SENT_15	[p1l608t1569r668b1599],
34	received	VBN	O	receive	advcl	30	SENT_15	[p1l676t1569r809b1600],
35	one	CD	NUMBER	one	nn	40	SENT_15	[p1l817t1579r877b1599],
36	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l885t1579r920b1599],
37	two	CD	NUMBER	two	conj_or	35	SENT_15	[p1l927t1575r986b1600],
38	prior	JJ	O	prior	amod	40	SENT_15	[p1l995t1569r1077b1608],
39	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nn	40	SENT_15	[p1l1084t1569r1320b1608],
40	regimens	NNS	O	regimen	dobj	34	SENT_15	[p1l1326t1569r1489b1608],
41	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1326t1569r1489b1608],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_16	[p1l90t1618r153b1649],
2	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubjpass	4	SENT_16	[p1l162t1619r292b1658],
3	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_16	[p1l301t1629r379b1649],
4	stratified	VBN	O	stratify	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l389t1618r534b1649],
5	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l543t1618r707b1658],
6	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	4	SENT_16	[p1l715t1625r746b1649],
7	center	NN	O	center	pobj	4	SENT_16	[p1l756t1625r864b1656],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l756t1625r864b1656],
9	performance	NN	O	performance	nn	10	SENT_16	[p1l875t1618r1086b1658],
10	status	NN	O	status	conj_and	7	SENT_16	[p1l1096t1625r1201b1656],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1096t1625r1201b1656],
12	response	NN	O	response	conj_and	7	SENT_16	[p1l1212t1628r1360b1658],
13	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1369t1625r1400b1649],
14	prior	JJ	O	prior	amod	15	SENT_16	[p1l1409t1619r1492b1658],
15	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_to	12	SENT_16	[p1l92t1669r332b1708],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l92t1669r332b1708],
17	number	NN	O	number	conj_and	7	SENT_16	[p1l343t1669r474b1700],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l482t1668r521b1699],
19	prior	JJ	O	prior	amod	20	SENT_16	[p1l523t1669r605b1708],
20	regimens	NNS	O	regimen	prep_of	17	SENT_16	[p1l613t1669r775b1708],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l613t1669r775b1708],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l787t1669r847b1699],
23	prior	RB	O	prior	advmod	25	SENT_16	[p1l856t1669r938b1708],
24	platinum-based	JJ	O	platinum-based	amod	25	SENT_16	[p1l946t1669r1205b1708],
25	therapy	NN	O	therapy	conj_and	7	SENT_16	[p1l1214t1669r1337b1708],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1344t1669r1405b1699],
27	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	29	SENT_16	[p1l1412t1679r1491b1700],
28	randomly	RB	O	randomly	advmod	29	SENT_16	[p1l92t1719r255b1758],
29	assigned	VBN	O	assign	conj_and	4	SENT_16	[p1l264t1719r413b1758],
30	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l424t1719r456b1749],
31	a	DT	O	a	det	33	SENT_16	[p1l467t1729r485b1749],
32	2:1	CD	NUMBER	2:1	num	33	SENT_16	[p1l496t1721r547b1749],
33	ratio	NN	O	ratio	prep_in	29	SENT_16	[p1l559t1719r636b1749],
34	to	TO	O	to	aux	35	SENT_16	[p1l648t1725r680b1749],
35	receive	VB	O	receive	xcomp	29	SENT_16	[p1l692t1719r806b1750],
36	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	37	SENT_16	[p1l818t1719r883b1749],
37	erlotinib	NN	O	erlotinib	dobj	35	SENT_16	[p1l895t1719r1049b1756],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l895t1719r1049b1756],
39	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1062t1725r1094b1749],
40	a	DT	O	a	det	41	SENT_16	[p1l1103t1729r1121b1749],
41	dose	NN	O	dose	prep_at	29	SENT_16	[p1l1132t1719r1209b1749],
42	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1221t1718r1260b1749],
43	150	CD	NUMBER	150	num	44	SENT_16	[p1l1266t1721r1326b1749],
44	mg	NN	O	mg	prep_of	41	SENT_16	[p1l1337t1729r1393b1758],
45	daily	RB	SET	daily	advmod	44	SENT_16	[p1l1403t1719r1488b1758],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1403t1719r1488b1758],
47	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l92t1779r127b1800],
48	placebo	NN	O	placebo	conj_or	44	SENT_16	[p1l136t1769r276b1808],
49	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l136t1769r276b1808],

1	R	NN	O	r	nn	3	SENT_17	[p1l94t1874r108b1893],
2	E	NN	O	e	nn	3	SENT_17	[p1l115t1874r128b1893],
3	S	NN	O	s	nsubj	18	SENT_17	[p1l133t1874r147b1893],
4	U	NNP	O	U	nn	8	SENT_17	[p1l154t1874r171b1893],
5	LTS	NNP	O	LTS	nn	8	SENT_17	[p1l179t1874r228b1893],
6	The	NNP	O	The	nn	8	SENT_17	[p1l90t1913r154b1944],
7	median	JJ	O	median	amod	8	SENT_17	[p1l166t1913r291b1944],
8	age	NN	O	age	dep	3	SENT_17	[p1l303t1923r359b1952],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l372t1913r412b1944],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_17	[p1l417t1913r468b1943],
11	731	CD	NUMBER	731	num	12	SENT_17	[p1l481t1915r541b1944],
12	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_of	3	SENT_17	[p1l553t1913r686b1952],
13	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	14	SENT_17	[p1l697t1913r769b1944],
14	underwent	VBD	O	undergo	rcmod	12	SENT_17	[p1l782t1913r964b1944],
15	randomization	NN	O	randomization	dobj	14	SENT_17	[p1l974t1913r1223b1944],
16	was	VBD	O	be	cop	18	SENT_17	[p1l1233t1923r1297b1944],
17	61.4	CD	DURATION	61.4	num	18	SENT_17	[p1l1310t1915r1382b1944],
18	years	NNS	NUMBER	year	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1393t1923r1489b1952],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1393t1923r1489b1952],
20	49	CD	PERCENT	49	num	21	SENT_17	[p1l91t1965r131b1994],
21	percent	NN	PERCENT	percent	nsubj	23	SENT_17	[p1l143t1969r270b2002],
22	had	VBD	O	have	aux	23	SENT_17	[p1l281t1963r342b1994],
23	received	VBN	O	receive	parataxis	18	SENT_17	[p1l355t1963r491b1994],
24	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	27	SENT_17	[p1l504t1970r564b1994],
25	prior	JJ	O	prior	amod	27	SENT_17	[p1l577t1964r661b2002],
26	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nn	27	SENT_17	[p1l674t1963r914b2002],
27	regimens	NNS	O	regimen	dobj	23	SENT_17	[p1l925t1963r1091b2002],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l925t1963r1091b2002],
29	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1106t1963r1167b1994],
30	93	CD	PERCENT	93	num	31	SENT_17	[p1l1181t1965r1219b1994],
31	percent	NN	PERCENT	percent	nsubj	33	SENT_17	[p1l1233t1970r1360b2002],
32	had	VBD	O	have	aux	33	SENT_17	[p1l1371t1963r1432b1994],
33	received	VBN	O	receive	parataxis	18	SENT_17	[p1l1445t1973r1490b1994, p1l92t2013r194b2044],
34	platinum-based	JJ	O	platinum-based	amod	35	SENT_17	[p1l208t2013r468b2052],
35	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	dobj	33	SENT_17	[p1l481t2013r719b2052],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l481t2013r719b2052],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_18	[p1l732t2013r794b2044],
2	response	NN	O	response	nn	3	SENT_18	[p1l807t2023r953b2052],
3	rate	NN	O	rate	nsubj	6	SENT_18	[p1l966t2020r1026b2044],
4	was	VBD	O	be	cop	6	SENT_18	[p1l1037t2023r1099b2044],
5	8.9	CD	PERCENT	8.9	num	6	SENT_18	[p1l1113t2016r1163b2044],
6	percent	NN	PERCENT	percent	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1175t2020r1298b2052],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1309t2014r1340b2043],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_18	[p1l1353t2013r1403b2044],
9	erlotinib	NN	O	erlotinib	prep_in	6	SENT_18	[p1l1416t2013r1490b2044, p1l92t2133r166b2164],

1	group	NN	O	group	nsubj	25	SENT_19	[p1l175t2143r272b2172],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l281t2133r341b2164],
3	less	JJR	O	less	mwe	4	SENT_19	[p1l350t2133r409b2164],
4	than	IN	O	than	quantmod	5	SENT_19	[p1l419t2133r492b2163],
5	1	CD	PERCENT	1	num	6	SENT_19	[p1l502t2135r519b2163],
6	percent	NN	PERCENT	percent	nsubj	25	SENT_19	[p1l528t2139r649b2172],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l655t2133r687b2163],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_19	[p1l695t2133r745b2164],
9	placebo	NN	O	placebo	nn	10	SENT_19	[p1l752t2133r877b2172],
10	group	NN	O	group	prep_in	6	SENT_19	[p1l885t2143r981b2172],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_19	[p1l992t2135r1158b2170],
12	P	NN	O	p	npadvmod	13	SENT_19	[p1l992t2135r1158b2170],
13	<	JJR	O	<	amod	6	SENT_19	[p1l992t2135r1158b2170],
14	0.001	CD	NUMBER	0.001	num	15	SENT_19	[p1l992t2135r1158b2170],
15	)	NN	O	)	dep	6	SENT_19	[p1l992t2135r1158b2170],
16	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l992t2135r1158b2170],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_19	[p1l1168t2133r1217b2163],
18	median	JJ	O	median	amod	19	SENT_19	[p1l1226t2133r1346b2164],
19	duration	NN	O	duration	dep	6	SENT_19	[p1l1355t2133r1491b2164],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l92t2183r131b2214],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_19	[p1l134t2183r183b2214],
22	response	NN	O	response	prep_of	19	SENT_19	[p1l193t2193r337b2222],
23	was	VBD	O	be	cop	25	SENT_19	[p1l346t2193r407b2214],
24	7.9	CD	DURATION	7.9	num	25	SENT_19	[p1l419t2185r468b2214],
25	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l478t2183r606b2214],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l619t2183r681b2214],
27	3.7	CD	DURATION	3.7	num	28	SENT_19	[p1l694t2185r745b2214],
28	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	conj_and	25	SENT_19	[p1l758t2183r898b2220],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l758t2183r898b2220],
30	respectively	RB	O	respectively	advmod	25	SENT_19	[p1l912t2183r1115b2222],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l912t2183r1115b2222],

1	Progression-free	JJ	O	progression-free	amod	2	SENT_20	[p1l1129t2183r1411b2222],
2	survival	NN	O	survival	nsubj	5	SENT_20	[p1l1425t2193r1490b2214, p1l90t2233r166b2264],
3	was	VBD	O	be	cop	5	SENT_20	[p1l175t2243r239b2264],
4	2.2	CD	DURATION	2.2	num	5	SENT_20	[p1l251t2236r303b2264],
5	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l314t2233r444b2264],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l455t2233r517b2264],
7	1.8	CD	DURATION	1.8	num	8	SENT_20	[p1l530t2236r580b2264],
8	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	conj_and	5	SENT_20	[p1l592t2233r732b2270],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l592t2233r732b2270],
10	respectively	RB	O	respectively	dep	13	SENT_20	[p1l745t2233r943b2272],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	13	SENT_20	[p1l954t2233r1081b2269],
12	hazard	NN	O	hazard	nn	13	SENT_20	[p1l954t2233r1081b2269],
13	ratio	NN	O	ratio	dep	8	SENT_20	[p1l1092t2234r1180b2270],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1092t2234r1180b2270],
15	0.61	CD	NUMBER	0.61	appos	13	SENT_20	[p1l1193t2236r1276b2271],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1193t2236r1276b2271],
17	adjusted	VBN	O	adjust	partmod	8	SENT_20	[p1l1289t2233r1431b2272],
18	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1442t2233r1491b2264],
19	stratification	NN	O	stratification	nn	20	SENT_20	[p1l92t2353r308b2384],
20	categories	NNS	O	category	prep_for	17	SENT_20	[p1l334t2354r516b2393],
21	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l334t2354r516b2393],
22	P	NN	O	p	dep	23	SENT_20	[p1l542t2356r704b2389],
23	<	JJR	O	<	dep	8	SENT_20	[p1l542t2356r704b2389],
24	0.001	CD	NUMBER	0.001	num	25	SENT_20	[p1l542t2356r704b2389],
25	)	NN	O	)	dep	23	SENT_20	[p1l542t2356r704b2389],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l542t2356r704b2389],

1	Overall	JJ	O	overall	amod	2	SENT_21	[p1l732t2353r852b2384],
2	survival	NN	O	survival	nsubj	5	SENT_21	[p1l877t2353r1005b2384],
3	was	VBD	O	be	cop	5	SENT_21	[p1l1029t2364r1093b2384],
4	6.7	CD	DURATION	6.7	num	5	SENT_21	[p1l1119t2356r1170b2384],
5	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1196t2353r1325b2384],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1351t2353r1413b2384],
7	4.7	CD	DURATION	4.7	num	8	SENT_21	[p1l1438t2356r1490b2384],
8	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	conj_and	5	SENT_21	[p1l92t2403r231b2441],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l92t2403r231b2441],
10	respectively	RB	O	respectively	advmod	13	SENT_21	[p1l245t2403r443b2442],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	13	SENT_21	[p1l455t2403r582b2439],
12	hazard	NN	O	hazard	nn	13	SENT_21	[p1l455t2403r582b2439],
13	ratio	NN	O	ratio	appos	5	SENT_21	[p1l594t2404r681b2440],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l594t2404r681b2440],
15	0.70	CD	NUMBER	0.70	appos	13	SENT_21	[p1l693t2406r772b2440],
16	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l693t2406r772b2440],
17	P	NN	O	p	dep	18	SENT_21	[p1l783t2406r942b2440],
18	<	JJR	O	<	dep	5	SENT_21	[p1l783t2406r942b2440],
19	0.001	CD	NUMBER	0.001	num	20	SENT_21	[p1l783t2406r942b2440],
20	)	NN	O	)	dep	18	SENT_21	[p1l783t2406r942b2440],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l783t2406r942b2440],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l954t2404r986b2433],
23	favor	NN	O	favor	prep_in	5	SENT_21	[p1l997t2403r1079b2434],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1089t2403r1128b2434],
25	erlotinib	NN	O	erlotinib	prep_of	23	SENT_21	[p1l1132t2403r1281b2434],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1132t2403r1281b2434],

1	Five	CD	PERCENT	five	num	2	SENT_22	[p1l1293t2404r1358b2434],
2	percent	NN	PERCENT	percent	nsubj	5	SENT_22	[p1l1368t2410r1493b2442],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l92t2453r131b2484],
4	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_of	2	SENT_22	[p1l133t2454r263b2492],
5	discontinued	VBN	O	discontinue	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l274t2453r487b2484],
6	erlotinib	NN	O	erlotinib	dobj	5	SENT_22	[p1l497t2453r636b2484],
7	because	IN	O	because	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l646t2453r775b2484],
8	of	IN	O	of	prepc_because_of	5	SENT_22	[p1l785t2453r824b2484],
9	toxic	JJ	O	toxic	amod	10	SENT_22	[p1l827t2454r905b2484],
10	effects	NNS	O	effect	pobj	5	SENT_22	[p1l914t2453r1029b2484],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l914t2453r1029b2484],

1	CONCLUSIONS	NNS	MISC	conclusion	nn	2	SENT_23	[p1l92t2564r331b2583],
2	Erlotinib	NN	MISC	erlotinib	nsubj	4	SENT_23	[p1l91t2604r236b2634],
3	can	MD	O	can	aux	4	SENT_23	[p1l249t2614r304b2634],
4	prolong	VB	O	prolong	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l316t2604r449b2643],
5	survival	NN	O	survival	dobj	4	SENT_23	[p1l460t2604r584b2635],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l595t2604r627b2634],
7	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	4	SENT_23	[p1l639t2604r768b2643],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l780t2604r853b2635],
9	non	JJ	O	non	amod	15	SENT_23	[p1l865t2604r1110b2634],
10	—	JJ	O	—	amod	15	SENT_23	[p1l865t2604r1110b2634],
11	small	JJ	O	small	amod	15	SENT_23	[p1l865t2604r1110b2634],
12	—	NN	O	—	nn	15	SENT_23	[p1l865t2604r1110b2634],
13	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	15	SENT_23	[p1l865t2604r1110b2634],
14	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	15	SENT_23	[p1l1122t2604r1197b2643],
15	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_with	7	SENT_23	[p1l1208t2614r1315b2634],
16	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1326t2603r1401b2634],
17	ﬂrstline	NN	O	ﬂrstline	prep_after	4	SENT_23	[p1l1412t2603r1490b2634, p1l91t2653r152b2684],
18	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l161t2663r196b2684],
19	second-line	JJ	O	second-line	amod	20	SENT_23	[p1l205t2653r395b2684],
20	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_after	4	SENT_23	[p1l405t2653r645b2692],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l405t2653r645b2692],

1	N	NN	O	n	nn	3	SENT_24	[p1l431t2854r445b2869],
2	ENGLJ	NN	O	englj	nn	3	SENT_24	[p1l460t2853r544b2875],
3	MED	NN	O	med	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l559t2854r612b2869],
4	353	CD	NUMBER	353	dep	3	SENT_24	[p1l624t2853r688b2875],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l624t2853r688b2875],
6	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	8	SENT_24	[p1l624t2853r688b2875],
7	WWW.NEjM.ORG	NN	O	www.nejm.org	nn	8	SENT_24	[p1l723t2853r934b2875],
8	JULY14	NN	O	july14	dep	4	SENT_24	[p1l967t2853r1074b2875],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l967t2853r1074b2875],
10	2005	CD	DATE	2005	appos	8	SENT_24	[p1l1087t2853r1151b2875],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_25	[p1l750t2950r801b2974],
2	New	NNP	O	New	nn	4	SENT_25	[p1l810t2951r872b2974],
3	England	NNP	O	England	nn	4	SENT_25	[p1l881t2950r992b2981],
4	Joumal	NNP	O	Joumal	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1001t2950r1098b2974],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1108t2950r1137b2974],
6	Medicine	NNP	O	Medicine	prep_of	4	SENT_25	[p1l1143t2950r1269b2974],

1	From	IN	O	from	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1282r1594b1303],
2	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1605t1279r1645b1303],
3	Departments	NNP	O	Departments	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1658t1282r1824b1311],
4	of	IN	O	of	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1835t1279r1863b1303],
5	Medical	NNP	O	Medical	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1871t1279r1968b1303],
6	Oncology	NNP	O	Oncology	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1980t1279r2065b1303, p1l1529t1325r1573b1348],
7	and	CC	O	and	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1580t1317r1624b1341],
8	Hematology	NNP	O	Hematology	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1636t1317r1787b1348],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1797t1318r1884b1348],
10	F.A.S.	NNP	O	F.A.S.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1797t1318r1884b1348],
11	)	NN	O	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1797t1318r1884b1348],
12	and	CC	O	and	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1895t1317r1939b1341],
13	Radiation	NNP	O	Radiation	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1950t1317r2065b1341],
14	Oncology	NNP	O	Oncology	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1530t1354r1649b1386],
15	(	NNP	O	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1659t1356r1734b1385],
16	A.B.	NNP	PERSON	A.B.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1659t1356r1734b1385],
17	)	NNP	O	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1659t1356r1734b1385],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1659t1356r1734b1385],
19	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1742t1354r1781b1378],
20	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1791t1356r1914b1385],
21	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1923t1354r2003b1378],
22	Network	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Network	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l2015t1356r2066b1378, p1l1529t1392r1596b1420],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l2015t1356r2066b1378, p1l1529t1392r1596b1420],
24	Princess	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Princess	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1619t1394r1724b1416],
25	Margaret	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Margaret	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1747t1394r1862b1423],
26	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1883t1392r1989b1423],
27	Site	NN	ORGANIZATION	site	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l2011t1394r2064b1420],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l2011t1394r2064b1420],
29	and	CC	O	and	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1530t1429r1574b1453],
30	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1585t1429r1624b1453],
31	University	NNP	O	University	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1636t1431r1758b1460],
32	ofToronto	NNP	O	ofToronto	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1768t1429r1896b1453],
33	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1910t1431r1994b1460],
34	F.A.S.	NNP	O	F.A.S.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1910t1431r1994b1460],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1910t1431r1994b1460],
36	A.B.	NNP	PERSON	A.B.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l2005t1431r2063b1460],
37	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l2005t1431r2063b1460],
38	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1528t1477r1560b1479],
39	both	DT	O	both	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1571t1462r1627b1486],
40	in	IN	O	in	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1641t1464r1661b1486],
41	Toronto	NNP	LOCATION	Toronto	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1673t1464r1781b1490],
42	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1673t1464r1781b1490],
43	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1793t1462r1833b1486],
44	Instituto	NNP	MISC	Instituto	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1847t1464r1955b1486],
45	de	NNP	MISC	de	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1967t1462r1996b1486],
46	Cancer	NNP	MISC	Cancer	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l2009t1464r2065b1486, p1l1529t1508r1568b1524],
47	Arnaldo	NNP	PERSON	Arnaldo	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1576t1500r1677b1524],
48	Vieira	NNP	PERSON	Vieira	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1686t1502r1758b1524],
49	de	IN	PERSON	de	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1769t1500r1798b1524],
50	Carvalho	NNP	PERSON	Carvalho	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1809t1500r1926b1528],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1809t1500r1926b1528],
52	Sao	NNP	LOCATION	Sao	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1938t1502r1984b1524],
53	Paulo	NNP	LOCATION	Paulo	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1996t1500r2065b1524],
54	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1539r1621b1569],
55	J.R.P.	NNP	O	J.R.P.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1539r1621b1569],
56	)	NN	O	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1539r1621b1569],
57	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1539r1621b1569],
58	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1631t1537r1670b1561],
59	Oncological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncological	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1681t1537r1827b1569],
60	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1840t1540r1940b1561],
61	Ion	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ion	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1953t1540r1989b1561],
62	Chiricuta	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chiricuta	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l2001t1537r2066b1561, p1l1529t1580r1588b1603],
63	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l2001t1537r2066b1561, p1l1529t1580r1588b1603],
64	Cluj-Napoca	NNP	LOCATION	Cluj-Napoca	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1599t1575r1761b1606],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1599t1575r1761b1606],
66	Romania	NNP	LOCATION	Romania	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1773t1577r1883b1599],
67	(	NNP	O	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1893t1577r1964b1606],
68	T.C.	NNP	O	T.C.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1893t1577r1964b1606],
69	)	NNP	O	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1893t1577r1964b1606],
70	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1893t1577r1964b1606],
71	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1974t1575r2013b1599],
72	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l2025t1577r2065b1599, p1l1531t1617r1646b1643],
73	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1659t1612r1687b1636],
74	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1699t1612r1797b1636],
75	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1813t1612r1939b1644],
76	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1813t1612r1939b1644],
77	National	NNP	O	National	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1957t1612r2064b1636],
78	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1530t1652r1618b1674],
79	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1625t1652r1714b1678],
80	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1625t1652r1714b1678],
81	Singapore	NNP	LOCATION	Singapore	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1724t1652r1852b1681],
82	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1863t1652r1965b1681],
83	E.H.T.	NNP	O	E.H.T.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1863t1652r1965b1681],
84	)	NN	O	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1863t1652r1965b1681],
85	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1863t1652r1965b1681],
86	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1974t1650r2014b1674],
87	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l2024t1652r2065b1674, p1l1531t1692r1648b1719],
88	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1660t1687r1688b1711],
89	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1696t1688r1822b1719],
90	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1696t1688r1822b1719],
91	McGill	NNP	ORGANIZATION	McGill	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1838t1688r1918b1711],
92	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1934t1690r2064b1719],
93	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1934t1690r2064b1719],
94	Montreal	NNP	LOCATION	Montreal	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1531t1725r1645b1749],
95	(	NNP	O	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1661t1727r1740b1756],
96	V.H.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	V.H.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1661t1727r1740b1756],
97	)	NNP	O	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1661t1727r1740b1756],
98	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1661t1727r1740b1756],
99	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1752t1725r1792b1749],
100	Faculty	NNP	MISC	Faculty	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1806t1725r1893b1756],
101	of	IN	MISC	of	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1904t1725r1932b1749],
102	Medicine	NNP	MISC	Medicine	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1941t1725r2064b1753],
103	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1941t1725r2064b1753],
104	Chiangmai	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chiangmai	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1530t1763r1662b1794],
105	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1674t1765r1799b1794],
106	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1674t1765r1799b1794],
107	Chiangmai	NNP	LOCATION	Chiangmai	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1809t1763r1949b1794],
108	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1809t1763r1949b1794],
109	Thailand	NNP	LOCATION	Thailand	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1958t1763r2065b1787],
110	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1802r1603b1831],
111	S.T.	NNP	LOCATION	S.T.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1802r1603b1831],
112	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1802r1603b1831],
113	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1802r1603b1831],
114	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1612t1800r1652b1824],
115	Conﬁdence	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Conﬁdence	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1661t1800r1804b1824],
116	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1814t1800r1912b1824],
117	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1922t1802r2009b1828],
118	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1922t1802r2009b1828],
119	San	NNP	LOCATION	San	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l2019t1802r2064b1824],
120	Isidro	NNP	LOCATION	Isidro	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1531t1838r1609b1866],
121	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1531t1838r1609b1866],
122	Argentina	NNP	LOCATION	Argentina	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1621t1839r1746b1869],
123	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1760t1840r1842b1869],
124	D.C.	NNP	LOCATION	D.C.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1760t1840r1842b1869],
125	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1760t1840r1842b1869],
126	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1760t1840r1842b1869],
127	Pramongkutklao	NNP	LOCATION	Pramongkutklao	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1857t1838r2065b1869],
128	Hospital	NNP	LOCATION	Hospital	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1531t1870r1641b1901],
129	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1531t1870r1641b1901],
130	Bangkok	NNP	LOCATION	Bangkok	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1657t1870r1767b1901],
131	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1657t1870r1767b1901],
132	Thailand	NNP	LOCATION	Thailand	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1780t1870r1886b1894],
133	(	NNP	O	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1903t1872r1984b1901],
134	S.M.	NNP	LOCATION	S.M.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1903t1872r1984b1901],
135	)	NN	O	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1903t1872r1984b1901],
136	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1903t1872r1984b1901],
137	Cross	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cross	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1998t1872r2065b1894],
138	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1530t1909r1618b1931],
139	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1627t1909r1738b1935],
140	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1627t1909r1738b1935],
141	Edmonton	NNP	LOCATION	Edmonton	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1749t1907r1889b1935],
142	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1749t1907r1889b1935],
143	A	DT	O	a	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1898t1907r1962b1935],
144	|	JJ	O	|	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1898t1907r1962b1935],
145	ta.	NN	O	ta.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1898t1907r1962b1935],
146	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1898t1907r1962b1935],
147	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1971t1907r2065b1931],
148	(	NNP	O	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1946r1617b1976],
149	M.S.	NNP	LOCATION	M.S.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1946r1617b1976],
150	)	NNP	O	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1946r1617b1976],
151	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1532t1946r1617b1976],
152	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1630t1944r1670b1968],
153	Instituto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Instituto	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1685t1947r1791b1968],
154	Nacional	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nacional	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1806t1944r1917b1968],
155	de	NNP	ORGANIZATION	de	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1931t1944r1960b1968],
156	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1973t1946r2064b1972],
157	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1973t1946r2064b1972],
158	Praca	NNP	LOCATION	Praca	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1531t1984r1598b2013],
159	da	NNP	O	da	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1613t1982r1642b2006],
160	Cruz	NNP	PERSON	Cruz	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1657t1984r1714b2006],
161	Vermelha	NNP	PERSON	Vermelha	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1728t1982r1855b2010],
162	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1728t1982r1855b2010],
163	Rio	NNP	LOCATION	Rio	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1872t1984r1911b2006],
164	de	IN	LOCATION	de	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1925t1982r1955b2006],
165	Janeiro	NNP	LOCATION	Janeiro	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1964t1984r2064b2013],
166	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1964t1984r2064b2013],
167	Brazil	NNP	LOCATION	Brazil	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1531t2020r1600b2043],
168	(	NNP	O	(	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1618t2022r1705b2051],
169	R.M.	NNP	LOCATION	R.M.	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1618t2022r1705b2051],
170	)	NNP	O	)	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1618t2022r1705b2051],
171	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1618t2022r1705b2051],
172	the	DT	O	the	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1719t2020r1759b2043],
173	Instituto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Instituto	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1774t2022r1882b2044],
174	Medico	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medico	dep	175	SENT_26	[p1l1897t2020r1991b2044],
175	Alexander	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Alexander	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l2004t2020r2065b2044, p1l1530t2127r1603b2151],

1	Fleming	NNP	PERSON	Fleming	nn	7	SENT_27	[p1l1616t2127r1725b2158],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1616t2127r1725b2158],
3	Buenos	NNP	PERSON	Buenos	appos	7	SENT_27	[p1l1741t2129r1834b2151],
4	Aires	NNP	PERSON	Aires	nn	7	SENT_27	[p1l1846t2128r1911b2151],
5	(	NNP	O	(	nn	7	SENT_27	[p1l1926t2129r2013b2158],
6	M.K.	NNP	LOCATION	M.K.	nn	7	SENT_27	[p1l1926t2129r2013b2158],
7	)	NNP	O	)	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1926t2129r2013b2158],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1926t2129r2013b2158],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_27	[p1l2025t2127r2065b2151],
10	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	nn	11	SENT_27	[p1l1530t2164r1653b2196],
11	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	7	SENT_27	[p1l1670t2167r1782b2192],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1670t2167r1782b2192],
13	Bucharest	NNP	LOCATION	Bucharest	appos	7	SENT_27	[p1l1801t2164r1934b2193],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1801t2164r1934b2193],
15	Romania	NNP	LOCATION	Romania	nn	18	SENT_27	[p1l1953t2167r2065b2188],
16	(	NNP	O	(	nn	18	SENT_27	[p1l1532t2204r1622b2233],
17	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	nn	18	SENT_27	[p1l1532t2204r1622b2233],
18	)	NNP	O	)	appos	7	SENT_27	[p1l1532t2204r1622b2233],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1532t2204r1622b2233],
20	Hotel	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hotel	nn	24	SENT_27	[p1l1636t2202r1704b2226],
21	Dieu	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dieu	nn	24	SENT_27	[p1l1718t2204r1774b2226],
22	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	24	SENT_27	[p1l1788t2202r1870b2226],
23	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	nn	24	SENT_27	[p1l1883t2204r1993b2226],
24	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	18	SENT_27	[p1l2006t2204r2065b2226, p1l1531t2240r1592b2271],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l2006t2204r2065b2226, p1l1531t2240r1592b2271],
26	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	34	SENT_27	[p1l1604t2242r1635b2264],
27	Catharines	NNP	LOCATION	Catharines	nn	34	SENT_27	[p1l1647t2240r1791b2268],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1647t2240r1791b2268],
29	Ont.	NNP	LOCATION	Ont.	appos	34	SENT_27	[p1l1804t2242r1867b2268],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1804t2242r1867b2268],
31	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	appos	34	SENT_27	[p1l1879t2240r1974b2264],
32	(	NNP	O	(	nn	34	SENT_27	[p1l1988t2242r2064b2271],
33	B.F.	NNP	LOCATION	B.F.	nn	34	SENT_27	[p1l1988t2242r2064b2271],
34	)	NNP	O	)	appos	7	SENT_27	[p1l1988t2242r2064b2271],
35	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1988t2242r2064b2271],

1	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_28	[p1l1529t2347r1569b2371],
2	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	4	SENT_28	[p1l1586t2347r1692b2371],
3	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	4	SENT_28	[p1l1709t2349r1796b2371],
4	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1813t2349r1917b2371],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1932t2347r1960b2371],
6	Canada	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Canada	prep_of	4	SENT_28	[p1l1971t2347r2065b2371],
7	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	amod	17	SENT_28	[p1l1530t2385r1621b2409],
8	Trials	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Trials	nn	17	SENT_28	[p1l1630t2385r1697b2409],
9	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	nn	17	SENT_28	[p1l1707t2387r1795b2416],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1707t2387r1795b2416],
11	Kingston	NNP	LOCATION	Kingston	appos	17	SENT_28	[p1l1807t2387r1925b2416],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1807t2387r1925b2416],
13	Ont.	NNP	LOCATION	Ont.	appos	17	SENT_28	[p1l1936t2387r1999b2413],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1936t2387r1999b2413],
15	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	appos	17	SENT_28	[p1l2009t2387r2065b2409, p1l1530t2422r1574b2446],
16	(	NNP	O	(	nn	17	SENT_28	[p1l1586t2424r1651b2453],
17	D.T.	NNP	LOCATION	D.T.	dep	6	SENT_28	[p1l1586t2424r1651b2453],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1586t2424r1651b2453],
19	D.J.	NNP	PERSON	D.J.	dep	6	SENT_28	[p1l1664t2424r1714b2453],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1664t2424r1714b2453],
21	L.S.	NNP	LOCATION	L.S.	nn	22	SENT_28	[p1l1726t2424r1788b2453],
22	)	NNP	O	)	dep	6	SENT_28	[p1l1726t2424r1788b2453],
23	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1726t2424r1788b2453],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1799t2422r1844b2446],
25	OSI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	OSI	nn	26	SENT_28	[p1l1855t2424r1901b2446],
26	Pharmaceuticals	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceuticals	dep	6	SENT_28	[p1l1914t2422r2065b2446, p1l1529t2460r1602b2488],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1914t2422r2065b2446, p1l1529t2460r1602b2488],
28	Boulder	NNP	LOCATION	Boulder	dep	32	SENT_28	[p1l1614t2460r1716b2488],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1614t2460r1716b2488],
30	Colo.	NNP	LOCATION	Colo.	dep	28	SENT_28	[p1l1727t2460r1790b2484],
31	(	NNP	O	(	nn	32	SENT_28	[p1l1803t2462r1873b2491],
32	G.C.	NNP	LOCATION	G.C.	appos	4	SENT_28	[p1l1803t2462r1873b2491],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1803t2462r1873b2491],
34	P.S.	NNP	O	P.S.	nn	35	SENT_28	[p1l1886t2462r1950b2491],
35	)	NNP	O	)	appos	32	SENT_28	[p1l1886t2462r1950b2491],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1886t2462r1950b2491],

1	*	NN	O	*	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1529t2535r1592b2559],
2	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_29	[p1l1529t2535r1592b2559],
3	investigators	NNS	O	investigator	dep	1	SENT_29	[p1l1602t2537r1766b2566],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1776t2535r1822b2559],
5	centers	NNS	O	center	dep	1	SENT_29	[p1l1832t2539r1924b2559],
6	participating	VBG	O	participate	partmod	1	SENT_29	[p1l1936t2537r2065b2566, p1l1547t2575r1585b2604],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1600t2575r1620b2596],
8	this	DT	O	this	det	11	SENT_29	[p1l1635t2572r1681b2596],
9	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	11	SENT_29	[p1l1698t2572r1805b2596],
10	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	11	SENT_29	[p1l1820t2574r1908b2596],
11	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	prep_in	6	SENT_29	[p1l1923t2575r2028b2596],
12	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l2042t2572r2070b2596],
13	Canada	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Canada	nn	15	SENT_29	[p1l1546t2610r1637b2634],
14	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	amod	15	SENT_29	[p1l1647t2610r1734b2634],
15	Trials	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Trials	prep_of	11	SENT_29	[p1l1743t2610r1807b2634],
16	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	nn	17	SENT_29	[p1l1816t2612r1895b2641],
17	study	NN	O	study	nsubjpass	19	SENT_29	[p1l1904t2610r1970b2641],
18	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	19	SENT_29	[p1l1978t2619r2014b2634],
19	listed	VBN	O	list	rcmod	15	SENT_29	[p1l2024t2610r2066b2634, p1l1546t2647r1574b2671],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1584t2649r1604b2670],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_29	[p1l1613t2647r1652b2671],
22	Appendix	NNP	O	Appendix	prep_in	19	SENT_29	[p1l1659t2647r1782b2678],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1659t2647r1782b2678],

1	N	NN	MISC	n	nn	3	SENT_30	[p1l1531t2712r1549b2733],
2	Englj	NNP	MISC	Englj	nn	3	SENT_30	[p1l1563t2710r1630b2741],
3	Med	NNP	O	Med	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1644t2710r1697b2734],
4	2005	CD	DATE	2005	num	3	SENT_30	[p1l1708t2711r1925b2738],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1708t2711r1925b2738],
6	353:123	CD	NUMBER	353:123	number	7	SENT_30	[p1l1708t2711r1925b2738],
7	-32	CD	NUMBER	-32	dep	3	SENT_30	[p1l1708t2711r1925b2738],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1708t2711r1925b2738],

1	Copyright	NN	O	copyright	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1530t2752r1623b2777],
2	©	CD	NUMBER	©	num	6	SENT_31	[p1l1631t2754r1652b2775],
3	2005	CD	DATE	2005	num	6	SENT_31	[p1l1661t2753r1710b2771],
4	Massachusetts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Massachusetts	nn	6	SENT_31	[p1l1718t2752r1858b2771],
5	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	6	SENT_31	[p1l1866t2752r1943b2771],
6	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	dep	1	SENT_31	[p1l1949t2753r2021b2777],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1949t2753r2021b2777],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_32	[p1l715t3138r752b3159],
2	NEW	NNP	O	NEW	nn	4	SENT_32	[p1l764t3140r845b3159],
3	ENGLAND	NNP	O	ENGLAND	nn	4	SENT_32	[p1l859t3140r1034b3159],
4	JOURNAL	NNP	O	JOURNAL	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1048t3140r1214b3166],
5	ofMEDICINE	NN	O	ofmedicine	dep	4	SENT_32	[p1l1228t3138r1444b3165],

1	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	2	SENT_34	[p1l332t3503r607b3556],
2	death	NN	O	death	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l649t3478r881b3556],
3	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l925t3503r1225b3578],
4	men	NNS	O	man	prep_among	2	SENT_34	[p1l1266t3503r1452b3556],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l1495t3478r1652b3556],
6	women	NNS	O	woman	conj_and	4	SENT_34	[p1l1692t3503r2010b3557],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l2054t3479r2135b3555],
8	North	NNP	LOCATION	North	nn	9	SENT_34	[p1l329t3607r577b3685],
9	America	NNP	LOCATION	America	prep_in	2	SENT_34	[p1l591t3607r958b3685],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l591t3607r958b3685],

1	1	CD	NUMBER	1	npadvmod	13	SENT_35	[p1l969t3601r1003b3645],
2	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1020t3614r1106b3684],
3	advanced	JJ	O	advanced	amod	5	SENT_35	[p1l1124t3606r1506b3686],
4	non	JJ	O	non	amod	5	SENT_35	[p1l1524t3606r2137b3685],
5	—	NN	O	—	prep_in	13	SENT_35	[p1l1524t3606r2137b3685],
6	small	JJ	O	small	amod	10	SENT_35	[p1l1524t3606r2137b3685],
7	—	NN	O	—	nn	10	SENT_35	[p1l1524t3606r2137b3685],
8	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	10	SENT_35	[p1l1524t3606r2137b3685],
9	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	10	SENT_35	[p2l11t32r201b132],
10	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	5	SENT_35	[p2l231t57r517b127],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l231t57r517b127],
12	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nsubj	13	SENT_35	[p2l556t31r1154b132],
13	offers	VBZ	O	offer	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1182t31r1418b110],
14	symptomatic	JJ	O	symptomatic	amod	15	SENT_35	[p2l1454t32r1993b132],
15	relief	NN	O	relief	dobj	13	SENT_35	[p2l2025t58r2134b110, p2l11t158r157b236],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l164t158r318b236],
17	modest	JJ	O	modest	amod	18	SENT_35	[p2l343t159r656b236],
18	improvement	NN	O	improvement	conj_and	15	SENT_35	[p2l676t159r1242b258],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1262t159r1342b235],
20	survivalz	NN	O	survivalz	prep_in	15	SENT_35	[p2l1369t154r1744b253],
21	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1369t154r1744b253],
22	responses	NNS	O	response	nsubj	24	SENT_35	[p2l1774t184r2134b258, p2l12t313r95b365],
23	are	VBP	O	be	cop	24	SENT_35	[p2l123t313r252b365],
24	brief	JJ	O	brief	parataxis	13	SENT_35	[p2l280t286r505b382],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l280t286r505b382],
26	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l533t287r727b366],
27	a	DT	O	a	det	29	SENT_35	[p2l752t313r797b365],
28	median	JJ	O	median	amod	29	SENT_35	[p2l822t287r1146b365],
29	time	NN	O	time	prep_with	24	SENT_35	[p2l1173t287r1364b365],
30	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1391t303r1472b365],
31	progression	NN	O	progression	prep_to	29	SENT_35	[p2l1498t287r2023b387],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l2050t286r2152b365],
33	three	CD	NUMBER	three	number	35	SENT_35	[p2l12t414r229b493],
34	to	TO	O	to	dep	35	SENT_35	[p2l267t431r348b493],
35	ﬁve	CD	NUMBER	ﬁve	num	36	SENT_35	[p2l386t414r535b494],
36	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	prep_of	31	SENT_35	[p2l573t415r929b493],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l573t415r929b493],

1	Second	JJ	ORDINAL	second	amod	4	SENT_36	[p2l974t414r1481b493],
2	—	NN	O	—	nn	4	SENT_36	[p2l974t414r1481b493],
3	line	NN	O	line	nn	4	SENT_36	[p2l974t414r1481b493],
4	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nsubj	8	SENT_36	[p2l1520t414r2138b515],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l7t543r196b622],
6	docetaxel	NN	O	docetaxel	prep_with	4	SENT_36	[p2l219t542r616b621],
7	can	MD	O	can	aux	8	SENT_36	[p2l639t568r782b621],
8	prolong	VB	O	prolong	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l803t542r1145b643],
9	survival	NN	O	survival	dobj	8	SENT_36	[p2l1165t543r1483b622],
10	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1504t542r1697b621],
11	platinumbased	JJ	O	platinumbased	amod	12	SENT_36	[p2l1715t542r2134b643, p2l12t670r258b747],
12	therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_after	8	SENT_36	[p2l296t670r619b769],
13	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l652t669r777b747],
14	non	JJ	O	non	amod	20	SENT_36	[p2l811t669r1457b747],
15	—	JJ	O	—	amod	20	SENT_36	[p2l811t669r1457b747],
16	small	JJ	O	small	amod	20	SENT_36	[p2l811t669r1457b747],
17	—	NN	O	—	nn	20	SENT_36	[p2l811t669r1457b747],
18	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	20	SENT_36	[p2l811t669r1457b747],
19	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	20	SENT_36	[p2l1493t670r1689b769],
20	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_for	12	SENT_36	[p2l1725t665r2134b747],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1725t665r2134b747],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1725t665r2134b747],
2	°	NN	O	°	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1725t665r2134b747],
3	”	CD	NUMBER	”	num	4	SENT_37	[p2l1725t665r2134b747],
4	4	CD	NUMBER	4	nsubj	8	SENT_37	[p2l1725t665r2134b747],
5	However	RB	O	however	advmod	8	SENT_37	[p2l11t805r414b893],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l11t805r414b893],
7	there	EX	O	there	expl	8	SENT_37	[p2l458t798r677b876],
8	is	VBZ	O	be	rcmod	2	SENT_37	[p2l715t798r781b876],
9	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l821t814r902b876],
10	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	13	SENT_37	[p2l934t814r1262b898],
11	no	DT	O	no	det	13	SENT_37	[p2l1295t823r1403b876],
12	deﬁned	JJ	O	deﬁned	amod	13	SENT_37	[p2l1444t797r1768b876],
13	role	NN	O	role	prep_at	8	SENT_37	[p2l1806t797r1972b876],
14	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l2010t797r2137b876],
15	third	JJ	ORDINAL	third	amod	18	SENT_37	[p2l12t925r421b1004],
16	—	NN	O	—	nn	18	SENT_37	[p2l12t925r421b1004],
17	line	NN	O	line	nn	18	SENT_37	[p2l12t925r421b1004],
18	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_for	13	SENT_37	[p2l464t926r1095b1026],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l464t926r1095b1026],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_38	[p2l1138t925r1301b1004],
2	futility	NN	O	futility	nsubjpass	10	SENT_38	[p2l1343t925r1626b1026],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1664t925r1765b1004],
4	offering	VBG	O	offer	prepc_of	2	SENT_38	[p2l1789t925r2138b1026],
5	third	JJ	ORDINAL	third	amod	8	SENT_38	[p2l12t1053r401b1132],
6	—	NN	O	—	nn	8	SENT_38	[p2l12t1053r401b1132],
7	line	NN	O	line	nn	8	SENT_38	[p2l12t1053r401b1132],
8	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	dobj	4	SENT_38	[p2l424t1053r1021b1154],
9	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_38	[p2l1035t1080r1194b1133],
10	demonstrated	VBN	O	demonstrate	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1218t1053r1795b1132],
11	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1818t1053r1914b1154],
12	Massarelli	NNP	PERSON	Massarelli	agent	10	SENT_38	[p2l1929t1061r2134b1132, p2l13t1180r271b1258],
13	et	FW	O	et	nn	15	SENT_38	[p2l295t1197r372b1258],
14	al.	FW	O	al.	nn	15	SENT_38	[p2l391t1176r561b1275],
15	,5	NN	O	,5	dobj	10	SENT_38	[p2l391t1176r561b1275],
16	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	17	SENT_38	[p2l583t1181r769b1259],
17	reported	VBD	O	report	rcmod	15	SENT_38	[p2l795t1181r1161b1280],
18	a	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_38	[p2l1184t1207r1228b1258],
19	response	NN	O	response	nn	20	SENT_38	[p2l1250t1206r1637b1280],
20	rate	NN	O	rate	dobj	17	SENT_38	[p2l1662t1196r1821b1258],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1846t1180r1947b1258],
22	only	RB	O	only	quantmod	23	SENT_38	[p2l1954t1181r2139b1280],
23	2	CD	PERCENT	2	num	24	SENT_38	[p2l11t1314r59b1386],
24	percent	NN	PERCENT	percent	prep_of	20	SENT_38	[p2l93t1325r420b1409],
25	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l450t1309r608b1387],
26	a	DT	O	a	det	28	SENT_38	[p2l643t1335r687b1387],
27	median	JJ	O	median	amod	28	SENT_38	[p2l720t1309r1042b1387],
28	survival	NN	O	survival	conj_and	20	SENT_38	[p2l1079t1309r1404b1388],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1440t1308r1542b1387],
30	four	CD	DURATION	four	num	31	SENT_38	[p2l1559t1308r1740b1388],
31	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	prep_of	28	SENT_38	[p2l1772t1308r2129b1387],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1772t1308r2129b1387],

1	Shepherd	NNP	O	Shepherd	nsubj	5	SENT_39	[p2l13t1436r420b1536],
2	et	FW	O	et	nn	3	SENT_39	[p2l444t1452r520b1514],
3	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	1	SENT_39	[p2l538t1429r678b1514],
4	6	CD	NUMBER	6	dep	1	SENT_39	[p2l538t1429r678b1514],
5	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l703t1436r1026b1515],
6	that	IN	O	that	complm	24	SENT_39	[p2l1050t1436r1217b1514],
7	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1235t1461r1534b1536],
8	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_among	24	SENT_39	[p2l1553t1437r1888b1536],
9	treated	VBN	O	treat	partmod	8	SENT_39	[p2l1913t1452r2134b1514, p2l12t1565r108b1643],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l138t1565r327b1644],
11	docetaxel	NN	O	docetaxel	prep_with	9	SENT_39	[p2l364t1565r761b1643],
12	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l795t1564r989b1643],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_39	[p2l1022t1565r1151b1643],
14	failure	NN	O	failure	prep_after	9	SENT_39	[p2l1186t1564r1455b1644],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1492t1564r1592b1643],
16	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	20	SENT_39	[p2l1609t1581r1761b1644],
17	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1799t1590r1888b1643],
18	more	JJR	O	more	num	20	SENT_39	[p2l1918t1590r2135b1643],
19	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nn	20	SENT_39	[p2l12t1693r609b1793],
20	regimens	NNS	O	regimen	prep_of	14	SENT_39	[p2l645t1693r1057b1793],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l645t1693r1057b1793],
22	survival	NN	O	survival	nsubj	24	SENT_39	[p2l1105t1693r1417b1772],
23	was	VBD	O	be	cop	24	SENT_39	[p2l1453t1719r1613b1772],
24	identical	JJ	O	identical	ccomp	5	SENT_39	[p2l1655t1693r2013b1771],
25	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l2056t1709r2134b1771],
26	that	DT	O	that	prep_to	24	SENT_39	[p2l12t1821r179b1899],
27	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l198t1846r497b1921],
28	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_among	26	SENT_39	[p2l518t1821r852b1921],
29	treated	VBN	O	treat	partmod	28	SENT_39	[p2l880t1820r1168b1899],
30	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1189t1821r1378b1900],
31	supportive	JJ	O	supportive	amod	32	SENT_39	[p2l1405t1821r1848b1921],
32	care	NN	O	care	prep_with	29	SENT_39	[p2l1873t1847r2067b1899],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1873t1847r2067b1899],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_40	[p2l137t1948r298b2027],
2	epidermal	JJ	O	epidermal	amod	5	SENT_40	[p2l340t1949r764b2049],
3	growth	NN	O	growth	nn	5	SENT_40	[p2l804t1949r1107b2049],
4	factor	NN	O	factor	nn	5	SENT_40	[p2l1147t1948r1394b2027],
5	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nsubj	11	SENT_40	[p2l1431t1965r1782b2049],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	9	SENT_40	[p2l1824t1954r2130b2040],
7	EGFR	NN	ORGANIZATION	egfr	nn	9	SENT_40	[p2l1824t1954r2130b2040],
8	)	NN	O	)	nn	9	SENT_40	[p2l1824t1954r2130b2040],
9	family	NN	O	family	dep	5	SENT_40	[p2l11t2076r277b2177],
10	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	11	SENT_40	[p2l293t2077r358b2155],
11	part	NN	O	part	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l381t2093r554b2177],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l571t2076r672b2155],
13	a	DT	O	a	det	18	SENT_40	[p2l675t2103r719b2155],
14	complex	JJ	O	complex	amod	18	SENT_40	[p2l740t2077r1101b2177],
15	signal	NN	O	signal	nn	18	SENT_40	[p2l1121t2076r1950b2177],
16	—	NN	O	—	nn	18	SENT_40	[p2l1121t2076r1950b2177],
17	transduction	NN	O	transduction	nn	18	SENT_40	[p2l1121t2076r1950b2177],
18	network	NN	O	network	prep_of	11	SENT_40	[p2l1971t2093r2134b2155, p2l7t2205r229b2284],
19	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	21	SENT_40	[p2l257t2205r424b2283],
20	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	21	SENT_40	[p2l451t2205r515b2283],
21	central	JJ	O	central	rcmod	18	SENT_40	[p2l551t2204r838b2283],
22	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l870t2221r949b2283],
23	several	JJ	O	several	amod	26	SENT_40	[p2l984t2205r1269b2284],
24	critical	JJ	O	critical	amod	26	SENT_40	[p2l1301t2205r1585b2283],
25	cellular	JJ	O	cellular	amod	26	SENT_40	[p2l1618t2205r1929b2284],
26	processes	NNS	O	process	prep_to	21	SENT_40	[p2l1957t2230r2134b2305, p2l12t2359r297b2411],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1957t2230r2134b2305, p2l12t2359r297b2411],

1	Since	IN	O	since	mark	5	SENT_41	[p2l342t2333r563b2411],
2	EGFR	NN	ORGANIZATION	egfr	nsubjpass	5	SENT_41	[p2l600t2338r859b2416],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_41	[p2l885t2333r950b2411],
4	often	RB	O	often	advmod	5	SENT_41	[p2l991t2332r1207b2411],
5	found	VBN	O	find	advcl	20	SENT_41	[p2l1245t2332r1496b2412],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1532t2333r1613b2410],
7	non	JJ	O	non	amod	12	SENT_41	[p2l1650t2332r2134b2411, p2l12t2459r155b2537],
8	—	NN	O	—	nn	12	SENT_41	[p2l1650t2332r2134b2411, p2l12t2459r155b2537],
9	smallcell	NN	O	smallcell	nn	12	SENT_41	[p2l1650t2332r2134b2411, p2l12t2459r155b2537],
10	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	12	SENT_41	[p2l191t2459r388b2559],
11	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	12	SENT_41	[p2l422t2485r703b2537],
12	cells	NNS	O	cell	prep_in	5	SENT_41	[p2l738t2455r1062b2554],
13	,7	CD	NUMBER	,7	number	14	SENT_41	[p2l738t2455r1062b2554],
14	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	12	SENT_41	[p2l738t2455r1062b2554],
15	8	CD	NUMBER	8	dep	14	SENT_41	[p2l738t2455r1062b2554],
16	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	20	SENT_41	[p2l1099t2460r1160b2537],
17	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	20	SENT_41	[p2l1192t2460r1334b2537],
18	been	VBN	O	be	cop	20	SENT_41	[p2l1374t2460r1577b2537],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_41	[p2l1614t2460r1746b2537],
20	focus	NN	O	focus	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1783t2459r2011b2538],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l2051t2459r2152b2537],
22	efforts	NNS	O	effort	prep_of	20	SENT_41	[p2l12t2587r289b2666],
23	to	TO	O	to	aux	24	SENT_41	[p2l320t2604r399b2666],
24	develop	VB	O	develop	infmod	22	SENT_41	[p2l427t2587r748b2688],
25	new	JJ	O	new	amod	26	SENT_41	[p2l776t2613r951b2667],
26	agents	NNS	O	agent	dobj	24	SENT_41	[p2l973t2604r1245b2688],
27	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	28	SENT_41	[p2l1274t2588r1441b2666],
28	target	VBP	O	target	rcmod	26	SENT_41	[p2l1462t2604r1711b2688],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_41	[p2l1733t2587r1862b2666],
30	EGFR	NN	ORGANIZATION	egfr	nn	31	SENT_41	[p2l1886t2593r2146b2671],
31	pathway	NN	O	pathway	dobj	28	SENT_41	[p2l10t2716r377b2816],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l10t2716r377b2816],

1	Erlotinib	NNP	O	Erlotinib	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l412t2716r784b2794],
2	(	NNP	O	(	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l820t2721r1186b2811],
3	Tarceva	NNP	O	Tarceva	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l820t2721r1186b2811],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l820t2721r1186b2811],
5	OSI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	OSI	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1223t2721r1378b2794],
6	Pharmaceuticals	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceuticals	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1406t2715r2130b2807],
7	)	NN	O	)	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1406t2715r2130b2807],
8	and	CC	O	and	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l11t2843r166b2922],
9	geﬁtinib	NN	O	geﬁtinib	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l198t2843r562b2944],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l601t2851r907b2939],
11	Iressa	NNP	O	Iressa	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l601t2851r907b2939],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l601t2851r907b2939],
13	AstraZeneca	NNP	ORGANIZATION	AstraZeneca	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l943t2851r1504b2935],
14	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l943t2851r1504b2935],
15	inhibit	VBP	O	inhibit	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1543t2844r1835b2922],
16	the	DT	O	the	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1864t2844r1995b2922],
17	ty	NN	O	ty	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l2029t2860r2133b2944],
18	—	NN	O	—	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l2029t2860r2133b2944],
19	rosine	NN	O	rosine	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l11t2972r273b3050],
20	kinase	NN	O	kinase	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l302t2972r569b3051],
21	activity	NN	O	activity	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l598t2972r890b3072],
22	of	IN	O	of	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l915t2971r1015b3050],
23	EGFR	NN	ORGANIZATION	egfr	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1023t2977r1281b3055],
24	and	CC	O	and	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1298t2972r1453b3050],
25	have	VBP	O	have	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1481t2972r1667b3051],
26	been	VBN	O	be	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1698t2972r1895b3050],
27	studied	VBN	O	study	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1925t2971r2134b3051, p2l11t3100r135b3178],
28	eXtensively	RB	O	extensively	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l155t3094r793b3200],
29	.9	CD	NUMBER	.9	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l155t3094r793b3200],
30	'12	CD	NUMBER	'12	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l155t3094r793b3200],
31	In	IN	O	in	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l814t3107r902b3177],
32	randomized	JJ	O	randomized	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l925t3100r1446b3178],
33	phase	NN	O	phase	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1467t3100r1718b3200],
34	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1741t3106r1788b3177],
35	trials	NNS	O	trial	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1813t3100r2025b3178],
36	of	IN	O	of	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l2051t3099r2152b3178],
37	geﬁtinib	NN	O	geﬁtinib	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l11t3227r362b3328],
38	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l393t3234r666b3319],
39	Iressa	NNP	O	Iressa	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l393t3234r666b3319],
40	Dose	NNP	O	Dose	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l688t3234r899b3306],
41	Evaluation	NN	O	evaluation	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l923t3228r1363b3307],
42	in	IN	O	in	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1387t3228r1468b3305],
43	Advanced	NNP	O	Advanced	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1490t3227r1898b3307],
44	Lung	NN	O	lung	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1921t3235r2139b3328],
45	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l11t3361r313b3433],
46	[	CD	NUMBER	[	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l346t3362r684b3445],
47	IDEAL	JJ	O	ideal	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l346t3362r684b3445],
48	]	NN	O	]	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l346t3362r684b3445],
49	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l725t3361r769b3432],
50	and	CC	O	and	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l797t3355r955b3433],
51	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l983t3349r1286b3450],
52	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l983t3349r1286b3450],
53	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l983t3349r1286b3450],
54	°	CD	NUMBER	°	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l983t3349r1286b3450],
55	’“	IN	O	’“	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l983t3349r1286b3450],
56	the	DT	O	the	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1315t3355r1445b3433],
57	tumors	NNS	O	tumor	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1474t3371r1780b3434],
58	of	IN	O	of	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1811t3354r1912b3433],
59	10	CD	NUMBER	10	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1925t3361r2023b3433],
60	to	TO	O	to	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l2052t3371r2132b3433],
61	20	CD	PERCENT	20	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l11t3489r113b3562],
62	percent	NN	PERCENT	percent	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l144t3500r471b3584],
63	of	IN	O	of	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l499t3483r601b3562],
64	patients	NNS	O	patient	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l613t3484r955b3584],
65	who	WP	O	who	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l985t3484r1170b3563],
66	were	VBD	O	be	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1199t3510r1404b3563],
67	previously	RB	DATE	previously	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1435t3483r1879b3584],
68	treated	VBN	O	treat	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1907t3500r2133b3562, p2l12t3612r109b3690],
69	with	IN	O	with	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l125t3612r318b3691],
70	platinum	NN	O	platinum	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l340t3611r1021b3712],
71	—	NN	O	—	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l340t3611r1021b3712],
72	based	VBN	O	base	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l340t3611r1021b3712],
73	regimens	NNS	O	regimen	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1044t3612r1444b3712],
74	responded	VBD	O	respond	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1469t3611r1948b3712],
75	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1469t3611r1948b3712],
76	and	CC	O	and	dep	113	SENT_42	[p2l1976t3611r2134b3690],
77	in	IN	O	in	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l11t21r94b98],
78	a	DT	O	a	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l133t47r177b99],
79	phase	NN	O	phase	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l216t21r468b121],
80	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l509t26r555b98],
81	trial	NN	O	trial	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l598t21r771b99],
82	of	IN	O	of	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l812t20r914b99],
83	erlotinib	NN	O	erlotinib	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l936t21r1307b99],
84	among	IN	O	among	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1348t46r1654b121],
85	previously	RB	DATE	previously	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1690t21r2139b121],
86	treated	VBN	O	treat	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l12t148r307b227],
87	patients	NNS	O	patient	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l337t149r674b249],
88	with	IN	O	with	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l698t149r884b228],
89	non	JJ	O	non	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l910t149r1526b227],
90	—	JJ	O	—	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l910t149r1526b227],
91	small	JJ	O	small	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l910t149r1526b227],
92	—	NN	O	—	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l910t149r1526b227],
93	cell	NN	O	cell	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l910t149r1526b227],
94	lung	NN	O	lung	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1551t149r1741b249],
95	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1765t174r2034b227],
96	in	IN	O	in	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l2056t149r2137b226],
97	which	WDT	O	which	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l7t277r262b356],
98	10	CD	PERCENT	10	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l304t282r402b355],
99	percent	NN	PERCENT	percent	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l440t293r767b377],
100	or	CC	O	or	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l801t302r892b355],
101	more	JJR	O	more	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l927t302r1150b355],
102	of	IN	O	of	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1190t276r1292b355],
103	the	DT	O	the	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1312t276r1443b355],
104	cells	NNS	O	cell	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1482t277r1669b355],
105	expressed	VBD	O	express	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1711t276r2134b377],
106	EGFR	NN	ORGANIZATION	egfr	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l10t410r278b500],
107	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l10t410r278b500],
108	the	DT	O	the	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l313t405r440b483],
109	response	NN	O	response	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l469t430r842b505],
110	rate	NN	O	rate	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l870t421r1024b483],
111	Was	VBD	O	be	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1048t431r1207b484],
112	12.3	CD	PERCENT	12.3	dep	113	SENT_42	[p3l1241t410r1414b483],
113	percent	NN	PERCENT	percent	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1445t399r1862b505],
114	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1445t399r1862b505],

1	”	NN	O	”	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1445t399r1862b505],
2	These	DT	O	these	det	4	SENT_43	[p3l1888t405r2135b483],
3	promising	JJ	O	promising	amod	4	SENT_43	[p3l10t533r452b633],
4	rates	NNS	O	rate	nsubj	7	SENT_43	[p3l472t549r669b611],
5	are	VBP	O	be	cop	7	SENT_43	[p3l693t559r817b611],
6	perhaps	RB	O	perhaps	advmod	7	SENT_43	[p3l840t532r1174b633],
7	higher	JJR	O	higher	rcmod	1	SENT_43	[p3l1200t533r1475b633],
8	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1496t533r1682b611],
9	those	DT	O	those	det	10	SENT_43	[p3l1706t532r1930b611],
10	possible	JJ	O	possible	prep_than	7	SENT_43	[p3l1953t558r2134b633, p3l13t660r209b738],
11	With	IN	O	with	dep	1	SENT_43	[p3l238t660r430b739],
12	other	JJ	O	other	amod	13	SENT_43	[p3l464t660r692b738],
13	forms	NNS	O	form	pobj	11	SENT_43	[p3l722t659r975b738],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1010t659r1112b738],
15	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_of	13	SENT_43	[p3l1128t653r1874b760],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1128t653r1874b760],
17	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1128t653r1874b760],
18	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1128t653r1874b760],
19	°	CD	NUMBER	°	nsubj	25	SENT_43	[p3l1128t653r1874b760],
20	"	``	O	"	punct	19	SENT_43	[p3l1128t653r1874b760],
21	6	CD	NUMBER	6	dep	19	SENT_43	[p3l1128t653r1874b760],
22	but	CC	O	but	prep	19	SENT_43	[p3l1908t660r2050b739],
23	it	PRP	O	it	dep	22	SENT_43	[p3l2078t661r2139b738],
24	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	25	SENT_43	[p3l11t789r77b867],
25	unknown	JJ	O	unknown	ccomp	1	SENT_43	[p3l99t789r497b868],
26	Whether	IN	O	whether	complm	33	SENT_43	[p3l513t789r859b868],
27	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nsubj	33	SENT_43	[p3l876t805r1284b867],
28	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1294t789r1481b868],
29	an	DT	O	a	det	32	SENT_43	[p3l1501t814r1600b867],
30	EGFRinhib	NN	O	egfrinhib	nn	32	SENT_43	[p3l1619t788r2134b872],
31	—	NN	O	—	nn	32	SENT_43	[p3l1619t788r2134b872],
32	itor	NN	O	itor	prep_with	27	SENT_43	[p3l11t917r158b995],
33	prolongs	VBZ	O	prolong	ccomp	25	SENT_43	[p3l175t917r554b1017],
34	survival	NN	O	survival	dobj	33	SENT_43	[p3l581t917r921b996],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l581t917r921b996],

1	For	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l947t924r1092b995],
2	this	DT	O	this	det	3	SENT_44	[p3l1111t917r1263b995],
3	reason	NN	O	reason	prep_for	19	SENT_44	[p3l1288t942r1592b1012],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1288t942r1592b1012],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_44	[p3l1620t916r1749b995],
6	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	8	SENT_44	[p3l1769t917r2135b996],
7	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	8	SENT_44	[p3l11t1050r307b1123],
8	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	nsubj	19	SENT_44	[p3l345t1045r697b1124],
9	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l741t1044r841b1123],
10	Canada	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Canada	nn	12	SENT_44	[p3l865t1044r1181b1123],
11	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	amod	12	SENT_44	[p3l1222t1044r1543b1123],
12	Trials	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Trials	prep_of	8	SENT_44	[p3l1581t1045r1817b1123],
13	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	nn	17	SENT_44	[p3l1862t1050r2134b1145],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_44	[p3l16t1179r118b1264],
15	N	NNP	O	N	nn	17	SENT_44	[p3l16t1179r118b1264],
16	CIC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CIC	nn	17	SENT_44	[p3l122t1178r278b1251],
17	CTG	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CTG	dep	12	SENT_44	[p3l309t1178r533b1264],
18	)	NN	O	)	dep	17	SENT_44	[p3l309t1178r533b1264],
19	conducted	VBD	O	conduct	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l568t1172r1008b1252],
20	a	DT	O	a	det	23	SENT_44	[p3l1036t1199r1080b1251],
21	trial	NN	O	trial	nn	23	SENT_44	[p3l1108t1173r1274b1251],
22	(	NN	O	(	nn	23	SENT_44	[p3l1307t1178r1623b1264],
23	BR	NN	O	br	dobj	19	SENT_44	[p3l1307t1178r1623b1264],
24	.21	CD	NUMBER	.21	num	25	SENT_44	[p3l1307t1178r1623b1264],
25	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	27	SENT_44	[p3l1307t1178r1623b1264],
26	to	TO	O	to	aux	27	SENT_44	[p3l1658t1189r1737b1251],
27	compare	VB	O	compare	infmod	23	SENT_44	[p3l1768t1198r2135b1273],
28	erlotinib	NN	O	erlotinib	dobj	27	SENT_44	[p3l12t1300r370b1379],
29	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l397t1301r586b1380],
30	placebo	NN	O	placebo	prep_with	27	SENT_44	[p3l614t1300r941b1401],
31	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l972t1300r1165b1379],
32	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_44	[p3l1192t1301r1322b1379],
33	failure	NN	O	failure	prep_after	27	SENT_44	[p3l1352t1300r1621b1380],
34	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1651t1300r1752b1379],
35	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	36	SENT_44	[p3l1765t1300r2135b1379],
36	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_of	33	SENT_44	[p3l12t1429r619b1529],
37	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l639t1428r762b1507],
38	non	JJ	O	non	amod	44	SENT_44	[p3l784t1428r1416b1507],
39	—	JJ	O	—	amod	44	SENT_44	[p3l784t1428r1416b1507],
40	small	JJ	O	small	amod	44	SENT_44	[p3l784t1428r1416b1507],
41	—	NN	O	—	nn	44	SENT_44	[p3l784t1428r1416b1507],
42	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	44	SENT_44	[p3l784t1428r1416b1507],
43	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	44	SENT_44	[p3l1439t1429r1633b1529],
44	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_for	36	SENT_44	[p3l1655t1454r1946b1507],
45	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1655t1454r1946b1507],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_45	[p3l1974t1429r2134b1507],
2	inclusion	NN	O	inclusion	nsubjpass	10	SENT_45	[p3l11t1557r403b1636],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l430t1556r531b1635],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_45	[p3l538t1583r583b1635],
5	control	NN	O	control	nn	6	SENT_45	[p3l609t1557r911b1635],
6	group	NN	O	group	prep_of	2	SENT_45	[p3l938t1582r1189b1657],
7	receiving	VBG	O	receive	partmod	6	SENT_45	[p3l1217t1557r1599b1657],
8	placebo	NN	O	placebo	dobj	7	SENT_45	[p3l1622t1556r1948b1657],
9	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_45	[p3l1972t1583r2133b1636],
10	considered	VBN	O	consider	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l12t1684r468b1763],
11	ethical	JJ	O	ethical	acomp	10	SENT_45	[p3l489t1685r761b1763],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l781t1685r861b1762],
13	view	NN	O	view	prep_in	11	SENT_45	[p3l877t1685r1067b1764],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1085t1684r1185b1763],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_45	[p3l1187t1685r1314b1763],
16	lack	NN	O	lack	prep_of	13	SENT_45	[p3l1334t1684r1506b1764],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1522t1684r1622b1763],
18	beneﬁt	NN	O	beneﬁt	prep_of	16	SENT_45	[p3l1625t1684r1916b1763],
19	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1931t1684r2136b1763],
20	further	JJ	O	further	amod	21	SENT_45	[p3l11t1812r306b1892],
21	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_from	18	SENT_45	[p3l336t1813r942b1913],
22	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l968t1812r1161b1891],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_45	[p3l1190t1812r1319b1891],
24	failure	NN	O	failure	prep_after	21	SENT_45	[p3l1350t1812r1618b1892],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1650t1812r1751b1891],
26	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	29	SENT_45	[p3l1765t1812r2135b1891],
27	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nn	29	SENT_45	[p3l12t1934r553b2019],
28	.5	CD	NUMBER	.5	num	29	SENT_45	[p3l12t1934r553b2019],
29	’	NN	O	’	prep_of	24	SENT_45	[p3l12t1934r553b2019],
30	6	CD	NUMBER	6	tmod	11	SENT_45	[p3l12t1934r553b2019],

1	METHODS	NNS	O	method	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l790t2277r1340b2336],

1	STU	NNP	O	STU	nn	4	SENT_47	[p3l11t2454r156b2503],
2	M	NN	O	m	nn	4	SENT_47	[p3l177t2454r277b2503],
3	D	NN	O	d	nn	4	SENT_47	[p3l319t2454r366b2503],
4	ES	NN	O	e	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l383t2454r467b2503],
5	I	PRP	O	I	dep	6	SENT_47	[p3l485t2454r497b2503],
6	c	NN	O	c	dep	4	SENT_47	[p3l517t2454r564b2503],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l517t2454r564b2503],
8	N	NN	O	n	dep	6	SENT_47	[p3l586t2454r630b2503],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_48	[p3l7t2554r192b2633],
2	international	JJ	O	international	nsubjpass	48	SENT_48	[p3l229t2555r799b2650],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l229t2555r799b2650],
4	phase	NN	O	phase	appos	2	SENT_48	[p3l839t2554r1086b2655],
5	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	4	SENT_48	[p3l1123t2560r1193b2650],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1123t2560r1193b2650],
7	randomized	VBN	O	randomize	partmod	2	SENT_48	[p3l1235t2554r1770b2650],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1235t2554r1770b2650],
9	doubleblind	NN	O	doubleblind	nn	14	SENT_48	[p3l1812t2554r2134b2634, p3l11t2683r253b2778],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1812t2554r2134b2634, p3l11t2683r253b2778],
11	placebo	NN	O	placebo	dep	14	SENT_48	[p3l282t2682r1081b2783],
12	—	NN	O	—	nn	14	SENT_48	[p3l282t2682r1081b2783],
13	controlled	VBN	O	control	amod	14	SENT_48	[p3l282t2682r1081b2783],
14	trial	NN	O	trial	dobj	7	SENT_48	[p3l1106t2682r1273b2761],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1299t2682r1398b2761],
16	erlotinib	NN	O	erlotinib	prep_of	14	SENT_48	[p3l1406t2682r1764b2761],
17	after	IN	O	after	mark	38	SENT_48	[p3l1790t2682r1983b2761],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_48	[p3l2006t2682r2135b2761],
19	failure	NN	O	failure	nsubjpass	38	SENT_48	[p3l10t2810r282b2890],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l322t2810r423b2889],
21	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	nn	23	SENT_48	[p3l443t2810r814b2889],
22	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	23	SENT_48	[p3l443t2810r814b2889],
23	line	NN	O	line	prep_of	19	SENT_48	[p3l443t2810r814b2889],
24	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l854t2836r944b2889],
25	second	JJ	ORDINAL	second	amod	28	SENT_48	[p3l981t2810r1480b2889],
26	—	NN	O	—	nn	28	SENT_48	[p3l981t2810r1480b2889],
27	line	NN	O	line	nn	28	SENT_48	[p3l981t2810r1480b2889],
28	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nsubjpass	38	SENT_48	[p3l1519t2811r2139b2911],
29	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l10t2938r134b3017],
30	non	JJ	O	non	amod	36	SENT_48	[p3l154t2938r779b3017],
31	—	JJ	O	—	amod	36	SENT_48	[p3l154t2938r779b3017],
32	small	JJ	O	small	amod	36	SENT_48	[p3l154t2938r779b3017],
33	—	NN	O	—	nn	36	SENT_48	[p3l154t2938r779b3017],
34	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	36	SENT_48	[p3l154t2938r779b3017],
35	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	36	SENT_48	[p3l802t2939r994b3039],
36	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_for	28	SENT_48	[p3l1015t2964r1288b3017],
37	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	38	SENT_48	[p3l1304t2965r1464b3018],
38	designed	VBN	O	design	dep	14	SENT_48	[p3l1491t2938r1867b3039],
39	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1891t2938r1988b3039],
40	the	DT	O	the	det	45	SENT_48	[p3l2007t2939r2135b3017],
41	N	NN	O	n	nn	45	SENT_48	[p3l8t3074r83b3145],
42	CIC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CIC	nn	45	SENT_48	[p3l86t3072r244b3145],
43	CT	NNP	O	CT	nn	45	SENT_48	[p3l276t3072r400b3145],
44	G.	NNP	O	G.	nn	45	SENT_48	[p3l402t3072r498b3145],
45	Patients	NNPS	O	Patients	agent	38	SENT_48	[p3l531t3067r872b3145],
46	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	48	SENT_48	[p3l899t3093r1103b3146],
47	randomly	RB	O	randomly	advmod	48	SENT_48	[p3l1133t3067r1549b3167],
48	assigned	VBN	O	assign	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1573t3067r1952b3167],
49	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1980t3067r2063b3144],
50	a	DT	O	a	det	52	SENT_48	[p3l2091t3093r2135b3145],
51	2:1	CD	NUMBER	2:1	num	52	SENT_48	[p3l10t3200r138b3273],
52	ratio	NN	O	ratio	prep_in	48	SENT_48	[p3l162t3195r351b3273],
53	to	TO	O	to	aux	54	SENT_48	[p3l376t3211r454b3273],
54	receive	VB	O	receive	xcomp	48	SENT_48	[p3l478t3195r759b3274],
55	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	56	SENT_48	[p3l784t3194r943b3273],
56	erlotinib	NN	O	erlotinib	dobj	54	SENT_48	[p3l966t3194r1317b3273],
57	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1341t3211r1420b3273],
58	a	DT	O	a	det	59	SENT_48	[p3l1438t3221r1482b3273],
59	dose	NN	O	dose	prep_at	54	SENT_48	[p3l1505t3195r1695b3273],
60	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1720t3194r1819b3273],
61	150	CD	NUMBER	150	num	62	SENT_48	[p3l1828t3200r1976b3273],
62	mg	NN	O	mg	prep_of	59	SENT_48	[p3l2000t3221r2139b3295],
63	daily	JJ	SET	daily	amod	62	SENT_48	[p3l11t3323r217b3423],
64	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l247t3348r338b3401],
65	placebo	NN	O	placebo	prep_of	59	SENT_48	[p3l366t3322r729b3423],
66	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l366t3322r729b3423],

1	Randomization	NN	O	randomization	nsubjpass	3	SENT_49	[p3l767t3323r1444b3406],
2	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_49	[p3l1473t3349r1637b3402],
3	performed	VBN	O	perform	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1671t3322r2134b3423],
4	centrally	RB	O	centrally	amod	11	SENT_49	[p3l11t3450r381b3551],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l411t3451r508b3551],
6	Applied	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Applied	nn	10	SENT_49	[p3l534t3450r872b3551],
7	Logic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Logic	nn	10	SENT_49	[p3l904t3451r1140b3551],
8	Associates	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Associates	nn	10	SENT_49	[p3l1170t3451r1622b3529],
9	(	NNP	O	(	nn	10	SENT_49	[p3l1662t3458r2129b3546],
10	Houston	NNP	LOCATION	Houston	prep_by	4	SENT_49	[p3l1662t3458r2129b3546],
11	)	NN	O	)	dobj	3	SENT_49	[p3l1662t3458r2129b3546],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1662t3458r2129b3546],
13	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l6t3579r195b3658],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_49	[p3l240t3579r369b3657],
15	use	NN	O	use	prep_with	3	SENT_49	[p3l415t3605r553b3658],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l599t3578r700b3657],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_49	[p3l727t3579r855b3657],
18	minimization	NN	O	minimization	nn	19	SENT_49	[p3l901t3580r1477b3657],
19	method	NN	O	method	prep_of	15	SENT_49	[p3l1522t3573r1957b3657],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1522t3573r1957b3657],

1	”	NN	O	”	nn	2	SENT_50	[p3l1522t3573r1957b3657],
2	Patients	NNS	O	patient	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l2002t3586r2133b3657, p3l11t3707r240b3785],

1	Were	VBD	O	be	cop	2	SENT_51	[p3l275t3733r477b3786],
2	stratiﬁed	JJ	O	stratiﬁed	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l516t3706r890b3785],
3	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l926t3706r1348b3807],
4	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	2	SENT_51	[p3l1383t3723r1462b3785],
5	center	NN	O	center	pobj	2	SENT_51	[p3l1500t3723r1777b3802],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l1500t3723r1777b3802],
7	Eastern	NNP	MISC	Eastern	appos	5	SENT_51	[p3l1819t3714r2135b3785],

1	Cooperative	NNP	O	Cooperative	nn	5	SENT_52	[p4l10t21r513b121],
2	Oncology	NNP	O	Oncology	nn	5	SENT_52	[p4l551t20r961b121],
3	Group	NNP	O	Group	nn	5	SENT_52	[p4l994t26r1267b121],
4	performance	NN	O	performance	nn	5	SENT_52	[p4l1304t20r1847b121],
5	status	NN	O	status	nsubj	28	SENT_52	[p4l1887t37r2133b100],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_52	[p4l15t154r92b240],
7	o	NN	O	o	dep	5	SENT_52	[p4l15t154r92b240],
8	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l137t174r226b227],
9	1	CD	NUMBER	1	conj_or	5	SENT_52	[p4l270t154r314b226],
10	vs.	CC	O	vs.	prep	9	SENT_52	[p4l353t175r463b228],
11	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	10	SENT_52	[p4l511t154r558b226],
12	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l603t174r693b227],
13	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	10	SENT_52	[p4l734t154r805b244],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l734t154r805b244],
15	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l849t148r1038b228],
16	higher	JJR	O	higher	amod	17	SENT_52	[p4l1082t149r1360b249],
17	scores	NNS	O	score	prep_with	28	SENT_52	[p4l1402t174r1663b227],
18	indicating	VBG	O	indicate	partmod	17	SENT_52	[p4l1708t149r2138b249],
19	greater	JJR	O	greater	amod	21	SENT_52	[p4l10t293r307b377],
20	impairment	NN	O	impairment	nn	21	SENT_52	[p4l334t277r893b377],
21	)	NN	O	)	dobj	18	SENT_52	[p4l334t277r893b377],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l334t277r893b377],
23	best	JJS	O	best	amod	24	SENT_52	[p4l929t277r1104b355],
24	response	NN	O	response	nsubj	28	SENT_52	[p4l1128t302r1508b377],
25	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l1539t293r1617b355],
26	prior	JJ	O	prior	amod	27	SENT_52	[p4l1647t277r1860b377],
27	therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_to	24	SENT_52	[p4l1887t277r2134b355, p4l9t431r108b505],
28	(	VBD	O	(	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l139t405r557b505],
29	complete	JJ	O	complete	amod	32	SENT_52	[p4l139t405r557b505],
30	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l588t430r677b483],
31	partial	JJ	O	partial	amod	32	SENT_52	[p4l703t404r974b505],
32	response	NN	O	response	nsubj	45	SENT_52	[p4l1003t430r1382b505],
33	vs.	CC	O	vs.	prep	32	SENT_52	[p4l1408t431r1517b484],
34	stable	JJ	O	stable	amod	35	SENT_52	[p4l1554t404r1801b483],
35	disease	NN	O	disease	dep	33	SENT_52	[p4l1832t404r2135b483],
36	vs.	CC	O	vs.	prep	35	SENT_52	[p4l6t559r115b612],
37	progressive	JJ	O	progressive	amod	39	SENT_52	[p4l143t533r628b633],
38	disease	NN	O	disease	nn	39	SENT_52	[p4l653t532r1015b628],
39	)	NN	O	)	dep	36	SENT_52	[p4l653t532r1015b628],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l653t532r1015b628],
41	number	NN	O	number	appos	39	SENT_52	[p4l1044t533r1380b612],
42	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l1402t532r1503b611],
43	prior	JJ	O	prior	amod	44	SENT_52	[p4l1507t533r1719b633],
44	regimens	NNS	O	regimen	prep_of	41	SENT_52	[p4l1740t533r2133b633],
45	received	VBD	O	receive	ccomp	28	SENT_52	[p4l10t660r352b740],
46	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	47	SENT_52	[p4l384t667r567b752],
47	one	CD	NUMBER	one	dobj	45	SENT_52	[p4l384t667r567b752],
48	vs.	IN	O	vs.	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l590t687r700b740],
49	two	CD	NUMBER	two	number	50	SENT_52	[p4l734t667r945b756],
50	)	CD	NUMBER	)	prep_vs.	47	SENT_52	[p4l734t667r945b756],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l734t667r945b756],
52	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l979t660r1134b739],
53	exposure	NN	O	exposure	prep_vs.	47	SENT_52	[p4l1163t686r1542b761],
54	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l1571t677r1650b739],
55	prior	JJ	O	prior	amod	57	SENT_52	[p4l1678t661r1890b761],
56	platinum	NN	O	platinum	nn	57	SENT_52	[p4l1914t661r2134b761, p4l10t814r205b868],
57	therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_to	53	SENT_52	[p4l230t789r548b889],
58	(	CD	NUMBER	(	tmod	28	SENT_52	[p4l573t796r728b889],
59	yes	UH	O	yes	dobj	28	SENT_52	[p4l573t796r728b889],
60	vs.	CC	O	vs.	prep	28	SENT_52	[p4l750t815r859b868],
61	no	DT	O	no	det	62	SENT_52	[p4l890t796r1055b880],
62	)	NN	O	)	dep	60	SENT_52	[p4l890t796r1055b880],
63	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l890t796r1055b880],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_53	[p4l136t916r299b995],
2	primary	JJ	O	primary	amod	4	SENT_53	[p4l350t917r694b1017],
3	end	NN	O	end	nn	4	SENT_53	[p4l741t916r897b995],
4	point	NN	O	point	nsubj	7	SENT_53	[p4l948t917r1180b1017],
5	was	VBD	O	be	cop	7	SENT_53	[p4l1223t943r1386b996],
6	overall	JJ	O	overall	amod	7	SENT_53	[p4l1441t916r1726b996],
7	survival	NN	O	survival	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l1779t916r2128b996],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l1779t916r2128b996],

1	Secondary	JJ	O	secondary	amod	3	SENT_54	[p4l12t1044r456b1145],
2	end	NN	O	end	nn	3	SENT_54	[p4l493t1045r649b1123],
3	points	NNS	O	point	nsubj	4	SENT_54	[p4l687t1045r958b1145],
4	included	VBD	O	include	ccomp	13	SENT_54	[p4l1000t1044r1373b1124],
5	progression	NN	O	progression	npadvmod	7	SENT_54	[p4l1412t1044r2134b1145],
6	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	5	SENT_54	[p4l1412t1044r2134b1145],
7	free	JJ	O	free	amod	8	SENT_54	[p4l1412t1044r2134b1145],
8	survival	NN	O	survival	dobj	4	SENT_54	[p4l12t1173r361b1268],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l12t1173r361b1268],
10	overall	JJ	O	overall	amod	12	SENT_54	[p4l397t1173r681b1252],
11	response	NN	O	response	nn	12	SENT_54	[p4l709t1198r1096b1273],
12	rate	NN	O	rate	nsubj	13	SENT_54	[p4l1125t1189r1285b1251],
13	(	VBD	O	(	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1319t1172r1745b1273],
14	complete	JJ	O	complete	amod	17	SENT_54	[p4l1319t1172r1745b1273],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1774t1173r1932b1251],
16	partial	JJ	O	partial	conj_and	14	SENT_54	[p4l1959t1199r2133b1273, p4l11t1301r201b1396],
17	)	NN	O	)	dobj	13	SENT_54	[p4l1959t1199r2133b1273, p4l11t1301r201b1396],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1959t1199r2133b1273, p4l11t1301r201b1396],
19	duration	NN	O	duration	conj_and	17	SENT_54	[p4l231t1301r599b1380],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l624t1300r725b1379],
21	response	NN	O	response	prep_of	19	SENT_54	[p4l731t1326r1142b1401],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l731t1326r1142b1401],
23	toxic	JJ	O	toxic	amod	24	SENT_54	[p4l1172t1301r1377b1379],
24	effects	NNS	O	effect	appos	21	SENT_54	[p4l1401t1300r1704b1396],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1401t1300r1704b1396],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1733t1301r1891b1379],
27	quality	NN	O	quality	dobj	13	SENT_54	[p4l1916t1300r2133b1401, p4l10t1429r112b1529],
28	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l134t1428r235b1507],
29	life	NN	O	life	prep_of	27	SENT_54	[p4l242t1428r396b1507],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l242t1428r396b1507],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_57	[p4l1661t2202r2130b2295],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p4l1661t2202r2130b2295],

1	C30	NN	O	c30	nn	2	SENT_58	[p4l1661t2202r2130b2295],
2	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1661t2202r2130b2295],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l10t2324r165b2403],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_58	[p4l211t2325r340b2403],
5	quality	NN	O	quality	nn	6	SENT_58	[p4l388t2324r960b2425],
6	—	NN	O	—	conj_and	2	SENT_58	[p4l388t2324r960b2425],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l388t2324r960b2425],
8	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	10	SENT_58	[p4l388t2324r960b2425],
9	life	NN	O	life	nn	10	SENT_58	[p4l388t2324r960b2425],
10	questionnaire	NN	O	questionnaire	prep_of	6	SENT_58	[p4l1007t2325r1587b2425],
11	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1633t2324r1757b2403],
12	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_for	10	SENT_58	[p4l1798t2325r2133b2425],
13	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l6t2453r198b2532],
14	lung	NN	O	lung	prep_with	12	SENT_58	[p4l225t2452r423b2553],
15	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	2	SENT_58	[p4l448t2478r729b2531],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_58	[p4l759t2458r1140b2551],
17	QLQ	NN	O	qlq	dep	15	SENT_58	[p4l759t2458r1140b2551],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l759t2458r1140b2551],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l759t2458r1140b2551],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l759t2458r1140b2551],

1	LC	NN	O	lc	nsubjpass	5	SENT_60	[p4l759t2458r1140b2551],
2	13	CD	NUMBER	13	num	3	SENT_60	[p4l1153t2458r1281b2544],
3	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_60	[p4l1153t2458r1281b2544],
4	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_60	[p4l1310t2479r1516b2532],
5	used	VBN	O	use	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l1544t2452r1743b2532],
6	to	TO	O	to	aux	7	SENT_60	[p4l1771t2469r1851b2531],
7	evaluate	VB	O	evaluate	xcomp	5	SENT_60	[p4l1881t2453r2132b2532, p4l10t2597r131b2659],
8	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	10	SENT_60	[p4l158t2581r519b2681],
9	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	10	SENT_60	[p4l158t2581r519b2681],
10	quality	NN	O	quality	xcomp	7	SENT_60	[p4l549t2581r835b2681],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l856t2580r957b2659],
12	life	NN	O	life	prep_of	10	SENT_60	[p4l962t2580r1116b2659],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l962t2580r1116b2659],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_61	[p4l136t2708r299b2787],
2	protocol	NN	O	protocol	nsubjpass	4	SENT_61	[p4l322t2709r686b2809],
3	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_61	[p4l705t2735r868b2788],
4	approved	VBN	O	approve	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l892t2709r1291b2809],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l1314t2708r1412b2809],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_61	[p4l1432t2709r1562b2787],
7	ethics	NNS	O	ethic	agent	4	SENT_61	[p4l1587t2709r1836b2787],
8	review	VBP	O	review	rcmod	7	SENT_61	[p4l1860t2709r2138b2788],
9	boards	NNS	O	board	dobj	8	SENT_61	[p4l11t2836r302b2915],
10	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l336t2853r415b2915],
11	all	DT	O	all	det	13	SENT_61	[p4l441t2836r540b2915],
12	participating	VBG	O	participate	amod	13	SENT_61	[p4l570t2837r1116b2937],
13	institutions	NNS	O	institution	prep_at	9	SENT_61	[p4l1143t2837r1650b2932],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l1143t2837r1650b2932],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l1687t2837r1842b2915],
16	all	DT	O	all	det	17	SENT_61	[p4l1873t2836r1971b2915],
17	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	18	SENT_61	[p4l2001t2863r2134b2937, p4l11t2965r240b3043],
18	provided	VBD	O	provide	conj_and	4	SENT_61	[p4l268t2964r639b3065],
19	written	VBN	O	write	amod	21	SENT_61	[p4l661t2965r965b3044],
20	informed	VBN	O	inform	amod	21	SENT_61	[p4l990t2964r1385b3043],
21	consent	NN	O	consent	dobj	18	SENT_61	[p4l1412t2981r1765b3043],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l1412t2981r1765b3043],

1	Support	NN	O	support	nsubjpass	3	SENT_62	[p4l1800t2970r2140b3065],
2	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_62	[p4l6t3119r170b3172],
3	provided	VBN	O	provide	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l202t3092r584b3193],
4	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l616t3093r714b3193],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_62	[p4l741t3092r873b3171],
6	N	NN	O	n	nn	7	SENT_62	[p4l902t3100r977b3171],
7	CIC	NN	ORGANIZATION	cic	agent	3	SENT_62	[p4l982t3098r1140b3171],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l1173t3093r1332b3171],
9	OSI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	OSI	nn	10	SENT_62	[p4l1363t3098r1521b3171],
10	Pharmaceuticals	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceuticals	agent	3	SENT_62	[p4l1550t3093r2131b3172, p4l11t3221r197b3299],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l1550t3093r2131b3172, p4l11t3221r197b3299],

1	Data	NNS	O	datum	nsubjpass	3	SENT_63	[p4l242t3227r440b3299],
2	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_63	[p4l470t3247r669b3300],
3	collected	VBN	O	collect	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l706t3221r1095b3316],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l706t3221r1095b3316],
5	managed	VBD	O	manage	dep	3	SENT_63	[p4l1137t3220r1544b3321],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l1137t3220r1544b3321],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l1585t3220r1739b3299],
8	analyzed	VBN	O	analyze	dep	3	SENT_63	[p4l1775t3220r2135b3321],
9	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l11t3349r107b3449],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_63	[p4l124t3348r251b3427],
11	N	NN	O	n	prep_by	8	SENT_63	[p4l270t3356r346b3428],
12	CIC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CIC	nn	13	SENT_63	[p4l350t3354r508b3427],
13	CTG	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CTG	nsubj	5	SENT_63	[p4l535t3354r757b3444],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l535t3354r757b3444],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l787t3349r944b3427],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_63	[p4l970t3349r1100b3427],
17	manuscript	NN	O	manuscript	nsubjpass	19	SENT_63	[p4l1126t3349r1623b3449],
18	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	19	SENT_63	[p4l1638t3375r1801b3428],
19	written	VBN	O	write	conj_and	3	SENT_63	[p4l1824t3349r2134b3428],
20	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l11t3477r109b3577],
21	members	NNS	O	member	agent	19	SENT_63	[p4l140t3477r541b3555],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l578t3476r678b3555],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_63	[p4l694t3476r823b3555],
24	NCIC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	NCIC	nn	25	SENT_63	[p4l855t3482r1089b3555],
25	CTG	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CTG	prep_of	21	SENT_63	[p4l1124t3482r1343b3555],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l1124t3482r1343b3555],

1	OSI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	OSI	nn	2	SENT_64	[p4l1383t3482r1538b3555],
2	Pharmaceuticals	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceuticals	nsubj	8	SENT_64	[p4l1569t3477r2134b3556, p4l11t3604r166b3683],
3	reviewed	VBD	O	review	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l214t3604r583b3684],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_64	[p4l629t3605r758b3683],
5	ﬁnal	JJ	O	ﬁnal	amod	6	SENT_64	[p4l803t3604r992b3683],
6	manuscript	NN	O	manuscript	dobj	3	SENT_64	[p4l1037t3605r1525b3705],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1564t3604r1720b3683],
8	provided	VBN	O	provide	conj_and	3	SENT_64	[p4l1763t3604r2135b3705],
9	comments	NNS	O	comment	dobj	8	SENT_64	[p5l11t37r452b99],
10	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_64	[p5l481t46r586b99],
11	it	PRP	O	it	prep_on	8	SENT_64	[p5l611t21r687b99],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p5l611t21r687b99],

1	Conﬁdentiality	NN	O	conﬁdentiality	nsubjpass	3	SENT_65	[p5l719t20r1339b121],
2	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_65	[p5l1356t47r1516b100],
3	maintained	VBN	O	maintain	_	0	SENT_65	[p5l1543t20r2018b99],
4	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_65	[p5l2044t21r2140b121],
5	both	CC	O	both	preconj	9	SENT_65	[p5l11t149r201b227],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_65	[p5l232t149r359b227],
7	N	NN	O	n	nn	9	SENT_65	[p5l387t156r462b228],
8	CIC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CIC	nn	9	SENT_65	[p5l464t154r618b227],
9	CTG	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CTG	agent	3	SENT_65	[p5l650t154r843b227],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_65	[p5l874t148r1028b227],
11	OSI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	OSI	nn	12	SENT_65	[p5l1057t154r1211b227],
12	Pharmaceuticals	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceuticals	conj_and	9	SENT_65	[p5l1238t149r1944b228],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p5l1238t149r1944b228],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_66	[p5l1976t149r2135b227],
2	study	NN	O	study	nn	3	SENT_66	[p5l12t276r234b377],
3	chair	NN	O	chair	nsubj	16	SENT_66	[p5l251t277r476b372],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l251t277r476b372],
5	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	6	SENT_66	[p5l501t283r624b355],
6	Shepherd	NNP	PERSON	Shepherd	nsubj	16	SENT_66	[p5l654t276r1072b377],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l654t276r1072b377],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1097t276r1252b355],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_66	[p5l1273t277r1401b355],
10	physician	NN	O	physician	nn	11	SENT_66	[p5l1421t277r1815b377],
11	coordinator	NN	O	coordinator	conj_and	3	SENT_66	[p5l1838t277r2134b355, p5l10t421r248b500],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1838t277r2134b355, p5l10t421r248b500],
13	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	14	SENT_66	[p5l275t411r401b483],
14	Seymour	NNP	PERSON	Seymour	appos	3	SENT_66	[p5l435t410r830b505],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l435t410r830b505],
16	reviewed	VBN	O	review	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l862t405r1240b484],
17	all	PDT	O	all	predet	19	SENT_66	[p5l1265t405r1366b483],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_66	[p5l1393t405r1525b483],
19	data	NNS	O	datum	dobj	16	SENT_66	[p5l1553t405r1735b483],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1759t404r1917b483],
21	confirmed	VBD	O	confirm	conj_and	16	SENT_66	[p5l1945t430r2133b483, p5l10t532r298b611],
22	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	23	SENT_66	[p5l325t533r527b611],
23	completeness	NN	O	completeness	dobj	21	SENT_66	[p5l552t533r1130b633],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1157t532r1313b611],
25	accuracy	NN	O	accuracy	conj_and	23	SENT_66	[p5l1337t559r1712b633],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1337t559r1712b633],

1	124	CD	NUMBER	124	num	3	SENT_67	[p5l149t708r205b729],
2	N	NN	O	n	nn	3	SENT_67	[p5l918t710r932b725],
3	ENGLJ	NN	O	englj	nsubj	4	SENT_67	[p5l947t709r1031b731],
4	MED	VBD	O	med	_	0	SENT_67	[p5l1046t710r1099b725],
5	35	CD	NUMBER	35	number	6	SENT_67	[p5l1111t709r1136b731],
6	:2	CD	NUMBER	:2	dobj	4	SENT_67	[p5l1155t709r1175b729],
7	WWW.NEjM.ORG	NNP	O	WWW.NEjM.ORG	nn	8	SENT_67	[p5l1210t709r1421b731],
8	JULY	NNP	DATE	JULY	dep	6	SENT_67	[p5l1455t710r1515b731],
9	14	CD	DATE	14	num	8	SENT_67	[p5l1527t709r1562b731],
10	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p5l1527t709r1562b731],
11	2005	CD	DATE	2005	num	8	SENT_67	[p5l1575t709r1638b731],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_68	[p5l935t742r986b766],
2	New	NNP	O	New	nn	4	SENT_68	[p5l995t743r1057b766],
3	Englan	NNP	O	Englan	nn	4	SENT_68	[p5l1066t742r1160b773],
4	oumal	NN	O	oumal	_	0	SENT_68	[p5l1200t742r1283b766],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_68	[p5l1293t742r1322b766],
6	Medicine	NN	MISC	medicine	prep_of	4	SENT_68	[p5l1329t742r1454b766],

1	ERLOTINIB	NNP	O	ERLOTINIB	nsubj	4	SENT_69	[p5l480t930r667b949],
2	IN	IN	O	in	prep	1	SENT_69	[p5l682t930r720b949],
3	PREVIOUSLY	RB	DATE	previously	pcomp	2	SENT_69	[p5l736t930r941b949],
4	TREATED	VBN	O	treat	_	0	SENT_69	[p5l952t930r1103b949],
5	NON	NN	O	non	dobj	4	SENT_69	[p5l1118t930r1422b949],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p5l1118t930r1422b949],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_70	[p5l1118t930r1422b949],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p5l1118t930r1422b949],

1	SMALL-CELL	NN	O	small-cell	nn	2	SENT_71	[p5l1118t930r1422b949],
2	LUNG	NN	O	lung	_	0	SENT_71	[p5l1436t930r1530b949],
3	CANCER	NNP	O	CANCER	dep	2	SENT_71	[p5l1544t930r1680b949],
