1	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	nsubj	2	SENT_1	[p1l53t81r153b106],
2	Causes	VBZ	O	cause	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l165t81r263b106],
3	Control	NN	O	control	dobj	2	SENT_1	[p1l277t81r383b106],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	9	SENT_1	[p1l397t81r488b112],
5	2009	CD	DATE	2009	dep	4	SENT_1	[p1l397t81r488b112],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	9	SENT_1	[p1l397t81r488b112],
7	20	CD	NUMBER	20	num	9	SENT_1	[p1l503t81r669b106],
8	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l503t81r669b106],
9	l2l-127	CD	NUMBER	l2l-127	dep	13	SENT_1	[p1l503t81r669b106],
10	DOI	NNP	O	DOI	dep	9	SENT_1	[p1l52t124r114b150],
11	10.1007	CD	NUMBER	10.1007	num	10	SENT_1	[p1l130t124r528b150],
12	/	:	O	/	punct	13	SENT_1	[p1l130t124r528b150],
13	s10552-008-9226-6	CD	NUMBER	s10552-008-9226-6	dep	2	SENT_1	[p1l130t124r528b150],

1	Coffee	NNP	O	Coffee	nn	2	SENT_2	[p1l55t342r235b390],
2	consumption	NN	O	consumption	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l254t342r632b402],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l254t342r632b402],
4	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	5	SENT_2	[p1l652t342r849b402],
5	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	appos	2	SENT_2	[p1l867t342r1238b402],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1256t343r1361b389],
7	bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	9	SENT_2	[p1l1379t343r1598b389],
8	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	9	SENT_2	[p1l1617t356r1803b389],
9	risk	NN	O	risk	appos	2	SENT_2	[p1l1822t342r1930b389],

1	Cristina	NNP	PERSON	Cristina	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l54t477r197b507],
2	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	3	SENT_3	[p1l212t478r260b507],
3	Villanueva	NNP	PERSON	Villanueva	dep	1	SENT_3	[p1l275t477r467b507],
4	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l482t488r489b495],
5	Debra	NNP	PERSON	Debra	nn	7	SENT_3	[p1l504t478r614b507],
6	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	nn	7	SENT_3	[p1l630t478r665b507],
7	Silverman	NNP	PERSON	Silverman	dep	1	SENT_3	[p1l682t477r863b507],
8	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l878t488r886b495],
9	Cristiane	NNP	PERSON	Cristiane	nn	12	SENT_3	[p1l902t477r1064b507],
10	Murta-Nascimento	NNP	PERSON	Murta-Nascimento	nn	12	SENT_3	[p1l1079t477r1415b507],
11	Nliria	NNP	PERSON	Nliria	nn	12	SENT_3	[p1l1431t488r1438b495, p1l52t527r156b559],
12	Malats	NNP	PERSON	Malats	dep	7	SENT_3	[p1l170t529r291b559],
13	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l307t540r315b547],
14	Montserrat	NNP	LOCATION	Montserrat	nn	15	SENT_3	[p1l330t529r533b559],
15	Garcia-Closas	NNP	O	Garcia-Closas	dep	12	SENT_3	[p1l548t529r798b559],
16	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l814t540r821b547],
17	Francesc	NNP	PERSON	Francesc	nn	18	SENT_3	[p1l836t529r995b559],
18	Castro	NNP	PERSON	Castro	dep	7	SENT_3	[p1l1011t529r1129b559],
19	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1145t540r1152b547],
20	Adonina	NNP	PERSON	Adonina	nn	21	SENT_3	[p1l1167t529r1318b559],
21	Tardon	NNP	PERSON	Tardon	dep	1	SENT_3	[p1l1333t529r1466b559],
22	Reina	NNP	PERSON	Reina	nn	23	SENT_3	[p1l1481t540r1489b547, p1l53t581r155b611],
23	Garcia-Closas	NNP	PERSON	Garcia-Closas	dep	21	SENT_3	[p1l171t581r421b611],
24	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l437t592r444b599],
25	Consol	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Consol	nn	26	SENT_3	[p1l461t581r580b611],
26	Serra	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Serra	dep	21	SENT_3	[p1l596t581r694b611],
27	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l709t592r717b599],
28	Alfredo	NNP	PERSON	Alfredo	nn	29	SENT_3	[p1l732t581r867b611],
29	Carrato	NNP	PERSON	Carrato	dep	26	SENT_3	[p1l884t581r1024b611],
30	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1040t592r1048b599],
31	Nathaniel	NNP	PERSON	Nathaniel	nn	32	SENT_3	[p1l1063t581r1235b611],
32	Rothman	NNP	PERSON	Rothman	dep	21	SENT_3	[p1l1250t581r1415b611],
33	Francisco	NNP	PERSON	Francisco	nn	35	SENT_3	[p1l1430t592r1437b599, p1l52t633r225b663],
34	X.	NNP	PERSON	X.	nn	35	SENT_3	[p1l240t633r278b663],
35	Real	NNP	PERSON	Real	dep	32	SENT_3	[p1l295t633r374b663],
36	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l390t644r397b651],
37	Mustafa	NNP	PERSON	Mustafa	nn	38	SENT_3	[p1l412t633r559b663],
38	Dosemeci	NNP	PERSON	Dosemeci	dep	32	SENT_3	[p1l573t633r741b663],
39	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l757t644r764b651],
40	Manolis	NNP	PERSON	Manolis	nn	41	SENT_3	[p1l779t633r922b663],
41	Kogevinas	NNP	PERSON	Kogevinas	dep	38	SENT_3	[p1l937t633r1121b671],

1	Received	VBN	O	receive	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l52t746r191b771],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l52t746r191b771],
3	30	CD	DATE	30	num	4	SENT_4	[p1l207t746r240b771],
4	May	NNP	DATE	May	dobj	1	SENT_4	[p1l253t747r317b778],
5	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	4	SENT_4	[p1l330t746r416b771],
6	/	:	O	/	punct	7	SENT_4	[p1l330t746r416b771],
7	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	dep	4	SENT_4	[p1l422t746r562b778],
8	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l422t746r562b778],
9	2	CD	DATE	2	num	10	SENT_4	[p1l578t746r594b770],
10	September	NNP	DATE	September	dep	7	SENT_4	[p1l608t746r758b778],
11	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	10	SENT_4	[p1l771t746r856b771],
12	/	:	O	/	punct	7	SENT_4	[p1l771t746r856b771],
13	Published	VBN	O	publish	partmod	4	SENT_4	[p1l862t746r1001b771],
14	online	NN	O	online	prep	13	SENT_4	[p1l1014t746r1109b771],
15	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1014t746r1109b771],
16	17	CD	DATE	17	num	17	SENT_4	[p1l1127t746r1157b771],
17	September	NNP	DATE	September	dep	4	SENT_4	[p1l1172t746r1322b778],
18	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	17	SENT_4	[p1l1335t746r1403b771],
19	©	NNP	O	©	nn	21	SENT_4	[p1l13t798r66b851],
20	Springer	NNP	O	Springer	nn	21	SENT_4	[p1l98t798r358b867],
21	Science	NNP	O	Science	dep	17	SENT_4	[p1l386t798r932b851],
22	+	CC	O	+	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l386t798r932b851],
23	Business	NNP	O	Business	nn	25	SENT_4	[p1l386t798r932b851],
24	Media	NNP	O	Media	nn	25	SENT_4	[p1l961t798r1155b851],
25	B.V.	NNP	O	B.V.	dep	17	SENT_4	[p1l1182t799r1320b851],
26	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	25	SENT_4	[p1l1352t798r1499b851],

1	Abstract	JJ	O	abstract	amod	2	SENT_5	[p1l10t1029r343b1093],
2	Objective	NN	O	objective	nsubj	22	SENT_5	[p1l14t1142r353b1222],
3	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	4	SENT_5	[p1l445t1144r569b1205],
4	evaluated	VBD	O	evaluate	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l612t1142r955b1205],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_5	[p1l996t1142r1103b1205],
6	bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	8	SENT_5	[p1l1144t1142r1415b1205],
7	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	8	SENT_5	[p1l1456t1162r1690b1205],
8	risk	NN	O	risk	dobj	4	SENT_5	[p1l1729t1142r1864b1205],
9	associated	VBN	O	associate	partmod	8	SENT_5	[p1l1905t1142r2148b1205, p1l12t1253r159b1316],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l200t1253r357b1316],
11	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nn	12	SENT_5	[p1l399t1253r620b1316],
12	consumption	NN	O	consumption	prep_with	9	SENT_5	[p1l664t1253r1126b1334],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1167t1253r1235b1315],
14	a	DT	O	a	det	18	SENT_5	[p1l1278t1273r1315b1316],
15	case	NN	O	case	nn	18	SENT_5	[p1l1356t1253r1807b1316],
16	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	18	SENT_5	[p1l1356t1253r1807b1316],
17	control	NN	O	control	nn	18	SENT_5	[p1l1356t1253r1807b1316],
18	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	9	SENT_5	[p1l1853t1253r2041b1334],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l2083t1253r2151b1315],
20	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	prep_in	18	SENT_5	[p1l13t1364r212b1445],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l242t1364r369b1427],
22	examined	VBD	O	examine	conj_and	4	SENT_5	[p1l396t1364r744b1427],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_5	[p1l771t1364r878b1427],
24	gene	NN	O	gene	nsubj	27	SENT_5	[p1l907t1364r1576b1445],
25	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	27	SENT_5	[p1l907t1364r1576b1445],
26	enVironment	NN	O	environment	nn	27	SENT_5	[p1l907t1364r1576b1445],
27	interactions	NNS	O	interaction	xcomp	22	SENT_5	[p1l1602t1364r2019b1427],
28	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l2049t1364r2153b1427],
29	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	30	SENT_5	[p1l11t1475r266b1556],
30	Variants	NNS	O	variant	prep_for	27	SENT_5	[p1l302t1475r583b1538],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l618t1475r695b1537],
32	caffeine-metabolizing	JJ	O	caffeine-metabolizing	amod	33	SENT_5	[p1l722t1475r1510b1556],
33	enzymes	NNS	O	enzyme	prep_of	30	SENT_5	[p1l1545t1494r1875b1556],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1545t1494r1875b1556],

1	Methods	NNS	O	method	nsubj	4	SENT_6	[p1l7t1585r317b1647],
2	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_6	[p1l410t1585r547b1647],
3	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	dep	1	SENT_6	[p1l576t1585r875b1666],
4	included	VBD	O	include	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l903t1584r1212b1647],
5	1,136	CD	NUMBER	1,136	num	7	SENT_6	[p1l1247t1584r1436b1659],
6	incident	NN	O	incident	nn	7	SENT_6	[p1l1465t1585r1754b1647],
7	cases	NNS	O	case	dobj	4	SENT_6	[p1l1780t1604r1964b1647],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1994t1585r2151b1647],
9	urothelial	JJ	O	urothelial	amod	10	SENT_6	[p1l10t1695r354b1758],
10	carcinoma	NN	O	carcinoma	prep_with	4	SENT_6	[p1l411t1696r785b1758],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l840t1695r917b1758],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_6	[p1l967t1696r1074b1758],
13	urinary	JJ	O	urinary	amod	14	SENT_6	[p1l1130t1696r1387b1777],
14	bladder	NN	O	bladder	prep_of	10	SENT_6	[p1l1443t1696r1714b1758],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1770t1696r1896b1758],
16	1,138	CD	NUMBER	1,138	num	17	SENT_6	[p1l1960t1696r2148b1770],
17	controls	NNS	O	control	prep_of	10	SENT_6	[p1l11t1808r316b1871],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l11t1808r316b1871],

1	Odds	NNS	O	odds	nn	2	SENT_7	[p1l362t1808r545b1871],
2	ratios	NNS	O	ratio	nsubj	11	SENT_7	[p1l586t1808r782b1871],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_7	[p1l827t1808r1003b1885],
4	OR	NN	O	or	nn	5	SENT_7	[p1l827t1808r1003b1885],
5	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_7	[p1l827t1808r1003b1885],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1047t1808r1174b1871],
7	95	CD	PERCENT	95	number	8	SENT_7	[p1l1214t1808r1371b1872],
8	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	10	SENT_7	[p1l1214t1808r1371b1872],
9	conﬁdence	NN	O	conﬁdence	nn	10	SENT_7	[p1l1416t1808r1802b1871],
10	intervals	NNS	O	interval	conj_and	2	SENT_7	[p1l1843t1808r2149b1871],
11	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l13t1920r154b1997],
12	CI	NN	O	ci	nn	13	SENT_7	[p1l13t1920r154b1997],
13	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	15	SENT_7	[p1l13t1920r154b1997],
14	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	15	SENT_7	[p1l194t1940r365b1983],
15	adjusted	VBN	O	adjust	ccomp	11	SENT_7	[p1l403t1920r700b2001],
16	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l735t1920r839b1983],
17	area	NN	O	area	prep_for	15	SENT_7	[p1l875t1940r1040b1994],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l875t1940r1040b1994],
19	age	NN	O	age	prep_for	15	SENT_7	[p1l1081t1940r1221b2001],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1081t1940r1221b2001],
21	gender	NN	O	gender	prep_for	15	SENT_7	[p1l1262t1920r1522b2001],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1262t1920r1522b2001],
23	amount	NN	O	amount	prep_for	15	SENT_7	[p1l1563t1929r1830b1983],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1866t1920r1943b1983],
25	cigarette	NN	O	cigarette	nn	26	SENT_7	[p1l1973t1920r2148b2001, p1l9t2040r168b2094],
26	smoking	NN	O	smoking	prep_of	23	SENT_7	[p1l228t2031r551b2112],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l228t2031r551b2112],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l612t2031r738b2094],
29	years	NNS	DURATION	year	prep_for	15	SENT_7	[p1l793t2051r979b2112],
30	since	IN	O	since	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1040t2031r1219b2094],
31	quitting	VBG	O	quit	prepc_since	29	SENT_7	[p1l1277t2031r1553b2112],
32	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1612t2051r1852b2112],
33	former	JJ	O	former	amod	34	SENT_7	[p1l1908t2031r2152b2094],
34	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_among	31	SENT_7	[p1l13t2142r325b2205],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l13t2142r325b2205],

1	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	3	SENT_8	[p1l11t2423r74b2476],
2	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	3	SENT_8	[p1l105t2424r186b2476],
3	Villanueva	NNP	PERSON	Villanueva	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l217t2423r552b2476],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_8	[p1l581t2419r711b2488],
5	E	NN	O	e	npadvmod	3	SENT_8	[p1l581t2419r711b2488],
6	)	SYM	O	)	dep	17	SENT_8	[p1l581t2419r711b2488],
7	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l747t2451r756b2460],
8	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	9	SENT_8	[p1l788t2423r851b2476],
9	Murta-Nascimento	NNP	PERSON	Murta-Nascimento	dep	17	SENT_8	[p1l883t2423r1457b2476],
10	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1491t2451r1499b2460],
11	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	14	SENT_8	[p1l1531t2424r1599b2476],
12	Malats	NNP	PERSON	Malats	nn	14	SENT_8	[p1l1630t2423r1835b2476],
13	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	14	SENT_8	[p1l1870t2451r1879b2460, p1l10t2512r65b2564],
14	Castro	NNP	PERSON	Castro	dep	9	SENT_8	[p1l98t2511r293b2564],
15	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l327t2539r335b2548],
16	M.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	M.	nn	17	SENT_8	[p1l367t2512r448b2564],
17	Kogevinas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kogevinas	dep	5	SENT_8	[p1l481t2511r802b2580],
18	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	dep	17	SENT_8	[p1l11t2599r211b2652],
19	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l239t2599r327b2652],
20	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	prep_for	17	SENT_8	[p1l353t2599r631b2652],
21	in	IN	ORGANIZATION	in	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l657t2599r716b2651],
22	Environmental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Environmental	nn	23	SENT_8	[p1l741t2599r1194b2652],
23	Epidemiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Epidemiology	prep_in	3	SENT_8	[p1l1222t2599r1653b2668],
24	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	25	SENT_8	[p1l1683t2599r1995b2664],
25	CREAL	NNP	MISC	CREAL	dep	23	SENT_8	[p1l1683t2599r1995b2664],
26	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	25	SENT_8	[p1l1683t2599r1995b2664],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1683t2599r1995b2664],
28	PRBB	NNP	O	PRBB	nn	29	SENT_8	[p1l10t2688r198b2739],
29	Building	NNP	O	Building	appos	25	SENT_8	[p1l230t2686r512b2755],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l230t2686r512b2755],
31	Doctor	NNP	O	Doctor	nn	32	SENT_8	[p1l542t2688r754b2740],
32	Aiguader	NNP	PERSON	Aiguader	appos	25	SENT_8	[p1l780t2686r1078b2755],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l780t2686r1078b2755],
34	88	CD	NUMBER	88	appos	25	SENT_8	[p1l1111t2687r1199b2749],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1111t2687r1199b2749],
36	08003	CD	NUMBER	08003	num	39	SENT_8	[p1l1230t2687r1414b2740],
37	Barcelona	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barcelona	nn	39	SENT_8	[p1l1445t2687r1769b2750],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1445t2687r1769b2750],
39	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	25	SENT_8	[p1l1802t2686r1972b2755],
40	e	SYM	O	e	dep	42	SENT_8	[p1l11t2775r220b2829],
41	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	42	SENT_8	[p1l11t2775r220b2829],
42	mail	NN	O	mail	dep	3	SENT_8	[p1l11t2775r220b2829],
43	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l11t2775r220b2829],
44	cVillanueVa@creal.cat	NN	O	cvillanueva@creal.cat	dep	3	SENT_8	[p1l254t2775r933b2829],

1	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l11t2955r74b3008],
2	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	3	SENT_9	[p1l105t2956r186b3008],
3	Villanueva	NNP	PERSON	Villanueva	dep	1	SENT_9	[p1l217t2954r552b3008],
4	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l584t2983r593b2992],
5	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	6	SENT_9	[p1l626t2955r689b3008],
6	Murta-Nascimento	NNP	PERSON	Murta-Nascimento	dep	1	SENT_9	[p1l720t2954r1294b3008],
7	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1328t2983r1337b2992],
8	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	11	SENT_9	[p1l1369t2956r1437b3008],
9	Malats	NNP	PERSON	Malats	nn	11	SENT_9	[p1l1467t2955r1672b3008],
10	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	11	SENT_9	[p1l1707t2983r1716b2992, p1l10t3044r65b3096],
11	Castro	NNP	PERSON	Castro	dep	6	SENT_9	[p1l98t3043r293b3096],
12	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l327t3071r335b3080],
13	M.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	M.	nn	16	SENT_9	[p1l367t3044r448b3096],
14	Kogevinas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kogevinas	nn	16	SENT_9	[p1l481t3042r802b3111],
15	Municipal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Municipal	nn	16	SENT_9	[p1l10t3130r322b3199],
16	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	21	SENT_9	[p1l350t3130r598b3183],
17	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l628t3130r693b3183],
18	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	19	SENT_9	[p1l715t3130r963b3183],
19	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	prep_of	16	SENT_9	[p1l991t3130r1270b3183],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	21	SENT_9	[p1l1300t3130r1790b3199],
21	IMIM-Hospital	JJ	O	imim-hospital	dep	28	SENT_9	[p1l1300t3130r1790b3199],
22	del	FW	O	del	dep	21	SENT_9	[p1l11t3219r101b3272],
23	Mar	NNP	DATE	Mar	dep	22	SENT_9	[p1l129t3219r296b3284],
24	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	23	SENT_9	[p1l129t3219r296b3284],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l129t3219r296b3284],
26	Barcelona	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barcelona	appos	23	SENT_9	[p1l326t3219r650b3282],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l326t3219r650b3282],
28	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	dep	1	SENT_9	[p1l683t3218r853b3287],

1	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l11t3398r74b3451],
2	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	3	SENT_10	[p1l105t3399r186b3450],
3	Villanueva	NNP	PERSON	Villanueva	dep	1	SENT_10	[p1l217t3397r552b3450],
4	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l584t3426r593b3435],
5	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	6	SENT_10	[p1l624t3399r680b3450],
6	Castro	NNP	PERSON	Castro	dep	3	SENT_10	[p1l712t3398r907b3451],
7	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l941t3426r950b3435],
8	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	14	SENT_10	[p1l982t3399r1063b3450],
9	Kogevinas	NNP	PERSON	Kogevinas	nn	14	SENT_10	[p1l1095t3397r1417b3466],
10	CIBER	NNP	O	CIBER	nn	14	SENT_10	[p1l11t3485r234b3538],
11	Epidemiologia	NNP	O	Epidemiologia	nn	14	SENT_10	[p1l260t3482r710b3554],
12	y	NNP	O	y	nn	14	SENT_10	[p1l737t3502r772b3554],
13	Salud	NNP	PERSON	Salud	nn	14	SENT_10	[p1l802t3485r973b3538],
14	Pliblica	NNP	PERSON	Pliblica	dep	1	SENT_10	[p1l999t3483r1228b3538],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_10	[p1l1256t3485r1676b3551],
16	CIBERESP	NNP	O	CIBERESP	dep	14	SENT_10	[p1l1256t3485r1676b3551],
17	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	16	SENT_10	[p1l1256t3485r1676b3551],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1256t3485r1676b3551],
19	Barcelona	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barcelona	appos	16	SENT_10	[p1l10t3574r334b3637],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l10t3574r334b3637],
21	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	16	SENT_10	[p1l368t3574r537b3643],

1	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l10t3754r78b3806],
2	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	nn	3	SENT_11	[p1l109t3754r169b3806],
3	Silverman	NNP	PERSON	Silverman	dep	1	SENT_11	[p1l202t3753r513b3806],
4	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l546t3782r555b3790],
5	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	6	SENT_11	[p1l587t3754r667b3806],
6	Garcia-Closas	NNP	PERSON	Garcia-Closas	dep	1	SENT_11	[p1l700t3753r1127b3806],
7	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1162t3782r1170b3790],
8	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	10	SENT_11	[p1l1202t3754r1271b3806],
9	Rothman	NNP	PERSON	Rothman	nn	10	SENT_11	[p1l1302t3753r1581b3806],
10	M.	NNP	O	M.	dep	6	SENT_11	[p1l1613t3782r1622b3790, p2l10t30r91b82],

1	Dosemeci	NNP	O	Dosemeci	nn	2	SENT_12	[p2l122t29r424b82],
2	Occupational	NNP	O	Occupational	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l11t120r415b188],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l445t120r553b173],
4	Environmental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Environmental	nn	5	SENT_12	[p2l579t120r1032b173],
5	Epidemiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Epidemiology	conj_and	2	SENT_12	[p2l1060t120r1490b189],
6	Branch	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Branch	nn	8	SENT_12	[p2l1519t120r1754b183],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l1519t120r1754b183],
8	Division	NNP	O	Division	dep	2	SENT_12	[p2l10t210r271b263],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l299t210r365b263],
10	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	11	SENT_12	[p2l388t210r603b263],
11	Epidemiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Epidemiology	prep_of	8	SENT_12	[p2l629t210r1060b279],
12	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l1090t210r1197b263],
13	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	nn	23	SENT_12	[p2l1225t210r1505b273],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l1225t210r1505b273],
15	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	appos	23	SENT_12	[p2l1536t210r1797b263],
16	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	23	SENT_12	[p2l11t300r226b353],
17	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	nn	23	SENT_12	[p2l252t299r517b362],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l252t299r517b362],
19	Bethesda	NNP	LOCATION	Bethesda	appos	23	SENT_12	[p2l548t299r842b362],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l548t299r842b362],
21	MD	NNP	O	MD	appos	23	SENT_12	[p2l872t300r1009b362],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l872t300r1009b362],
23	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	conj_and	11	SENT_12	[p2l1039t299r1190b353],

1	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	_	0	SENT_13	[p2l10t478r78b531],
2	Tardon	NNP	PERSON	Tardon	nn	5	SENT_13	[p2l110t478r329b531],
3	Universidad	NNP	PERSON	Universidad	nn	5	SENT_13	[p2l10t565r382b619],
4	de	IN	PERSON	de	amod	5	SENT_13	[p2l410t565r478b619],
5	Oviedo	NNP	PERSON	Oviedo	dep	1	SENT_13	[p2l508t565r745b629],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p2l508t565r745b629],
7	Oviedo	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oviedo	nn	9	SENT_13	[p2l777t565r1014b629],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p2l777t565r1014b629],
9	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	5	SENT_13	[p2l1047t565r1217b634],

1	R.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	R.	nn	6	SENT_14	[p2l10t746r74b797],
2	Garcia-Closas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Garcia-Closas	nn	6	SENT_14	[p2l107t744r534b798],
3	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	nn	6	SENT_14	[p2l10t832r266b901],
4	Universitario	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universitario	nn	6	SENT_14	[p2l294t832r694b886],
5	de	IN	ORGANIZATION	de	amod	6	SENT_14	[p2l724t833r792b886],
6	Canarias	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Canarias	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l822t833r1102b895],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l822t833r1102b895],
8	Santa	NNP	LOCATION	Santa	nn	11	SENT_14	[p2l1135t833r1301b886],
9	Cruz	NNP	LOCATION	Cruz	nn	11	SENT_14	[p2l1329t833r1474b886],
10	de	IN	LOCATION	de	amod	11	SENT_14	[p2l1503t833r1572b886],
11	Tenerife	NNP	LOCATION	Tenerife	appos	6	SENT_14	[p2l1600t832r1873b895],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l1600t832r1873b895],
13	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	nn	14	SENT_14	[p2l12t922r182b990],
14	Results	NNS	O	result	appos	6	SENT_14	[p2l6t1024r266b1087],
15	The	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_14	[p2l359t1024r496b1087],
16	OR	NN	O	or	nn	21	SENT_14	[p2l529t1025r650b1087],
17	(	NN	O	(	nn	21	SENT_14	[p2l683t1024r868b1101],
18	95	CD	PERCENT	95	num	21	SENT_14	[p2l683t1024r868b1101],
19	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nn	21	SENT_14	[p2l683t1024r868b1101],
20	CI	NN	O	ci	nn	21	SENT_14	[p2l904t1024r1017b1101],
21	)	NN	O	)	dep	14	SENT_14	[p2l904t1024r1017b1101],
22	for	IN	O	for	dep	24	SENT_14	[p2l1051t1024r1155b1087],
23	ever	RB	O	ever	advmod	24	SENT_14	[p2l1185t1044r1339b1087],
24	consumed	VBN	O	consume	dep	6	SENT_14	[p2l1369t1024r1730b1087],
25	coffee	NN	O	coffee	dobj	24	SENT_14	[p2l1762t1024r1983b1087],
26	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	24	SENT_14	[p2l2016t1044r2150b1087],
27	1.25	CD	NUMBER	1.25	nsubjpass	24	SENT_14	[p2l17t1136r159b1199],
28	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	29	SENT_14	[p2l198t1136r630b1214],
29	0.95	CD	NUMBER	0.95	dep	27	SENT_14	[p2l198t1136r630b1214],
30	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	31	SENT_14	[p2l198t1136r630b1214],
31	1.64	CD	NUMBER	1.64	num	32	SENT_14	[p2l198t1136r630b1214],
32	)	NN	O	)	dep	29	SENT_14	[p2l198t1136r630b1214],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l198t1136r630b1214],

1	For	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l667t1138r791b1199],
2	consumers	NNS	O	consumer	prep_for	21	SENT_15	[p2l821t1156r1202b1199],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1237t1136r1314b1199],
4	1	CD	NUMBER	1	prep_of	2	SENT_15	[p2l1348t1137r1401b1211],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1348t1137r1401b1211],
6	2	CD	NUMBER	2	prep_of	2	SENT_15	[p2l1438t1137r1498b1211],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1438t1137r1498b1211],
8	3	CD	NUMBER	3	conj_and	4	SENT_15	[p2l1536t1137r1595b1211],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1536t1137r1595b1211],
10	and	CC	NUMBER	and	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1633t1136r1759b1199],
11	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	14	SENT_15	[p2l1790t1137r1832b1198],
12	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1866t1156r1939b1199],
13	more	JJR	O	more	num	14	SENT_15	[p2l1969t1156r2151b1199],
14	cups/day	NN	O	cups/day	npadvmod	15	SENT_15	[p2l9t1248r325b1329],
15	relative	JJ	O	relative	amod	18	SENT_15	[p2l354t1248r623b1311],
16	to	TO	O	to	dep	15	SENT_15	[p2l653t1258r720b1311],
17	never	RB	O	never	neg	15	SENT_15	[p2l750t1268r949b1311],
18	drinkers	NNS	O	drinker	conj_and	4	SENT_15	[p2l978t1248r1288b1323],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l978t1248r1288b1323],
20	OR	NN	O	or	nsubj	21	SENT_15	[p2l1322t1249r1443b1311],
21	were	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1472t1268r1663b1323],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1472t1268r1663b1323],
23	respectively	RB	O	respectively	advmod	21	SENT_15	[p2l1694t1248r2148b1329],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1694t1248r2148b1329],
25	1.24	CD	NUMBER	1.24	number	26	SENT_15	[p2l17t1360r162b1422],
26	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	27	SENT_15	[p2l211t1359r645b1437],
27	O.	NNP	O	O.	nsubj	30	SENT_15	[p2l211t1359r645b1437],
28	92	CD	NUMBER	92	number	29	SENT_15	[p2l211t1359r645b1437],
29	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	30	SENT_15	[p2l211t1359r645b1437],
30	l.	NN	O	l.	xcomp	21	SENT_15	[p2l211t1359r645b1437],
31	66	CD	NUMBER	66	num	32	SENT_15	[p2l211t1359r645b1437],
32	)	NN	O	)	dep	30	SENT_15	[p2l211t1359r645b1437],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l211t1359r645b1437],
34	1.11	CD	PERCENT	1.11	num	38	SENT_15	[p2l703t1360r841b1422],
35	(	CD	PERCENT	(	number	36	SENT_15	[p2l898t1359r1083b1437],
36	95	CD	PERCENT	95	dep	37	SENT_15	[p2l898t1359r1083b1437],
37	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	38	SENT_15	[p2l898t1359r1083b1437],
38	CI	NN	O	ci	conj_and	30	SENT_15	[p2l1134t1360r1220b1422],
39	0.82-1	CD	NUMBER	0.82-1	num	41	SENT_15	[p2l1267t1359r1673b1436],
40	.51	CD	NUMBER	.51	num	41	SENT_15	[p2l1267t1359r1673b1436],
41	)	NN	O	)	dep	38	SENT_15	[p2l1267t1359r1673b1436],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1267t1359r1673b1436],
43	1.57	CD	NUMBER	1.57	conj_and	30	SENT_15	[p2l1730t1359r1873b1422],
44	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	45	SENT_15	[p2l1925t1360r2153b1436, p2l10t1471r212b1548],
45	1.132.19	CD	NUMBER	1.132.19	num	46	SENT_15	[p2l1925t1360r2153b1436, p2l10t1471r212b1548],
46	)	NN	O	)	dep	43	SENT_15	[p2l1925t1360r2153b1436, p2l10t1471r212b1548],
47	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1925t1360r2153b1436, p2l10t1471r212b1548],
48	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l238t1471r364b1533],
49	1.27	CD	NUMBER	1.27	number	50	SENT_15	[p2l392t1471r536b1533],
50	(	CD	NUMBER	(	conj_and	30	SENT_15	[p2l562t1471r994b1548],
51	O.	NNP	O	O.	dep	50	SENT_15	[p2l562t1471r994b1548],
52	88	CD	NUMBER	88	num	51	SENT_15	[p2l562t1471r994b1548],
53	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	54	SENT_15	[p2l562t1471r994b1548],
54	1.81	CD	NUMBER	1.81	num	55	SENT_15	[p2l562t1471r994b1548],
55	)	NN	O	)	dep	50	SENT_15	[p2l562t1471r994b1548],
56	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l562t1471r994b1548],

1	Coffee	NNP	O	Coffee	nn	2	SENT_16	[p2l1020t1471r1262b1534],
2	consumption	NN	O	consumption	nsubj	10	SENT_16	[p2l1283t1471r1746b1552],
3	was	VBD	O	be	cop	10	SENT_16	[p2l1767t1490r1901b1534],
4	higher	JJR	O	higher	amod	10	SENT_16	[p2l1924t1471r2153b1552],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l8t1581r76b1642],
6	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_in	4	SENT_16	[p2l98t1581r391b1643],
7	compared	VBN	O	compare	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l413t1581r766b1662],
8	to	TO	O	to	prepc_compared_to	6	SENT_16	[p2l785t1590r852b1643],
9	never	RB	O	never	pcomp	6	SENT_16	[p2l872t1600r1071b1643],
10	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1092t1581r1404b1643],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1092t1581r1404b1643],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_17	[p2l1428t1581r1565b1643],
2	OR	NN	O	or	nsubj	16	SENT_17	[p2l1587t1581r1708b1644],
3	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1728t1580r1831b1643],
4	drinking	NN	O	drinking	prep_for	2	SENT_17	[p2l1850t1581r2151b1662],
5	at	IN	O	at	advmod	16	SENT_17	[p2l10t1701r72b1754],
6	least	JJS	O	least	pobj	5	SENT_17	[p2l93t1692r257b1754],
7	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	8	SENT_17	[p2l278t1692r320b1753],
8	cups/day	NN	O	cups/day	dep	5	SENT_17	[p2l353t1692r670b1773],
9	was	VBD	O	be	cop	16	SENT_17	[p2l693t1711r827b1754],
10	1.13	CD	NUMBER	1.13	number	11	SENT_17	[p2l860t1692r1001b1755],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_17	[p2l1031t1691r1443b1769],
12	O.	NNP	O	O.	nn	16	SENT_17	[p2l1031t1691r1443b1769],
13	61	CD	NUMBER	61	number	14	SENT_17	[p2l1031t1691r1443b1769],
14	—	CD	NUMBER	—	amod	16	SENT_17	[p2l1031t1691r1443b1769],
15	2.09	CD	NUMBER	2.09	dep	14	SENT_17	[p2l1031t1691r1443b1769],
16	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1031t1691r1443b1769],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1467t1692r1535b1753],
18	current	JJ	DATE	current	amod	19	SENT_17	[p2l1558t1701r1811b1754],
19	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_in	16	SENT_17	[p2l1835t1692r2149b1766],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1835t1692r2149b1766],
21	1.57	CD	NUMBER	1.57	num	22	SENT_17	[p2l17t1804r160b1867],
22	(	CD	NUMBER	(	appos	19	SENT_17	[p2l187t1804r599b1881],
23	0.86	CD	NUMBER	0.86	num	24	SENT_17	[p2l187t1804r599b1881],
24	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	38	SENT_17	[p2l187t1804r599b1881],
25	2.90	CD	NUMBER	2.90	num	26	SENT_17	[p2l187t1804r599b1881],
26	)	NN	O	)	dep	24	SENT_17	[p2l187t1804r599b1881],
27	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l624t1804r692b1866],
28	former	JJ	O	former	amod	29	SENT_17	[p2l713t1804r957b1867],
29	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_in	26	SENT_17	[p2l981t1804r1294b1878],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l981t1804r1294b1878],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1321t1804r1448b1867],
32	1.23	CD	NUMBER	1.23	number	33	SENT_17	[p2l1477t1804r1619b1867],
33	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	24	SENT_17	[p2l1648t1804r2059b1881],
34	O.	NNP	O	O.	dep	33	SENT_17	[p2l1648t1804r2059b1881],
35	55	CD	NUMBER	55	dep	38	SENT_17	[p2l1648t1804r2059b1881],
36	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	37	SENT_17	[p2l1648t1804r2059b1881],
37	2.76	CD	NUMBER	2.76	num	38	SENT_17	[p2l1648t1804r2059b1881],
38	)	NN	O	)	dep	41	SENT_17	[p2l1648t1804r2059b1881],
39	in	IN	O	in	prep	38	SENT_17	[p2l2084t1804r2152b1866],
40	never	RB	O	never	pcomp	39	SENT_17	[p2l8t1936r208b1979],
41	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	dep	16	SENT_17	[p2l276t1916r589b1979],
42	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l276t1916r589b1979],

1	Gene	NNP	O	Gene	nn	4	SENT_18	[p2l662t1916r1118b1979],
2	—	NNP	O	—	nn	4	SENT_18	[p2l662t1916r1118b1979],
3	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nn	4	SENT_18	[p2l662t1916r1118b1979],
4	interactions	NNS	O	interaction	nsubjpass	17	SENT_18	[p2l1186t1916r1604b1979],
5	evaluated	VBN	O	evaluate	partmod	4	SENT_18	[p2l1674t1916r2018b1979],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l2084t1916r2152b1978],
7	NAT2	NN	O	nat2	prep_in	5	SENT_18	[p2l8t2029r254b2102],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l8t2029r254b2102],
9	CYP1A2	NN	O	cyp1a2	prep_in	5	SENT_18	[p2l294t2028r637b2102],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l294t2028r637b2102],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l678t2028r804b2091],
12	CYP2E1-02	NN	O	cyp2e1-02	prep_in	5	SENT_18	[p2l839t2028r1274b2091],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l1311t2028r1438b2091],
14	CYP1A1	NN	O	cyp1a1	prep_in	5	SENT_18	[p2l1472t2028r1790b2091],
15	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	17	SENT_18	[p2l1833t2048r2004b2091],
16	not	RB	O	not	neg	17	SENT_18	[p2l2039t2038r2153b2091],
17	identiﬁed	VBN	O	identiﬁed	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l8t2140r348b2203],
18	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l376t2140r538b2203],
19	adjusting	VBG	O	adjust	prepc_after	17	SENT_18	[p2l566t2140r891b2221],
20	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l919t2140r1023b2203],
21	multiple	JJ	O	multiple	amod	22	SENT_18	[p2l1048t2140r1347b2221],
22	testing	NN	O	testing	prep_for	19	SENT_18	[p2l1374t2140r1630b2221],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l1374t2140r1630b2221],

1	C.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	C.	nn	3	SENT_19	[p2l9t2383r72b2436],
2	Serra	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Serra	nn	3	SENT_19	[p2l105t2383r264b2436],
3	Unit	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Unit	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l8t2470r143b2524],
4	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l170t2470r236b2523],
5	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	prep_of	3	SENT_19	[p2l259t2470r537b2523],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l565t2470r622b2523],
7	Occupational	NNP	O	Occupational	nn	8	SENT_19	[p2l651t2470r1055b2539],
8	Health	NNP	O	Health	prep_in	5	SENT_19	[p2l1084t2470r1302b2533],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1084t2470r1302b2533],
10	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	prep_of	3	SENT_19	[p2l1333t2472r1693b2539],
11	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l9t2558r75b2611],
12	Experimental	JJ	ORGANIZATION	experimental	prep_of	10	SENT_19	[p2l97t2558r508b2627],
13	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l537t2558r645b2611],
14	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	15	SENT_19	[p2l672t2558r874b2611],
15	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	conj_and	5	SENT_19	[p2l904t2558r1184b2621],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l904t2558r1184b2621],
17	Universitat	NNP	PERSON	Universitat	nn	19	SENT_19	[p2l1214t2558r1553b2612],
18	Pompeu	NNP	PERSON	Pompeu	nn	19	SENT_19	[p2l8t2648r256b2715],
19	Fabra	NNP	PERSON	Fabra	appos	15	SENT_19	[p2l284t2647r472b2709],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l284t2647r472b2709],
21	Barcelona	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barcelona	appos	15	SENT_19	[p2l503t2647r827b2709],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l503t2647r827b2709],
23	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	15	SENT_19	[p2l860t2646r1030b2715],

1	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	6	SENT_20	[p2l9t2825r72b2878],
2	Serra	NNP	PERSON	Serra	nn	6	SENT_20	[p2l105t2825r264b2878],
3	Consorci	NNP	PERSON	Consorci	nn	6	SENT_20	[p2l9t2913r281b2966],
4	Hospitalari	NNP	PERSON	Hospitalari	nn	6	SENT_20	[p2l310t2913r647b2982],
5	Parc	NNP	PERSON	Parc	nn	6	SENT_20	[p2l675t2915r808b2966],
6	Tauli	NNP	PERSON	Tauli	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l837t2910r1013b2976],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l837t2910r1013b2976],
8	Sabadell	NNP	LOCATION	Sabadell	nn	10	SENT_20	[p2l1045t2913r1321b2976],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1045t2913r1321b2976],
10	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	6	SENT_20	[p2l1354t2913r1524b2982],

1	A.	NN	O	a.	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l8t3092r76b3145],
2	Carrato	NNP	O	Carrato	nn	6	SENT_21	[p2l109t3092r334b3145],
3	Hospital	NNP	O	Hospital	nn	6	SENT_21	[p2l8t3181r265b3250],
4	General	NNP	O	General	nn	6	SENT_21	[p2l294t3181r532b3234],
5	de	NNP	PERSON	de	nn	6	SENT_21	[p2l562t3181r631b3234],
6	Elche	NNP	PERSON	Elche	dep	1	SENT_21	[p2l658t3181r848b3244],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l658t3181r848b3244],
8	Elche	NNP	LOCATION	Elche	nn	10	SENT_21	[p2l878t3181r1067b3244],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l878t3181r1067b3244],
10	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	6	SENT_21	[p2l1100t3181r1270b3250],

1	F.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	F.	nn	2	SENT_22	[p2l8t3361r63b3412],
2	X.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	X.	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l95t3361r163b3412],
3	Real	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Real	nn	4	SENT_22	[p2l194t3359r332b3412],
4	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	2	SENT_22	[p2l8t3449r368b3516],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l396t3447r462b3501],
6	Experimental	JJ	ORGANIZATION	experimental	prep_of	4	SENT_22	[p2l484t3447r895b3516],
7	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l925t3447r1032b3501],
8	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	9	SENT_22	[p2l1059t3448r1262b3501],
9	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	prep_of	4	SENT_22	[p2l1291t3447r1571b3510],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1291t3447r1571b3510],
11	Universitat	NNP	PERSON	Universitat	nn	13	SENT_22	[p2l8t3537r347b3590],
12	Pompeu	NNP	PERSON	Pompeu	nn	13	SENT_22	[p2l374t3538r622b3605],
13	Fabra	NNP	PERSON	Fabra	appos	9	SENT_22	[p2l649t3537r838b3600],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l649t3537r838b3600],
15	Barcelona	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barcelona	appos	9	SENT_22	[p2l869t3537r1194b3600],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l869t3537r1194b3600],
17	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	9	SENT_22	[p2l1226t3537r1396b3605],

1	F.	NNP	O	F.	nn	3	SENT_23	[p2l8t3717r63b3769],
2	X.	NNP	O	X.	nn	3	SENT_23	[p2l95t3717r163b3769],
3	Real	NNP	O	Real	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l194t3715r332b3769],

1	Cellular	JJ	O	cellular	amod	6	SENT_24	[p3l9t24r255b77],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l283t24r390b77],
3	Molecular	JJ	ORGANIZATION	molecular	conj_and	1	SENT_24	[p3l417t24r731b77],
4	Biology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biology	nn	6	SENT_24	[p3l757t24r1001b93],
5	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	6	SENT_24	[p3l1029t24r1307b77],
6	Unit	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Unit	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l1335t24r1485b87],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l1335t24r1485b87],
8	Municipal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Municipal	nn	9	SENT_24	[p3l1515t24r1828b93],
9	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	appos	6	SENT_24	[p3l8t112r256b165],
10	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l286t112r352b165],
11	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	12	SENT_24	[p3l374t112r622b165],
12	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	prep_of	9	SENT_24	[p3l650t112r929b165],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_24	[p3l959t112r1450b181],
14	IMIM-Hospital	JJ	O	imim-hospital	amod	15	SENT_24	[p3l959t112r1450b181],
15	del	FW	O	del	dep	6	SENT_24	[p3l1479t112r1569b165],
16	Mar	NNP	DATE	Mar	tmod	15	SENT_24	[p3l1597t113r1765b178],
17	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	16	SENT_24	[p3l1597t113r1765b178],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l1597t113r1765b178],
19	Barcelona	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barcelona	nn	21	SENT_24	[p3l8t201r333b264],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l8t201r333b264],
21	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	15	SENT_24	[p3l366t200r536b269],

1	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	3	SENT_25	[p3l8t381r89b432],
2	Kogevinas	NNP	PERSON	Kogevinas	nn	3	SENT_25	[p3l121t379r443b448],
3	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	_	0	SENT_25	[p3l8t468r368b536],
4	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_25	[p3l396t467r462b520],
5	Social	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Social	nn	6	SENT_25	[p3l486t467r673b520],
6	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	prep_of	3	SENT_25	[p3l701t467r1005b530],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p3l701t467r1005b530],
8	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	9	SENT_25	[p3l1035t467r1284b520],
9	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	appos	6	SENT_25	[p3l1314t467r1539b530],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p3l1314t467r1539b530],
11	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	3	SENT_25	[p3l1569t467r1889b536],
12	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_25	[p3l9t556r75b609],
13	Crete	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Crete	prep_of	11	SENT_25	[p3l98t556r277b619],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p3l98t556r277b619],
15	Crete	NNP	LOCATION	Crete	nn	17	SENT_25	[p3l309t556r488b619],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p3l309t556r488b619],
17	Greece	NNP	LOCATION	Greece	appos	13	SENT_25	[p3l520t556r733b610],

1	@	SYM	O	@	dep	2	SENT_26	[p3l1783t781r1860b876],
2	Springer	NN	PERSON	springer	_	0	SENT_26	[p3l1890t804r2153b879],
3	122	CD	NUMBER	122	num	4	SENT_26	[p3l56t954r104b978],
4	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	nsubj	5	SENT_26	[p3l1490t954r1590b979],
5	Causes	VBZ	O	cause	rcmod	2	SENT_26	[p3l1602t954r1700b979],
6	Control	NN	O	control	dobj	5	SENT_26	[p3l1714t954r1820b979],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_26	[p3l1835t954r1926b984],
8	2009	CD	DATE	2009	dep	6	SENT_26	[p3l1835t954r1926b984],
9	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	10	SENT_26	[p3l1835t954r1926b984],
10	20:121	CD	NUMBER	20:121	dep	8	SENT_26	[p3l1940t954r2106b979],
11	—	NN	O	—	dep	10	SENT_26	[p3l1940t954r2106b979],
12	127	CD	NUMBER	127	num	11	SENT_26	[p3l1940t954r2106b979],

1	Conclusion	NN	O	conclusion	nsubj	3	SENT_27	[p3l12t1120r415b1183],
2	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	3	SENT_27	[p3l508t1122r630b1183],
3	observed	VBD	O	observe	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l692t1120r1014b1183],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_27	[p3l1074t1140r1111b1183],
5	modest	JJ	O	modest	amod	9	SENT_27	[p3l1169t1120r1428b1183],
6	increased	VBN	O	increase	amod	9	SENT_27	[p3l1486t1120r1825b1183],
7	bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	9	SENT_27	[p3l1882t1120r2153b1183],
8	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	9	SENT_27	[p3l9t1252r243b1295],
9	risk	NN	O	risk	dobj	3	SENT_27	[p3l285t1232r420b1295],
10	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l465t1252r705b1313],
11	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nn	12	SENT_27	[p3l751t1232r972b1295],
12	drinkers	NNS	O	drinker	prep_among	3	SENT_27	[p3l1019t1232r1309b1295],
13	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	20	SENT_27	[p3l1355t1232r1489b1295],
14	may	MD	O	may	aux	20	SENT_27	[p3l1533t1252r1704b1313],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l1533t1252r1704b1313],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l1753t1232r1820b1294],
17	part	NN	O	part	prep_in	20	SENT_27	[p3l1863t1241r2021b1313],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l1863t1241r2021b1313],
19	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_27	[p3l2068t1232r2151b1295],
20	explained	VBN	O	explain	rcmod	12	SENT_27	[p3l9t1343r358b1424],
21	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l391t1343r479b1424],
22	residual	JJ	O	residual	amod	23	SENT_27	[p3l515t1343r799b1405],
23	confounding	NN	O	confounding	agent	20	SENT_27	[p3l835t1343r1286b1424],
24	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l1321t1343r1409b1424],
25	smoking	NN	O	smoking	agent	20	SENT_27	[p3l1449t1343r1771b1424],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l1449t1343r1771b1424],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_28	[p3l1811t1343r1949b1405],
2	ﬁndings	NNS	O	ﬁndings	nsubj	9	SENT_28	[p3l1986t1343r2149b1405, p3l8t1454r153b1535],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_28	[p3l190t1454r363b1517],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_28	[p3l396t1454r503b1517],
5	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	8	SENT_28	[p3l539t1454r976b1535],
6	—	NN	O	—	nn	8	SENT_28	[p3l539t1454r976b1535],
7	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nn	8	SENT_28	[p3l539t1454r976b1535],
8	interactions	NNS	O	interaction	prep_from	2	SENT_28	[p3l1011t1454r1428b1517],
9	need	VBP	O	need	_	0	SENT_28	[p3l1464t1454r1633b1517],
10	replication	NN	O	replication	dobj	9	SENT_28	[p3l1665t1454r2050b1535],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_28	[p3l2084t1454r2152b1516],
12	further	JJ	O	further	amod	13	SENT_28	[p3l8t1565r253b1628],
13	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_in	10	SENT_28	[p3l287t1565r549b1628],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p3l287t1565r549b1628],

1	Keywords	NNPS	O	Keywords	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l9t1790r395b1870],
2	Bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	3	SENT_29	[p3l488t1790r773b1852],
3	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	1	SENT_29	[p3l805t1809r1039b1852],
4	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l1077t1823r1087b1833],
5	Coffee	NNP	O	Coffee	nn	7	SENT_29	[p3l1125t1790r1367b1853],
6	Genetic	NNP	O	Genetic	nn	7	SENT_29	[p3l1406t1823r1416b1833, p3l10t1901r284b1964],
7	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	dep	1	SENT_29	[p3l323t1901r798b1982],
8	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l838t1934r847b1944],
9	Epidemiology	NN	O	epidemiology	dep	7	SENT_29	[p3l885t1901r1394b1982],

1	Introduction	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_30	[p3l8t2144r495b2208],

1	Coffee	NNP	O	Coffee	nsubj	5	SENT_31	[p3l9t2369r251b2432],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	5	SENT_31	[p3l293t2369r349b2432],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_31	[p3l394t2389r431b2432],
4	complex	JJ	O	complex	amod	5	SENT_31	[p3l472t2369r779b2450],
5	mixture	NN	O	mixture	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l821t2369r1099b2432],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l1143t2369r1220b2432],
7	chemicals	NNS	O	chemical	prep_of	5	SENT_31	[p3l1256t2369r1633b2432],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l1256t2369r1633b2432],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_32	[p3l1679t2369r1816b2432],
2	carcinogenic	JJ	O	carcinogenic	amod	3	SENT_32	[p3l1859t2369r2149b2432, p3l9t2480r199b2561],
3	potential	NN	O	potential	nsubjpass	8	SENT_32	[p3l250t2480r564b2561],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l616t2480r693b2543],
5	coffee	NN	O	coffee	prep_of	3	SENT_32	[p3l737t2480r959b2543],
6	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	8	SENT_32	[p3l1008t2480r1124b2543],
7	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_32	[p3l1174t2480r1343b2543],
8	examined	VBN	O	examine	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1393t2480r1742b2543],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1791t2480r1859b2542],
10	animal	NN	O	animal	nn	11	SENT_32	[p3l1910t2480r2151b2543],
11	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_in	8	SENT_32	[p3l11t2591r254b2654],
12	with	IN	O	with	mark	15	SENT_32	[p3l294t2591r451b2654],
13	inconsistent	JJ	O	inconsistent	amod	14	SENT_32	[p3l488t2591r918b2654],
14	results	NNS	O	result	nsubj	15	SENT_32	[p3l953t2591r1184b2654],
15	[	VBP	O	[	advcl	8	SENT_32	[p3l1230t2592r1344b2667],
16	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	17	SENT_32	[p3l1230t2592r1344b2667],
17	]	CD	NUMBER	]	dobj	15	SENT_32	[p3l1230t2592r1344b2667],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1230t2592r1344b2667],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1386t2593r1459b2653],
2	humans	NNS	O	human	prep_in	6	SENT_33	[p3l1495t2591r1792b2665],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1495t2591r1792b2665],
4	epidemiological	JJ	O	epidemiological	amod	5	SENT_33	[p3l1834t2591r2149b2672, p3l9t2701r297b2782],
5	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	6	SENT_33	[p3l325t2701r567b2763],
6	suggest	VBP	O	suggest	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l596t2710r862b2782],
7	that	IN	O	that	complm	11	SENT_33	[p3l885t2701r1019b2763],
8	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nsubj	11	SENT_33	[p3l1043t2701r1264b2763],
9	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	11	SENT_33	[p3l1289t2701r1345b2763],
10	possibly	RB	O	possibly	advmod	11	SENT_33	[p3l1370t2701r1668b2782],
11	carcinogenic	JJ	O	carcinogenic	ccomp	6	SENT_33	[p3l1693t2701r2150b2782],
12	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l8t2821r75b2874],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_33	[p3l133t2812r241b2874],
14	urinary	JJ	O	urinary	amod	18	SENT_33	[p3l298t2812r556b2893],
15	bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	18	SENT_33	[p3l613t2812r884b2874],
16	[	NN	O	[	nn	18	SENT_33	[p3l946t2812r1061b2887],
17	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	18	SENT_33	[p3l946t2812r1061b2887],
18	]	NN	O	]	prep_to	11	SENT_33	[p3l946t2812r1061b2887],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l946t2812r1061b2887],
20	although	IN	O	although	mark	24	SENT_33	[p3l1124t2812r1435b2893],
21	evidence	NN	O	evidence	nsubj	24	SENT_33	[p3l1493t2812r1810b2874],
22	remains	VBZ	O	remain	cop	24	SENT_33	[p3l1868t2812r2150b2874],
23	controversial	JJ	O	controversial	amod	24	SENT_33	[p3l9t2923r476b2985],
24	[	NN	O	[	advcl	11	SENT_33	[p3l532t2923r646b2998],
25	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	26	SENT_33	[p3l532t2923r646b2998],
26	]	NN	O	]	dep	24	SENT_33	[p3l532t2923r646b2998],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l532t2923r646b2998],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_34	[p3l700t2923r762b2985],
2	number	NN	O	number	nsubj	6	SENT_34	[p3l810t2923r1085b2985],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1134t2922r1211b2985],
4	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	2	SENT_34	[p3l1257t2923r1500b2985],
5	have	VBP	O	have	aux	6	SENT_34	[p3l1549t2923r1717b2985],
6	reported	VBN	O	report	dep	22	SENT_34	[p3l1766t2923r2067b3004],
7	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_34	[p3l2116t2942r2153b2985],
8	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	14	SENT_34	[p3l7t3035r291b3116],
9	association	NN	O	association	nn	14	SENT_34	[p3l328t3035r725b3098],
10	[	NN	O	[	nn	14	SENT_34	[p3l767t3036r947b3111],
11	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	14	SENT_34	[p3l767t3036r947b3111],
12	—	NN	O	—	nn	14	SENT_34	[p3l767t3036r947b3111],
13	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	14	SENT_34	[p3l767t3036r947b3111],
14	]	NN	O	]	dobj	6	SENT_34	[p3l767t3036r947b3111],
15	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	18	SENT_34	[p3l988t3035r1122b3098],
16	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	18	SENT_34	[p3l1157t3055r1291b3098],
17	not	RB	O	not	neg	18	SENT_34	[p3l1329t3045r1443b3098],
18	replicated	VBN	O	replicate	dep	6	SENT_34	[p3l1476t3035r1832b3116],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1866t3035r1934b3097],
20	other	JJ	O	other	amod	21	SENT_34	[p3l1970t3035r2153b3098],
21	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_in	18	SENT_34	[p3l11t3146r254b3209],
22	[	VBP	O	[	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l307t3146r556b3222],
23	8	CD	NUMBER	8	num	24	SENT_34	[p3l307t3146r556b3222],
24	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dobj	22	SENT_34	[p3l307t3146r556b3222],
25	11	CD	NUMBER	11	num	26	SENT_34	[p3l307t3146r556b3222],
26	]	NN	O	]	nsubj	22	SENT_34	[p3l307t3146r556b3222],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l307t3146r556b3222],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_35	[p3l605t3146r742b3209],
2	body	NN	O	body	nsubj	5	SENT_35	[p3l787t3146r964b3227],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1011t3146r1088b3209],
4	evidence	NN	O	evidence	prep_of	2	SENT_35	[p3l1127t3146r1444b3209],
5	excludes	VBZ	O	exclude	dep	13	SENT_35	[p3l1491t3146r1800b3209],
6	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_35	[p3l1849t3166r1886b3209],
7	strong	JJ	O	strong	amod	8	SENT_35	[p3l1933t3155r2151b3227],
8	effect	NN	O	effect	dobj	5	SENT_35	[p3l9t3257r230b3331],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l9t3257r230b3331],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l291t3257r418b3319],
11	causality	NN	O	causality	dobj	5	SENT_35	[p3l473t3257r789b3338],
12	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_35	[p3l846t3257r902b3319],
13	questioned	VBN	O	question	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l960t3257r1348b3338],
14	given	VBN	O	give	prep	13	SENT_35	[p3l1403t3257r1600b3338],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_35	[p3l1654t3257r1762b3319],
16	moderate	JJ	O	moderate	amod	17	SENT_35	[p3l1818t3257r2151b3319],
17	association	NN	O	association	npadvmod	33	SENT_35	[p3l10t3368r426b3442],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l10t3368r426b3442],
19	a	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_35	[p3l490t3388r527b3431],
20	lack	NN	O	lack	npadvmod	33	SENT_35	[p3l586t3368r735b3431],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l794t3368r871b3431],
22	a	DT	O	a	det	26	SENT_35	[p3l926t3388r963b3431],
23	clear	JJ	O	clear	amod	26	SENT_35	[p3l1021t3368r1195b3431],
24	dose	NN	O	dose	nn	26	SENT_35	[p3l1254t3368r1795b3449],
25	—	NN	O	—	nn	26	SENT_35	[p3l1254t3368r1795b3449],
26	response	NN	O	response	prep_of	20	SENT_35	[p3l1254t3368r1795b3449],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1254t3368r1795b3449],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1859t3368r1985b3431],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_35	[p3l2044t3368r2151b3431],
30	potential	JJ	O	potential	amod	32	SENT_35	[p3l7t3479r322b3560],
31	residual	JJ	O	residual	amod	32	SENT_35	[p3l354t3479r638b3542],
32	confounding	NN	O	confounding	npadvmod	33	SENT_35	[p3l671t3479r1123b3560],
33	by	IN	O	by	pcomp	14	SENT_35	[p3l1155t3479r1243b3560],
34	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	35	SENT_35	[p3l1279t3479r1582b3560],
35	[	NN	O	[	pobj	33	SENT_35	[p3l1623t3480r1916b3555],
36	12	CD	NUMBER	12	number	37	SENT_35	[p3l1623t3480r1916b3555],
37	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	35	SENT_35	[p3l1623t3480r1916b3555],
38	14	CD	NUMBER	14	num	39	SENT_35	[p3l1623t3480r1916b3555],
39	]	NN	O	]	nsubjpass	13	SENT_35	[p3l1623t3480r1916b3555],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1623t3480r1916b3555],

1	Apart	RB	O	apart	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l111t3591r314b3671],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l376t3590r549b3653],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_36	[p3l613t3610r650b3653],
4	recent	JJ	O	recent	amod	5	SENT_36	[p3l711t3600r932b3653],
5	evaluation	NN	O	evaluation	prep_apart_from	25	SENT_36	[p3l993t3590r1367b3653],
6	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	7	SENT_36	[p3l1436t3590r1597b3666],
7	15	CD	NUMBER	15	num	8	SENT_36	[p3l1436t3590r1597b3666],
8	]	NN	O	]	dep	5	SENT_36	[p3l1436t3590r1597b3666],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1436t3590r1597b3666],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_36	[p3l1662t3590r1769b3653],
11	interplay	NN	O	interplay	conj_and	5	SENT_36	[p3l1833t3590r2151b3671],
12	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l7t3700r307b3762],
13	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nn	14	SENT_36	[p3l342t3700r563b3762],
14	consumption	NN	O	consumption	prep_between	11	SENT_36	[p3l599t3700r1062b3781],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1097t3700r1224b3762],
16	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	17	SENT_36	[p3l1259t3700r1515b3781],
17	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	conj_and	5	SENT_36	[p3l1554t3700r2029b3781],
18	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l2066t3719r2152b3762],
19	bladder	NN	O	bladder	prep_on	17	SENT_36	[p4l7t23r278b85],
20	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	21	SENT_36	[p4l323t42r557b85],
21	risk	NN	O	risk	nsubjpass	25	SENT_36	[p4l601t23r736b85],
22	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	25	SENT_36	[p4l780t23r896b85],
23	not	RB	O	not	neg	25	SENT_36	[p4l943t32r1057b85],
24	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	25	SENT_36	[p4l1101t23r1271b85],
25	examined	VBN	O	examine	_	0	SENT_36	[p4l1317t23r1683b85],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p4l1317t23r1683b85],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1733t24r1806b85],
2	humans	NNS	O	human	prep_in	7	SENT_37	[p4l1851t23r2148b97],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1851t23r2148b97],
4	caffeine	NN	O	caffeine	nsubjpass	7	SENT_37	[p4l9t133r297b196],
5	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_37	[p4l324t134r379b196],
6	mainly	RB	O	mainly	advmod	7	SENT_37	[p4l407t134r655b215],
7	metabolized	VBN	O	metabolize	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l682t134r1122b196],
8	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1147t134r1235b215],
9	cytochrome	NN	O	cytochrome	nn	10	SENT_37	[p4l1263t134r1685b215],
10	P450	NN	O	p450	agent	7	SENT_37	[p4l1712t133r1893b197],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_37	[p4l1923t134r2149b211],
12	CYP	NN	O	cyp	nn	15	SENT_37	[p4l1923t134r2149b211],
13	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	15	SENT_37	[p4l1923t134r2149b211],
14	1A2	NN	O	1a2	nn	15	SENT_37	[p4l17t246r159b308],
15	enzyme	NN	O	enzyme	dobj	7	SENT_37	[p4l195t266r472b327],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l506t246r574b308],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_37	[p4l607t246r715b309],
18	liver	NN	O	liver	prep_in	15	SENT_37	[p4l750t246r930b309],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l750t246r930b309],

1	Additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	3	SENT_38	[p4l968t246r1351b309],
2	CYPs	NNS	O	cyp	nn	3	SENT_38	[p4l1387t246r1590b309],
3	isoforms	NNS	O	isoform	nsubj	28	SENT_38	[p4l1626t246r1937b309],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	3	SENT_38	[p4l1974t247r2148b327],
5	e.g.	FW	O	e.g.	dep	3	SENT_38	[p4l1974t247r2148b327],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l1974t247r2148b327],
7	CYPIAI	NNP	LOCATION	CYPIAI	appos	5	SENT_38	[p4l13t358r335b431],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l13t358r335b431],
9	2E1	NN	O	2e1	appos	5	SENT_38	[p4l392t358r554b431],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l392t358r554b431],
11	3A4	NN	O	3a4	nn	12	SENT_38	[p4l611t357r802b434],
12	)	NN	O	)	appos	5	SENT_38	[p4l611t357r802b434],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l611t357r802b434],
14	N	NN	O	n	nn	16	SENT_38	[p4l856t357r1553b438],
15	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	16	SENT_38	[p4l856t357r1553b438],
16	acetyltransferase	NN	O	acetyltransferase	appos	5	SENT_38	[p4l856t357r1553b438],
17	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	18	SENT_38	[p4l1609t358r1649b419],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_38	[p4l1706t358r1968b434],
19	NAT2	NN	O	nat2	nn	20	SENT_38	[p4l1706t358r1968b434],
20	)	NN	O	)	dep	16	SENT_38	[p4l1706t358r1968b434],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l2026t357r2152b420],
22	xanthine	NN	O	xanthine	nn	23	SENT_38	[p4l9t468r315b530],
23	oxidase	NN	O	oxidase	dep	16	SENT_38	[p4l358t468r629b530],
24	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	26	SENT_38	[p4l673t468r845b545],
25	Xo	NNP	O	Xo	nn	26	SENT_38	[p4l673t468r845b545],
26	)	NN	O	)	dep	16	SENT_38	[p4l673t468r845b545],
27	also	RB	O	also	advmod	28	SENT_38	[p4l891t468r1030b530],
28	appear	VBP	O	appear	dep	39	SENT_38	[p4l1073t487r1312b549],
29	to	TO	O	to	aux	31	SENT_38	[p4l1350t477r1418b530],
30	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	31	SENT_38	[p4l1458t468r1541b530],
31	involved	VBN	O	involve	xcomp	28	SENT_38	[p4l1582t468r1896b531],
32	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l1936t468r2004b530],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	34	SENT_38	[p4l2044t468r2151b530],
34	formation	NN	O	formation	prep_in	31	SENT_38	[p4l9t579r362b642],
35	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l441t579r519b642],
36	certain	JJ	O	certain	amod	38	SENT_38	[p4l592t579r834b642],
37	secondary	JJ	O	secondary	amod	38	SENT_38	[p4l916t579r1275b660],
38	metabolites	NNS	O	metabolite	prep_of	34	SENT_38	[p4l1354t579r1767b642],
39	[	VBP	O	[	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l1853t579r2147b655],
40	l6	NN	O	l6	dobj	39	SENT_38	[p4l1853t579r2147b655],
41	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	43	SENT_38	[p4l1853t579r2147b655],
42	l8	NN	O	l8	nn	43	SENT_38	[p4l1853t579r2147b655],
43	]	NN	O	]	nsubj	39	SENT_38	[p4l1853t579r2147b655],
44	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l1853t579r2147b655],

1	However	RB	O	however	advmod	13	SENT_39	[p4l8t692r355b764],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l8t692r355b764],
3	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	4	SENT_39	[p4l389t690r644b771],
4	variants	NNS	O	variant	nsubjpass	13	SENT_39	[p4l676t690r957b753],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l989t690r1066b753],
6	most	JJS	O	most	prep_of	4	SENT_39	[p4l1090t700r1264b753],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l1293t690r1370b753],
8	those	DT	O	those	det	9	SENT_39	[p4l1393t690r1580b753],
9	genes	NNS	O	gene	prep_of	6	SENT_39	[p4l1611t710r1811b771],
10	have	VBP	O	have	aux	13	SENT_39	[p4l1841t690r2008b753],
11	not	RB	O	not	neg	13	SENT_39	[p4l2039t700r2153b753],
12	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_39	[p4l7t801r176b864],
13	examined	VBN	O	examine	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l220t801r569b864],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l611t801r679b863],
15	relation	NN	O	relation	prep_in	13	SENT_39	[p4l721t801r996b864],
16	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l1039t811r1106b864],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_39	[p4l1150t801r1257b864],
18	bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	20	SENT_39	[p4l1300t801r1570b864],
19	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	20	SENT_39	[p4l1613t821r1848b864],
20	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_to	13	SENT_39	[p4l1888t801r2023b864],
21	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l2063t801r2151b882],
22	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nn	23	SENT_39	[p4l9t910r230b973],
23	consumption	NN	O	consumption	agent	13	SENT_39	[p4l265t911r745b992],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l265t911r745b992],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	22	SENT_40	[p4l110t1024r232b1085],
2	evaluated	VBD	O	evaluate	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l299t1023r643b1085],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_40	[p4l707t1023r814b1085],
4	association	NN	O	association	dobj	2	SENT_40	[p4l882t1023r1279b1085],
5	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l1342t1023r1642b1086],
6	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nn	7	SENT_40	[p4l1707t1022r1928b1085],
7	consumption	NN	O	consumption	prep_between	4	SENT_40	[p4l1995t1042r2149b1085, p4l11t1134r341b1215],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l380t1134r507b1196],
9	bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	11	SENT_40	[p4l542t1134r813b1196],
10	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	11	SENT_40	[p4l849t1153r1084b1196],
11	risk	NN	O	risk	conj_and	7	SENT_40	[p4l1118t1134r1253b1196],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l1289t1134r1357b1195],
13	a	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_40	[p4l1396t1153r1433b1196],
14	case	NN	O	case	nn	17	SENT_40	[p4l1469t1134r1922b1196],
15	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	17	SENT_40	[p4l1469t1134r1922b1196],
16	control	NN	O	control	nn	17	SENT_40	[p4l1469t1134r1922b1196],
17	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	7	SENT_40	[p4l1963t1134r2151b1215],
18	conducted	VBN	O	conduct	partmod	17	SENT_40	[p4l9t1246r377b1309],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l419t1246r486b1308],
20	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	prep_in	18	SENT_40	[p4l530t1246r731b1327],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l775t1246r901b1309],
22	examined	VBD	O	examine	conj_and	2	SENT_40	[p4l943t1246r1292b1309],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_40	[p4l1333t1246r1440b1309],
24	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	27	SENT_40	[p4l1483t1246r2153b1327],
25	—	NN	O	—	nn	27	SENT_40	[p4l1483t1246r2153b1327],
26	environment	NN	O	environment	nn	27	SENT_40	[p4l1483t1246r2153b1327],
27	interactions	NNS	O	interaction	dobj	22	SENT_40	[p4l8t1357r426b1420],
28	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l485t1357r589b1420],
29	variants	NNS	O	variant	prep_for	22	SENT_40	[p4l644t1357r926b1420],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l986t1357r1063b1420],
31	genes	NNS	O	gene	prep_of	29	SENT_40	[p4l1115t1377r1314b1438],
32	coding	VBG	O	code	partmod	31	SENT_40	[p4l1374t1357r1615b1438],
33	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l1674t1357r1778b1420],
34	caffeinemetabolizing	VBG	O	caffeinemetabolize	amod	35	SENT_40	[p4l1834t1357r2149b1420, p4l8t1468r477b1549],
35	enzymes	NNS	O	enzyme	prep_for	32	SENT_40	[p4l511t1487r842b1549],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l511t1487r842b1549],

1	Material	NN	O	material	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l8t1711r341b1775],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l376t1713r516b1775],
3	methods	NNS	O	method	conj_and	1	SENT_41	[p4l549t1713r870b1775],

1	Study	NNP	O	Study	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l10t1937r215b2018],
2	design	NN	O	design	dep	1	SENT_42	[p4l249t1936r481b2018],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l515t1937r641b1999],
4	population	NN	O	population	dep	1	SENT_42	[p4l672t1937r1056b2018],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_43	[p4l7t2162r130b2223],
2	conducted	VBD	O	conduct	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l179t2160r547b2223],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_43	[p4l595t2180r632b2223],
4	multicenter	JJ	O	multicenter	amod	6	SENT_43	[p4l677t2160r1088b2223],
5	hospital	NN	O	hospital	nn	6	SENT_43	[p4l1133t2160r1652b2241],
6	—	NN	O	—	nsubj	7	SENT_43	[p4l1133t2160r1652b2241],
7	based	VBN	O	base	ccomp	2	SENT_43	[p4l1133t2160r1652b2241],
8	case	NN	O	case	nn	11	SENT_43	[p4l1699t2160r2151b2223],
9	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	11	SENT_43	[p4l1699t2160r2151b2223],
10	control	NN	O	control	nn	11	SENT_43	[p4l1699t2160r2151b2223],
11	study	NN	O	study	dobj	7	SENT_43	[p4l11t2271r200b2352],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l222t2271r299b2334],
13	bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	14	SENT_43	[p4l313t2271r583b2334],
14	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	11	SENT_43	[p4l603t2291r837b2334],
15	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l855t2271r1155b2334],
16	June	NNP	DATE	June	prep_between	14	SENT_43	[p4l1174t2273r1336b2334],
17	1998	CD	DATE	1998	num	16	SENT_43	[p4l1366t2271r1532b2335],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l1557t2271r1684b2334],
19	June	NNP	DATE	June	ccomp	2	SENT_43	[p4l1703t2273r1865b2334],
20	2001	CD	DATE	2001	num	19	SENT_43	[p4l1888t2271r2056b2334],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l2084t2271r2152b2333],
22	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	prep_in	19	SENT_43	[p4l11t2382r229b2463],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l11t2382r229b2463],

1	Study	NNP	O	Study	nn	2	SENT_44	[p4l282t2382r486b2463],
2	subjects	NNS	O	subject	nsubjpass	4	SENT_44	[p4l536t2382r818b2463],
3	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_44	[p4l867t2402r1038b2445],
4	recruited	VBN	O	recruit	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l1084t2382r1405b2445],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l1451t2382r1518b2444],
6	18	CD	NUMBER	18	num	8	SENT_44	[p4l1572t2382r1648b2445],
7	participating	VBG	O	participate	amod	8	SENT_44	[p4l1696t2382r2151b2463],
8	hospitals	NNS	O	hospital	prep_in	4	SENT_44	[p4l8t2492r324b2573],
9	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l355t2492r528b2555],
10	ﬁve	NN	O	ﬁve	nn	11	SENT_44	[p4l556t2492r687b2555],
11	areas	NNS	O	area	prep_from	8	SENT_44	[p4l718t2512r917b2555],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l718t2512r917b2555],
13	Barcelona	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barcelona	nn	15	SENT_44	[p4l952t2493r1335b2566],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l952t2493r1335b2566],
15	Valles/Bages	NNP	O	Valles/Bages	prep_in	4	SENT_44	[p4l1367t2489r1838b2573],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_44	[p4l1872t2492r2149b2570, p4l8t2604r120b2685],
17	including	VBG	O	include	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l1872t2492r2149b2570, p4l8t2604r120b2685],
18	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	19	SENT_44	[p4l154t2613r285b2667],
19	cities	NNS	O	city	prep_including	15	SENT_44	[p4l321t2604r528b2667],
20	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l321t2604r528b2667],
21	Sabadell	NNP	LOCATION	Sabadell	conj_and	8	SENT_44	[p4l571t2604r876b2667],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l912t2604r1038b2667],
23	Manresa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Manresa	conj_and	8	SENT_44	[p4l1071t2605r1428b2681],
24	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	23	SENT_44	[p4l1071t2605r1428b2681],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l1071t2605r1428b2681],
26	Alicante	NNP	LOCATION	Alicante	nn	28	SENT_44	[p4l1465t2604r1789b2678],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l1465t2604r1789b2678],
28	Tenerife	NNP	LOCATION	Tenerife	conj_and	8	SENT_44	[p4l1825t2604r2148b2678],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l1825t2604r2148b2678],
30	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l10t2715r137b2778],
31	Asturias	NNP	LOCATION	Asturias	conj_and	8	SENT_44	[p4l180t2715r495b2778],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l180t2715r495b2778],

1	Cases	NNS	O	case	nsubjpass	3	SENT_45	[p4l545t2716r749b2778],
2	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_45	[p4l796t2735r967b2778],
3	identiﬁed	VBN	O	identiﬁed	_	0	SENT_45	[p4l1013t2715r1351b2778],
4	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_45	[p4l1395t2715r1673b2796],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_45	[p4l1716t2715r1823b2778],
6	hospital	NN	O	hospital	nn	8	SENT_45	[p4l1868t2715r2151b2796],
7	urological	JJ	O	urological	amod	8	SENT_45	[p4l8t2825r371b2906],
8	services	NNS	O	service	prep_through	3	SENT_45	[p4l393t2824r675b2887],
9	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_45	[p4l696t2834r758b2887],
10	diagnosis	NN	O	diagnosis	prep_at	8	SENT_45	[p4l775t2825r1110b2906],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p4l1131t2825r1258b2887],
12	were	VBD	O	be	cop	13	SENT_45	[p4l1275t2844r1446b2887],
13	patients	NNS	O	patient	conj_and	3	SENT_45	[p4l1463t2825r1741b2906],
14	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_45	[p4l1760t2825r1917b2887],
15	newly	RB	O	newly	advmod	16	SENT_45	[p4l1934t2825r2151b2906],
16	diagnosed	VBN	O	diagnose	prepc_with	13	SENT_45	[p4l9t2936r372b3017],
17	histologically	RB	O	histologically	advmod	3	SENT_45	[p4l395t2936r884b3017],
18	conﬁrmed	VBN	O	conﬁrmed	dep	3	SENT_45	[p4l910t2935r1272b2998],
19	primary	JJ	O	primary	amod	21	SENT_45	[p4l1295t2936r1579b3017],
20	bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	21	SENT_45	[p4l1602t2936r1873b2998],
21	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dobj	18	SENT_45	[p4l1897t2955r2148b3009],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p4l1897t2955r2148b3009],

1	@	IN	O	@	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l7t3179r84b3274],
2	Springer	NNP	PERSON	Springer	pobj	1	SENT_46	[p4l114t3202r376b3277],
3	aged	JJ	O	aged	amod	2	SENT_46	[p4l9t3304r176b3385],
4	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l204t3304r503b3367],
5	20	CD	NUMBER	20	nn	8	SENT_46	[p4l535t3305r621b3367],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l653t3304r779b3367],
7	80	CD	DURATION	80	nn	8	SENT_46	[p4l812t3305r896b3367],
8	years	NNS	NUMBER	year	prep_between	3	SENT_46	[p4l929t3324r1114b3385],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1148t3304r1274b3367],
10	living	VBG	O	live	conj_and	3	SENT_46	[p4l1305t3304r1511b3385],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1543t3304r1610b3366],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_46	[p4l1640t3304r1747b3367],
13	catchment	NN	O	catchment	nn	14	SENT_46	[p4l1779t3304r2149b3367],
14	area	NN	O	area	prep_in	10	SENT_46	[p4l9t3435r156b3478],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l188t3415r265b3478],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_46	[p4l292t3415r399b3478],
17	participating	VBG	O	participate	amod	18	SENT_46	[p4l431t3415r884b3496],
18	hospitals	NNS	O	hospital	prep_of	14	SENT_46	[p4l917t3415r1253b3496],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l917t3415r1253b3496],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1290t3417r1363b3477],
2	addition	NN	O	addition	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1397t3415r1688b3478],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1720t3425r1787b3478],
4	registries	NNS	O	registry	prep_in_addition_to	13	SENT_47	[p4l1819t3415r2145b3496],
5	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l8t3526r180b3588],
6	urological	JJ	O	urological	amod	7	SENT_47	[p4l209t3526r572b3607],
7	services	NNS	O	service	prep_from	4	SENT_47	[p4l605t3526r909b3600],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l605t3526r909b3600],
9	complete	JJ	O	complete	amod	11	SENT_47	[p4l942t3526r1269b3607],
10	case	NN	O	case	nn	11	SENT_47	[p4l1301t3545r1451b3588],
11	ascertainment	NN	O	ascertainment	nsubjpass	13	SENT_47	[p4l1484t3526r1982b3588],
12	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_47	[p4l2011t3545r2146b3589],
13	secured	VBN	O	secure	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l10t3636r280b3698],
14	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l298t3636r386b3717],
15	regular	JJ	O	regular	amod	16	SENT_47	[p4l405t3636r660b3717],
16	evaluations	NNS	O	evaluation	agent	13	SENT_47	[p4l680t3636r1085b3698],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1107t3636r1184b3698],
18	hospital	NN	O	hospital	nn	20	SENT_47	[p4l1197t3636r1480b3717],
19	discharge	NN	O	discharge	nn	20	SENT_47	[p4l1502t3636r1842b3717],
20	records	NNS	O	record	prep_of	16	SENT_47	[p4l1862t3636r2143b3709],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1862t3636r2143b3709],

1	pathology	NN	O	pathology	_	0	SENT_48	[p5l6t22r364b103],
2	records	NNS	O	record	dep	1	SENT_48	[p5l383t22r665b96],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p5l383t22r665b96],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_48	[p5l690t22r816b84],
5	local	JJ	O	local	amod	7	SENT_48	[p5l835t22r1007b84],
6	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	7	SENT_48	[p5l1028t41r1261b84],
7	registries	NNS	O	registry	conj_and	2	SENT_48	[p5l1279t22r1624b103],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p5l1279t22r1624b103],

1	Controls	NNP	O	Controls	nsubj	3	SENT_49	[p5l1650t22r1954b85],
2	were	VBD	O	be	cop	3	SENT_49	[p5l1976t41r2146b85],
3	patients	NNS	O	patient	_	0	SENT_49	[p5l6t134r283b215],
4	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_49	[p5l313t134r469b197],
5	diagnoses	NNS	O	diagnosis	prep_with	3	SENT_49	[p5l496t134r845b215],
6	unrelated	JJ	O	unrelated	amod	5	SENT_49	[p5l874t134r1207b197],
7	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_49	[p5l1234t144r1300b197],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_49	[p5l1328t134r1435b197],
9	bladder	NN	O	bladder	nn	12	SENT_49	[p5l1461t134r1731b197],
10	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	12	SENT_49	[p5l1757t154r1991b197],
11	risk	NN	O	risk	nn	12	SENT_49	[p5l2015t134r2150b197],
12	factors	NNS	O	factor	prep_to	6	SENT_49	[p5l8t245r248b308],
13	under	IN	O	under	_	0	SENT_49	[p5l291t245r496b308],
14	study	NN	O	study	nn	18	SENT_49	[p5l539t245r747b326],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p5l539t245r747b326],
16	particularly	RB	O	particularly	advmod	18	SENT_49	[p5l792t245r1206b326],
17	tobacco	NN	O	tobacco	nn	18	SENT_49	[p5l1249t245r1525b308],
18	use	NN	O	use	prep_under	12	SENT_49	[p5l1569t265r1704b308],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p5l1569t265r1704b308],

1	They	PRP	O	they	nsubjpass	4	SENT_50	[p5l1751t245r1932b326],
2	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_50	[p5l1976t265r2146b308],
3	individually	RB	O	individually	advmod	4	SENT_50	[p5l7t356r440b437],
4	matched	VBN	O	match	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l467t356r771b419],
5	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l796t366r863b419],
6	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_to	4	SENT_50	[p5l891t376r1076b419],
7	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l1103t356r1190b437],
8	gender	NN	O	gender	agent	4	SENT_50	[p5l1218t356r1478b437],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l1218t356r1478b437],
10	age	NN	O	age	nn	11	SENT_50	[p5l1510t376r1629b437],
11	group	NN	O	group	agent	4	SENT_50	[p5l1658t376r1863b437],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	13	SENT_50	[p5l1893t356r2149b437],
13	5	CD	NUMBER	5	amod	17	SENT_50	[p5l1893t356r2149b437],
14	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	15	SENT_50	[p5l1893t356r2149b437],
15	year	NN	NUMBER	year	tmod	13	SENT_50	[p5l1893t356r2149b437],
16	strata	NN	O	stratum	nn	17	SENT_50	[p5l10t468r249b545],
17	)	NN	O	)	dep	11	SENT_50	[p5l10t468r249b545],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l10t468r249b545],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l285t467r411b530],
20	residence	NN	O	residence	nn	21	SENT_50	[p5l440t467r779b530],
21	area	NN	O	area	conj_and	8	SENT_50	[p5l812t487r977b530],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l812t487r977b530],

1	Controls	NNP	O	Controls	nsubjpass	3	SENT_51	[p5l1013t467r1317b530],
2	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_51	[p5l1350t487r1521b530],
3	admitted	VBN	O	admit	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1555t467r1867b530],
4	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1897t477r1964b530],
5	hospitals	NNS	O	hospital	prep_to	3	SENT_51	[p5l1995t467r2145b530, p5l6t579r198b660],
6	for	IN	O	for	mark	8	SENT_51	[p5l239t579r343b642],
7	hernias	NNS	O	hernia	nsubj	8	SENT_51	[p5l379t579r635b642],
8	(	VBP	O	(	advcl	3	SENT_51	[p5l679t580r917b657],
9	37	CD	PERCENT	37	num	10	SENT_51	[p5l679t580r917b657],
10	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dobj	8	SENT_51	[p5l679t580r917b657],
11	)	CD	NUMBER	)	tmod	8	SENT_51	[p5l679t580r917b657],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l679t580r917b657],
13	other	JJ	O	other	amod	16	SENT_51	[p5l961t579r1143b642],
14	abdominal	JJ	O	abdominal	amod	16	SENT_51	[p5l1183t579r1558b642],
15	surgery	NN	O	surgery	nn	16	SENT_51	[p5l1601t599r1863b660],
16	(	NN	O	(	dep	19	SENT_51	[p5l1906t580r2144b657],
17	11	CD	PERCENT	11	number	18	SENT_51	[p5l1906t580r2144b657],
18	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	16	SENT_51	[p5l1906t580r2144b657],
19	)	CD	NUMBER	)	ccomp	3	SENT_51	[p5l1906t580r2144b657],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1906t580r2144b657],
21	fractures	NNS	O	fracture	nsubj	22	SENT_51	[p5l8t690r318b752],
22	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	3	SENT_51	[p5l345t690r583b767],
23	23	CD	PERCENT	23	num	24	SENT_51	[p5l345t690r583b767],
24	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dobj	22	SENT_51	[p5l345t690r583b767],
25	)	CD	NUMBER	)	tmod	22	SENT_51	[p5l345t690r583b767],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l345t690r583b767],
27	other	JJ	O	other	amod	29	SENT_51	[p5l610t690r793b752],
28	orthopedic	JJ	O	orthopedic	amod	29	SENT_51	[p5l815t690r1194b771],
29	problems	NNS	O	problem	nsubj	30	SENT_51	[p5l1217t690r1549b771],
30	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	3	SENT_51	[p5l1576t690r1769b767],
31	7	CD	PERCENT	7	num	32	SENT_51	[p5l1576t690r1769b767],
32	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dobj	30	SENT_51	[p5l1576t690r1769b767],
33	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	32	SENT_51	[p5l1576t690r1769b767],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1576t690r1769b767],
35	hydrocele	NN	O	hydrocele	appos	32	SENT_51	[p5l1794t690r2147b771],
36	(	CD	PERCENT	(	num	35	SENT_51	[p5l10t801r248b878],
37	12	CD	PERCENT	12	number	38	SENT_51	[p5l10t801r248b878],
38	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	35	SENT_51	[p5l10t801r248b878],
39	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	35	SENT_51	[p5l10t801r248b878],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l10t801r248b878],
41	circulatory	JJ	O	circulatory	amod	42	SENT_51	[p5l275t801r662b882],
42	disorders	NNS	O	disorder	nsubj	43	SENT_51	[p5l687t801r1012b863],
43	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	3	SENT_51	[p5l1039t801r1232b878],
44	4	CD	PERCENT	4	num	45	SENT_51	[p5l1039t801r1232b878],
45	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dobj	43	SENT_51	[p5l1039t801r1232b878],
46	)	CD	NUMBER	)	tmod	43	SENT_51	[p5l1039t801r1232b878],
47	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1039t801r1232b878],
48	dermatological	JJ	O	dermatological	amod	49	SENT_51	[p5l1260t801r1797b882],
49	disorders	NNS	O	disorder	nsubj	50	SENT_51	[p5l1821t801r2146b863],
50	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	3	SENT_51	[p5l10t911r203b988],
51	2	CD	PERCENT	2	num	52	SENT_51	[p5l10t911r203b988],
52	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dobj	50	SENT_51	[p5l10t911r203b988],
53	)	CD	NUMBER	)	tmod	50	SENT_51	[p5l10t911r203b988],
54	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l10t911r203b988],
55	ophthalmologic	JJ	O	ophthalmologic	amod	56	SENT_51	[p5l249t911r810b992],
56	disorders	NNS	O	disorder	nsubj	57	SENT_51	[p5l854t911r1178b973],
57	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	3	SENT_51	[p5l1224t911r1417b988],
58	1	CD	PERCENT	1	num	59	SENT_51	[p5l1224t911r1417b988],
59	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dobj	57	SENT_51	[p5l1224t911r1417b988],
60	)	CD	NUMBER	)	tmod	57	SENT_51	[p5l1224t911r1417b988],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1224t911r1417b988],
62	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1464t911r1590b973],
63	other	JJ	O	other	amod	64	SENT_51	[p5l1632t911r1815b973],
64	diseases	NNS	O	disease	nsubj	65	SENT_51	[p5l1856t911r2146b973],
65	(	VBP	O	(	conj_and	3	SENT_51	[p5l10t1024r202b1100],
66	3	CD	PERCENT	3	num	67	SENT_51	[p5l10t1024r202b1100],
67	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dobj	65	SENT_51	[p5l10t1024r202b1100],
68	)	CD	NUMBER	)	tmod	65	SENT_51	[p5l10t1024r202b1100],
69	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l10t1024r202b1100],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_52	[p5l235t1023r371b1086],
2	study	NN	O	study	nsubjpass	4	SENT_52	[p5l404t1023r592b1104],
3	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_52	[p5l621t1043r756b1086],
4	approved	VBN	O	approve	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l788t1023r1118b1104],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l1145t1023r1233b1104],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_52	[p5l1261t1023r1368b1086],
7	ethics	NNS	O	ethic	nn	8	SENT_52	[p5l1398t1023r1603b1086],
8	committees	NNS	O	committee	agent	4	SENT_52	[p5l1634t1023r2045b1086],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l2076t1023r2153b1086],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_52	[p5l7t1134r114b1197],
11	participating	VBG	O	participate	amod	12	SENT_52	[p5l151t1134r605b1215],
12	centers	NNS	O	center	prep_of	8	SENT_52	[p5l644t1144r915b1208],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l644t1144r915b1208],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l958t1134r1084b1197],
15	subjects	NNS	O	subject	nsubjpass	17	SENT_52	[p5l1123t1134r1406b1215],
16	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	17	SENT_52	[p5l1446t1154r1616b1197],
17	enrolled	VBN	O	enrol	conj_and	4	SENT_52	[p5l1655t1134r1948b1197],
18	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l1986t1134r2149b1197],
19	written	VBN	O	write	amod	21	SENT_52	[p5l8t1245r261b1308],
20	informed	JJ	O	informed	amod	21	SENT_52	[p5l286t1245r614b1308],
21	consent	NN	O	consent	prep_after	17	SENT_52	[p5l640t1255r930b1308],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l640t1255r930b1308],

1	Personal	JJ	O	personal	amod	2	SENT_53	[p5l7t1468r314b1531],
2	information	NN	O	information	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l347t1468r770b1531],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l805t1468r931b1531],
4	response	NN	O	response	nn	5	SENT_53	[p5l962t1488r1273b1549],
5	rates	NNS	O	rate	conj_and	2	SENT_53	[p5l1306t1478r1472b1531],

1	Trained	VBN	O	train	amod	2	SENT_54	[p5l7t1692r286b1754],
2	interviewers	NNS	O	interviewer	_	0	SENT_54	[p5l324t1692r765b1755],
3	administered	VBN	O	administer	partmod	2	SENT_54	[p5l807t1692r1269b1754],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_54	[p5l1309t1711r1346b1754],
5	comprehensive	JJ	O	comprehensive	amod	7	SENT_54	[p5l1384t1692r1926b1773],
6	computer	NN	O	computer	nn	7	SENT_54	[p5l1966t1711r2145b1754, p5l6t1803r500b1884],
7	—	NN	O	—	dobj	3	SENT_54	[p5l1966t1711r2145b1754, p5l6t1803r500b1884],
8	assisted	VBN	O	assist	partmod	2	SENT_54	[p5l1966t1711r2145b1754, p5l6t1803r500b1884],
9	personal	JJ	O	personal	amod	10	SENT_54	[p5l524t1803r826b1884],
10	interview	NN	O	interview	dobj	8	SENT_54	[p5l853t1803r1190b1866],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_54	[p5l1220t1803r1475b1880],
12	CAPI	NNP	O	CAPI	dep	10	SENT_54	[p5l1220t1803r1475b1880],
13	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	12	SENT_54	[p5l1220t1803r1475b1880],
14	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_54	[p5l1503t1812r1569b1865],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_54	[p5l1596t1803r1703b1865],
16	participants	NNS	O	participant	prep_to	8	SENT_54	[p5l1728t1803r2146b1884],
17	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_54	[p5l8t1913r238b1994],
18	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	20	SENT_54	[p5l277t1913r441b1975],
19	hospital	NN	O	hospital	nn	20	SENT_54	[p5l476t1913r759b1994],
20	stay	NN	O	stay	prep_during	8	SENT_54	[p5l800t1922r956b1994],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p5l800t1922r956b1994],

1	Collected	VBN	O	collect	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l999t1913r1343b1976],
2	information	NN	O	information	dobj	1	SENT_55	[p5l1379t1913r1802b1975],
3	included	VBD	O	include	dep	1	SENT_55	[p5l1840t1913r2149b1975],
4	socio	NN	O	socio	dobj	3	SENT_55	[p5l10t2025r693b2106],
5	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	7	SENT_55	[p5l10t2025r693b2106],
6	demographic	JJ	O	demographic	amod	7	SENT_55	[p5l10t2025r693b2106],
7	characteristics	NNS	O	characteristic	nsubj	1	SENT_55	[p5l734t2025r1266b2099],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l734t2025r1266b2099],
9	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	10	SENT_55	[p5l1310t2025r1613b2106],
10	habits	NNS	O	habit	nsubj	1	SENT_55	[p5l1651t2025r1884b2099],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1651t2025r1884b2099],
12	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nn	13	SENT_55	[p5l1925t2025r2146b2088],
13	consumption	NN	O	consumption	nsubj	1	SENT_55	[p5l8t2136r489b2217],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l8t2136r489b2217],
15	occupational	JJ	O	occupational	nsubj	1	SENT_55	[p5l531t2136r1007b2217],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l531t2136r1007b2217],
17	residential	JJ	O	residential	amod	20	SENT_55	[p5l1047t2136r1421b2199],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1461t2136r1587b2199],
19	medical	JJ	O	medical	conj_and	17	SENT_55	[p5l1624t2136r1908b2199],
20	histories	NNS	O	history	conj_and	7	SENT_55	[p5l1944t2136r2144b2199, p5l6t2247r154b2321],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1944t2136r2144b2199, p5l6t2247r154b2321],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l212t2247r339b2310],
23	familial	JJ	O	familial	amod	24	SENT_55	[p5l392t2247r670b2310],
24	history	NN	O	history	conj_and	7	SENT_55	[p5l723t2247r970b2328],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1026t2247r1103b2310],
26	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	24	SENT_55	[p5l1151t2267r1400b2310],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1151t2267r1400b2310],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_56	[p5l1459t2248r1522b2309],
2	food	NN	O	food	nn	4	SENT_56	[p5l1575t2247r1737b2310],
3	frequency	NN	O	frequency	nn	4	SENT_56	[p5l1790t2247r2147b2328],
4	questionnaire	NN	O	questionnaire	nsubj	7	SENT_56	[p5l8t2358r489b2439],
5	was	VBD	O	be	cop	7	SENT_56	[p5l534t2378r668b2421],
6	self	NN	O	self	nn	7	SENT_56	[p5l716t2358r1354b2421],
7	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_56	[p5l716t2358r1354b2421],
8	administered	VBN	O	administer	partmod	7	SENT_56	[p5l716t2358r1354b2421],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p5l716t2358r1354b2421],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_57	[p5l1401t2360r1524b2421],
2	identiﬁed	VBD	O	identiﬁed	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l1567t2358r1906b2421],
3	1,457	CD	NUMBER	1,457	num	5	SENT_57	[p5l1957t2358r2145b2432],
4	eligible	JJ	O	eligible	amod	5	SENT_57	[p5l8t2469r275b2550],
5	cases	NNS	O	case	dobj	2	SENT_57	[p5l321t2489r505b2532],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l553t2469r679b2532],
7	1,465	CD	NUMBER	1,465	num	9	SENT_57	[p5l731t2469r917b2544],
8	eligible	JJ	O	eligible	amod	9	SENT_57	[p5l966t2469r1233b2550],
9	controls	NNS	O	control	conj_and	5	SENT_57	[p5l1279t2469r1583b2532],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l1279t2469r1583b2532],

1	Among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l1632t2470r1897b2550],
2	these	DT	O	these	prep_among	18	SENT_58	[p5l1942t2469r2144b2543],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l1942t2469r2144b2543],
4	84	CD	PERCENT	84	num	5	SENT_58	[p5l11t2581r165b2643],
5	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nsubj	18	SENT_58	[p5l11t2581r165b2643],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l196t2580r273b2643],
7	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	5	SENT_58	[p5l293t2600r478b2643],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	9	SENT_58	[p5l508t2581r576b2658],
9	n	NN	O	n	dep	7	SENT_58	[p5l508t2581r576b2658],
10	=	JJ	O	=	amod	12	SENT_58	[p5l613t2609r674b2633],
11	1,219	CD	NUMBER	1,219	tmod	10	SENT_58	[p5l717t2581r935b2658],
12	)	NN	O	)	dep	9	SENT_58	[p5l717t2581r935b2658],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l965t2580r1091b2643],
14	88	CD	PERCENT	88	num	15	SENT_58	[p5l1120t2581r1274b2643],
15	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_of	5	SENT_58	[p5l1120t2581r1274b2643],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l1305t2580r1382b2643],
17	controls	NNS	O	control	prep_of	15	SENT_58	[p5l1402t2580r1687b2643],
18	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l1717t2581r1786b2658],
19	n	NN	O	n	dobj	18	SENT_58	[p5l1717t2581r1786b2658],
20	=	JJ	O	=	amod	19	SENT_58	[p5l1822t2609r1883b2633],
21	1,271	CD	NUMBER	1,271	advmod	18	SENT_58	[p5l1927t2581r2145b2658],
22	)	CD	NUMBER	)	nsubj	23	SENT_58	[p5l1927t2581r2145b2658],
23	responded	VBD	O	respond	dep	18	SENT_58	[p5l6t2692r375b2773],
24	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l429t2701r496b2754],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_58	[p5l551t2692r658b2754],
26	questionnaire	NN	O	questionnaire	prep_to	23	SENT_58	[p5l715t2692r1215b2773],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l715t2692r1215b2773],

1	Biological	JJ	O	biological	amod	2	SENT_59	[p5l1275t2692r1648b2773],
2	samples	NNS	O	sample	nsubjpass	7	SENT_59	[p5l1706t2692r1988b2773],
3	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l2046t2692r2149b2754],
4	DNA	NN	MISC	dna	nn	5	SENT_59	[p5l7t2803r198b2866],
5	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	prep_for	2	SENT_59	[p5l232t2803r530b2884],
6	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_59	[p5l564t2822r735b2866],
7	obtained	VBN	O	obtain	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l768t2803r1076b2865],
8	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l1107t2803r1280b2865],
9	97	CD	PERCENT	97	num	10	SENT_59	[p5l1312t2803r1469b2866],
10	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_from	7	SENT_59	[p5l1312t2803r1469b2866],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l1505t2803r1583b2865],
12	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	10	SENT_59	[p5l1609t2822r1794b2865],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l1829t2803r1955b2865],
14	91	CD	PERCENT	91	num	15	SENT_59	[p5l1987t2803r2143b2866],
15	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_from	7	SENT_59	[p5l1987t2803r2143b2866],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l8t2914r85b2976],
17	controls	NNS	O	control	prep_of	15	SENT_59	[p5l112t2914r416b2976],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l112t2914r416b2976],

1	Of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l453t2914r549b2977],
2	these	DT	O	these	prep_of	11	SENT_60	[p5l574t2914r776b2988],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l574t2914r776b2988],
4	88.5	CD	PERCENT	88.5	num	5	SENT_60	[p5l815t2914r1036b2977],
5	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nsubj	11	SENT_60	[p5l815t2914r1036b2977],
6	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_60	[p5l1072t2933r1243b2976],
7	based	VBN	O	base	rcmod	5	SENT_60	[p5l1274t2914r1478b2976],
8	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l1509t2933r1596b2976],
9	blood	NN	O	blood	nn	10	SENT_60	[p5l1626t2914r1829b2976],
10	samples	NNS	O	sample	prep_on	7	SENT_60	[p5l1863t2914r2146b2995],
11	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l10t3026r195b3103],
12	94	CD	PERCENT	94	num	14	SENT_60	[p5l10t3026r195b3103],
13	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nn	14	SENT_60	[p5l10t3026r195b3103],
14	cases	NNS	O	case	dobj	11	SENT_60	[p5l233t3045r438b3099],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l233t3045r438b3099],
16	83	CD	PERCENT	83	number	17	SENT_60	[p5l478t3026r633b3088],
17	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	18	SENT_60	[p5l478t3026r633b3088],
18	controls	NNS	O	control	appos	14	SENT_60	[p5l671t3025r1006b3102],
19	)	RB	O	)	advmod	11	SENT_60	[p5l671t3025r1006b3102],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l671t3025r1006b3102],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l1044t3025r1170b3088],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_60	[p5l1202t3025r1310b3088],
23	rest	NN	O	rest	nsubj	24	SENT_60	[p5l1343t3035r1472b3088],
24	were	VBD	O	be	conj_and	11	SENT_60	[p5l1504t3045r1675b3088],
25	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l1710t3025r1883b3088],
26	buccal	JJ	O	buccal	amod	28	SENT_60	[p5l1913t3025r2147b3088],
27	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	28	SENT_60	[p5l8t3137r135b3200],
28	samples	NNS	O	sample	prep_from	24	SENT_60	[p5l171t3137r473b3218],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l171t3137r473b3218],

1	Coffee	NNP	O	Coffee	nn	2	SENT_61	[p5l8t3360r249b3424],
2	data	NNS	O	datum	_	0	SENT_61	[p5l283t3361r431b3423],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_62	[p5l6t3586r129b3647],
2	ascertained	VBD	O	ascertain	_	0	SENT_62	[p5l176t3584r578b3647],
3	whether	IN	O	whether	complm	7	SENT_62	[p5l623t3584r911b3647],
4	participants	NNS	O	participant	nsubj	7	SENT_62	[p5l953t3584r1370b3665],
5	had	VBD	O	have	aux	7	SENT_62	[p5l1416t3584r1545b3647],
6	ever	RB	O	ever	advmod	7	SENT_62	[p5l1589t3604r1743b3647],
7	consumed	VBN	O	consume	ccomp	2	SENT_62	[p5l1786t3584r2148b3647],
8	coffee	NN	O	coffee	dobj	7	SENT_62	[p5l8t3695r249b3769],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p5l8t3695r249b3769],
10	age	NN	O	age	appos	8	SENT_62	[p5l285t3714r405b3776],
11	when	WRB	O	when	advmod	12	SENT_62	[p5l437t3695r628b3758],
12	started	VBN	O	start	dep	10	SENT_62	[p5l661t3695r896b3757],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p5l928t3695r1054b3757],
14	quit	VBN	O	quit	dep	10	SENT_62	[p5l1085t3695r1222b3776],
15	coffee	NN	O	coffee	nn	16	SENT_62	[p5l1252t3695r1474b3757],
16	consumption	NN	O	consumption	dobj	14	SENT_62	[p5l1505t3695r1986b3776],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p5l1505t3695r1986b3776],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p5l2022t3695r2148b3757],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_62	[p6l7t22r114b84],
20	average	JJ	O	average	amod	21	SENT_62	[p6l159t41r434b103],
21	amount	NN	O	amount	conj_and	8	SENT_62	[p6l479t31r745b84],
22	consumed	VBN	O	consume	partmod	21	SENT_62	[p6l787t22r1149b84],
23	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_62	[p6l1189t41r1304b103],
24	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	22	SENT_62	[p6l1345t22r1471b103],
25	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_62	[p6l1514t22r1744b103],
26	adult	JJ	O	adult	amod	27	SENT_62	[p6l1789t22r1966b84],
27	life	NN	O	life	prep_during	22	SENT_62	[p6l2007t22r2142b84],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p6l2007t22r2142b84],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_63	[p6l7t133r144b195],
2	actual	JJ	O	actual	amod	3	SENT_63	[p6l174t133r385b195],
3	questions	NNS	O	question	nsubj	5	SENT_63	[p6l413t133r748b214],
4	were	VBD	O	be	cop	5	SENT_63	[p6l778t152r948b196],
5	“	CD	NUMBER	“	_	0	SENT_63	[p6l985t133r1159b195],
6	Did	VBD	O	do	rcmod	5	SENT_63	[p6l985t133r1159b195],
7	you	PRP	O	you	nsubj	9	SENT_63	[p6l1186t152r1317b214],
8	ever	RB	O	ever	advmod	9	SENT_63	[p6l1346t152r1499b196],
9	drink	VBP	O	drink	ccomp	6	SENT_63	[p6l1526t133r1714b195],
10	at	IN	O	at	quantmod	12	SENT_63	[p6l1742t142r1804b195],
11	least	JJS	O	least	mwe	10	SENT_63	[p6l1830t133r1993b195],
12	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	13	SENT_63	[p6l2021t152r2147b195],
13	cup	NN	O	cup	dobj	9	SENT_63	[p6l8t264r134b325],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_63	[p6l170t244r247b307],
15	coffee	NN	O	coffee	prep_of	13	SENT_63	[p6l276t244r497b307],
16	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_63	[p6l532t264r647b325],
17	week	NN	DURATION	week	prep_per	15	SENT_63	[p6l680t244r869b307],
18	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_63	[p6l901t244r1005b307],
19	a	DT	DURATION	a	det	20	SENT_63	[p6l1039t264r1076b307],
20	year	NN	DURATION	year	prep_for	17	SENT_63	[p6l1109t264r1263b325],
21	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_63	[p6l1298t264r1370b307],
22	longer	JJR	O	longer	prep_for	17	SENT_63	[p6l1403t244r1742b325],
23	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_63	[p6l1403t244r1742b325],

1	”	NN	O	”	_	0	SENT_64	[p6l1403t244r1742b325],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_64	[p6l1403t244r1742b325],
3	“	CD	NUMBER	“	dep	1	SENT_64	[p6l1789t245r2000b307],
4	How	WRB	O	how	advmod	5	SENT_64	[p6l1789t245r2000b307],
5	old	JJ	O	old	advmod	7	SENT_64	[p6l2036t244r2148b307],
6	were	VBD	O	be	cop	7	SENT_64	[p6l8t375r178b418],
7	you	PRP	O	you	rcmod	3	SENT_64	[p6l209t375r342b436],
8	when	WRB	O	when	advmod	10	SENT_64	[p6l372t355r564b418],
9	you	PRP	O	you	nsubj	10	SENT_64	[p6l593t375r725b436],
10	ﬁrst	VBP	O	ﬁrst	advcl	7	SENT_64	[p6l757t355r894b418],
11	had	VBD	O	have	ccomp	10	SENT_64	[p6l922t355r1050b418],
12	at	IN	O	at	quantmod	14	SENT_64	[p6l1082t365r1144b418],
13	least	JJS	O	least	mwe	12	SENT_64	[p6l1173t355r1337b418],
14	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	15	SENT_64	[p6l1367t375r1492b418],
15	cup	NN	O	cup	dobj	11	SENT_64	[p6l1523t375r1649b436],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_64	[p6l1681t355r1759b418],
17	coffee	NN	O	coffee	prep_of	15	SENT_64	[p6l1783t355r2004b418],
18	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_64	[p6l2034t375r2149b436],
19	week	NN	DURATION	week	prep_per	17	SENT_64	[p6l8t466r306b540],
20	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_64	[p6l8t466r306b540],

1	”	NN	O	”	_	0	SENT_65	[p6l8t466r306b540],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_65	[p6l8t466r306b540],
3	“	CD	NUMBER	“	dep	1	SENT_65	[p6l342t467r554b529],
4	How	WRB	O	how	advmod	5	SENT_65	[p6l342t467r554b529],
5	old	JJ	O	old	advmod	7	SENT_65	[p6l579t466r692b529],
6	were	VBD	O	be	cop	7	SENT_65	[p6l714t486r885b529],
7	you	PRP	O	you	rcmod	3	SENT_65	[p6l910t486r1042b547],
8	when	WRB	O	when	advmod	11	SENT_65	[p6l1066t466r1258b529],
9	you	PRP	O	you	nsubj	11	SENT_65	[p6l1281t486r1413b547],
10	last	JJ	O	last	advmod	11	SENT_65	[p6l1438t466r1561b529],
11	drank	VBD	O	drink	advcl	7	SENT_65	[p6l1585t466r1788b529],
12	coffee	NN	O	coffee	dobj	11	SENT_65	[p6l1810t466r2144b540],
13	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_65	[p6l1810t466r2144b540],

1	”	NN	O	”	nsubj	39	SENT_66	[p6l1810t466r2144b540],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l1810t466r2144b540],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l9t576r136b638],
4	“	CD	NUMBER	“	nsubj	39	SENT_66	[p6l184t576r552b657],
5	Thinking	VBG	O	think	partmod	4	SENT_66	[p6l184t576r552b657],
6	about	IN	O	about	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l595t576r791b638],
7	all	PDT	O	all	predet	9	SENT_66	[p6l833t576r919b638],
8	the	DT	DURATION	the	det	9	SENT_66	[p6l960t576r1067b638],
9	years	NNS	DURATION	year	prep_about	5	SENT_66	[p6l1108t595r1294b657],
10	that	IN	O	that	complm	12	SENT_66	[p6l1336t576r1470b638],
11	you	PRP	O	you	nsubj	12	SENT_66	[p6l1509t595r1641b657],
12	drank	VBD	O	drink	ccomp	5	SENT_66	[p6l1683t576r1886b638],
13	coffee	NN	O	coffee	dobj	12	SENT_66	[p6l1926t576r2146b638],
14	over	IN	O	over	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l8t708r166b751],
15	most	JJS	O	most	prep_over	12	SENT_66	[p6l193t698r366b751],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l394t688r471b751],
17	your	PRP$	O	you	poss	19	SENT_66	[p6l493t708r657b769],
18	adult	JJ	O	adult	amod	19	SENT_66	[p6l685t688r862b751],
19	life	NN	O	life	prep_of	15	SENT_66	[p6l890t688r1027b763],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l890t688r1027b763],
21	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	24	SENT_66	[p6l1058t688r1275b751],
22	could	MD	O	could	aux	24	SENT_66	[p6l1304t688r1501b751],
23	be	VB	O	be	cop	24	SENT_66	[p6l1528t688r1610b751],
24	different	JJ	O	different	rcmod	19	SENT_66	[p6l1640t688r1948b751],
25	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l1976t688r2148b751],
26	what	WP	O	what	dep	28	SENT_66	[p6l8t799r180b862],
27	you	PRP	O	you	nsubj	28	SENT_66	[p6l204t819r336b880],
28	do	VBP	O	do	prepc_from	24	SENT_66	[p6l361t799r446b862],
29	now	RB	DATE	now	advmod	28	SENT_66	[p6l471t819r642b873],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l471t819r642b873],
31	how	WRB	O	how	advmod	32	SENT_66	[p6l669t799r821b862],
32	many	JJ	O	many	dep	36	SENT_66	[p6l845t819r1043b880],
33	cups	NNS	O	cup	nsubj	36	SENT_66	[p6l1068t819r1228b880],
34	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l1255t799r1332b862],
35	coffee	NN	O	coffee	prep_of	33	SENT_66	[p6l1351t799r1572b862],
36	did	VBD	O	do	ccomp	28	SENT_66	[p6l1598t799r1710b862],
37	you	PRP	O	you	dobj	36	SENT_66	[p6l1734t819r1866b880],
38	usually	RB	O	usually	advmod	36	SENT_66	[p6l1889t799r2147b880],
39	drink	VBP	O	drink	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l8t910r196b972],
40	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l224t929r339b991],
41	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	39	SENT_66	[p6l369t910r603b991],
42	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_66	[p6l369t910r603b991],

1	”	NN	O	”	_	0	SENT_67	[p6l369t910r603b991],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p6l369t910r603b991],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_68	[p6l638t910r849b972],
2	questions	NNS	O	question	nsubjpass	4	SENT_68	[p6l882t910r1216b991],
3	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_68	[p6l1249t929r1419b973],
4	repeated	VBN	O	repeat	_	0	SENT_68	[p6l1450t910r1755b991],
5	separately	RB	O	separately	advmod	4	SENT_68	[p6l1788t910r2147b991],
6	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_68	[p6l8t1021r111b1083],
7	decaffeinated	VBN	O	decaffeinate	prep_for	4	SENT_68	[p6l143t1021r626b1083],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_68	[p6l660t1021r787b1083],
9	regular	JJ	O	regular	amod	10	SENT_68	[p6l818t1021r1072b1102],
10	coffee	NN	O	coffee	prep_for	4	SENT_68	[p6l1104t1021r1344b1083],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p6l1104t1021r1344b1083],

1	Genotyping	VBG	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_69	[p6l9t1244r428b1325],

1	Single	JJ	O	single	amod	3	SENT_70	[p6l10t1468r230b1549],
2	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	3	SENT_70	[p6l265t1468r630b1531],
3	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubj	4	SENT_70	[p6l664t1468r1210b1549],
4	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_70	[p6l1248t1468r1494b1545],
5	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	nsubj	14	SENT_70	[p6l1248t1468r1494b1545],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	nsubjpass	8	SENT_70	[p6l1248t1468r1494b1545],
7	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_70	[p6l1531t1488r1700b1531],
8	analyzed	VBN	O	analyze	rcmod	5	SENT_70	[p6l1736t1468r2048b1549],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_70	[p6l2081t1468r2149b1530],
10	DNA	NN	MISC	dna	prep_in	8	SENT_70	[p6l7t1578r197b1640],
11	extracted	VBN	O	extract	partmod	10	SENT_70	[p6l219t1578r540b1640],
12	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_70	[p6l561t1578r732b1640],
13	leukocytes	NNS	O	leukocyte	prep_from	11	SENT_70	[p6l751t1578r1125b1659],
14	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	4	SENT_70	[p6l1151t1578r1370b1655],
15	1,107	CD	NUMBER	1,107	num	16	SENT_70	[p6l1151t1578r1370b1655],
16	cases	NNS	O	case	dobj	14	SENT_70	[p6l1394t1597r1597b1652],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_70	[p6l1394t1597r1597b1652],
18	1,032	CD	NUMBER	1,032	num	19	SENT_70	[p6l1628t1578r1815b1652],
19	controls	NNS	O	control	appos	16	SENT_70	[p6l1838t1578r2145b1655],
20	)	IN	O	)	amod	19	SENT_70	[p6l1838t1578r2145b1655],

1	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	nsubj	2	SENT_71	[p6l53t1734r153b1759],
2	Causes	VBZ	O	cause	_	0	SENT_71	[p6l165t1734r263b1759],
3	Control	NN	O	control	dobj	2	SENT_71	[p6l277t1734r383b1759],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	3	SENT_71	[p6l397t1734r488b1764],
5	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	6	SENT_71	[p6l397t1734r488b1764],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	2	SENT_71	[p6l397t1734r488b1764],
7	201121-127	CD	NUMBER	201121-127	num	8	SENT_71	[p6l503t1734r669b1759],
8	123	CD	NUMBER	123	dep	6	SENT_71	[p6l2058t1734r2105b1759],

1	or	CC	O	or	cc	4	SENT_72	[p6l8t1922r81b1965],
2	mouthwash	NN	O	mouthwash	nn	3	SENT_72	[p6l105t1902r510b1965],
3	samples	NNS	O	sample	nsubj	4	SENT_72	[p6l538t1902r814b1983],
4	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_72	[p6l845t1903r954b1979],
5	43	CD	NUMBER	43	num	6	SENT_72	[p6l845t1903r954b1979],
6	cases	NNS	O	case	dobj	4	SENT_72	[p6l984t1922r1186b1976],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p6l984t1922r1186b1976],
8	117	CD	NUMBER	117	num	9	SENT_72	[p6l1224t1903r1342b1965],
9	controls	NNS	O	control	appos	6	SENT_72	[p6l1372t1902r1697b1980],
10	)	RB	O	)	advmod	4	SENT_72	[p6l1372t1902r1697b1980],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p6l1372t1902r1697b1980],

1	Genotyping	VBG	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1730t1902r2140b1983],
2	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_73	[p6l8t2033r140b2076],
3	performed	VBN	O	perform	aux	1	SENT_73	[p6l157t2013r523b2094],
4	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l540t2023r602b2076],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_73	[p6l615t2013r721b2076],
6	Core	NNP	O	Core	nn	8	SENT_73	[p6l738t2014r906b2076],
7	Genotyping	NNP	O	Genotyping	nn	8	SENT_73	[p6l923t2013r1335b2094],
8	Facility	NNP	O	Facility	prep_at	3	SENT_73	[p6l1350t2013r1617b2094],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1634t2013r1711b2076],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_73	[p6l1719t2013r1825b2076],
11	Division	NN	O	division	prep_of	8	SENT_73	[p6l1841t2013r2142b2076],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l8t2124r85b2186],
13	Cancer	NN	ORGANIZATION	cancer	nn	14	SENT_73	[p6l109t2124r358b2187],
14	Epidemiology	NN	ORGANIZATION	epidemiology	prep_of	11	SENT_73	[p6l385t2124r881b2205],
15	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l913t2124r1038b2186],
16	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	nn	21	SENT_73	[p6l1068t2124r1391b2198],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1068t2124r1391b2198],
18	US	NNP	ORGANIZATION	US	appos	21	SENT_73	[p6l1423t2124r1530b2187],
19	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	21	SENT_73	[p6l1563t2124r1864b2186],
20	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	21	SENT_73	[p6l1895t2124r2144b2187],
21	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	conj_and	8	SENT_73	[p6l7t2234r292b2296],
22	using	VBG	O	use	partmod	21	SENT_73	[p6l323t2234r511b2315],
23	TaqMan	NNP	O	TaqMan	nn	27	SENT_73	[p6l543t2215r891b2315],
24	®	CD	NUMBER	®	num	27	SENT_73	[p6l543t2215r891b2315],
25	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	27	SENT_73	[p6l927t2234r1236b2315],
26	Applied	NNP	O	Applied	nn	27	SENT_73	[p6l927t2234r1236b2315],
27	Biosystems	NNP	O	Biosystems	dobj	22	SENT_73	[p6l1266t2234r1687b2315],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1266t2234r1687b2315],
29	Foster	NNP	LOCATION	Foster	nn	30	SENT_73	[p6l1721t2236r1941b2296],
30	City	NNP	LOCATION	City	conj_and	27	SENT_73	[p6l1971t2234r2139b2315],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1971t2234r2139b2315],
32	CA	NNP	LOCATION	CA	conj_and	27	SENT_73	[p6l8t2345r146b2419],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l8t2345r146b2419],
34	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	conj_and	27	SENT_73	[p6l190t2345r391b2422],
35	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	34	SENT_73	[p6l190t2345r391b2422],
36	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l435t2345r559b2407],
37	Go1denGate	NN	O	go1dengate	conj_and	27	SENT_73	[p6l600t2326r1072b2408],
38	®	CD	NUMBER	®	num	41	SENT_73	[p6l600t2326r1072b2408],
39	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	41	SENT_73	[p6l1117t2326r1510b2422],
40	Illumina	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Illumina	nn	41	SENT_73	[p6l1117t2326r1510b2422],
41	®	NNP	O	®	nsubj	1	SENT_73	[p6l1117t2326r1510b2422],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1117t2326r1510b2422],
43	San	NNP	LOCATION	San	nn	48	SENT_73	[p6l1556t2345r1684b2408],
44	Diego	NNP	LOCATION	Diego	nn	48	SENT_73	[p6l1724t2345r1956b2426],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1724t2345r1956b2426],
46	CA	NNP	LOCATION	CA	appos	48	SENT_73	[p6l2000t2345r2139b2419],
47	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l2000t2345r2139b2419],
48	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	appos	41	SENT_73	[p6l7t2458r208b2534],
49	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	48	SENT_73	[p6l7t2458r208b2534],
50	assays	NNS	O	assay	dep	48	SENT_73	[p6l238t2477r475b2538],
51	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l238t2477r475b2538],

1	Procedure	NN	O	procedure	nsubjpass	5	SENT_74	[p6l506t2457r860b2520],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l889t2457r965b2520],
3	genotyping	NN	O	genotyping	prep_of	1	SENT_74	[p6l987t2457r1378b2538],
4	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_74	[p6l1405t2457r1461b2520],
5	detailed	VBN	O	detail	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l1490t2457r1766b2520],
6	elsewhere	RB	O	elsewhere	advmod	5	SENT_74	[p6l1792t2457r2140b2520],
7	[	RB	O	[	amod	11	SENT_74	[p6l14t2569r140b2644],
8	19	CD	NUMBER	19	tmod	7	SENT_74	[p6l14t2569r140b2644],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l14t2569r140b2644],
10	20	CD	NUMBER	20	dep	11	SENT_74	[p6l172t2569r303b2644],
11	]	NN	O	]	dobj	5	SENT_74	[p6l172t2569r303b2644],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l172t2569r303b2644],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_75	[p6l333t2568r468b2631],
2	description	NN	O	description	nsubjpass	10	SENT_75	[p6l497t2568r885b2649],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_75	[p6l912t2568r1036b2631],
4	methods	NNS	O	method	conj_and	2	SENT_75	[p6l1062t2568r1356b2631],
5	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_75	[p6l1385t2568r1487b2631],
6	each	DT	O	each	det	7	SENT_75	[p6l1512t2568r1672b2631],
7	assay	NN	O	assay	prep_for	2	SENT_75	[p6l1700t2588r1885b2649],
8	can	MD	O	can	aux	10	SENT_75	[p6l1913t2588r2034b2631],
9	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_75	[p6l2059t2568r2141b2631],
10	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_75	[p6l8t2679r211b2742],
11	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_75	[p6l265t2689r327b2742],
12	http://snp500cancer.nci.nih.gov	NN	O	http://snp500cancer.nci.nih.gov	prep_at	10	SENT_75	[p6l377t2679r1500b2760],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p6l377t2679r1500b2760],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_76	[p6l1558t2679r1692b2742],
2	four	CD	NUMBER	four	num	3	SENT_76	[p6l1746t2679r1893b2742],
3	genes	NNS	O	gene	nsubj	4	SENT_76	[p6l1944t2699r2139b2760],
4	included	VBN	O	include	dep	9	SENT_76	[p6l7t2790r310b2853],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l348t2790r416b2852],
6	this	DT	O	this	det	7	SENT_76	[p6l455t2790r578b2853],
7	analysis	NN	O	analysis	prep_in	4	SENT_76	[p6l622t2790r899b2871],
8	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_76	[p6l941t2810r1110b2853],
9	selected	VBN	O	select	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l1153t2790r1432b2853],
10	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l1471t2790r1642b2853],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_76	[p6l1680t2790r1785b2853],
12	literature	NN	O	literature	prep_from	9	SENT_76	[p6l1827t2790r2140b2853],
13	based	VBN	O	base	partmod	12	SENT_76	[p6l6t2901r206b2964],
14	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l259t2921r345b2964],
15	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	16	SENT_76	[p6l395t2901r556b2964],
16	effect	NN	O	effect	prep_on	13	SENT_76	[p6l607t2901r806b2964],
17	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l857t2921r944b2964],
18	caffeine	NN	O	caffeine	nn	19	SENT_76	[p6l995t2901r1276b2964],
19	metabolism	NN	O	metabolism	prep_on	16	SENT_76	[p6l1328t2901r1739b2964],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	21	SENT_76	[p6l1791t2902r2138b2979],
21	CYPIA2	NN	O	cypia2	nsubjpass	9	SENT_76	[p6l1791t2902r2138b2979],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l1791t2902r2138b2979],
23	CYPIAI	NNP	O	CYPIAI	appos	21	SENT_76	[p6l12t3012r328b3085],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l12t3012r328b3085],
25	CYPZEI	NNP	O	CYPZEI	appos	21	SENT_76	[p6l368t3012r660b3074],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l701t3012r826b3074],
27	NAT	NNP	O	NAT	appos	21	SENT_76	[p6l855t3013r1027b3074],
28	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	29	SENT_76	[p6l1019t3012r1109b3088],
29	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	23	SENT_76	[p6l1019t3012r1109b3088],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l1019t3012r1109b3088],

1	SNP	NN	ORGANIZATION	snp	nn	2	SENT_77	[p6l1148t3012r1306b3074],
2	selection	NN	O	selection	nsubj	3	SENT_77	[p6l1342t3012r1649b3074],
3	favored	VBD	O	favor	ccomp	9	SENT_77	[p6l1683t3012r1950b3074],
4	nonsynonymous	JJ	O	nonsynonymous	amod	5	SENT_77	[p6l1982t3031r2139b3074, p6l10t3142r448b3204],
5	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	dobj	3	SENT_77	[p6l479t3123r688b3197],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l479t3123r688b3197],
7	those	DT	O	those	nsubj	9	SENT_77	[p6l718t3123r901b3185],
8	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	9	SENT_77	[p6l927t3123r1297b3204],
9	evaluated	VBN	O	evaluate	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l1325t3123r1660b3186],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l1687t3123r1755b3185],
11	relation	NN	O	relation	prep_in	9	SENT_77	[p6l1780t3123r2047b3185],
12	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l2074t3132r2141b3185],
13	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	14	SENT_77	[p6l8t3253r238b3296],
14	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_to	9	SENT_77	[p6l259t3234r391b3296],
15	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l414t3253r486b3296],
16	those	DT	O	those	conj_or	14	SENT_77	[p6l508t3234r690b3296],
17	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l715t3234r871b3297],
18	evidence	NN	O	evidence	prep_with	9	SENT_77	[p6l894t3234r1205b3297],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l1230t3234r1307b3296],
20	functional	JJ	O	functional	amod	21	SENT_77	[p6l1324t3234r1677b3296],
21	signiﬁcance	NN	O	signiﬁcance	prep_of	18	SENT_77	[p6l1705t3234r2137b3315],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l1705t3234r2137b3315],

1	All	DT	O	all	nsubj	4	SENT_78	[p6l7t3345r117b3407],
2	studied	VBN	O	study	partmod	1	SENT_78	[p6l139t3345r388b3408],
3	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	dobj	2	SENT_78	[p6l408t3346r596b3408],
4	were	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_78	[p6l617t3365r786b3408],
5	under	IN	O	under	_	0	SENT_78	[p6l804t3345r1004b3408],
6	Hardy	NNP	PERSON	Hardy	prep_under	4	SENT_78	[p6l1021t3345r1629b3426],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_78	[p6l1021t3345r1629b3426],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_79	[p6l1021t3345r1629b3426],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_79	[p6l1021t3345r1629b3426],

1	Weinberg	NNP	PERSON	Weinberg	_	0	SENT_80	[p6l1021t3345r1629b3426],
2	equilibrium	NN	O	equilibrium	dep	1	SENT_80	[p6l1649t3345r2058b3426],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_80	[p6l2075t3345r2142b3407],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_80	[p6l7t3456r112b3519],
5	control	NN	O	control	nn	6	SENT_80	[p6l133t3456r378b3519],
6	population	NN	O	population	prep_in	2	SENT_80	[p6l396t3456r771b3537],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_80	[p6l792t3456r916b3519],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_80	[p6l934t3456r1088b3519],
9	minor	JJ	O	minor	amod	11	SENT_80	[p6l1106t3456r1317b3519],
10	allele	NN	O	allele	nn	11	SENT_80	[p6l1336t3456r1522b3519],
11	frequency	NN	O	frequency	prep_with	2	SENT_80	[p6l1542t3456r1890b3537],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	13	SENT_80	[p6l1912t3457r2153b3533],
13	MAF	NN	O	maf	dep	2	SENT_80	[p6l1912t3457r2153b3533],
14	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	15	SENT_80	[p6l1912t3457r2153b3533],
15	>	JJR	O	>	dep	1	SENT_80	[p6l23t3567r249b3630],
16	0.05	CD	NUMBER	0.05	dep	15	SENT_80	[p6l23t3567r249b3630],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_80	[p6l23t3567r249b3630],

1	Pairwise	JJ	MISC	pairwise	amod	6	SENT_81	[p6l281t3567r580b3630],
2	linkage	NN	O	linkage	nn	6	SENT_81	[p6l608t3567r864b3648],
3	disequilibrium	NN	O	disequilibrium	nn	6	SENT_81	[p6l893t3567r1404b3648],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_81	[p6l1432t3568r1600b3644],
5	LD	NN	O	ld	nn	6	SENT_81	[p6l1432t3568r1600b3644],
6	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	10	SENT_81	[p6l1432t3568r1600b3644],
7	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_81	[p6l1629t3567r1923b3630],
8	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	prep_between	6	SENT_81	[p6l1951t3567r2139b3630],
9	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_81	[p6l8t3697r140b3740],
10	estimated	VBN	O	estimate	_	0	SENT_81	[p6l167t3677r503b3739],
11	based	VBN	O	base	_	0	SENT_81	[p6l525t3677r724b3739],
12	on	IN	O	on	prepc_based_on	10	SENT_81	[p6l749t3697r834b3739],
13	D’	NN	O	d’	nn	16	SENT_81	[p6l856t3671r937b3738],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_81	[p6l967t3677r1091b3739],
15	r2	NN	O	r2	nn	16	SENT_81	[p6l1117t3658r1179b3738],
16	values	NNS	O	value	pobj	10	SENT_81	[p6l1203t3677r1424b3739],
17	using	VBG	O	use	partmod	16	SENT_81	[p6l1449t3677r1637b3758],
18	R.	NNP	O	R.	dobj	17	SENT_81	[p6l1659t3679r1731b3739],

1	Statistical	JJ	O	statistical	amod	2	SENT_82	[p7l9t111r359b174],
2	analysis	NN	O	analysis	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l394t111r677b192],
