1	60	CD	NUMBER	60	dep	8	SENT_2	[p1l1929t83r1963b108],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1929t83r1963b108],
3	No.	NN	O	no.	appos	1	SENT_2	[p1l1975t82r2018b104],
4	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	3	SENT_2	[p1l2030t82r2050b108],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l2030t82r2050b108],
6	2012	CD	DATE	2012	appos	1	SENT_2	[p1l2061t83r2118b104],
7	©	CD	DATE	©	dep	8	SENT_2	[p1l45t114r66b137],
8	2012	CD	DATE	2012	dep	17	SENT_2	[p1l77t115r135b137],
9	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l145t114r174b144],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_2	[p1l183t114r219b136],
11	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	12	SENT_2	[p1l229t114r345b136],
12	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	prep_by	8	SENT_2	[p1l356t114r444b144],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l455t114r482b136],
14	Cardiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cardiology	nn	16	SENT_2	[p1l489t114r619b144],
15	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Foundation	nn	16	SENT_2	[p1l629t114r765b136],
16	ISSN	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ISSN	prep_of	12	SENT_2	[p1l1825t114r1890b137],
17	0735-1097	CD	DURATION	0735-1097	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1901t114r2118b137],
18	/	:	O	/	punct	19	SENT_2	[p1l1901t114r2118b137],
19	$	$	MONEY	$	dep	17	SENT_2	[p1l1901t114r2118b137],
20	36.00	CD	MONEY	36.00	num	19	SENT_2	[p1l1901t114r2118b137],
21	Published	VBN	O	publish	partmod	17	SENT_2	[p1l44t147r159b169],
22	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l169t147r198b177],
23	Elsevier	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Elsevier	nn	25	SENT_2	[p1l208t147r300b169],
24	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	nn	25	SENT_2	[p1l310t147r353b169],
25	http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.jacc.2012.03.031	NN	O	http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.jacc.2012.03.031	agent	21	SENT_2	[p1l1597t147r2117b177],

1	Heart	NNP	O	Heart	nn	3	SENT_3	[p1l1611t237r1718b265],
2	Rhythm	NNP	O	Rhythm	nn	3	SENT_3	[p1l1735t237r1882b272],
3	Disorders	NNPS	O	Disorders	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1900t236r2089b265],

1	Common	JJ	O	common	amod	2	SENT_4	[p1l119t357r392b416],
2	Variation	NN	O	variation	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l421t358r705b416],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l737t358r790b415],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_4	[p1l818t358r919b416],
5	NOSIAP	NN	O	nosiap	nn	6	SENT_4	[p1l950t357r1216b416],
6	Gene	NN	O	gene	prep_in	2	SENT_4	[p1l1236t357r1393b416],

1	Is	VBZ	O	be	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l122t458r174b516],
2	Associated	NNP	O	Associated	nsubj	1	SENT_5	[p1l200t458r540b516],
3	With	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l570t458r713b516],
4	Drug-Induced	JJ	O	drug-induced	prep_with	1	SENT_5	[p1l746t458r1167b527],

1	QT	NNP	O	QT	nn	2	SENT_6	[p1l119t557r203b627],
2	Prolongation	NNP	O	Prolongation	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l232t558r630b627],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l661t558r773b616],
4	Ventricular	JJ	O	ventricular	amod	5	SENT_6	[p1l802t558r1154b616],
5	Arrhythmia	NN	O	arrhythmium	conj_and	2	SENT_6	[p1l1179t558r1528b627],

1	Yalda	NNP	PERSON	Yalda	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l118t702r224b736],
2	Jamshidi	NNP	PERSON	Jamshidi	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l235t702r410b745],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l235t702r410b745],
4	PHD	NNP	O	PHD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l428t702r547b744],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l428t702r547b744],
6	*	CD	NUMBER	*	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l428t702r547b744],
7	Ilja	NNP	PERSON	Ilja	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l563t702r622b748],
8	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l637t702r691b736],
9	Nolte	NNP	PERSON	Nolte	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l710t702r824b744],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l710t702r824b744],
11	PHD	NNP	O	PHD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l842t702r968b743],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l842t702r968b743],
13	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l842t702r968b743],
14	r	NN	O	r	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l842t702r968b743],
15	Chrysoula	NNP	PERSON	Chrysoula	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l987t702r1173b748],
16	Dalageorgou	NNP	PERSON	Dalageorgou	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1189t702r1434b748],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1189t702r1434b748],
18	BSC	NNP	O	BSC	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1453t702r1558b743],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1453t702r1558b743],
20	*	CD	NUMBER	*	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1453t702r1558b743],
21	Dongling	NNP	PERSON	Dongling	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1575t702r1752b748],
22	Zheng	NNP	PERSON	Zheng	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1768t702r1899b748],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1768t702r1899b748],
24	PHD	NNP	O	PHD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1918t702r2036b743],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1918t702r2036b743],
26	*	NNP	O	*	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1918t702r2036b743],
27	Toby	NNP	PERSON	Toby	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l118t757r218b804],
28	Johnson	NNP	PERSON	Johnson	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l228t758r392b801],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l228t758r392b801],
30	PHD	NNP	O	PHD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l410t758r537b799],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l410t758r537b799],
32	IlI	NNP	O	IlI	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l410t758r537b799],
33	Rachel	NNP	PERSON	Rachel	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l555t758r679b792],
34	Bastiaenen	NNP	PERSON	Bastiaenen	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l696t758r904b799],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l696t758r904b799],
36	MBBS	NNP	O	MBBS	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l922t758r1085b799],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l922t758r1085b799],
38	§	NNP	O	§	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l922t758r1085b799],
39	Suzanne	NNP	PERSON	Suzanne	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1107t758r1259b792],
40	Ruddy	NNP	PERSON	Ruddy	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1277t758r1408b804],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1277t758r1408b804],
42	PHD	NNP	O	PHD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1426t758r1545b799],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1426t758r1545b799],
44	*	NNP	O	*	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1426t758r1545b799],
45	Daniel	NNP	PERSON	Daniel	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1562t758r1686b792],
46	Talbott	NNP	PERSON	Talbott	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1700t757r1849b800],
47	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1700t757r1849b800],
48	BSC	NNP	O	BSC	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1867t758r1973b800],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1867t758r1973b800],
50	*	CD	NUMBER	*	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1867t758r1973b800],
51	Kris	NNP	PERSON	Kris	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l121t815r234b858],
52	Norris	NNP	PERSON	Norris	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l253t815r381b856],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l253t815r381b856],
54	RN	NNP	O	RN	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l401t810r492b859],
55	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l401t810r492b859],
56	“	NNP	O	“	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l401t810r492b859],
57	Harold	NNP	PERSON	Harold	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l511t814r642b849],
58	Snieder	NNP	PERSON	Snieder	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l660t814r807b856],
59	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l660t814r807b856],
60	PHD	NNP	O	PHD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l826t814r952b856],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l826t814r952b856],
62	T	NN	O	t	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l826t814r952b856],
63	Alfred	NNP	PERSON	Alfred	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l968t814r1087b849],
64	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1104t815r1141b849],
65	George	NNP	PERSON	George	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1161t814r1306b861],
66	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1161t814r1306b861],
67	MD	NNP	O	MD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1324t810r1430b859],
68	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1324t810r1430b859],
69	“	NNP	O	“	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1324t810r1430b859],
70	Vanessa	NNP	PERSON	Vanessa	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1449t815r1596b849],
71	Marshall	NNP	PERSON	Marshall	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1612t814r1785b856],
72	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1612t814r1785b856],
73	MBBSAI	NNP	O	MBBSAI	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1803t814r1970b856],
74	Saad	NNP	PERSON	Saad	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l121t871r206b905],
75	Shakir	NNP	PERSON	Shakir	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l225t871r351b913],
76	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l225t871r351b913],
77	MD	NNP	O	MD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l369t871r488b913],
78	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l369t871r488b913],
79	l	NN	O	l	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l369t871r488b913],
80	Prince	NNP	PERSON	Prince	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l506t871r662b915],
81	Kannankeril	NNP	PERSON	Kannankeril	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l683t871r917b913],
82	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l683t871r917b913],
83	MD	NNP	O	MD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l934t871r1051b913],
84	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l934t871r1051b913],
85	#	#	O	#	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l934t871r1051b913],
86	Patricia	NNP	PERSON	Patricia	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1067t871r1207b905],
87	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1223t871r1261b905],
88	Munroe	NNP	PERSON	Munroe	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1279t871r1439b913],
89	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1279t871r1439b913],
90	PHD	NNP	O	PHD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1458t871r1584b913],
91	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1458t871r1584b913],
92	Il	NNP	O	Il	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1458t871r1584b913],
93	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1458t871r1584b913],
94	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1599t870r1643b905],
95	John	NNP	PERSON	John	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1657t871r1747b915],
96	Camm	NNP	PERSON	Camm	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1765t871r1900b913],
97	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1765t871r1900b913],
98	MD	NNP	O	MD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1918t871r2033b913],
99	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1918t871r2033b913],
100	§	NNP	O	§	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1918t871r2033b913],
101	Steve	NNP	PERSON	Steve	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l121t934r216b968],
102	Jeffery	NNP	PERSON	Jeffery	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l229t934r356b980],
103	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l229t934r356b980],
104	PHD	NNP	O	PHD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l375t934r493b975],
105	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l375t934r493b975],
106	*	NNP	O	*	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l375t934r493b975],
107	Dan	NNP	PERSON	Dan	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l510t934r590b968],
108	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l606t934r659b968],
109	Roden	NNP	PERSON	Roden	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l679t934r809b975],
110	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l679t934r809b975],
111	MD	NNP	O	MD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l827t934r946b975],
112	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l827t934r946b975],
113	l	NN	O	l	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l827t934r946b975],
114	Elijah	NNP	PERSON	Elijah	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l964t934r1073b980],
115	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1091t934r1129b968],
116	Behr	NNP	PERSON	Behr	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1149t934r1247b975],
117	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1149t934r1247b975],
118	MBBS	NNP	O	MBBS	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1265t934r1405b976],
119	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1265t934r1405b976],
120	MD	NNP	O	MD	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1422t934r1526b974],
121	§	NNP	O	§	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1422t934r1526b974],
122	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l118t993r251b1025],
123	and	CC	O	and	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l269t993r339b1025],
124	Southampton	NNP	LOCATION	Southampton	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l352t992r588b1038],
125	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l352t992r588b1038],
126	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l613t992r734b1025],
127	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l745t992r917b1038],
128	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l745t992r917b1038],
129	Groningen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Groningen	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l938t992r1128b1038],
130	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l938t992r1128b1038],
131	t/ye	JJ	O	t/ye	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1149t993r1200b1026],
132	Netber/ands	NNS	O	netber/ands	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1214t993r1435b1030],
133	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1214t993r1435b1030],
134	and	CC	O	and	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1452t993r1522b1025],
135	Nos/wille	NNP	O	Nos/wille	dep	137	SENT_7	[p1l1531t992r1706b1030],
136	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1531t992r1706b1030],
137	Tennessee	NNP	LOCATION	Tennessee	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1730t992r1895b1025],

1	Objectives	NNS	O	objective	nsubj	4	SENT_8	[p1l195t1121r369b1154],
2	This	DT	O	this	det	3	SENT_8	[p1l493t1125r550b1148],
3	study	NN	O	study	dep	1	SENT_8	[p1l561t1125r637b1153],
4	sought	VBD	O	seek	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l647t1125r743b1153],
5	to	TO	O	to	aux	6	SENT_8	[p1l754t1126r781b1148],
6	determine	VB	O	determine	xcomp	4	SENT_8	[p1l792t1125r938b1148],
7	whether	IN	O	whether	complm	11	SENT_8	[p1l949t1125r1064b1148],
8	variations	NNS	O	variation	nsubj	11	SENT_8	[p1l1074t1125r1213b1148],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1226t1125r1248b1147],
10	NOSIAP	NN	O	nosiap	prep_in	8	SENT_8	[p1l1260t1124r1381b1148],
11	affect	VBP	O	affect	ccomp	6	SENT_8	[p1l1391t1124r1472b1148],
12	drug-induced	JJ	O	drug-induced	amod	17	SENT_8	[p1l1484t1125r1666b1153],
13	long	JJ	O	long	amod	17	SENT_8	[p1l1680t1125r1739b1153],
14	QT	NN	O	qt	nn	17	SENT_8	[p1l1750t1124r1787b1152],
15	syndrome	NN	O	syndrome	nn	17	SENT_8	[p1l1796t1125r1936b1153],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_8	[p1l1948t1124r2047b1153],
17	LQTS	NNS	O	lqt	dobj	11	SENT_8	[p1l1948t1124r2047b1153],
18	)	CD	NUMBER	)	tmod	11	SENT_8	[p1l1948t1124r2047b1153],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1948t1124r2047b1153],

1	Background	NN	O	background	nn	2	SENT_9	[p1l196t1164r393b1197],
2	Use	NN	O	use	nsubjpass	7	SENT_9	[p1l496t1167r545b1191],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l557t1167r584b1191],
4	antiarrhythmic	JJ	O	antiarrhythmic	amod	5	SENT_9	[p1l594t1167r802b1197],
5	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_of	2	SENT_9	[p1l814t1167r891b1196],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_9	[p1l904t1167r924b1191],
7	limited	VBN	O	limit	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l936t1167r1032b1191],
8	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1046t1167r1076b1197],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_9	[p1l1087t1167r1131b1191],
10	high	JJ	O	high	amod	11	SENT_9	[p1l1144t1167r1202b1196],
11	incidence	NN	O	incidence	agent	7	SENT_9	[p1l1215t1167r1349b1191],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1360t1167r1387b1191],
13	serious	JJ	O	serious	amod	15	SENT_9	[p1l1397t1167r1499b1191],
14	adverse	JJ	O	adverse	amod	15	SENT_9	[p1l1510t1167r1620b1191],
15	events	NNS	O	event	prep_of	11	SENT_9	[p1l1632t1169r1724b1191],
16	including	VBG	O	include	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1736t1167r1864b1196],
17	QT	NNP	O	QT	nn	18	SENT_9	[p1l1874t1167r1911b1195],
18	prolongation	NN	O	prolongation	prep_including	15	SENT_9	[p1l1923t1167r2099b1197],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l495t1211r546b1234],
20	torsades	NNS	O	torsade	prep_including	15	SENT_9	[p1l558t1211r680b1234],
21	de	IN	O	de	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l691t1211r724b1234],
22	pointes	NNS	O	pointe	prep_de	18	SENT_9	[p1l737t1211r847b1239],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l737t1211r847b1239],

1	NOSIAP	NN	O	nosiap	nn	3	SENT_10	[p1l859t1210r980b1234],
2	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	3	SENT_10	[p1l989t1213r1058b1239],
3	variants	NNS	O	variant	nsubj	4	SENT_10	[p1l1069t1211r1182b1234],
4	play	VBP	O	play	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1194t1211r1251b1239],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_10	[p1l1262t1216r1277b1234],
6	role	NN	O	role	dobj	4	SENT_10	[p1l1291t1211r1342b1234],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1355t1211r1377b1234],
8	modulating	VBG	O	modulate	prepc_in	4	SENT_10	[p1l1390t1211r1552b1239],
9	QT	NNP	O	QT	nn	10	SENT_10	[p1l1562t1211r1599b1238],
10	intervals	NNS	O	interval	dobj	8	SENT_10	[p1l1610t1211r1729b1234],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1741t1211r1764b1234],
12	healthy	JJ	O	healthy	amod	13	SENT_10	[p1l1777t1211r1881b1239],
13	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_in	10	SENT_10	[p1l1891t1211r2008b1240],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l2019t1211r2070b1234],
15	severity	NN	O	severity	conj_and	10	SENT_10	[p1l494t1255r603b1284],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l614t1255r641b1279],
17	presentation	NN	O	presentation	prep_of	15	SENT_10	[p1l653t1255r829b1284],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l843t1255r865b1278],
19	LQTS	NNP	O	LQTS	prep_in	8	SENT_10	[p1l879t1255r956b1283],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l879t1255r956b1283],

1	Methods	NNS	O	method	nsubj	14	SENT_11	[p1l196t1295r339b1321],
2	This	DT	O	this	det	3	SENT_11	[p1l493t1298r550b1321],
3	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	4	SENT_11	[p1l561t1298r637b1327],
4	carried	VBD	O	carry	rcmod	1	SENT_11	[p1l648t1298r744b1321],
5	out	RP	O	out	prt	4	SENT_11	[p1l757t1300r802b1321],
6	an	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_11	[p1l813t1304r846b1321],
7	association	NN	O	association	nn	8	SENT_11	[p1l858t1298r1018b1321],
8	study	NN	O	study	dobj	4	SENT_11	[p1l1029t1298r1106b1327],
9	using	VBG	O	use	xcomp	4	SENT_11	[p1l1118t1298r1192b1327],
10	167	CD	NUMBER	167	num	13	SENT_11	[p1l1203t1298r1259b1321],
11	single	JJ	O	single	amod	13	SENT_11	[p1l1270t1298r1354b1327],
12	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	13	SENT_11	[p1l1366t1298r1512b1321],
13	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	dobj	9	SENT_11	[p1l1525t1298r1742b1327],
14	(	VBP	O	(	dep	28	SENT_11	[p1l1753t1298r1832b1327],
15	SNP	NN	ORGANIZATION	snp	nn	16	SENT_11	[p1l1753t1298r1832b1327],
16	)	NN	O	)	dobj	14	SENT_11	[p1l1753t1298r1832b1327],
17	spanning	VBG	O	span	partmod	16	SENT_11	[p1l1843t1298r1974b1327],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_11	[p1l1984t1298r2029b1321],
19	NOSIAP	NN	O	nosiap	nn	20	SENT_11	[p1l495t1341r615b1366],
20	gene	NN	O	gene	dobj	17	SENT_11	[p1l625t1345r694b1371],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l706t1342r729b1365],
22	58	CD	NUMBER	58	num	24	SENT_11	[p1l741t1342r779b1365],
23	Caucasian	JJ	MISC	caucasian	amod	24	SENT_11	[p1l790t1342r935b1365],
24	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	17	SENT_11	[p1l949t1342r1063b1371],
25	experiencing	VBG	O	experience	partmod	24	SENT_11	[p1l1074t1342r1254b1371],
26	drug-induced	JJ	O	drug-induced	amod	27	SENT_11	[p1l1265t1342r1447b1371],
27	LQTS	NNS	O	lqt	dobj	25	SENT_11	[p1l1461t1342r1531b1370],
28	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1543t1342r1652b1371],
29	dLQTS	NN	O	dlqt	nn	30	SENT_11	[p1l1543t1342r1652b1371],
30	)	NN	O	)	dobj	28	SENT_11	[p1l1543t1342r1652b1371],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1664t1342r1715b1365],
32	87	CD	NUMBER	87	num	34	SENT_11	[p1l1727t1342r1764b1365],
33	Caucasian	JJ	MISC	caucasian	amod	34	SENT_11	[p1l1776t1342r1922b1365],
34	controls	NNS	O	control	dobj	28	SENT_11	[p1l1934t1342r2047b1365],
35	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l494t1386r560b1410],
36	the	DT	O	the	det	42	SENT_11	[p1l572t1386r617b1410],
37	DARE	NN	O	dare	npadvmod	39	SENT_11	[p1l629t1386r708b1409],
38	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	37	SENT_11	[p1l719t1386r917b1415],
39	Drug-Induced	JJ	O	drug-induced	amod	42	SENT_11	[p1l719t1386r917b1415],
40	Arrhythmia	NN	O	arrhythmium	nn	42	SENT_11	[p1l928t1386r1086b1415],
41	Risk	NN	O	risk	nn	42	SENT_11	[p1l1099t1386r1159b1410],
42	Evaluation	NN	O	evaluation	prep_from	28	SENT_11	[p1l1171t1386r1328b1415],
43	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	44	SENT_11	[p1l1171t1386r1328b1415],
44	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	28	SENT_11	[p1l1339t1386r1421b1415],
45	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1339t1386r1421b1415],

1	Results	NNS	O	result	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l196t1426r319b1452],
2	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_12	[p1l493t1429r544b1452],
3	rs10800397	NN	O	rs10800397	nn	4	SENT_12	[p1l557t1429r736b1452],
4	SNP	NN	O	snp	nsubjpass	7	SENT_12	[p1l747t1429r807b1452],
5	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_12	[p1l818t1435r873b1452],
6	significantly	RB	O	significantly	advmod	7	SENT_12	[p1l884t1429r1053b1458],
7	associated	VBN	O	associate	rcmod	1	SENT_12	[p1l1064t1429r1215b1452],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1227t1429r1285b1452],
9	dLQTS	NN	O	dlqt	nn	12	SENT_12	[p1l1298t1429r1387b1457],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_12	[p1l1398t1429r1476b1458],
11	odds	NNS	O	odds	nn	12	SENT_12	[p1l1398t1429r1476b1458],
12	ratio	NN	O	ratio	prep_with	7	SENT_12	[p1l1488t1429r1551b1452],
13	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	14	SENT_12	[p1l1563t1429r1631b1458],
14	OR	NN	O	or	dep	1	SENT_12	[p1l1563t1429r1631b1458],
15	]	CD	NUMBER	]	dep	14	SENT_12	[p1l1563t1429r1631b1458],
16	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1563t1429r1631b1458],
17	3.3	CD	NUMBER	3.3	dep	1	SENT_12	[p1l1643t1429r1696b1457],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1643t1429r1696b1457],
19	99.95	CD	PERCENT	99.95	num	22	SENT_12	[p1l1709t1429r1819b1452],
20	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nn	22	SENT_12	[p1l1709t1429r1819b1452],
21	confidence	NN	O	confidence	nn	22	SENT_12	[p1l1831t1429r1984b1452],
22	interval	NN	O	interval	appos	17	SENT_12	[p1l1997t1429r2099b1452],
23	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	25	SENT_12	[p1l496t1472r549b1501],
24	CI	NN	O	ci	nn	25	SENT_12	[p1l496t1472r549b1501],
25	]	NN	O	]	dep	22	SENT_12	[p1l496t1472r549b1501],
26	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l496t1472r549b1501],
27	1.0	CD	NUMBER	1.0	number	29	SENT_12	[p1l562t1472r606b1495],
28	to	TO	O	to	dep	29	SENT_12	[p1l617t1474r644b1495],
29	10.8	CD	NUMBER	10.8	dep	25	SENT_12	[p1l657t1472r729b1500],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l657t1472r729b1500],
31	p	NN	O	p	appos	17	SENT_12	[p1l742t1478r757b1501],
32	=	JJ	O	=	advmod	37	SENT_12	[p1l771t1480r792b1488],
33	3.7	CD	NUMBER	3.7	num	34	SENT_12	[p1l806t1472r851b1495],
34	X	NN	O	x	dep	32	SENT_12	[p1l866t1474r886b1494],
35	10	CD	NUMBER	10	number	36	SENT_12	[p1l901t1467r982b1501],
36	“‘	CD	NUMBER	“‘	num	37	SENT_12	[p1l901t1467r982b1501],
37	)	NN	O	)	rcmod	31	SENT_12	[p1l901t1467r982b1501],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l901t1467r982b1501],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_13	[p1l994t1472r1045b1495],
2	associations	NNS	O	association	nsubj	5	SENT_13	[p1l1056t1472r1232b1495],
3	were	VBD	O	be	cop	5	SENT_13	[p1l1243t1478r1311b1495],
4	more	RBR	O	more	advmod	5	SENT_13	[p1l1323t1478r1395b1495],
5	pronounced	JJ	O	pronounced	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1408t1472r1573b1501],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1587t1472r1609b1495],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_13	[p1l1621t1472r1666b1495],
8	subgroup	NN	O	subgroup	prep_in	5	SENT_13	[p1l1677t1472r1809b1501],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1820t1472r1847b1495],
10	amiodarone	NN	O	amiodarone	nn	11	SENT_13	[p1l1858t1472r2029b1495],
11	users	NNS	O	user	prep_of	8	SENT_13	[p1l2042t1478r2081b1495, p1l495t1522r544b1544],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l2042t1478r2081b1495, p1l495t1522r544b1544],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l557t1516r579b1539],
14	which	WDT	O	which	rel	23	SENT_13	[p1l591t1516r672b1540],
15	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	16	SENT_13	[p1l685t1516r702b1540],
16	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	nsubjpass	23	SENT_13	[p1l713t1516r795b1544],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l713t1516r795b1544],
18	including	VBG	O	include	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l809t1516r936b1545],
19	rs10800397	NN	O	rs10800397	prep_including	16	SENT_13	[p1l948t1516r1135b1544],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l948t1516r1135b1544],
21	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	23	SENT_13	[p1l1147t1522r1215b1540],
22	significantly	RB	O	significantly	advmod	23	SENT_13	[p1l1225t1516r1395b1545],
23	associated	VBN	O	associate	rcmod	11	SENT_13	[p1l1406t1516r1557b1540],
24	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	27	SENT_13	[p1l1569t1516r1650b1545],
25	most	RBS	O	most	advmod	26	SENT_13	[p1l1569t1516r1650b1545],
26	significant	JJ	O	significant	amod	27	SENT_13	[p1l1661t1516r1807b1545],
27	SNP	NN	O	snp	dobj	23	SENT_13	[p1l1818t1516r1885b1540],
28	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1818t1516r1885b1540],
29	rs10919035	NN	O	rs10919035	dep	27	SENT_13	[p1l1898t1516r2085b1540],
30	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1898t1516r2085b1540],
31	OR	NN	O	or	dep	29	SENT_13	[p1l495t1559r543b1582],
32	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l495t1559r543b1582],
33	5.5	CD	NUMBER	5.5	dep	27	SENT_13	[p1l555t1559r608b1587],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l555t1559r608b1587],
35	99.95	CD	PERCENT	99.95	num	37	SENT_13	[p1l621t1559r731b1582],
36	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nn	37	SENT_13	[p1l621t1559r731b1582],
37	CI	NN	O	ci	appos	33	SENT_13	[p1l743t1559r776b1582],
38	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l743t1559r776b1582],
39	1.1	CD	NUMBER	1.1	number	41	SENT_13	[p1l789t1559r835b1582],
40	to	TO	O	to	dep	41	SENT_13	[p1l845t1561r872b1582],
41	27.9	CD	NUMBER	27.9	dep	37	SENT_13	[p1l884t1559r956b1587],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l884t1559r956b1587],
43	p	NN	O	p	appos	27	SENT_13	[p1l970t1565r985b1588],
44	=	JJ	O	=	advmod	49	SENT_13	[p1l999t1567r1019b1575],
45	3.0	CD	NUMBER	3.0	num	46	SENT_13	[p1l1033t1559r1079b1582],
46	X	NN	O	x	dep	44	SENT_13	[p1l1094t1561r1113b1581],
47	10	CD	NUMBER	10	number	48	SENT_13	[p1l1129t1554r1210b1588],
48	”‘	CD	NUMBER	”‘	num	49	SENT_13	[p1l1129t1554r1210b1588],
49	)	NN	O	)	rcmod	43	SENT_13	[p1l1129t1554r1210b1588],
50	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1129t1554r1210b1588],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_14	[p1l1222t1559r1267b1582],
2	genotyped	VBD	O	genotype	ccomp	39	SENT_14	[p1l1279t1559r1425b1588],
3	rs10919035	NN	O	rs10919035	dobj	2	SENT_14	[p1l1439t1559r1619b1582],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1631t1559r1654b1582],
5	an	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_14	[p1l1666t1565r1699b1582],
6	independent	JJ	O	independent	amod	8	SENT_14	[p1l1713t1559r1890b1588],
7	replication	NN	O	replication	nn	8	SENT_14	[p1l1902t1559r2049b1588],
8	cohort	NN	O	cohort	prep_in	2	SENT_14	[p1l2061t1565r2102b1582, p1l496t1602r550b1626],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l562t1602r589b1626],
10	28	CD	NUMBER	28	num	13	SENT_14	[p1l599t1602r637b1626],
11	amiodarone	NN	O	amiodarone	nn	13	SENT_14	[p1l648t1602r819b1626],
12	dLQTS	NN	O	dlqt	nn	13	SENT_14	[p1l831t1602r920b1630],
13	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	8	SENT_14	[p1l932t1608r1011b1626],
14	versus	CC	O	versus	prep	13	SENT_14	[p1l1022t1608r1113b1626],
15	173	CD	NUMBER	173	num	17	SENT_14	[p1l1125t1602r1180b1626],
16	control	JJ	O	control	amod	17	SENT_14	[p1l1192t1602r1288b1626],
17	subjects	NNS	O	subject	nn	19	SENT_14	[p1l1300t1602r1417b1632],
18	(	JJ	O	(	amod	19	SENT_14	[p1l1429t1602r1636b1631],
19	meta-analysis	NN	O	meta-analysis	dep	14	SENT_14	[p1l1429t1602r1636b1631],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1647t1602r1674b1626],
21	both	CC	O	both	dep	22	SENT_14	[p1l1686t1602r1746b1626],
22	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	19	SENT_14	[p1l1758t1602r1867b1626],
23	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1758t1602r1867b1626],
24	OR	NN	O	or	dep	22	SENT_14	[p1l1880t1602r1928b1626],
25	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1880t1602r1928b1626],
26	2.81	CD	NUMBER	2.81	dep	22	SENT_14	[p1l1940t1602r2013b1630],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1940t1602r2013b1630],
28	99.95	CD	PERCENT	99.95	num	30	SENT_14	[p1l495t1646r605b1670],
29	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nn	30	SENT_14	[p1l495t1646r605b1670],
30	Cl	NN	O	cl	appos	26	SENT_14	[p1l617t1646r650b1670],
31	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l617t1646r650b1670],
32	1.62	CD	NUMBER	1.62	dep	22	SENT_14	[p1l664t1646r727b1670],
33	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l739t1648r767b1670],
34	4.89	CD	NUMBER	4.89	prep_to	2	SENT_14	[p1l778t1646r851b1674],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l778t1646r851b1674],
36	p	NN	O	p	nsubj	39	SENT_14	[p1l865t1652r880b1675],
37	=	JJ	O	=	amod	36	SENT_14	[p1l894t1654r914b1662],
38	2.4	CD	NUMBER	2.4	tmod	37	SENT_14	[p1l929t1646r975b1669],
39	X	NN	O	x	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l990t1648r1009b1668],
40	10	CD	NUMBER	10	dobj	39	SENT_14	[p1l1025t1641r1106b1675],
41	"	``	O	"	punct	40	SENT_14	[p1l1025t1641r1106b1675],
42	)	NN	O	)	dep	40	SENT_14	[p1l1025t1641r1106b1675],
43	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1025t1641r1106b1675],

1	Analysis	NN	O	analysis	nsubj	13	SENT_15	[p1l1118t1646r1240b1675],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1252t1646r1279b1670],
3	corrected	VBN	O	correct	amod	5	SENT_15	[p1l1291t1646r1428b1670],
4	QT	NNP	O	QT	nn	5	SENT_15	[p1l1442t1646r1479b1674],
5	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_of	1	SENT_15	[p1l1491t1646r1599b1670],
6	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1612t1649r1714b1675],
7	74	CD	NUMBER	74	num	9	SENT_15	[p1l1726t1646r1763b1669],
8	control	JJ	O	control	amod	9	SENT_15	[p1l1776t1646r1876b1670],
9	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_among	1	SENT_15	[p1l1888t1646r2010b1676],
10	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l2022t1646r2090b1670],
11	our	PRP$	O	we	poss	12	SENT_15	[p1l495t1695r541b1712],
12	dataset	NN	O	dataset	prep_from	9	SENT_15	[p1l553t1689r664b1712],
13	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l676t1689r786b1712],
14	a	DT	O	a	det	16	SENT_15	[p1l800t1695r816b1712],
15	similar	JJ	O	similar	amod	16	SENT_15	[p1l828t1689r930b1712],
16	pattern	NN	O	pattern	dobj	13	SENT_15	[p1l943t1691r1047b1718],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1061t1689r1089b1712],
18	significance	NN	O	significance	prep_of	16	SENT_15	[p1l1100t1689r1275b1718],
19	over	IN	O	over	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1288t1695r1350b1712],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_15	[p1l1361t1689r1407b1712],
21	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	22	SENT_15	[p1l1420t1692r1491b1718],
22	region	NN	O	region	prep_over	13	SENT_15	[p1l1505t1689r1594b1718],
23	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1608t1695r1640b1712],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_15	[p1l1652t1689r1698b1712],
25	case-control	JJ	O	case-control	amod	26	SENT_15	[p1l1711t1689r1888b1712],
26	analysis	NN	O	analysis	prep_as	13	SENT_15	[p1l1902t1689r2028b1718],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1902t1689r2028b1718],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_16	[p1l2041t1689r2100b1712],
2	pattern	NN	O	pattern	nsubjpass	4	SENT_16	[p1l496t1734r599b1761],
3	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_16	[p1l613t1738r670b1756],
4	confirmed	VBN	O	confirm	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l682t1732r829b1756],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l843t1732r866b1755],
6	1,480	CD	NUMBER	1,480	num	8	SENT_16	[p1l881t1732r968b1760],
7	control	JJ	O	control	amod	8	SENT_16	[p1l981t1732r1080b1756],
8	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_in	4	SENT_16	[p1l1094t1732r1216b1762],
9	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1227t1732r1295b1756],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_16	[p1l1309t1732r1355b1756],
11	BRIGHT	NNP	O	BRIGHT	prep_from	8	SENT_16	[p1l1369t1732r1480b1756],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_16	[p1l1492t1732r1595b1761],
13	British	JJ	ORGANIZATION	british	amod	14	SENT_16	[p1l1492t1732r1595b1761],
14	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	22	SENT_16	[p1l1609t1732r1736b1756],
15	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1749t1732r1776b1756],
16	Hypertension	NN	ORGANIZATION	hypertension	nn	17	SENT_16	[p1l1790t1732r1981b1761],
17	Study	NN	ORGANIZATION	study	prep_of	14	SENT_16	[p1l1994t1732r2086b1761],
18	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	19	SENT_16	[p1l1994t1732r2086b1761],
19	cohort	NN	O	cohort	dep	22	SENT_16	[p1l495t1777r587b1801],
20	(	NN	O	(	nn	22	SENT_16	[p1l600t1777r656b1806],
21	top	JJ	O	top	amod	22	SENT_16	[p1l600t1777r656b1806],
22	SNP	NN	O	snp	dep	8	SENT_16	[p1l668t1777r729b1801],
23	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l741t1777r809b1801],
24	DARE	NN	O	dare	prep_from	22	SENT_16	[p1l824t1777r913b1800],
25	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l824t1777r913b1800],
26	rs12734991	NN	O	rs12734991	dep	8	SENT_16	[p1l927t1777r1114b1801],
27	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1127t1777r1150b1800],
28	meta-analysis	NN	O	meta-analysis	prep_in	26	SENT_16	[p1l1165t1777r1377b1806],
29	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1165t1777r1377b1806],
30	increase	NN	O	increase	dep	26	SENT_16	[p1l1392t1777r1514b1801],
31	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1528t1777r1551b1800],
32	corrected	VBN	O	correct	amod	34	SENT_16	[p1l1565t1777r1702b1801],
33	QT	NN	O	qt	nn	34	SENT_16	[p1l1716t1777r1753b1805],
34	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_in	30	SENT_16	[p1l1766t1777r1873b1801],
35	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1888t1783r1934b1806],
36	o	NN	O	o	nn	37	SENT_16	[p1l1946t1777r1964b1801],
37	allele	NN	O	allele	prep_per	34	SENT_16	[p1l1976t1777r2063b1801],
38	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1976t1777r2063b1801],
39	9.1	CD	NUMBER	9.1	dep	30	SENT_16	[p1l495t1820r542b1844],
40	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l557t1822r577b1843],
41	3.2	CD	NUMBER	3.2	num	42	SENT_16	[p1l593t1820r639b1844],
42	ms	NNS	O	m	dep	39	SENT_16	[p1l654t1826r704b1848],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l654t1826r704b1848],
44	p	NN	O	p	appos	42	SENT_16	[p1l718t1826r733b1849],
45	=	JJ	O	=	rcmod	44	SENT_16	[p1l749t1828r769b1836],
46	1.7	CD	NUMBER	1.7	iobj	45	SENT_16	[p1l786t1820r831b1844],
47	X	NN	O	x	dobj	45	SENT_16	[p1l848t1822r868b1842],
48	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	47	SENT_16	[p1l884t1815r968b1849],
49	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l884t1815r968b1849],
50	“	CD	NUMBER	“	num	51	SENT_16	[p1l884t1815r968b1849],
51	)	NN	O	)	dep	44	SENT_16	[p1l884t1815r968b1849],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l884t1815r968b1849],

1	Conclusions	NNS	O	conclusion	nsubj	4	SENT_17	[p1l195t1860r396b1887],
2	These	DT	O	these	det	3	SENT_17	[p1l493t1864r574b1887],
3	results	NNS	O	result	dep	1	SENT_17	[p1l585t1864r675b1887],
4	provide	VBP	O	provide	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l686t1864r784b1893],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_17	[p1l793t1864r837b1887],
6	first	JJ	ORDINAL	first	amod	7	SENT_17	[p1l847t1864r899b1887],
7	demonstration	NN	O	demonstration	dobj	4	SENT_17	[p1l909t1864r1107b1887],
8	that	IN	O	that	complm	16	SENT_17	[p1l1118t1864r1173b1887],
9	common	JJ	O	common	amod	10	SENT_17	[p1l1183t1869r1303b1887],
10	variations	NNS	O	variation	nsubjpass	16	SENT_17	[p1l1314t1864r1447b1887],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1458t1864r1480b1887],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_17	[p1l1490t1864r1534b1887],
13	NOS1AP	NN	O	nos1ap	nn	14	SENT_17	[p1l1544t1863r1662b1888],
14	gene	NN	O	gene	prep_in	10	SENT_17	[p1l1670t1867r1737b1893],
15	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_17	[p1l1747t1869r1791b1887],
16	associated	VBN	O	associate	ccomp	4	SENT_17	[p1l1801t1864r1946b1887],
17	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1956t1864r2012b1887],
18	a	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_17	[p1l2024t1869r2039b1887],
19	significant	JJ	O	significant	amod	20	SENT_17	[p1l2049t1864r2096b1893, p1l496t1907r596b1931],
20	increase	NN	O	increase	prep_with	16	SENT_17	[p1l606t1908r720b1931],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l731t1908r753b1930],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_17	[p1l763t1908r807b1931],
23	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_in	20	SENT_17	[p1l818t1908r866b1931],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l876t1907r902b1931],
25	dLQTS	NN	O	dlqt	prep_of	23	SENT_17	[p1l912t1907r1005b1935],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l912t1907r1005b1935],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_18	[p1l1015t1908r1070b1931],
2	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	3	SENT_18	[p1l1079t1908r1153b1936],
3	suggests	VBZ	O	suggest	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1161t1909r1282b1936],
4	that	IN	O	that	complm	12	SENT_18	[p1l1292t1908r1346b1931],
5	common	JJ	O	common	amod	6	SENT_18	[p1l1356t1913r1477b1931],
6	variations	NNS	O	variation	nsubj	12	SENT_18	[p1l1488t1908r1621b1931],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1631t1908r1653b1930],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_18	[p1l1664t1908r1707b1931],
9	NOS1AP	NN	O	nos1ap	nn	10	SENT_18	[p1l1718t1907r1835b1931],
10	gene	NN	O	gene	prep_in	6	SENT_18	[p1l1844t1910r1910b1936],
11	may	MD	O	may	aux	12	SENT_18	[p1l1922t1913r1980b1936],
12	have	VB	O	have	ccomp	3	SENT_18	[p1l1991t1908r2054b1931],
13	relevance	NN	O	relevance	dobj	12	SENT_18	[p1l496t1950r625b1973],
14	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l635t1950r672b1973],
15	future	JJ	DATE	future	amod	17	SENT_18	[p1l681t1950r762b1973],
16	pharmacogenomic	JJ	O	pharmacogenomic	amod	17	SENT_18	[p1l774t1950r1031b1979],
17	applications	NNS	O	application	prep_for	12	SENT_18	[p1l1040t1950r1205b1979],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1216t1950r1238b1973],
19	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	20	SENT_18	[p1l1249t1950r1341b1973],
20	practice	NN	O	practice	prep_in	17	SENT_18	[p1l1354t1950r1460b1979],
21	permitting	VBG	O	permit	xcomp	12	SENT_18	[p1l1472t1950r1613b1979],
22	safer	JJR	O	safer	amod	23	SENT_18	[p1l1621t1950r1690b1973],
23	prescription	NN	O	prescription	dobj	21	SENT_18	[p1l1701t1950r1858b1979],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1870t1950r1896b1973],
25	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_of	23	SENT_18	[p1l1906t1950r1981b1979],
26	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1990t1950r2028b1973],
27	vulnerable	JJ	O	vulnerable	amod	28	SENT_18	[p1l2036t1950r2084b1973, p1l496t1993r597b2016],
28	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_for	25	SENT_18	[p1l608t1993r724b2022],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l608t1993r724b2022],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	2	SENT_19	[p1l765t1993r784b2022],
2	J	NN	O	j	nsubj	5	SENT_19	[p1l765t1993r784b2022],
3	Am	VBP	O	be	cop	5	SENT_19	[p1l795t1993r841b2016],
4	Coll	NNP	O	Coll	nn	5	SENT_19	[p1l852t1993r901b2016],
5	Cardiol	NNP	O	Cardiol	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l912t1993r1005b2016],
6	2012	CD	DATE	2012	dep	5	SENT_19	[p1l1017t1993r1264b2022],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1017t1993r1264b2022],
8	60:841	CD	NUMBER	60:841	number	9	SENT_19	[p1l1017t1993r1264b2022],
9	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	11	SENT_19	[p1l1017t1993r1264b2022],
10	50	CD	NUMBER	50	number	11	SENT_19	[p1l1017t1993r1264b2022],
11	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	5	SENT_19	[p1l1017t1993r1264b2022],
12	©	CD	NUMBER	©	num	13	SENT_19	[p1l1274t1993r1298b2016],
13	2012	CD	DATE	2012	dep	11	SENT_19	[p1l1307t1993r1381b2016],
14	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1393t1993r1423b2022],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_19	[p1l1432t1993r1476b2016],
16	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	17	SENT_19	[p1l1485t1993r1616b2016],
17	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	prep_by	5	SENT_19	[p1l1627t1993r1727b2022],
18	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1737t1993r1763b2016],
19	Cardiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cardiology	nn	20	SENT_19	[p1l1773t1993r1916b2022],
20	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Foundation	prep_of	17	SENT_19	[p1l1926t1993r2078b2016],

1	From	IN	O	from	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l10t2381r140b2424],
2	the	DT	O	the	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l173t2380r246b2424],
3	*	CD	NUMBER	*	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l279t2380r478b2424],
4	Human	JJ	O	human	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l279t2380r478b2424],
5	Genetics	NNP	O	Genetics	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l510t2380r709b2425],
6	Research	NNP	O	Research	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l743t2380r946b2424],
7	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l979t2380r1148b2434],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l979t2380r1148b2434],
9	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1183t2380r1240b2425],
10	George	NNP	ORGANIZATION	George	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1276t2380r1473b2440],
11	’s	POS	ORGANIZATION	’s	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1276t2380r1473b2440],
12	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1504t2381r1741b2440],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1770t2380r1822b2424],
14	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1846t2380r2042b2434],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1846t2380r2042b2434],
16	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l10t2453r206b2507],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l10t2453r206b2507],
18	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l233t2453r394b2498],
19	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l422t2453r650b2513],
20	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l422t2453r650b2513],
21	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l679t2453r989b2513],
22	l‘Department	NN	O	l‘department	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l679t2453r989b2513],
23	of	IN	O	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1015t2453r1068b2497],
24	Epidemiology	NNP	O	Epidemiology	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1087t2453r1420b2513],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1087t2453r1420b2513],
26	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1447t2454r1683b2513],
27	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1708t2453r1760b2497],
28	Groningen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Groningen	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1780t2453r2042b2513],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1780t2453r2042b2513],
30	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l8t2527r244b2586],
31	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l259t2526r448b2570],
32	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l467t2526r625b2571],
33	Groningen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Groningen	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l644t2526r907b2586],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l644t2526r907b2586],
35	Groningen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Groningen	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l929t2526r1192b2586],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l929t2526r1192b2586],
37	the	DT	O	the	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1213t2526r1284b2570],
38	Netherlands	NNP	LOCATION	Netherlands	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1303t2526r1595b2580],
39	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1303t2526r1595b2580],
40	Il	NNP	O	Il	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1616t2526r1824b2578],
41	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1616t2526r1824b2578],
42	Clinical	JJ	O	clinical	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1616t2526r1824b2578],
43	Pharmacology	NN	O	pharmacology	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1843t2526r2042b2570, p1l10t2599r158b2659],
44	and	CC	O	and	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l173t2599r256b2643],
45	Barts	NNS	PERSON	bart	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l273t2600r390b2643],
46	and	CC	O	and	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l409t2599r492b2643],
47	The	DT	O	the	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l507t2598r603b2643],
48	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l621t2599r805b2643],
49	Genome	NNP	O	Genome	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l824t2599r1022b2644],
50	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1041t2599r1210b2653],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1041t2599r1210b2653],
52	William	NNP	ORGANIZATION	William	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1226t2599r1417b2644],
53	Harvey	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Harvey	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1435t2600r1602b2659],
54	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1619t2599r1822b2643],
55	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1839t2600r2043b2653],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1839t2600r2043b2653],
57	Barts	NNP	PERSON	Barts	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l10t2673r126b2716],
58	and	CC	O	and	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l151t2672r234b2716],
59	The	DT	ORGANIZATION	the	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l254t2671r350b2716],
60	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l373t2672r557b2716],
61	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l582t2672r736b2717],
62	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l758t2672r811b2716],
63	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l824t2672r1042b2716],
64	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1066t2672r1149b2716],
65	Dentistry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dentistry	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1171t2673r1397b2732],
66	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1171t2673r1397b2732],
67	Qieen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Qieen	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1423t2672r1576b2728],
68	Mary	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mary	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1597t2673r1725b2732],
69	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1744t2673r1980b2732],
70	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l2000t2672r2053b2716],
71	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l10t2745r206b2799],
72	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l10t2745r206b2799],
73	Charterhouse	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Charterhouse	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l229t2745r537b2790],
74	Square	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Square	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l560t2745r725b2805],
75	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l560t2745r725b2805],
76	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l748t2745r944b2799],
77	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l748t2745r944b2799],
78	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l965t2745r1126b2790],
79	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1147t2745r1375b2805],
80	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1147t2745r1375b2805],
81	§	CD	NUMBER	§	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1400t2745r1623b2797],
82	Division	NN	O	division	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1400t2745r1623b2797],
83	of	IN	O	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1644t2745r1696b2789],
84	Cardiovascular	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cardiovascular	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1709t2745r2046b2790],
85	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l12t2818r212b2872],
86	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l12t2818r212b2872],
87	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l232t2818r288b2863],
88	George	NNP	ORGANIZATION	George	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l309t2818r506b2878],
89	’s	POS	ORGANIZATION	’s	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l309t2818r506b2878],
90	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l522t2819r759b2878],
91	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l772t2818r825b2862],
92	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l833t2818r1029b2872],
93	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l833t2818r1029b2872],
94	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1048t2818r1244b2872],
95	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1048t2818r1244b2872],
96	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1260t2818r1421b2863],
97	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1438t2818r1666b2878],
98	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1438t2818r1666b2878],
99	“	NNP	O	“	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1686t2813r1985b2878],
100	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1686t2813r1985b2878],
101	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l2001t2818r2053b2862],
102	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l8t2891r226b2935],
103	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l260t2891r343b2935],
104	Pharmacology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmacology	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l376t2891r713b2951],
105	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l376t2891r713b2951],
106	Vanderbilt	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Vanderbilt	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l748t2891r992b2936],
107	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1022t2892r1259b2951],
108	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1291t2891r1445b2936],
109	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1478t2891r1530b2935],
110	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1554t2891r1784b2945],
111	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1554t2891r1784b2945],
112	Nashville	NNP	LOCATION	Nashville	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1819t2891r2043b2945],
113	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1819t2891r2043b2945],
114	Tennessee	NNP	LOCATION	Tennessee	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l7t2963r258b3018],
115	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l7t2963r258b3018],
116	1lDrug	NNP	O	1lDrug	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l294t2965r450b3024],
117	Safety	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Safety	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l483t2964r622b3024],
118	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l654t2964r857b3008],
119	Unit	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Unit	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l889t2965r1006b3018],
120	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l889t2965r1006b3018],
121	Southampton	NNP	LOCATION	Southampton	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1044t2964r1367b3024],
122	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1044t2964r1367b3024],
123	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1400t2964r1560b3009],
124	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1594t2964r1822b3024],
125	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1594t2964r1822b3024],
126	and	CC	O	and	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1858t2964r1941b3008],
127	the	DT	O	the	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1973t2964r2044b3008],
128	#Department	NN	O	#department	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l7t3038r321b3097],
129	of	IN	O	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l358t3037r411b3082],
130	Pediatrics	NNP	MISC	Pediatrics	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l441t3038r676b3091],
131	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l441t3038r676b3091],
132	Vanderbilt	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Vanderbilt	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l716t3037r961b3082],
133	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l997t3038r1234b3097],
134	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1272t3037r1426b3082],
135	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1464t3037r1517b3082],
136	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1545t3037r1777b3091],
137	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1545t3037r1777b3091],
138	Nashville	NNP	LOCATION	Nashville	dep	140	SENT_20	[p1l1817t3037r2042b3091],
139	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1817t3037r2042b3091],
140	Tennessee	NNP	LOCATION	Tennessee	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l7t3109r257b3155],
141	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l7t3109r257b3155],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_21	[p1l281t3109r379b3155],
2	DARE	NN	O	dare	nn	3	SENT_21	[p1l403t3110r575b3154],
3	study	NN	O	study	nsubjpass	5	SENT_21	[p1l600t3111r726b3170],
4	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_21	[p1l745t3128r832b3155],
5	funded	VBN	O	fund	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l856t3110r1022b3155],
6	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1044t3110r1101b3170],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_21	[p1l1122t3111r1196b3155],
8	British	JJ	ORGANIZATION	british	amod	13	SENT_21	[p1l1220t3111r1381b3155],
9	Heart	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heart	nn	13	SENT_21	[p1l1405t3111r1544b3155],
10	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Foundation	nn	13	SENT_21	[p1l1567t3110r1844b3155],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	13	SENT_21	[p1l1869t3109r2043b3164],
12	BI-IF	NN	O	bi-if	nn	13	SENT_21	[p1l1869t3109r2043b3164],
13	)	NN	O	)	agent	5	SENT_21	[p1l1869t3109r2043b3164],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1869t3109r2043b3164],
15	Project	NN	O	project	nn	17	SENT_21	[p1l10t3184r177b3243],
16	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	nn	17	SENT_21	[p1l214t3183r357b3228],
17	No.	NNP	O	No.	appos	13	SENT_21	[p1l392t3184r479b3228],
18	06/094	CD	NUMBER	06/094	number	19	SENT_21	[p1l519t3183r686b3228],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	17	SENT_21	[p1l725t3182r788b3237],
20	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l725t3182r788b3237],
21	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	23	SENT_21	[p1l825t3184r904b3228],
22	Jamshidi	NNP	PERSON	Jamshidi	nn	23	SENT_21	[p1l937t3182r1167b3240],
23	)	NN	O	)	prep_to	5	SENT_21	[p1l937t3182r1167b3240],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1207t3184r1293b3228],
25	Special	JJ	O	special	amod	28	SENT_21	[p1l1331t3183r1497b3243],
26	Program	NN	O	program	nn	28	SENT_21	[p1l1533t3184r1738b3243],
27	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	nn	28	SENT_21	[p1l1777t3183r1919b3228],
28	No.	NNP	O	No.	prep_to	5	SENT_21	[p1l1954t3184r2041b3228],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1954t3184r2041b3228],

1	SP/02/001	NN	O	sp/02/001	nn	2	SENT_22	[p1l12t3256r262b3301],
2	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l300t3255r363b3310],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l300t3255r363b3310],
4	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	6	SENT_22	[p1l396t3257r474b3301],
5	Camm	NNP	PERSON	Camm	nn	6	SENT_22	[p1l510t3255r704b3310],
6	)	NN	O	)	prep_to	2	SENT_22	[p1l510t3255r704b3310],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l510t3255r704b3310],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_23	[p1l737t3255r835b3301],
2	Vanderbilt	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Vanderbilt	nn	3	SENT_23	[p1l868t3257r1122b3301],
3	study	NN	O	study	nsubjpass	5	SENT_23	[p1l1154t3257r1281b3316],
4	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_23	[p1l1308t3274r1394b3301],
5	supported	VBN	O	support	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1428t3256r1663b3316],
6	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1693t3257r1751b3316],
7	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	nn	8	SENT_23	[p1l1781t3256r1924b3301],
8	No.	NN	O	no.	agent	5	SENT_23	[p1l1954t3257r2042b3301],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1954t3257r2042b3301],

1	U01/U19	NN	O	u01/u19	nn	2	SENT_24	[p2l52t51r284b97],
2	HL65962	NN	O	hl65962	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l320t51r576b107],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l320t51r576b107],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_24	[p2l612t51r688b97],
5	Pharmacogenomics	NNP	O	Pharmacogenomics	conj_and	5	SENT_24	[p2l722t51r1197b113],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1233t51r1287b97],
7	Arrhythmia	NNP	O	Arrhythmia	nn	9	SENT_24	[p2l1311t50r1602b113],
8	Therapy	NN	O	therapy	nn	9	SENT_24	[p2l1633t50r1842b113],
9	site	NN	O	site	prep_of	5	SENT_24	[p2l1874t53r1954b97],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1989t51r2044b97],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_24	[p2l2069t51r2145b97],
12	Pharmacogenomics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmacogenomics	nn	14	SENT_24	[p2l54t127r528b189],
13	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	14	SENT_24	[p2l555t127r773b173],
14	Network	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Network	prep_of	9	SENT_24	[p2l797t127r1026b183],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l797t127r1026b183],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1053t127r1141b173],
17	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1163t127r1222b189],
18	a	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_24	[p2l1245t145r1269b173],
19	grant	NN	O	grant	prep_by	5	SENT_24	[p2l1291t139r1419b189],
20	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1442t127r1559b173],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_24	[p2l1583t127r1659b173],
22	Fondation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Fondation	nn	25	SENT_24	[p2l1684t127r1938b173],
23	Leducq	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Leducq	nn	25	SENT_24	[p2l1962t127r2146b189],
24	(	NNP	O	(	nn	25	SENT_24	[p2l55t202r440b259],
25	Trans	NNP	O	Trans	prep_from	19	SENT_24	[p2l55t202r440b259],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l55t202r440b259],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l55t202r440b259],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l55t202r440b259],

1	Atlantic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Atlantic	nn	2	SENT_26	[p2l55t202r440b259],
2	Network	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Network	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l456t203r675b249],
3	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l689t203r744b249],
4	Excellence	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Excellence	nn	6	SENT_26	[p2l754t203r1011b249],
5	“	NNP	ORGANIZATION	“	nn	6	SENT_26	[p2l1028t202r1250b249],
6	Alliance	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Alliance	prep_of	2	SENT_26	[p2l1028t202r1250b249],
7	Against	IN	ORGANIZATION	against	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1265t202r1457b265],
8	Sudden	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sudden	nn	10	SENT_26	[p2l1475t203r1657b249],
9	Cardiac	JJ	ORGANIZATION	cardiac	amod	10	SENT_26	[p2l1675t203r1864b249],
10	Death	NN	ORGANIZATION	death	prep_against	6	SENT_26	[p2l1881t203r2069b259],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1881t203r2069b259],
12	”	CD	NUMBER	”	number	13	SENT_26	[p2l1881t203r2069b259],
13	05	CD	NUMBER	05	num	14	SENT_26	[p2l2087t203r2143b249],
14	CVD	NN	O	cvd	appos	2	SENT_26	[p2l55t279r188b325],
15	01	CD	NUMBER	01	num	16	SENT_26	[p2l212t278r303b335],
16	)	NN	O	)	dep	14	SENT_26	[p2l212t278r303b335],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l212t278r303b335],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_27	[p2l326t278r427b325],
2	BRIGHT	JJ	O	bright	amod	3	SENT_27	[p2l450t278r698b325],
3	study	NN	O	study	nsubjpass	5	SENT_27	[p2l721t279r851b341],
4	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_27	[p2l868t297r957b325],
5	supported	VBN	O	support	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l981t279r1223b341],
6	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1243t279r1302b341],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_27	[p2l1321t279r1397b325],
8	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	10	SENT_27	[p2l1418t279r1619b325],
9	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	10	SENT_27	[p2l1642t279r1860b325],
10	Council	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Council	agent	5	SENT_27	[p2l1883t279r2077b325],
11	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l2098t279r2153b325],
12	Great	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Great	nn	16	SENT_27	[p2l55t355r195b401],
13	Britain	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Britain	nn	16	SENT_27	[p2l232t356r402b401],
14	(	NNP	O	(	nn	16	SENT_27	[p2l442t354r608b411],
15	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	nn	16	SENT_27	[p2l442t354r608b411],
16	No.	NN	O	no.	prep_of	10	SENT_27	[p2l645t356r735b401],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l645t356r735b401],

1	G9521010D	NN	O	g9521010d	nn	2	SENT_28	[p2l778t354r1105b411],
2	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l778t354r1105b411],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1148t355r1236b401],
4	by	IN	O	by	conj_and	2	SENT_28	[p2l1272t355r1332b417],
5	BHF	NNP	O	BHF	nn	7	SENT_28	[p2l1368t356r1496b400],
6	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	nn	7	SENT_28	[p2l1534t355r1681b401],
7	No.	NN	O	no.	pobj	4	SENT_28	[p2l1718t356r1808b401],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1718t356r1808b401],

1	PG/02/128	NN	O	pg/02/128	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1850t355r2142b401],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1850t355r2142b401],

1	Genotyping	VBG	O	genotype	csubjpass	7	SENT_30	[p2l55t431r347b493],
2	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l375t431r445b477],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_30	[p2l474t431r549b477],
4	Human_CVD	NN	MISC	human_cvd	nn	5	SENT_30	[p2l580t431r936b484],
5	BeadChip	NN	MISC	beadchip	prep_for	1	SENT_30	[p2l968t431r1214b493],
6	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_30	[p2l1243t449r1332b477],
7	supported	VBN	O	support	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1364t431r1605b493],
8	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1633t431r1693b493],
9	BHF	NNP	O	BHF	nn	11	SENT_30	[p2l1720t432r1848b476],
10	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	nn	11	SENT_30	[p2l1878t431r2024b477],
11	No.	NN	O	no.	agent	7	SENT_30	[p2l2052t432r2142b477],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l2052t432r2142b477],

1	PG/07/131	NN	O	pg/07/131	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l54t507r508b553],
2	/	:	O	/	punct	1	SENT_31	[p2l54t507r508b553],
3	24254	CD	NUMBER	24254	num	4	SENT_31	[p2l54t507r508b553],
4	(	NN	O	(	dep	1	SENT_31	[p2l536t506r601b563],
5	to	TO	O	to	dep	4	SENT_31	[p2l536t506r601b563],
6	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	8	SENT_31	[p2l629t508r709b553],
7	Munroe	NNP	PERSON	Munroe	nn	8	SENT_31	[p2l737t506r969b563],
8	)	NN	O	)	pobj	5	SENT_31	[p2l737t506r969b563],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l737t506r969b563],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_32	[p2l997t506r1109b553],
2	work	NN	O	work	nsubj	3	SENT_32	[p2l1134t507r1261b553],
3	forms	VBZ	O	form	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1284t507r1422b553],
4	part	NN	O	part	dobj	3	SENT_32	[p2l1449t519r1547b569],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1573t507r1628b553],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_32	[p2l1645t507r1721b553],
7	research	NN	O	research	nn	8	SENT_32	[p2l1748t507r1946b553],
8	themes	NNS	O	theme	prep_of	4	SENT_32	[p2l1972t507r2144b553],
9	contributing	VBG	O	contribute	partmod	8	SENT_32	[p2l54t583r357b645],
10	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l395t595r442b629],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_32	[p2l483t583r559b629],
12	translational	JJ	O	translational	amod	14	SENT_32	[p2l599t583r901b629],
13	research	NN	O	research	nn	14	SENT_32	[p2l941t583r1138b629],
14	portfolio	NN	O	portfolio	prep_to	9	SENT_32	[p2l1177t583r1389b645],
15	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1430t583r1499b629],
16	Barts	NNS	PERSON	bart	prep_for	14	SENT_32	[p2l1538t584r1663b629],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1706t583r1793b629],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_32	[p2l1833t583r1909b629],
19	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	nn	23	SENT_32	[p2l1950t583r2145b629],
20	Cardiovascular	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cardiovascular	nn	23	SENT_32	[p2l55t659r416b705],
21	Biomedical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biomedical	nn	23	SENT_32	[p2l445t659r720b705],
22	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	23	SENT_32	[p2l750t659r968b705],
23	Unit	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Unit	prep_for	14	SENT_32	[p2l996t660r1123b715],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l996t660r1123b715],
25	which	WDT	O	which	nsubjpass	27	SENT_32	[p2l1152t659r1301b705],
26	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	27	SENT_32	[p2l1331t661r1365b705],
27	supported	VBN	O	support	rcmod	14	SENT_32	[p2l1397t659r1638b721],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1668t659r1756b705],
29	funded	VBN	O	fund	rcmod	14	SENT_32	[p2l1785t659r1955b705],
30	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1983t659r2042b721],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_32	[p2l2069t659r2145b705],
32	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	33	SENT_32	[p2l53t736r267b781],
33	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	agent	27	SENT_32	[p2l291t736r497b781],
34	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l523t735r592b781],
35	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	36	SENT_32	[p2l617t736r787b781],
36	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	prep_for	33	SENT_32	[p2l814t736r1044b781],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l814t736r1044b781],

1	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	2	SENT_33	[p2l1073t736r1153b781],
2	Johnson	NNP	PERSON	Johnson	nsubj	4	SENT_33	[p2l1176t736r1381b794],
3	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	4	SENT_33	[p2l1406t735r1483b781],
4	received	VBN	O	receive	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1510t735r1707b781],
5	research	NN	O	research	nn	6	SENT_33	[p2l1732t736r1929b781],
6	funding	NN	O	funding	dobj	4	SENT_33	[p2l1954t735r2146b797],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l53t811r170b857],
8	Wellcome	NNP	O	Wellcome	nn	13	SENT_33	[p2l193t812r445b857],
9	Trust	NNP	O	Trust	nn	13	SENT_33	[p2l469t810r605b857],
10	(	NNP	O	(	nn	13	SENT_33	[p2l631t810r797b867],
11	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	nn	13	SENT_33	[p2l631t810r797b867],
12	No.	NN	O	no.	nn	13	SENT_33	[p2l821t812r910b857],
13	093078/Z/10	NN	O	093078/z/10	prep_from	4	SENT_33	[p2l939t810r1364b867],
14	/	:	O	/	punct	16	SENT_33	[p2l939t810r1364b867],
15	Z	NN	O	z	nn	16	SENT_33	[p2l939t810r1364b867],
16	)	NN	O	)	dep	4	SENT_33	[p2l939t810r1364b867],
17	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l939t810r1364b867],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1392t812r1480b857],
19	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	21	SENT_33	[p2l1505t814r1539b857],
20	an	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_33	[p2l1567t830r1622b857],
21	employee	NN	O	employee	conj_and	4	SENT_33	[p2l1648t812r1876b873],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1902t811r1957b857],
23	GlaxoSmithKline	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GlaxoSmithKline	prep_of	21	SENT_33	[p2l1975t811r2143b857, p2l56t887r349b933],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1975t811r2143b857, p2l56t887r349b933],

1	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	2	SENT_34	[p2l386t888r466b933],
2	George	NNP	PERSON	George	nsubj	4	SENT_34	[p2l504t887r683b949],
3	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	4	SENT_34	[p2l717t888r794b933],
4	received	VBN	O	receive	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l829t887r1026b933],
5	research	NN	O	research	nn	6	SENT_34	[p2l1059t888r1256b933],
6	grants	NNS	O	grant	dobj	4	SENT_34	[p2l1289t899r1437b949],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1471t887r1588b933],
8	Gilead	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Gilead	nn	9	SENT_34	[p2l1624t887r1787b933],
9	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	prep_from	4	SENT_34	[p2l1822t887r2022b933],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l2058t888r2146b933],
11	Allergan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Allergan	nn	12	SENT_34	[p2l52t962r263b1025],
12	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	prep_from	4	SENT_34	[p2l283t964r374b1009],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l283t964r374b1009],

1	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	2	SENT_35	[p2l397t964r478b1009],
2	Camm	NNP	PERSON	Camm	nsubj	5	SENT_35	[p2l503t963r669b1009],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	5	SENT_35	[p2l690t966r725b1009],
4	an	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_35	[p2l747t982r803b1009],
5	advisor	NN	O	advisor	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l824t963r996b1009],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1016t963r1104b1009],
7	speaker	NN	O	speaker	conj_and	5	SENT_35	[p2l1125t964r1305b1025],
8	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1324t963r1393b1009],
9	Boehringer	NNP	O	Boehringer	nn	10	SENT_35	[p2l1413t964r1687b1025],
10	lngelheim	NN	O	lngelheim	prep_for	5	SENT_35	[p2l1707t964r1969b1025],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1707t964r1969b1025],
12	Bayer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bayer	nn	18	SENT_35	[p2l1992t964r2143b1025],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1992t964r2143b1025],
14	Daiichi	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Daiichi	appos	18	SENT_35	[p2l53t1040r247b1095],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l53t1040r247b1095],
16	Pﬁzer	NNP	O	Pﬁzer	appos	18	SENT_35	[p2l274t1039r429b1095],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l274t1039r429b1095],
18	Bristol	NNP	LOCATION	Bristol	appos	10	SENT_35	[p2l456t1040r797b1101],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l456t1040r797b1101],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l456t1040r797b1101],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l456t1040r797b1101],

1	Myers	NNP	PERSON	Myers	nn	12	SENT_37	[p2l456t1040r797b1101],
2	Squibb	NNP	PERSON	Squibb	nn	12	SENT_37	[p2l824t1039r1007b1101],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l824t1039r1007b1101],
4	Sanoﬁ	NNP	PERSON	Sanoﬁ	appos	12	SENT_37	[p2l1036t1039r1201b1095],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1036t1039r1201b1095],
6	Servier	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Servier	appos	12	SENT_37	[p2l1230t1039r1408b1095],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1230t1039r1408b1095],
8	Xention	NNP	O	Xention	appos	12	SENT_37	[p2l1432t1040r1646b1095],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1432t1040r1646b1095],
10	Medtronic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medtronic	appos	12	SENT_37	[p2l1671t1040r1946b1095],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1671t1040r1946b1095],
12	Boston	NNP	LOCATION	Boston	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1973t1040r2145b1085],
13	842	CD	NUMBER	842	num	12	SENT_37	[p2l8t1120r121b1173],
14	lamshidi	NN	O	lamshidus	dep	12	SENT_37	[p2l328t1121r573b1174],
15	et	FW	O	et	nn	16	SENT_37	[p2l599t1123r656b1173],
16	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	14	SENT_37	[p2l673t1121r740b1173],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l673t1121r740b1173],

1	NOS1AP	NN	O	nos1ap	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l332t1209r571b1263],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l588t1210r690b1262],
3	Drug-Induced	JJ	O	drug-induced	amod	5	SENT_38	[p2l718t1210r1098b1272],
4	QT	NNP	O	QT	nn	5	SENT_38	[p2l1123t1209r1199b1272],
5	Prolongation	NNP	O	Prolongation	conj_and	1	SENT_38	[p2l1223t1210r1583b1272],

1	Currently	RB	DATE	currently	advmod	2	SENT_39	[p2l967t1432r1335b1521],
2	amiodarone	NN	O	amiodarone	nsubj	11	SENT_39	[p2l1400t1432r1842b1499],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	9	SENT_39	[p2l1910t1435r1963b1499],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_39	[p2l2033t1432r2149b1499],
5	most	RBS	O	most	advmod	7	SENT_39	[p2l965t1557r1146b1606],
6	commonly	RB	O	commonly	advmod	7	SENT_39	[p2l1212t1539r1604b1629],
7	used	VBN	O	use	amod	9	SENT_39	[p2l1666t1539r1832b1606],
8	antiarrhythmic	JJ	O	antiarrhythmic	amod	9	SENT_39	[p2l1899t1542r2146b1606, p2l964t1646r1289b1736],
9	drug	NN	O	drug	rcmod	2	SENT_39	[p2l1336t1646r1516b1736],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1336t1646r1516b1736],
11	followed	VBD	O	follow	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1566t1646r1871b1713],
12	closely	RB	O	closely	advmod	11	SENT_39	[p2l1918t1647r2153b1736],

1	Abbreviations	NNS	O	abbreviation	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l79t1474r512b1524],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l81t1555r190b1605],
3	Acronyms	NNS	O	acronym	conj_and	1	SENT_40	[p2l219t1555r530b1616],

1	CEU	NN	O	ceu	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l80t1720r186b1761],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	3	SENT_41	[p2l214t1733r250b1752],
3	western	JJ	O	western	dep	1	SENT_41	[p2l276t1721r481b1761],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l504t1720r595b1761],
5	northern	JJ	O	northern	amod	7	SENT_41	[p2l81t1805r294b1846],
6	European	JJ	MISC	european	amod	7	SENT_41	[p2l320t1805r555b1856],
7	ancestry	NN	O	ancestry	conj_and	3	SENT_41	[p2l578t1806r801b1856],

1	CI	NN	O	ci	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l80t1925r130b1967],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	4	SENT_42	[p2l160t1939r196b1958],
3	confidence	NN	O	confidence	nn	4	SENT_42	[p2l222t1925r503b1967],
4	interval	NN	O	interval	dep	1	SENT_42	[p2l527t1925r715b1967],

1	DNA	NN	O	dna	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l82t2046r192b2087],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	4	SENT_43	[p2l218t2060r254b2078],
3	deoxyribonucleic	JJ	O	deoxyribonucleic	amod	4	SENT_43	[p2l281t2046r715b2097],
4	acid	NN	O	acid	dep	1	SENT_43	[p2l80t2131r185b2172],

1	ECG	NN	O	ecg	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l82t2252r185b2294],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	3	SENT_44	[p2l214t2266r250b2284],
3	electrocardiogram	NN	O	electrocardiogram	dep	1	SENT_44	[p2l277t2252r747b2303],

1	IRB	NN	O	irb	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l82t2373r171b2414],
2	=	JJ	O	=	dep	1	SENT_45	[p2l198t2386r234b2405],
3	Institutional	JJ	O	institutional	amod	5	SENT_45	[p2l263t2373r571b2414],
4	Review	NNP	O	Review	nn	5	SENT_45	[p2l597t2373r780b2414],
5	Board	NNP	O	Board	dep	1	SENT_45	[p2l82t2458r228b2499],

1	LD	NN	O	ld	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l82t2578r144b2619],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	4	SENT_46	[p2l172t2591r208b2610],
3	linkage	NN	O	linkage	nn	4	SENT_46	[p2l236t2577r421b2629],
4	disequilibrium	NN	O	disequilibrium	dep	1	SENT_46	[p2l443t2577r799b2629],

1	LQTS	NN	O	lqt	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l82t2698r211b2748],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	5	SENT_47	[p2l238t2712r274b2731],
3	long	JJ	O	long	amod	5	SENT_47	[p2l302t2699r410b2750],
4	QT	NN	O	qt	nn	5	SENT_47	[p2l430t2698r498b2748],
5	syndrome	NN	O	syndrome	dep	1	SENT_47	[p2l518t2699r766b2750],
6	nNOS	NN	O	nno	nn	11	SENT_47	[p2l81t2820r220b2861],
7	=	JJ	O	=	amod	11	SENT_47	[p2l247t2833r283b2851],
8	neuronal	JJ	O	neuronal	amod	11	SENT_47	[p2l311t2820r529b2861],
9	nitric	JJ	O	nitric	amod	11	SENT_47	[p2l553t2819r684b2861],
10	oxide	NN	O	oxide	nn	11	SENT_47	[p2l80t2904r218b2946],
11	synthase	NN	O	synthase	dep	1	SENT_47	[p2l239t2905r470b2956],

1	NOS1AP	NN	O	nos1ap	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l82t3025r297b3067],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	4	SENT_48	[p2l324t3039r360b3057],
3	nitric	JJ	O	nitric	amod	4	SENT_48	[p2l388t3025r518b3067],
4	oxide	NN	O	oxide	dep	1	SENT_48	[p2l541t3025r678b3067],
5	synthase	NN	O	synthase	nn	8	SENT_48	[p2l80t3111r311b3161],
6	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	8	SENT_48	[p2l334t3111r366b3151],
7	adaptor	NN	O	adaptor	nn	8	SENT_48	[p2l387t3111r584b3161],
8	protein	NN	O	protein	dep	1	SENT_48	[p2l607t3110r783b3161],

1	OR	NN	O	or	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l81t3231r153b3272],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	3	SENT_49	[p2l181t3244r217b3262],
3	odds	NNS	O	odds	dep	1	SENT_49	[p2l244t3231r364b3272],
4	ratio	NN	O	ratio	dep	1	SENT_49	[p2l388t3231r503b3272],

1	SNP	NN	O	snp	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l79t3351r187b3393],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	5	SENT_50	[p2l214t3365r250b3383],
3	single	JJ	O	single	amod	5	SENT_50	[p2l276t3351r428b3403],
4	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	5	SENT_50	[p2l452t3351r719b3393],
5	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	dep	1	SENT_50	[p2l82t3436r435b3487],

1	TdP	NN	O	tdp	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l80t3558r177b3599],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	3	SENT_51	[p2l203t3572r239b3590],
3	torsades	NNS	O	torsade	dep	1	SENT_51	[p2l265t3558r489b3599],
4	de	IN	O	de	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l511t3558r571b3599],
5	pointes	NNS	O	pointe	prep_de	3	SENT_51	[p2l594t3558r781b3609],
6	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l963t1754r1049b1843],
7	sotalol	NN	O	sotalol	prep_by	5	SENT_51	[p2l1078t1754r1324b1820],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1078t1754r1324b1820],

1	However	RB	O	however	advmod	8	SENT_52	[p2l1360t1755r1703b1835],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1360t1755r1703b1835],
3	use	NN	O	use	nsubjpass	8	SENT_52	[p2l1736t1780r1848b1820],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1880t1754r1960b1820],
5	antiarrhythmic	JJ	O	antiarrhythmic	amod	6	SENT_52	[p2l1980t1757r2147b1820, p2l966t1861r1358b1950],
6	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_of	3	SENT_52	[p2l1411t1861r1602b1950],
7	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_52	[p2l1658t1864r1708b1927],
8	limited	VBN	O	limit	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1762t1861r2016b1927],
9	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l2067t1861r2154b1950],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_52	[p2l965t1968r1075b2035],
11	high	JJ	O	high	amod	12	SENT_52	[p2l1101t1968r1261b2058],
12	incidence	NN	O	incidence	agent	8	SENT_52	[p2l1286t1968r1620b2035],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1647t1968r1727b2035],
14	bradycardia	NN	O	bradycardium	nn	17	SENT_52	[p2l1738t1968r2151b2058],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l966t2075r1094b2142],
16	QT	NN	O	qt	nn	17	SENT_52	[p2l1123t2074r1254b2159],
17	prolongation	NN	O	prolongation	prep_of	12	SENT_52	[p2l1279t2075r1758b2165],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1279t2075r1758b2165],
19	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	21	SENT_52	[p2l1785t2076r2003b2142],
20	can	MD	O	can	aux	21	SENT_52	[p2l2032t2102r2150b2142],
21	result	VB	O	result	rcmod	12	SENT_52	[p2l964t2183r1169b2250],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1233t2186r1303b2249],
23	torsades	FW	O	torsades	nn	26	SENT_52	[p2l1368t2183r1665b2250],
24	de	FW	O	de	nn	26	SENT_52	[p2l1734t2183r1815b2250],
25	pointes	FW	O	pointes	nn	26	SENT_52	[p2l1881t2186r2148b2273],
26	(	FW	O	(	prep_in	21	SENT_52	[p2l968t2288r1180b2371],
27	TdP	NN	O	tdp	dep	26	SENT_52	[p2l968t2288r1180b2371],
28	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	29	SENT_52	[p2l968t2288r1180b2371],
29	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	27	SENT_52	[p2l1241t2288r1446b2371],
30	1-3	CD	NUMBER	1-3	num	31	SENT_52	[p2l1241t2288r1446b2371],
31	)	NN	O	)	dep	29	SENT_52	[p2l1241t2288r1446b2371],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1241t2288r1446b2371],

1	Amiodarone	NNP	O	Amiodarone	nsubj	7	SENT_53	[p2l1502t2289r1953b2357],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	7	SENT_53	[p2l2008t2294r2058b2357],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_53	[p2l2116t2317r2151b2357],
4	class	NN	O	class	nn	7	SENT_53	[p2l966t2398r1121b2464],
5	III	CD	NUMBER	iii	num	7	SENT_53	[p2l1148t2399r1243b2463],
6	antiarrhythmic	JJ	O	antiarrhythmic	amod	7	SENT_53	[p2l1273t2398r1802b2487],
7	agent	NN	O	agent	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1829t2415r2021b2487],
8	inhibiting	VBG	O	inhibit	partmod	7	SENT_53	[p2l2045t2401r2147b2463, p2l965t2504r1247b2594],
9	IKI	NNP	O	IKI	dobj	8	SENT_53	[p2l1282t2505r1385b2590],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1282t2505r1385b2590],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	12	SENT_53	[p2l1424t2502r1584b2585],
12	4,5	CD	NUMBER	4,5	num	13	SENT_53	[p2l1424t2502r1584b2585],
13	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	9	SENT_53	[p2l1424t2502r1584b2585],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1627t2504r1755b2571],
15	increasing	VBG	O	increase	amod	18	SENT_53	[p2l1792t2507r2151b2594],
16	action	NN	O	action	nn	18	SENT_53	[p2l966t2615r1181b2678],
17	potential	JJ	O	potential	amod	18	SENT_53	[p2l1207t2612r1524b2702],
18	duration	NN	O	duration	conj_and	9	SENT_53	[p2l1553t2611r1853b2678],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1883t2611r2011b2678],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_53	[p2l2038t2611r2149b2678],
21	effective	JJ	O	effective	amod	23	SENT_53	[p2l966t2719r1250b2786],
22	refractory	JJ	O	refractory	amod	23	SENT_53	[p2l1305t2719r1650b2808],
23	period	NN	O	period	conj_and	9	SENT_53	[p2l1700t2719r1928b2809],
24	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	25	SENT_53	[p2l1985t2717r2146b2800],
25	6,7	CD	NUMBER	6,7	dep	23	SENT_53	[p2l1985t2717r2146b2800],
26	)	NN	O	)	dep	25	SENT_53	[p2l1985t2717r2146b2800],
27	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	26	SENT_53	[p2l968t2824r1146b2907],
28	seen	VBN	O	see	partmod	23	SENT_53	[p2l968t2824r1146b2907],
29	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1177t2853r1240b2893],
30	QT	NN	O	qt	nn	31	SENT_53	[p2l1273t2825r1404b2910],
31	prolongation	NN	O	prolongation	prep_as	28	SENT_53	[p2l1431t2827r1891b2917],
32	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1921t2853r2009b2893],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	35	SENT_53	[p2l2038t2826r2149b2893],
34	surface	NN	O	surface	nn	35	SENT_53	[p2l966t2934r1187b3000],
35	electrocardiogram	NN	O	electrocardiogram	prep_on	8	SENT_53	[p2l1234t2934r1815b3023],
36	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	37	SENT_53	[p2l1867t2932r2149b3015],
37	ECG	NN	O	ecg	tmod	8	SENT_53	[p2l1867t2932r2149b3015],
38	]	CD	NUMBER	]	num	39	SENT_53	[p2l1867t2932r2149b3015],
39	)	NN	O	)	dep	37	SENT_53	[p2l1867t2932r2149b3015],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1867t2932r2149b3015],

1	Amiodarone	NNP	O	Amiodarone	nsubj	3	SENT_54	[p2l962t3040r1412b3108],
2	also	RB	O	also	advmod	3	SENT_54	[p2l1453t3041r1584b3108],
3	decreases	VBZ	O	decrease	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1625t3041r1948b3108],
4	conduction	NN	O	conduction	nn	5	SENT_54	[p2l1989t3068r2147b3108, p2l966t3148r1234b3215],
5	Velocity	NN	O	velocity	dobj	3	SENT_54	[p2l1256t3148r1531b3238],
6	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1550t3148r1637b3238],
7	blocking	VBG	O	block	prepc_by	3	SENT_54	[p2l1656t3148r1964b3238],
8	Na	NN	O	na	dobj	7	SENT_54	[p2l1988t3139r2143b3215],
9	+	CC	O	+	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1988t3139r2143b3215],
10	channels	NNS	O	channel	dobj	7	SENT_54	[p2l966t3256r1270b3322],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_54	[p2l1315t3253r1498b3336],
12	class	NN	O	class	nsubj	17	SENT_54	[p2l1315t3253r1498b3336],
13	I	CD	NUMBER	i	num	15	SENT_54	[p2l1539t3257r1567b3321],
14	effect	NN	O	effect	nn	15	SENT_54	[p2l1610t3253r1843b3337],
15	)	NN	O	)	dep	12	SENT_54	[p2l1610t3253r1843b3337],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1610t3253r1843b3337],
17	reduces	VBZ	O	reduce	rcmod	8	SENT_54	[p2l1886t3255r2148b3322],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_54	[p2l964t3363r1075b3429],
19	number	NN	O	number	dobj	17	SENT_54	[p2l1135t3363r1411b3429],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1468t3363r1548b3429],
21	beta-adrenergic	JJ	O	beta-adrenergic	amod	22	SENT_54	[p2l1592t3363r2150b3452],
22	receptors	NNS	O	receptor	prep_of	19	SENT_54	[p2l964t3487r1284b3561],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1309t3470r1471b3537],
24	a	DT	O	a	det	27	SENT_54	[p2l1499t3497r1534b3537],
25	resultant	JJ	O	resultant	amod	27	SENT_54	[p2l1559t3470r1869b3537],
26	antiad	JJ	O	antiad	amod	27	SENT_54	[p2l1896t3470r2147b3537],
27	—	NN	O	—	prep_with	17	SENT_54	[p2l1896t3470r2147b3537],
28	renergic	JJ	O	renergic	amod	34	SENT_54	[p2l964t3581r1251b3667],
29	effect	NN	O	effect	nn	34	SENT_54	[p2l1307t3578r1494b3645],
30	(	NN	O	(	nn	34	SENT_54	[p2l1551t3576r1734b3659],
31	class	NN	O	class	nn	34	SENT_54	[p2l1551t3576r1734b3659],
32	II	CD	NUMBER	ii	num	34	SENT_54	[p2l1792t3579r1854b3644],
33	effect	NN	O	effect	nn	34	SENT_54	[p2l1913t3576r2147b3659],
34	)	NN	O	)	dep	27	SENT_54	[p2l1913t3576r2147b3659],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1913t3576r2147b3659],

1	and	CC	O	and	cc	2	SENT_55	[p3l966t37r1095b103],
2	suppresses	VBZ	O	suppress	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1158t63r1524b127],
3	Ca2	NN	O	ca2	nsubj	4	SENT_55	[p3l1590t24r2150b104],
4	+	CC	O	+	xcomp	2	SENT_55	[p3l1590t24r2150b104],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1590t24r2150b104],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1590t24r2150b104],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1590t24r2150b104],

1	mediated	VBN	O	mediate	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1590t24r2150b104],
2	action	NN	O	action	nn	3	SENT_57	[p3l11t147r225b210],
3	potentials	NNS	O	potential	dobj	1	SENT_57	[p3l250t144r596b233],
4	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l621t144r708b233],
5	blocking	VBG	O	block	prepc_by	1	SENT_57	[p3l728t144r1036b233],
6	L	NN	O	l	nn	9	SENT_57	[p3l1062t145r1303b234],
7	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	9	SENT_57	[p3l1062t145r1303b234],
8	type	NN	O	type	nn	9	SENT_57	[p3l1062t145r1303b234],
9	calcium	NN	O	calcium	dobj	5	SENT_57	[p3l1331t144r1602b210],
10	channels	NNS	O	channel	dep	9	SENT_57	[p3l1630t144r1934b210],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_57	[p3l1965t142r2148b224],
12	class	NN	O	class	nn	15	SENT_57	[p3l1965t142r2148b224],
13	IV	CD	NUMBER	iv	num	15	SENT_57	[p3l9t252r105b318],
14	effect	NN	O	effect	nn	15	SENT_57	[p3l127t249r359b332],
15	)	NN	O	)	dep	10	SENT_57	[p3l127t249r359b332],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l127t249r359b332],

1	Sotalol	NNP	O	Sotalol	nsubj	6	SENT_58	[p3l391t251r635b318],
2	meanwhile	RB	O	meanwhile	advmod	6	SENT_58	[p3l659t251r1044b318],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	6	SENT_58	[p3l1069t254r1119b317],
4	an	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_58	[p3l1146t277r1227b317],
5	antiarrhythmic	JJ	O	antiarrhythmic	amod	6	SENT_58	[p3l1253t251r1782b340],
6	drug	NN	O	drug	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1806t251r1969b340],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1988t251r2150b318],
8	class	NN	O	class	prep_with	6	SENT_58	[p3l10t358r165b424],
9	II	CD	NUMBER	ii	num	8	SENT_58	[p3l200t359r261b423],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l298t358r425b424],
11	class	NN	O	class	conj_and	6	SENT_58	[p3l459t358r614b424],
12	III	CD	NUMBER	iii	num	13	SENT_58	[p3l648t359r743b423],
13	properties	NNS	O	property	dep	11	SENT_58	[p3l777t361r1131b448],
14	@	IN	O	@	quantmod	15	SENT_58	[p3l1169t356r1284b438],
15	6	CD	NUMBER	6	dep	13	SENT_58	[p3l1169t356r1284b438],
16	+	CC	O	+	cc	15	SENT_58	[p3l1169t356r1284b438],

1	It	PRP	O	it	nsubjpass	4	SENT_59	[p3l98t466r158b531],
2	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	4	SENT_59	[p3l188t465r301b531],
3	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_59	[p3l332t465r499b531],
4	suggested	VBN	O	suggest	ccomp	38	SENT_59	[p3l531t465r874b554],
5	that	IN	O	that	complm	8	SENT_59	[p3l904t465r1046b531],
6	every	DT	O	every	det	7	SENT_59	[p3l1077t491r1260b554],
7	individual	NN	O	individual	nsubj	8	SENT_59	[p3l1287t465r1642b531],
8	has	VBZ	O	have	ccomp	4	SENT_59	[p3l1672t465r1785b531],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_59	[p3l1819t491r1854b531],
10	physiological	JJ	O	physiological	amod	14	SENT_59	[p3l1883t465r2147b554, p3l8t572r239b661],
11	“	NN	O	“	nn	14	SENT_59	[p3l281t572r561b638],
12	cardiac	JJ	O	cardiac	amod	14	SENT_59	[p3l281t572r561b638],
13	repolarization	NN	O	repolarization	nn	14	SENT_59	[p3l604t572r1096b661],
14	reserve	NN	O	reserve	dobj	8	SENT_59	[p3l1139t572r1412b638],
15	”	CD	NUMBER	”	number	16	SENT_59	[p3l1139t572r1412b638],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	14	SENT_59	[p3l1460t570r1577b653],
17	8	CD	NUMBER	8	num	18	SENT_59	[p3l1460t570r1577b653],
18	)	NN	O	)	dep	16	SENT_59	[p3l1460t570r1577b653],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1460t570r1577b653],
20	which	WDT	O	which	nsubjpass	24	SENT_59	[p3l1619t572r1838b638],
21	may	MD	O	may	aux	24	SENT_59	[p3l1882t598r2031b661],
22	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	24	SENT_59	[p3l2068t572r2149b638],
23	genetically	RB	O	genetically	advmod	24	SENT_59	[p3l8t680r388b769],
24	determined	VBN	O	determine	rcmod	14	SENT_59	[p3l443t680r849b746],
25	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l907t680r1035b746],
26	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	27	SENT_59	[p3l1089t680r1307b746],
27	compensates	VBZ	O	compensate	conj_and	8	SENT_59	[p3l1366t697r1812b769],
28	for	IN	O	for	mark	34	SENT_59	[p3l1872t680r1973b746],
29	any	DT	O	any	det	33	SENT_59	[p3l2030t706r2154b769],
30	endogenous	JJ	O	endogenous	amod	33	SENT_59	[p3l10t814r431b903],
31	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l474t839r547b880],
32	exogenous	JJ	O	exogenous	amod	33	SENT_59	[p3l587t840r953b903],
33	factors	NNS	O	factor	nsubj	34	SENT_59	[p3l996t814r1228b880],
34	(	VBP	O	(	advcl	27	SENT_59	[p3l1274t812r1444b903],
35	e.g.	FW	O	e.g.	dobj	34	SENT_59	[p3l1274t812r1444b903],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1274t812r1444b903],
37	drugs	NNS	O	drug	nsubj	38	SENT_59	[p3l1488t812r1707b903],
38	)	VBP	O	)	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1488t812r1707b903],
39	that	DT	O	that	nsubj	42	SENT_59	[p3l1752t814r1894b880],
40	would	MD	O	would	aux	42	SENT_59	[p3l1929t814r2151b880],
41	either	RB	O	either	advmod	42	SENT_59	[p3l10t947r214b1014],
42	decrease	VB	O	decrease	ccomp	38	SENT_59	[p3l237t947r529b1014],
43	repolarizing	JJ	O	repolarizing	amod	47	SENT_59	[p3l553t947r980b1037],
44	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1002t973r1075b1014],
45	increase	NN	O	increase	amod	47	SENT_59	[p3l1096t950r1376b1014],
46	depolarizing	VBG	O	depolarize	amod	47	SENT_59	[p3l1401t947r1843b1037],
47	currents	NNS	O	current	dobj	42	SENT_59	[p3l1865t965r2148b1014],
48	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l10t1054r244b1144],
49	the	DT	O	the	det	51	SENT_59	[p3l297t1054r408b1121],
50	action	NN	O	action	nn	51	SENT_59	[p3l465t1057r679b1121],
51	potential	NN	O	potential	prep_during	42	SENT_59	[p3l733t1054r1067b1144],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l733t1054r1067b1144],

1	It	PRP	O	it	nsubj	3	SENT_60	[p3l1126t1055r1186b1121],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	3	SENT_60	[p3l1240t1057r1290b1121],
3	likely	RB	O	likely	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1346t1054r1554b1144],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1346t1054r1554b1144],
5	therefore	RB	O	therefore	advmod	3	SENT_60	[p3l1612t1054r1952b1135],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1612t1054r1952b1135],
7	that	IN	O	that	complm	15	SENT_60	[p3l2010t1054r2152b1121],
8	individuals	NNS	O	individual	nsubj	15	SENT_60	[p3l9t1161r393b1228],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l441t1161r603b1228],
10	reduced	VBN	O	reduce	amod	12	SENT_60	[p3l652t1161r931b1228],
11	repolarization	NN	O	repolarization	nn	12	SENT_60	[p3l981t1161r1473b1251],
12	reserve	NN	O	reserve	prep_with	8	SENT_60	[p3l1523t1187r1764b1228],
13	are	VBP	O	be	cop	15	SENT_60	[p3l1816t1187r1917b1228],
14	more	RBR	O	more	advmod	15	SENT_60	[p3l1969t1187r2149b1228],
15	vulnerable	JJ	O	vulnerable	ccomp	3	SENT_60	[p3l6t1268r372b1335],
16	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l395t1285r464b1334],
17	developing	VBG	O	develop	prepc_to	15	SENT_60	[p3l489t1268r876b1358],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_60	[p3l899t1267r1334b1352],
19	LT-interval	JJ	O	lt-interval	amod	20	SENT_60	[p3l899t1267r1334b1352],
20	prolongation	NN	O	prolongation	dobj	17	SENT_60	[p3l1355t1268r1814b1358],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1839t1268r1967b1334],
22	TdP	NN	O	tdp	dobj	17	SENT_60	[p3l1987t1267r2149b1334],
23	when	WRB	O	when	advmod	24	SENT_60	[p3l6t1376r201b1443],
24	exposed	VBN	O	expose	ccomp	15	SENT_60	[p3l228t1376r508b1466],
25	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l533t1393r602b1442],
26	potassium	NN	O	potassium	nn	28	SENT_60	[p3l628t1379r987b1466],
27	channel-blocking	NN	O	channel-blocking	nn	28	SENT_60	[p3l1015t1376r1655b1465],
28	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_to	24	SENT_60	[p3l1680t1376r1871b1465],
29	such	JJ	O	such	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1901t1376r2058b1442],
30	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l2085t1402r2148b1442],
31	amiodarone	NN	O	amiodarone	prep_such_as	28	SENT_60	[p3l11t1483r428b1549],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l464t1483r592b1549],
33	sotalol	NN	O	sotalol	prep_such_as	28	SENT_60	[p3l626t1483r872b1549],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l626t1483r872b1549],

1	Genome	NNP	O	Genome	dep	3	SENT_61	[p3l100t1590r613b1657],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	1	SENT_61	[p3l100t1590r613b1657],
3	wide	JJ	O	wide	amod	4	SENT_61	[p3l100t1590r613b1657],
4	analysis	NN	O	analysis	nsubj	29	SENT_61	[p3l654t1590r921b1679],
5	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	7	SENT_61	[p3l961t1590r1074b1656],
6	consistently	RB	O	consistently	advmod	7	SENT_61	[p3l1115t1590r1536b1679],
7	associated	VBN	O	associate	parataxis	29	SENT_61	[p3l1572t1590r1926b1656],
8	common	JJ	O	common	amod	9	SENT_61	[p3l1965t1616r2147b1656, p3l10t1723r170b1763],
9	variants	NNS	O	variant	dobj	7	SENT_61	[p3l198t1700r473b1763],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l507t1697r588b1763],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_61	[p3l607t1697r718b1763],
12	nitric	JJ	O	nitric	amod	14	SENT_61	[p3l751t1700r939b1763],
13	oxide	NN	O	oxide	nn	14	SENT_61	[p3l970t1697r1157b1763],
14	synthase	NN	O	synthase	prep_of	9	SENT_61	[p3l1191t1697r1489b1786],
15	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	17	SENT_61	[p3l1525t1700r1557b1762],
16	adaptor	NN	O	adaptor	nn	17	SENT_61	[p3l1595t1697r1864b1786],
17	protein	NN	O	protein	nsubj	7	SENT_61	[p3l1893t1700r2150b1786],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	21	SENT_61	[p3l12t1803r389b1885],
19	NOSJﬂP	NN	O	nosjﬂp	nn	21	SENT_61	[p3l12t1803r389b1885],
20	)	NN	O	)	nn	21	SENT_61	[p3l12t1803r389b1885],
21	gene	NN	O	gene	dep	7	SENT_61	[p3l425t1831r589b1894],
22	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l620t1805r782b1871],
23	QT	NN	O	qt	nn	24	SENT_61	[p3l818t1803r948b1888],
24	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_with	7	SENT_61	[p3l981t1805r1247b1871],
25	across	IN	O	across	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1281t1830r1488b1871],
26	independent	JJ	O	independent	amod	28	SENT_61	[p3l1524t1805r1970b1894],
27	replication	NN	O	replication	nn	28	SENT_61	[p3l2002t1830r2147b1894, p3l8t1911r271b1978],
28	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_across	24	SENT_61	[p3l318t1912r557b1978],
29	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l607t1909r867b1992],
30	9-12	CD	NUMBER	9-12	num	31	SENT_61	[p3l607t1909r867b1992],
31	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dobj	29	SENT_61	[p3l607t1909r867b1992],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l607t1909r867b1992],

1	Despite	IN	O	despite	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l917t1912r1191b2001],
2	attempts	NNS	O	attempt	prep_despite	29	SENT_62	[p3l1238t1928r1543b2001],
3	to	TO	O	to	aux	4	SENT_62	[p3l1590t1928r1658b1978],
4	identify	VB	O	identify	infmod	2	SENT_62	[p3l1705t1911r1980b2001],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l2022t1911r2151b1978],
6	validate	VB	O	validate	infmod	2	SENT_62	[p3l6t2018r280b2085],
7	a	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_62	[p3l322t2044r357b2085],
8	single	JJ	O	single	amod	9	SENT_62	[p3l397t2018r599b2107],
9	functional	JJ	O	functional	amod	10	SENT_62	[p3l640t2018r1001b2085],
10	variant	NN	O	variant	dobj	4	SENT_62	[p3l1036t2021r1284b2085],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l1322t2021r1390b2084],
12	NOS	NN	O	no	nn	14	SENT_62	[p3l1427t2021r1762b2085],
13	]	CD	NUMBER	]	num	14	SENT_62	[p3l1427t2021r1762b2085],
14	ﬂP	NN	O	ﬂp	prep_in	10	SENT_62	[p3l1427t2021r1762b2085],
15	associated	VBN	O	associate	partmod	14	SENT_62	[p3l1797t2018r2151b2085],
16	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l6t2125r168b2192],
17	QT	NN	O	qt	nn	18	SENT_62	[p3l197t2123r328b2209],
18	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_with	15	SENT_62	[p3l354t2125r639b2206],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l354t2125r639b2206],
20	resequencing	NN	O	resequencing	appos	18	SENT_62	[p3l669t2128r1134b2214],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l1160t2125r1240b2191],
22	all	DT	O	all	det	23	SENT_62	[p3l1257t2125r1337b2191],
23	exons	NNS	O	exon	prep_of	20	SENT_62	[p3l1364t2151r1559b2191],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l1588t2128r1656b2190],
25	NOS1ﬂP	NN	O	nos1ﬂp	prep_in	23	SENT_62	[p3l1680t2128r2015b2192],
26	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	29	SENT_62	[p3l2035t2125r2148b2191],
27	not	RB	O	not	neg	29	SENT_62	[p3l10t2249r128b2298],
28	yet	RB	O	yet	advmod	29	SENT_62	[p3l151t2249r258b2321],
29	identified	VBN	O	identify	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l283t2232r623b2298],
30	any	DT	O	any	det	31	SENT_62	[p3l651t2258r775b2321],
31	missense	NN	O	missense	dobj	29	SENT_62	[p3l799t2235r1109b2298],
32	mutations	NNS	O	mutation	nsubj	29	SENT_62	[p3l1138t2235r1492b2298],
33	that	WDT	O	that	dobj	34	SENT_62	[p3l1521t2232r1663b2298],
34	explain	VBP	O	explain	ccomp	32	SENT_62	[p3l1690t2232r1941b2322],
35	these	DT	O	these	det	36	SENT_62	[p3l1968t2232r2149b2298],
36	results	NNS	O	result	dobj	34	SENT_62	[p3l9t2340r254b2421],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l9t2340r254b2421],
38	suggesting	VBG	O	suggest	partmod	34	SENT_62	[p3l305t2343r679b2429],
39	that	IN	O	that	complm	49	SENT_62	[p3l724t2340r866b2406],
40	the	DT	O	the	det	42	SENT_62	[p3l910t2340r1021b2406],
41	functional	JJ	O	functional	amod	42	SENT_62	[p3l1069t2340r1429b2406],
42	variants	NNS	O	variant	nsubj	49	SENT_62	[p3l1471t2343r1747b2406],
43	associated	VBN	O	associate	partmod	42	SENT_62	[p3l1797t2340r2150b2406],
44	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l6t2448r168b2514],
45	these	DT	O	these	det	48	SENT_62	[p3l225t2448r405b2514],
46	single	JJ	O	single	amod	48	SENT_62	[p3l466t2448r667b2537],
47	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	48	SENT_62	[p3l727t2448r1093b2514],
48	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	prep_with	43	SENT_62	[p3l1151t2448r1700b2537],
49	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	38	SENT_62	[p3l1762t2446r1985b2528],
50	SNP	NN	O	snp	nn	51	SENT_62	[p3l1762t2446r1985b2528],
51	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	53	SENT_62	[p3l1762t2446r1985b2528],
52	are	VBP	O	be	cop	53	SENT_62	[p3l2048t2473r2149b2514],
53	likely	JJ	O	likely	ccomp	49	SENT_62	[p3l8t2554r200b2644],
54	to	TO	O	to	aux	56	SENT_62	[p3l230t2571r298b2621],
55	be	VB	O	be	cop	56	SENT_62	[p3l330t2555r411b2621],
56	regulatory	JJ	O	regulatory	xcomp	53	SENT_62	[p3l445t2555r806b2644],
57	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l835t2557r903b2620],
58	nature	NN	O	nature	prep_in	56	SENT_62	[p3l937t2572r1160b2621],
59	+	CC	O	+	dep	34	SENT_62	[p3l1197t2552r1313b2635],

1	Scientiﬁc	NNP	O	Scientiﬁc	nsubj	10	SENT_63	[p3l11t2898r253b2955],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l11t2898r253b2955],
3	Gilead	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Gilead	nsubj	10	SENT_63	[p3l280t2898r460b2955],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l280t2898r460b2955],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l486t2898r576b2944],
6	Menarini	NNP	LOCATION	Menarini	nsubj	10	SENT_63	[p3l597t2899r846b2955],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l597t2899r846b2955],
8	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	10	SENT_63	[p3l871t2900r907b2944],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_63	[p3l933t2916r957b2944],
10	data	NN	O	datum	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l980t2898r1084b2945],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1107t2898r1197b2944],
12	safety	NN	O	safety	nn	15	SENT_63	[p3l1221t2898r1362b2961],
13	monitoring	NN	O	monitoring	nn	15	SENT_63	[p3l1384t2900r1666b2961],
14	board	NN	O	board	nn	15	SENT_63	[p3l1687t2898r1830b2944],
15	member	NN	O	member	conj_and	10	SENT_63	[p3l1853t2898r2059b2944],
16	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l2081t2898r2151b2944],
17	Cameron	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cameron	nn	18	SENT_63	[p3l10t2975r242b3022],
18	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	prep_for	10	SENT_63	[p3l265t2975r453b3032],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l265t2975r453b3032],
20	Biotronik	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biotronik	prep_for	10	SENT_63	[p3l478t2975r732b3032],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l478t2975r732b3032],
22	Novartis	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Novartis	prep_for	10	SENT_63	[p3l756t2976r984b3032],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l756t2976r984b3032],
24	Astellas	NNP	O	Astellas	prep_for	10	SENT_63	[p3l1007t2974r1216b3032],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1007t2974r1216b3032],
26	Forest	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Forest	nn	27	SENT_63	[p3l1242t2976r1399b3022],
27	Labs	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Labs	conj_and	18	SENT_63	[p3l1421t2975r1554b3032],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1421t2975r1554b3032],
29	Servier	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Servier	conj_and	18	SENT_63	[p3l1581t2975r1764b3032],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1581t2975r1764b3032],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1790t2975r1880b3022],
32	Bioctcon	NNP	O	Bioctcon	nn	34	SENT_63	[p3l1903t2976r2148b3022],
33	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	34	SENT_63	[p3l1903t2976r2148b3022],
34	trol	NN	O	trol	conj_and	18	SENT_63	[p3l8t3053r108b3110],
35	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l8t3053r108b3110],
36	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	40	SENT_63	[p3l130t3055r165b3100],
37	an	DT	O	a	det	40	SENT_63	[p3l187t3071r244b3100],
38	events	NNS	O	event	nn	40	SENT_63	[p3l264t3066r416b3100],
39	committee	NN	O	committee	nn	40	SENT_63	[p3l437t3055r701b3100],
40	member	NN	O	member	conj_and	10	SENT_63	[p3l722t3053r927b3100],
41	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l945t3053r1016b3100],
42	Novartis	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Novartis	prep_for	40	SENT_63	[p3l1034t3054r1261b3110],
43	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1034t3054r1261b3110],
44	has	VBZ	O	have	conj_and	10	SENT_63	[p3l1282t3053r1361b3100],
45	research	NN	O	research	nn	46	SENT_63	[p3l1382t3053r1584b3100],
46	contracts	NNS	O	contract	dobj	44	SENT_63	[p3l1604t3065r1826b3100],
47	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1844t3053r1958b3100],
48	Sanoﬁ	NNP	PERSON	Sanoﬁ	prep_with	46	SENT_63	[p3l1980t3053r2149b3110],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1980t3053r2149b3110],
50	Boehringer	NNP	PERSON	Boehringer	nn	58	SENT_63	[p3l9t3130r289b3193],
51	Ingelheim	NNP	PERSON	Ingelheim	nn	58	SENT_63	[p3l315t3130r583b3193],
52	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l315t3130r583b3193],
53	Daiichi	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Daiichi	appos	58	SENT_63	[p3l612t3130r811b3187],
54	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l612t3130r811b3187],
55	Menarini	NNP	O	Menarini	appos	58	SENT_63	[p3l838t3131r1087b3187],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l838t3131r1087b3187],
57	Richmond	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Richmond	appos	58	SENT_63	[p3l1117t3130r1381b3176],
58	Pharmacology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmacology	appos	48	SENT_63	[p3l1407t3130r1777b3193],
59	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1407t3130r1777b3193],
60	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1807t3130r1896b3177],
61	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	63	SENT_63	[p3l1922t3132r1958b3176],
62	a	DT	O	a	det	63	SENT_63	[p3l1987t3148r2011b3176],
63	consultant	NN	O	consultant	conj_and	10	SENT_63	[p3l2038t3148r2148b3176, p3l9t3207r177b3253],
64	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l197t3207r268b3253],
65	Cardialysis	NNP	O	Cardialysis	prep_for	63	SENT_63	[p3l289t3207r573b3270],
66	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l289t3207r573b3270],

1	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	2	SENT_64	[p3l597t3208r679b3253],
2	Roden	NNP	PERSON	Roden	nsubj	4	SENT_64	[p3l705t3207r869b3253],
3	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	4	SENT_64	[p3l890t3207r969b3253],
4	received	VBN	O	receive	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l991t3207r1193b3253],
5	consulting	VBG	O	consult	amod	6	SENT_64	[p3l1214t3207r1472b3270],
6	fees	NNS	O	fee	dobj	4	SENT_64	[p3l1492t3207r1583b3253],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1605t3207r1725b3253],
8	Astellas	NNP	LOCATION	Astellas	prep_from	6	SENT_64	[p3l1744t3206r1954b3264],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1744t3206r1954b3264],
10	Sanoﬁ	NNP	O	Sanoﬁ	prep_from	6	SENT_64	[p3l1980t3207r2148b3264],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1980t3207r2148b3264],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l9t3284r99b3330],
13	Warner	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Warner	prep_from	6	SENT_64	[p3l125t3284r551b3331],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l125t3284r551b3331],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l125t3284r551b3331],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l125t3284r551b3331],

1	Chicott	NNP	PERSON	Chicott	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l125t3284r551b3331],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l125t3284r551b3331],

1	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	2	SENT_67	[p3l583t3285r666b3330],
2	Behr	NNP	PERSON	Behr	nsubj	4	SENT_67	[p3l697t3284r819b3330],
3	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	4	SENT_67	[p3l846t3284r926b3330],
4	received	VBN	O	receive	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l955t3284r1157b3330],
5	research	NN	O	research	nn	6	SENT_67	[p3l1185t3284r1387b3330],
6	funding	NN	O	funding	dobj	4	SENT_67	[p3l1415t3284r1612b3347],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1639t3284r1759b3330],
8	Biotronik	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biotronik	prep_from	6	SENT_67	[p3l1788t3284r2042b3341],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1788t3284r2042b3341],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_67	[p3l2072t3284r2150b3330],
11	International	NNP	O	International	nn	14	SENT_67	[p3l8t3361r335b3408],
12	Serious	NNP	O	Serious	nn	14	SENT_67	[p3l362t3361r540b3408],
13	Adverse	JJ	O	adverse	amod	14	SENT_67	[p3l564t3360r766b3408],
14	Events	NNS	O	event	conj_and	6	SENT_67	[p3l793t3362r961b3408],
15	Consortium	NNP	O	Consortium	dep	14	SENT_67	[p3l989t3361r1303b3418],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l989t3361r1303b3418],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1332t3361r1422b3408],
18	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	nn	20	SENT_67	[p3l1449t3361r1511b3408],
19	Jude	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jude	nn	20	SENT_67	[p3l1533t3361r1648b3421],
20	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	conj_and	6	SENT_67	[p3l1673t3361r1890b3408],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1673t3361r1890b3408],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	3	SENT_68	[p3l1917t3360r1995b3407],
2	other	JJ	O	other	amod	3	SENT_68	[p3l2020t3361r2151b3408],
3	authors	NNS	O	author	nsubj	5	SENT_68	[p3l9t3438r192b3484],
4	have	VBP	O	have	aux	5	SENT_68	[p3l214t3438r325b3485],
5	reported	VBN	O	report	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l346t3438r556b3501],
6	that	IN	O	that	complm	8	SENT_68	[p3l577t3438r676b3484],
7	they	PRP	O	they	nsubj	8	SENT_68	[p3l696t3438r804b3501],
8	have	VBP	O	have	ccomp	5	SENT_68	[p3l822t3438r933b3484],
9	no	DT	O	no	det	10	SENT_68	[p3l955t3456r1016b3484],
10	relationships	NNS	O	relationship	nsubj	11	SENT_68	[p3l1037t3438r1353b3501],
11	relevant	JJ	O	relevant	xcomp	8	SENT_68	[p3l1375t3438r1571b3484],
12	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l1591t3450r1639b3484],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_68	[p3l1661t3438r1738b3484],
14	contents	NNS	O	contents	prep_to	11	SENT_68	[p3l1760t3450r1969b3484],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l1991t3438r2048b3484],
16	this	DT	O	this	det	17	SENT_68	[p3l2060t3438r2149b3484],
17	paper	NN	O	paper	prep_of	14	SENT_68	[p3l8t3533r146b3578],
18	to	TO	O	to	aux	19	SENT_68	[p3l168t3528r216b3561],
19	disclose	VB	O	disclose	infmod	17	SENT_68	[p3l241t3515r444b3561],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l241t3515r444b3561],

1	Drs.	NNP	O	Drs.	nn	2	SENT_69	[p3l470t3516r575b3561],
2	Jamshidi	NNP	PERSON	Jamshidi	nsubj	5	SENT_69	[p3l594t3515r819b3574],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l843t3515r932b3561],
4	Nolte	NNP	PERSON	Nolte	nsubj	5	SENT_69	[p3l955t3515r1095b3561],
5	contributed	VBD	O	contribute	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1120t3515r1408b3561],
6	equally	RB	O	equally	advmod	5	SENT_69	[p3l1431t3515r1607b3578],
7	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1627t3527r1675b3561],
8	this	DT	O	this	det	9	SENT_69	[p3l1699t3515r1788b3561],
9	paper	NN	O	paper	prep_to	5	SENT_69	[p3l1812t3533r1962b3578],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1812t3533r1962b3578],

1	Manuscript	NN	O	manuscript	nsubj	2	SENT_70	[p3l69t3593r361b3655],
2	received	VBD	O	receive	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l381t3593r583b3639],
3	November	NNP	DATE	November	tmod	2	SENT_70	[p3l604t3593r868b3639],
4	9	CD	DATE	9	num	3	SENT_70	[p3l889t3595r931b3649],
5	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l889t3595r931b3649],
6	2011	CD	DATE	2011	num	3	SENT_70	[p3l953t3595r1092b3649],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l953t3595r1092b3649],
8	revised	VBN	O	revise	amod	9	SENT_70	[p3l1115t3593r1287b3639],
9	manuscript	NN	O	manuscript	dobj	2	SENT_70	[p3l1309t3595r1587b3655],
10	received	VBD	O	receive	rcmod	9	SENT_70	[p3l1607t3593r1809b3639],
11	February	NNP	DATE	February	tmod	10	SENT_70	[p3l1831t3593r2055b3655],
12	24	CD	DATE	24	num	11	SENT_70	[p3l2073t3595r2148b3649],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l2073t3595r2148b3649],

1	2012	CD	DATE	2012	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l7t3672r145b3726],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l7t3672r145b3726],
3	accepted	VBN	O	accept	partmod	1	SENT_71	[p3l171t3669r384b3732],
4	March	NNP	DATE	March	tmod	3	SENT_71	[p3l406t3670r573b3716],
5	6	CD	DATE	6	num	4	SENT_71	[p3l598t3672r639b3726],
6	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l598t3672r639b3726],
7	2012	CD	DATE	2012	num	4	SENT_71	[p3l663t3672r800b3716],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l663t3672r800b3716],

1	JACC	NNP	O	JACC	nn	2	SENT_72	[p3l1504t3753r1619b3804],
2	Vol	NNP	O	Vol	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1641t3753r1723b3804],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1641t3753r1723b3804],

1	60	CD	NUMBER	60	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1750t3753r1823b3812],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1750t3753r1823b3812],
3	No.	NN	O	no.	appos	1	SENT_73	[p3l1851t3753r1922b3804],
4	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	3	SENT_73	[p3l1948t3753r1990b3812],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1948t3753r1990b3812],
6	2012	CD	DATE	2012	appos	1	SENT_73	[p3l2016t3753r2139b3804],

1	August	NNP	DATE	August	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l1529t26r1687b89],
2	28	CD	DATE	28	num	1	SENT_74	[p4l1712t25r1785b85],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l1712t25r1785b85],
4	2012:841	CD	NUMBER	2012:841	num	1	SENT_74	[p4l1814t25r2140b76],
5	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	6	SENT_74	[p4l1814t25r2140b76],
6	5O	NN	O	5o	dep	1	SENT_74	[p4l1814t25r2140b76],

1	NOS1AP	NN	O	nos1ap	nsubj	4	SENT_75	[p4l99t243r452b311],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	4	SENT_75	[p4l481t248r532b311],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_75	[p4l565t271r599b311],
4	regulator	NN	O	regulator	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l627t245r945b334],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l973t245r1053b311],
6	neuronal	JJ	O	neuronal	amod	11	SENT_75	[p4l1071t245r1381b311],
7	nitric	JJ	O	nitric	amod	11	SENT_75	[p4l1410t248r1596b311],
8	oxide	NN	O	oxide	nn	11	SENT_75	[p4l1626t245r1812b311],
9	synthase	NN	O	synthase	nn	11	SENT_75	[p4l1843t245r2139b334],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_75	[p4l13t349r273b431],
11	nNOS	NN	O	nno	prep_of	4	SENT_75	[p4l13t349r273b431],
12	encoded	VBN	O	encode	partmod	11	SENT_75	[p4l324t351r617b417],
13	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l662t351r747b440],
14	NOS1	NN	O	nos1	nn	15	SENT_75	[p4l787t349r1055b432],
15	)	NN	O	)	agent	12	SENT_75	[p4l787t349r1055b432],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l787t349r1055b432],
17	an	DT	O	a	det	18	SENT_75	[p4l1107t377r1187b417],
18	isoform	NN	O	isoform	conj_and	4	SENT_75	[p4l1234t351r1504b417],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l1553t351r1633b417],
20	NOS	NN	O	no	prep_of	18	SENT_75	[p4l1667t351r1877b432],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l1667t351r1877b432],
22	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	23	SENT_75	[p4l1923t351r2140b417],
23	regulates	VBZ	O	regulate	rcmod	20	SENT_75	[p4l10t457r320b546],
24	intracellular	JJ	O	intracellular	amod	26	SENT_75	[p4l359t457r781b523],
25	calcium	NN	O	calcium	nn	26	SENT_75	[p4l818t457r1087b523],
26	levels	NNS	O	level	dobj	23	SENT_75	[p4l1124t457r1311b523],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l1352t457r1479b523],
28	myocyte	NN	O	myocyte	nn	29	SENT_75	[p4l1517t474r1808b546],
29	contraction	NN	O	contraction	conj_and	4	SENT_75	[p4l1847t474r2137b523, p4l10t565r150b627],
30	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l197t565r265b626],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	35	SENT_75	[p4l312t562r422b627],
32	heart	NN	O	heart	nn	35	SENT_75	[p4l470t562r651b627],
33	(	NN	O	(	nn	35	SENT_75	[p4l699t560r992b642],
34	13-15	CD	NUMBER	13-15	num	35	SENT_75	[p4l699t560r992b642],
35	)	NN	O	)	prep_in	29	SENT_75	[p4l699t560r992b642],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l699t560r992b642],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_76	[p4l1041t560r1188b627],
2	NOS1AP	NN	O	nos1ap	nsubj	3	SENT_76	[p4l1235t560r1589b627],
3	interacts	VBZ	O	interact	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1636t565r1933b627],
4	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1979t562r2140b627],
5	nNOS	NN	O	nno	prep_with	3	SENT_76	[p4l11t668r243b734],
6	to	TO	O	to	aux	7	SENT_76	[p4l281t685r349b734],
7	accelerate	VB	O	accelerate	xcomp	3	SENT_76	[p4l388t668r726b734],
8	cardiac	JJ	O	cardiac	amod	9	SENT_76	[p4l763t668r1009b734],
9	repolarization	NN	O	repolarization	dobj	7	SENT_76	[p4l1044t668r1534b757],
10	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1567t668r1653b757],
11	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	prep_by	7	SENT_76	[p4l1685t668r2036b734],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l2073t668r2152b734],
13	L	NN	O	l	nn	16	SENT_76	[p4l11t775r251b863],
14	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	16	SENT_76	[p4l11t775r251b863],
15	type	NN	O	type	nn	16	SENT_76	[p4l11t775r251b863],
16	calcium	NN	O	calcium	prep_of	11	SENT_76	[p4l314t774r583b840],
17	channels	NNS	O	channel	nsubj	18	SENT_76	[p4l645t774r948b840],
18	(	VBP	O	(	rcmod	11	SENT_76	[p4l1014t772r1319b855],
19	16-19	CD	NUMBER	16-19	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1014t772r1319b855],
20	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dobj	18	SENT_76	[p4l1014t772r1319b855],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1014t772r1319b855],
22	thereby	RB	O	thereby	advmod	23	SENT_76	[p4l1382t774r1649b863],
23	providing	VBG	O	provide	partmod	7	SENT_76	[p4l1704t774r2047b863],
24	a	DT	O	a	det	25	SENT_76	[p4l2107t800r2141b840],
25	rationale	NN	O	rationale	dobj	23	SENT_76	[p4l10t880r316b946],
26	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l348t880r448b946],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_76	[p4l477t880r587b946],
28	association	NN	O	association	prep_for	25	SENT_76	[p4l620t883r1003b946],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1034t880r1114b946],
30	NOSJAP	NN	O	nosjap	nn	32	SENT_76	[p4l1129t883r1463b946],
31	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	32	SENT_76	[p4l1485t906r1648b969],
32	variants	NNS	O	variant	prep_of	28	SENT_76	[p4l1676t883r1950b946],
33	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1979t880r2140b946],
34	(	NN	O	(	nn	36	SENT_76	[p4l12t983r445b1068],
35	LT-interval	NN	O	lt-interval	nn	36	SENT_76	[p4l12t983r445b1068],
36	duration	NN	O	duration	prep_with	23	SENT_76	[p4l478t985r795b1050],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l478t985r795b1050],
