1	Biochemistry	NNP	O	Biochemistry	nn	3	SENT_1	[p1l955t119r1131b149],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	3	SENT_1	[p1l1141t119r1222b149],
3	ISSN	NNP	O	ISSN	nsubjpass	7	SENT_1	[p1l1141t119r1222b149],
4	0006-2960	CD	DURATION	0006-2960	num	5	SENT_1	[p1l1232t119r1385b149],
5	)	CD	NUMBER	)	nsubjpass	7	SENT_1	[p1l1232t119r1385b149],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_1	[p1l1396t119r1416b143],
7	published	VBN	O	publish	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1425t119r1555b150],
8	weekly	JJ	SET	weekly	amod	10	SENT_1	[p1l1563t119r1659b150],
9	exce	NN	O	exce	nn	10	SENT_1	[p1l1669t127r1728b143],
10	t	NN	O	t	dobj	7	SENT_1	[p1l1746t122r1755b143],
11	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1764t119r1802b143],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_1	[p1l1810t119r1850b143],
13	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	prep_for	10	SENT_1	[p1l1860t119r1913b143],
14	week	NN	DATE	week	tmod	7	SENT_1	[p1l1921t119r1991b143],
15	in	IN	DATE	in	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l2001t119r2025b142],
16	January	NNP	DATE	January	prep_in	7	SENT_1	[p1l2034t120r2137b150],
17	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1002t152r1035b183],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_1	[p1l1044t152r1084b176],
19	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	21	SENT_1	[p1l1091t152r1222b176],
20	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	21	SENT_1	[p1l1232t152r1357b176],
21	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	prep_by	16	SENT_1	[p1l1369t152r1466b183],
22	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1476t156r1499b176],
23	1155	CD	DATE	1155	num	25	SENT_1	[p1l1511t153r1570b176],
24	16th	JJ	ORDINAL	16th	amod	25	SENT_1	[p1l1585t152r1640b176],
25	St.	NNP	O	St.	prep_at	16	SENT_1	[p1l1650t153r1691b181],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1650t153r1691b181],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1755t172r1760b181],
28	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	Washington	nn	30	SENT_1	[p1l1770t152r1935b183],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1770t152r1935b183],
30	DC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DC	appos	16	SENT_1	[p1l1945t153r1990b176],
31	20036	CD	NUMBER	20036	num	30	SENT_1	[p1l2000t153r2088b176],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l2000t153r2088b176],

1	Periodicals	NNS	O	periodical	nn	2	SENT_2	[p1l1047t185r1194b209],
2	postage	NN	O	postage	nsubj	3	SENT_2	[p1l1203t189r1304b216],
3	paid	VBN	O	pay	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1313t185r1370b216],
4	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1380t189r1403b209],
5	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	Washington	nn	7	SENT_2	[p1l1411t185r1575b216],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1411t185r1575b216],
7	DC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DC	prep_at	3	SENT_2	[p1l1586t186r1630b209],
8	an	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_2	[p1l1641t193r1671b209],
9	a	DT	O	a	dep	10	SENT_2	[p1l1697t193r1711b209],
10	itional	JJ	O	itional	amod	12	SENT_2	[p1l1745t185r1829b209],
11	mailing	NN	O	mailing	nn	12	SENT_2	[p1l1838t185r1939b216],
12	offices	NNS	O	office	dobj	3	SENT_2	[p1l1949t185r2044b209],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1949t185r2044b209],

1	I	PRP	O	I	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l373t242r375b271],
2	I	PRP	O	I	dep	1	SENT_3	[p1l756t242r758b271],

1	l	NN	O	l	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l240t251r242b271],
2	Slca	NNP	O	Slca	nn	3	SENT_4	[p1l317t243r368b271],
3	Chemlstiy	NNP	O	Chemlstiy	dep	1	SENT_4	[p1l388t242r525b277],
4	&	CC	O	&	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l533t245r551b272],
5	molecular	JJ	O	molecular	amod	6	SENT_4	[p1l563t242r699b271],
6	bio	NN	O	bio	conj_and	1	SENT_4	[p1l711t242r752b271],
7	09	CD	NUMBER	09	number	8	SENT_4	[p1l762t250r814b277],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	6	SENT_4	[p1l762t250r814b277],
9	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	10	SENT_4	[p1l762t250r814b277],
10	POSTMASTER	NN	O	postmaster	dep	8	SENT_4	[p1l1171t252r1394b276],
11	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1171t252r1394b276],
12	Send	VB	O	send	csubj	15	SENT_4	[p1l1407t252r1471b276],
13	address	NN	O	address	nn	14	SENT_4	[p1l1481t252r1579b276],
14	c	NN	O	c	dobj	12	SENT_4	[p1l1589t260r1602b276],
15	anges	VBZ	O	ange	dep	1	SENT_4	[p1l1620t260r1694b283],
16	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1704t255r1729b276],
17	Biochemistry	NNP	O	Biochemistry	prep_to	15	SENT_4	[p1l1737t252r1920b283],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1737t252r1920b283],
19	Subscription	NNP	O	Subscription	nn	20	SENT_4	[p1l1139t285r1305b316],
20	Services	NNPS	O	Services	appos	17	SENT_4	[p1l1316t285r1433b314],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1316t285r1433b314],
22	P.O.	NNP	O	P.O.	nn	23	SENT_4	[p1l1444t286r1496b309],
23	Box	NNP	O	Box	appos	17	SENT_4	[p1l1507t286r1562b309],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1639t305r1644b314],
25	Columbus	NNP	LOCATION	Columbus	appos	17	SENT_4	[p1l1655t285r1798b314],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1655t285r1798b314],
27	OH	NN	O	oh	appos	17	SENT_4	[p1l1809t286r1855b309],
28	43210	CD	NUMBER	43210	num	27	SENT_4	[p1l1864t286r1953b309],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1864t286r1953b309],

1	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	3	SENT_5	[p1l546t511r934b582],
2	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	3	SENT_5	[p1l955t511r1325b582],
3	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1345t511r1618b602],

1	1155	CD	DATE	1155	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l308t627r477b697],
2	16th	JJ	ORDINAL	16th	dep	1	SENT_6	[p1l510t624r663b697],
3	St.	NNP	O	St.	nn	9	SENT_6	[p1l684t627r792b712],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l684t627r792b712],
5	NW	NNP	O	NW	appos	9	SENT_6	[p1l811t627r991b712],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l811t627r991b712],
7	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	Washington	appos	9	SENT_6	[p1l1009t624r1466b718],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1009t624r1466b718],
9	DC	NNP	O	DC	dep	1	SENT_6	[p1l1487t627r1618b697],
10	20036	CD	NUMBER	20036	num	9	SENT_6	[p1l1638t627r1864b697],

1	(202) 872-4600	NN	O	(202) 872-4600	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l233t742r596b828],[p1l18t741r208b832],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l233t742r596b828],
3	TDD	NNP	O	TDD	dep	1	SENT_7	[p1l617t744r808b811],
4	(202) 872-6076	CD	NUMBER	(202) 872-6076	num	3	SENT_7	[p1l1046t742r1409b828],[p1l830t741r1021b832],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1046t742r1409b828],
6	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	3	SENT_7	[p1l1431t744r1571b812],
7	(202) 776-8264	CD	NUMBER	(202) 776-8264	num	6	SENT_7	[p1l1803t742r2148b813],[p1l1590t741r1781b832],

1	Customer	NN	ORGANIZATION	customer	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l446t972r832b1043],
2	Service	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Service	nn	5	SENT_8	[p1l853t972r1129b1043],
3	&	CC	O	&	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1150t972r1226b1043],
4	Information	NNP	O	Information	nn	5	SENT_8	[p1l1248t972r1719b1043],
5	http://pubshelp.acs.org	NNP	O	http://pubshelp.acs.org	dep	1	SENT_8	[p1l299t1085r1121b1177],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l299t1085r1121b1177],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1163t1085r1283b1158],
2	(202) 872-4376	CD	NUMBER	(202) 872-4376	dep	1	SENT_9	[p1l1519t1088r1862b1158],[p1l1304t1086r1495b1177],

1	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	nn	2	SENT_10	[p1l493t1199r739b1272],
2	suppoIt@services.acs.org	NN	O	suppoit@services.acs.org	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l760t1199r1672b1293],

1	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	3	SENT_11	[p1l575t1546r937b1618],
2	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	3	SENT_11	[p1l955t1546r1301b1619],
3	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1324t1546r1590b1638],
4	2540	CD	DATE	2540	dep	3	SENT_11	[p1l610t1664r791b1733],
5	Olentangy	NNP	MISC	Olentangy	nn	7	SENT_11	[p1l812t1661r1189b1753],
6	River	NNP	O	River	nn	7	SENT_11	[p1l1206t1661r1410b1734],
7	Rd.	NNP	O	Rd.	dep	4	SENT_11	[p1l1425t1661r1550b1734],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1425t1661r1550b1734],

1	P.O.	NN	O	p.o.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l395t1778r551b1848],
2	Box	NNP	O	Box	dep	1	SENT_12	[p1l575t1779r731b1848],
3	3330	CD	NUMBER	3330	num	2	SENT_12	[p1l750t1778r949b1863],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l750t1778r949b1863],
5	Columbus	NNP	LOCATION	Columbus	appos	2	SENT_12	[p1l971t1775r1363b1863],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l971t1775r1363b1863],
7	OH	NN	O	oh	appos	2	SENT_12	[p1l1386t1778r1522b1848],
8	43210	CD	NUMBER	43210	num	9	SENT_12	[p1l1540t1778r1767b1848],
9	(614) 447-3665	CD	NUMBER	(614) 447-3665	dep	7	SENT_12	[p1l635t1893r1002b1979],[p1l424t1892r614b1983],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l635t1893r1002b1979],
11	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	12	SENT_12	[p1l1024t1895r1164b1963],
12	(614) 447-3745	CD	NUMBER	(614) 447-3745	dep	7	SENT_12	[p1l1394t1893r1737b1964],[p1l1183t1892r1374b1983],

1	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	nn	2	SENT_13	[p1l625t2006r872b2077],
2	acsproof@acs.org	NN	O	acsproof@acs.org	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l891t2006r1540b2098],

1	ACS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ACS	nn	4	SENT_14	[p1l379t2238r567b2308],
2	Publications	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Publications	nn	4	SENT_14	[p1l588t2238r1059b2308],
3	Advertising	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Advertising	nn	4	SENT_14	[p1l1078t2238r1531b2329],
4	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Office	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1551t2238r1784b2308],

1	1155	CD	DATE	1155	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l308t2353r477b2423],
2	16th	JJ	ORDINAL	16th	dep	1	SENT_15	[p1l510t2352r663b2423],
3	St.	NNP	O	St.	nn	9	SENT_15	[p1l684t2353r792b2438],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l684t2353r792b2438],
5	NW	NNP	O	NW	appos	9	SENT_15	[p1l811t2355r991b2438],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l811t2355r991b2438],
7	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	Washington	appos	9	SENT_15	[p1l1009t2352r1466b2444],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1009t2352r1466b2444],
9	DC	NNP	O	DC	dep	1	SENT_15	[p1l1487t2353r1618b2423],
10	20036	CD	NUMBER	20036	num	9	SENT_15	[p1l1638t2353r1864b2423],

1	(610) 964-8061	NN	O	(610) 964-8061	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l579t2468r944b2553],[p1l366t2467r557b2559],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l579t2468r944b2553],
3	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	nn	4	SENT_16	[p1l966t2467r1212b2538],
4	carroll@acs.org	NN	O	carroll@acs.org	dep	1	SENT_16	[p1l1232t2467r1802b2559],

1	Subscription	NNP	O	Subscription	nn	2	SENT_17	[p1l673t2698r1161b2789],
2	Services	NNPS	O	Services	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1183t2698r1492b2769],

1	P.O.	NN	O	p.o.	dep	9	SENT_18	[p1l395t2815r551b2885],
2	Box	NNP	O	Box	dep	1	SENT_18	[p1l575t2816r731b2885],
3	3337	CD	NUMBER	3337	dep	2	SENT_18	[p1l750t2815r949b2900],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l750t2815r949b2900],
5	Columbus	NNP	LOCATION	Columbus	appos	3	SENT_18	[p1l971t2812r1363b2900],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l971t2812r1363b2900],
7	OH	NN	O	oh	dep	9	SENT_18	[p1l1386t2815r1522b2885],
8	43210	CD	NUMBER	43210	num	7	SENT_18	[p1l1540t2815r1767b2885],
9	Members	NNS	O	member	dep	13	SENT_18	[p1l405t2942r752b3014],
10	contact	NN	O	contact	dep	9	SENT_18	[p1l771t2954r1058b3014],
11	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l771t2954r1058b3014],
12	Member	NNP	O	Member	nn	13	SENT_18	[p1l1080t2945r1422b3014],
13	Services	NNPS	O	Services	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1443t2943r1753b3014],

1	(614) 447-3776	NN	O	(614) 447-3776	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l333t3058r701b3143],[p1l122t3057r313b3149],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l333t3058r701b3143],
3	(800) 333-951	CD	NUMBER	(800) 333-951	num	4	SENT_19	[p1l939t3058r1229b3129],[p1l725t3057r917b3149],
4	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l1248t3058r1304b3143],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1248t3058r1304b3143],
6	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	4	SENT_19	[p1l1326t3060r1465b3128],
7	(614) 447-3671	CD	NUMBER	(614) 447-3671	num	6	SENT_19	[p1l1696t3058r2034b3129],[p1l1484t3057r1675b3149],

1	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	nn	2	SENT_20	[p1l653t3173r900b3244],
2	service@acs.org	NN	O	service@acs.org	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l921t3173r1512b3265],

1	Agencies	NNPS	O	Agencies	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l6t3301r338b3392],
2	&	CC	O	&	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l360t3301r430b3372],
3	Institutions	NNPS	O	Institutions	conj_and	1	SENT_21	[p1l446t3303r846b3372],
4	contact	NN	O	contact	dep	1	SENT_21	[p1l865t3313r1152b3372],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l865t3313r1152b3372],
6	Sales	NNS	O	sale	dep	4	SENT_21	[p1l1178t3301r1368b3373],
7	Analysis	NNP	O	Analysis	dep	6	SENT_21	[p1l1387t3301r1713b3392],
8	&	CC	O	&	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1734t3301r1811b3372],
9	Support	NN	O	support	dep	6	SENT_21	[p1l1835t3301r2153b3392],

1	(614) 447-3674	NN	O	(614) 447-3674	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l334t3419r701b3505],[p1l122t3418r313b3509],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l334t3419r701b3505],
3	(888) 338-0012	CD	NUMBER	(888) 338-0012	dep	1	SENT_22	[p1l939t3419r1304b3505],[p1l726t3418r917b3509],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l939t3419r1304b3505],
5	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	3	SENT_22	[p1l1325t3421r1465b3489],
6	(614) 447-5475	CD	NUMBER	(614) 447-5475	num	5	SENT_22	[p1l1696t3419r2040b3490],[p1l1485t3418r1675b3509],

1	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	nn	2	SENT_23	[p1l448t3534r693b3605],
2	ACS_Pubs_Assist@acs.org	NN	O	acs_pubs_assist@acs.org	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l711t3534r1717b3626],

1	Publications	NNP	O	Publications	nn	2	SENT_24	[p1l734t3654r1138b3715],
2	Division	NNP	O	Division	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1154t3654r1424b3715],

1	Brian	NNP	PERSON	Brian	nn	3	SENT_25	[p2l631t30r805b91],
2	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	3	SENT_25	[p2l819t32r892b92],
3	Crawford	NNP	PERSON	Crawford	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l913t30r1224b105],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l913t30r1224b105],
5	President	NNP	O	President	appos	3	SENT_25	[p2l1242t30r1528b92],

1	Journals	NNPS	O	Journals	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l630t271r918b330],
2	Publishing	NNP	O	Publishing	nn	3	SENT_26	[p2l935t270r1287b348],
3	Group	NNP	O	Group	dep	1	SENT_26	[p2l1305t270r1525b348],

1	Susan	NNP	PERSON	Susan	nn	2	SENT_27	[p2l555t377r739b438],
2	King	NNP	PERSON	King	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l753t376r924b455],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l753t376r924b455],
4	Senior	NNP	O	Senior	nn	6	SENT_27	[p2l947t376r1147b438],
5	Vice	NNP	O	Vice	nn	6	SENT_27	[p2l1159t376r1306b438],
6	President	NNP	O	President	appos	2	SENT_27	[p2l1323t376r1608b438],

1	Anirban	NNP	PERSON	Anirban	nn	2	SENT_28	[p2l124t485r380b547],
2	Mahapatra	NNP	PERSON	Mahapatra	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l394t485r741b564],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l394t485r741b564],
4	Assistant	NNP	O	Assistant	nn	5	SENT_28	[p2l753t485r1036b547],
5	Director	NNP	O	Director	appos	2	SENT_28	[p2l1049t485r1315b560],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1049t485r1315b560],
7	Editorial	NNP	O	Editorial	nn	8	SENT_28	[p2l1334t485r1599b547],
8	Development	NNP	O	Development	appos	2	SENT_28	[p2l1614t485r2035b564],

1	J	NNP	O	J	nn	3	SENT_29	[p2l604t598r636b657],
2	itesh	NNP	O	itesh	nn	3	SENT_29	[p2l634t595r777b657],
3	Soares	NNP	PERSON	Soares	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l795t597r1012b670],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l795t597r1012b670],
5	Managing	VBG	O	manage	partmod	3	SENT_29	[p2l1030t596r1348b675],
6	Editor	NNP	O	Editor	dobj	5	SENT_29	[p2l1363t595r1557b657],

1	Robert	NNP	PERSON	Robert	nn	3	SENT_30	[p2l156t940r369b1002],
2	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	nn	3	SENT_30	[p2l387t942r441b1002],
3	O’Dell	NNP	PERSON	O’Dell	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l463t940r691b1015],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l463t940r691b1015],
5	Vice	NNP	O	Vice	nn	6	SENT_30	[p2l709t940r857b1002],
6	President	NNP	O	President	appos	3	SENT_30	[p2l872t940r1172b1015],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l872t940r1172b1015],
8	Manufacturing	NNP	O	Manufacturing	nn	9	SENT_30	[p2l1189t940r1648b1019],
9	Operations	NNP	O	Operations	appos	3	SENT_30	[p2l1666t940r2000b1019],

1	Diane	NNP	PERSON	Diane	nn	5	SENT_31	[p2l365t1048r551b1109],
2	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	nn	5	SENT_31	[p2l567t1051r630b1109],
3	Needharn	NNP	PERSON	Needharn	nn	5	SENT_31	[p2l647t1047r967b1122],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l647t1047r967b1122],
5	Manager	NNP	O	Manager	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l985t1051r1278b1127],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l985t1051r1278b1127],
7	Journals	NNPS	O	Journals	nn	8	SENT_31	[p2l1297t1047r1550b1109],
8	Editing	NNP	O	Editing	appos	5	SENT_31	[p2l1567t1047r1793b1127],

1	Sean	NNP	PERSON	Sean	nn	3	SENT_32	[p2l421t1156r571b1216],
2	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	3	SENT_32	[p2l585t1157r673b1216],
3	Larnrners	NNP	PERSON	Larnrners	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l692t1157r1005b1229],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l692t1157r1005b1229],
5	Senior	NNP	O	Senior	nn	7	SENT_32	[p2l1026t1155r1226b1217],
6	Associate	NNP	O	Associate	nn	7	SENT_32	[p2l1234t1155r1533b1216],
7	Editor	NNP	O	Editor	appos	3	SENT_32	[p2l1549t1155r1743b1216],

1	Sales	NNS	O	sale	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l770t1394r933b1455],
2	&	CC	O	&	rcmod	1	SENT_33	[p2l952t1394r1017b1455],
3	Marketing	NNP	O	Marketing	dep	1	SENT_33	[p2l1034t1394r1391b1472],

1	Brandon	NNP	PERSON	Brandon	nn	3	SENT_34	[p2l6t1501r276b1563],
2	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	3	SENT_34	[p2l289t1503r363b1563],
3	Nordin	NNP	PERSON	Nordin	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l380t1501r618b1576],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l380t1501r618b1576],
5	Vice	NNP	O	Vice	nn	13	SENT_34	[p2l635t1502r783b1563],
6	President	NNP	O	President	nn	13	SENT_34	[p2l799t1501r1098b1576],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l799t1501r1098b1576],
8	Sales	NNS	O	sale	nn	13	SENT_34	[p2l1120t1501r1293b1576],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1120t1501r1293b1576],
10	Marketing	NNP	O	Marketing	conj_and	6	SENT_34	[p2l1311t1501r1634b1581],
11	&	CC	O	&	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1651t1503r1713b1563],
12	Web	NN	O	web	nn	13	SENT_34	[p2l1729t1501r1880b1563],
13	Strategy	NN	O	strategy	appos	3	SENT_34	[p2l1901t1503r2153b1581],

1	Sean	NNP	PERSON	Sean	nn	2	SENT_35	[p2l513t1609r663b1670],
2	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l678t1610r750b1670],
3	Abell	NNP	PERSON	Abell	nn	5	SENT_35	[p2l769t1608r957b1683],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l769t1608r957b1683],
5	Director	NNP	O	Director	dep	2	SENT_35	[p2l975t1608r1232b1670],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1246t1608r1321b1670],
7	Marketing	NNP	O	Marketing	prep_of	5	SENT_35	[p2l1325t1608r1648b1687],

1	Jonathan	NNP	PERSON	Jonathan	nn	2	SENT_36	[p2l8t1716r284b1778],
2	Morgan	NNP	PERSON	Morgan	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l298t1718r562b1795],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l298t1718r562b1795],
4	Director	NNP	O	Director	nn	7	SENT_36	[p2l580t1716r850b1791],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l580t1716r850b1791],
6	Digital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Digital	appos	7	SENT_36	[p2l868t1716r1079b1795],
7	Strategy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Strategy	appos	2	SENT_36	[p2l1099t1717r1351b1795],
8	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	&	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1367t1717r1428b1778],
9	Platform	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Platform	nn	10	SENT_36	[p2l1445t1716r1716b1778],
10	Development	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Development	appos	2	SENT_36	[p2l1730t1716r2151b1795],

1	Tara	NNP	PERSON	Tara	nn	2	SENT_37	[p2l411t1827r549b1886],
2	Pritchett	NNP	PERSON	Pritchett	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l562t1824r832b1899],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l562t1824r832b1899],
4	Assistant	NNP	O	Assistant	nn	7	SENT_37	[p2l845t1824r1127b1886],
5	Director	NNP	O	Director	nn	7	SENT_37	[p2l1141t1824r1407b1899],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1141t1824r1407b1899],
7	Marketing	NNP	O	Marketing	appos	2	SENT_37	[p2l1425t1824r1748b1903],

1	Editorial	NN	O	editorial	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l630t2064r925b2125],
2	Oﬁice	NNP	O	Oﬁice	nn	3	SENT_38	[p2l942t2064r1141b2125],
3	Operations	NNP	O	Operations	dep	1	SENT_38	[p2l1158t2064r1526b2142],

1	Sarah	NNP	PERSON	Sarah	nn	3	SENT_39	[p2l276t2171r450b2233],
2	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	3	SENT_39	[p2l464t2173r532b2233],
3	Tegen	NNP	PERSON	Tegen	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l552t2173r755b2250],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l552t2173r755b2250],
5	Director	NNP	O	Director	nn	9	SENT_39	[p2l773t2171r1039b2246],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l773t2171r1039b2246],
7	Editorial	NNP	O	Editorial	appos	9	SENT_39	[p2l1058t2171r1322b2233],
8	Office	NNP	O	Office	nn	9	SENT_39	[p2l1340t2171r1532b2233],
9	Operations	NNP	O	Operations	appos	3	SENT_39	[p2l1550t2171r1885b2250],

1	Charley	NNP	PERSON	Charley	nn	2	SENT_40	[p2l89t2279r334b2359],
2	Trowbridge	NNP	PERSON	Trowbridge	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l349t2279r729b2359],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l349t2279r729b2359],
4	Assistant	NNP	O	Assistant	nn	9	SENT_40	[p2l741t2280r1023b2341],
5	Director	NNP	O	Director	nn	9	SENT_40	[p2l1037t2280r1306b2354],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1037t2280r1306b2354],
7	Peer	NNP	O	Peer	appos	9	SENT_40	[p2l1324t2283r1464b2341],
8	Review	NNP	O	Review	nn	9	SENT_40	[p2l1478t2280r1719b2341],
9	Operations	NNP	O	Operations	appos	2	SENT_40	[p2l1735t2280r2069b2359],

1	Samantha	NNP	PERSON	Samantha	nn	2	SENT_41	[p2l499t2388r805b2450],
2	Luck	NNP	PERSON	Luck	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l819t2388r996b2462],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l819t2388r996b2462],
4	Peer	NNP	O	Peer	nn	6	SENT_41	[p2l1013t2390r1154b2449],
5	Review	NNP	O	Review	nn	6	SENT_41	[p2l1167t2388r1407b2449],
6	Analyst	NNP	O	Analyst	appos	2	SENT_41	[p2l1421t2388r1664b2467],

1	Copyright	NN	O	copyright	nn	2	SENT_42	[p2l66t2567r189b2595],
2	Permission	NN	O	permission	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l196t2567r336b2589],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l196t2567r336b2589],
4	See	VB	O	see	dep	2	SENT_42	[p2l346t2567r386b2589],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_42	[p2l393t2566r428b2589],
6	ACS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ACS	nn	9	SENT_42	[p2l436t2567r491b2589],
7	Journal	NNP	O	Journal	nn	9	SENT_42	[p2l499t2566r585b2589],
8	Publishing	NNP	O	Publishing	nn	9	SENT_42	[p2l592t2566r716b2595],
9	Agreement	NNP	O	Agreement	dobj	4	SENT_42	[p2l724t2567r854b2595],
10	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l861t2566r894b2589],
11	certain	JJ	O	certain	amod	14	SENT_42	[p2l901t2566r976b2589],
12	rights	NNS	O	rights	nn	14	SENT_42	[p2l982t2566r1045b2595],
13	(	NN	O	(	nn	14	SENT_42	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
14	hup	NN	O	hup	prep_for	9	SENT_42	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
15	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
16	/	:	O	/	punct	4	SENT_42	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
17	/	:	O	/	punct	18	SENT_42	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
18	pubs	NNS	O	pub	dep	2	SENT_42	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],

1	acsorg/page/copyright	NN	O	acsorg/page/copyright	nn	2	SENT_43	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
2	ﬁournals	NNS	O	ﬁournals	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
3	/	:	O	/	punct	2	SENT_43	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
4	index	NN	O	index	dep	2	SENT_43	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],

1	html	NN	O	html	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
2	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_44	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1053t2566r1688b2595],

1	Reprographic	JJ	MISC	reprographic	amod	2	SENT_45	[p2l1705t2566r1856b2595],
2	copying	NN	O	copying	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1864t2566r1954b2595],
3	beyond	IN	O	beyond	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1961t2566r2045b2595],
4	that	DT	O	that	prep_beyond	2	SENT_45	[p2l2052t2566r2094b2589],
5	permitted	VBN	O	permit	partmod	4	SENT_45	[p2l66t2599r174b2628],
6	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l182t2599r211b2628],
7	Section	NN	O	section	agent	5	SENT_45	[p2l221t2599r304b2622],
8	107	CD	NUMBER	107	dep	2	SENT_45	[p2l316t2599r355b2622],
9	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l365t2606r389b2622],
10	108	CD	NUMBER	108	dep	2	SENT_45	[p2l401t2599r439b2622],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l450t2599r477b2622],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_45	[p2l482t2599r516b2622],
13	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	U.S.	nn	14	SENT_45	[p2l525t2599r574b2622],
14	Copyright	NN	MISC	copyright	prep_of	8	SENT_45	[p2l585t2599r698b2628],
15	Act	NNP	MISC	Act	nsubjpass	17	SENT_45	[p2l707t2599r749b2622],
16	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	17	SENT_45	[p2l758t2599r775b2622],
17	allowed	VBN	O	allow	rcmod	14	SENT_45	[p2l785t2599r879b2626],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l785t2599r879b2626],
19	provided	VBN	O	provide	partmod	8	SENT_45	[p2l888t2599r989b2628],
20	that	IN	O	that	complm	27	SENT_45	[p2l997t2599r1039b2622],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_45	[p2l1047t2599r1082b2622],
22	current	JJ	DATE	current	nsubjpass	27	SENT_45	[p2l1091t2602r1170b2622],
23	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1178t2606r1215b2628],
24	article	NN	O	article	nn	25	SENT_45	[p2l1224t2599r1291b2622],
25	fee	NN	O	fee	prep_per	22	SENT_45	[p2l1301t2599r1334b2622],
26	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	27	SENT_45	[p2l1344t2599r1362b2622],
27	paid	VBN	O	pay	ccomp	19	SENT_45	[p2l1370t2599r1420b2628],
28	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1428t2602r1450b2622],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_45	[p2l1459t2599r1493b2622],
30	Copyright	NN	O	copyright	nn	32	SENT_45	[p2l1503t2599r1617b2628],
31	Clearance	NNP	O	Clearance	nn	32	SENT_45	[p2l1626t2599r1736b2622],
32	Center	NNP	O	Center	prep_to	27	SENT_45	[p2l1746t2599r1825b2622],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1746t2599r1825b2622],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1836t2599r1879b2622],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1836t2599r1879b2622],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_46	[p2l1890t2599r1917b2621],
4	978-750-8400	CD	NUMBER	978-750-8400	dep	1	SENT_46	[p2l1930t2599r2093b2622],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1930t2599r2093b2622],

1	Republication	NN	O	republication	nsubjpass	15	SENT_47	[p2l66t2632r222b2661],
2	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l228t2639r252b2655],
3	reproduction	NN	O	reproduction	nsubjpass	15	SENT_47	[p2l256t2632r399b2661],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l404t2632r431b2655],
5	material	NN	O	material	prep_of	1	SENT_47	[p2l432t2632r523b2655],
6	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l529t2632r562b2655],
7	which	WDT	O	which	rel	9	SENT_47	[p2l566t2632r636b2655],
8	ACS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ACS	nsubj	9	SENT_47	[p2l641t2633r697b2655],
9	owns	VBZ	O	own	rcmod	5	SENT_47	[p2l704t2639r764b2655],
10	copyright	NN	O	copyright	dobj	9	SENT_47	[p2l770t2632r877b2661],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l882t2632r904b2654],
12	this	DT	O	this	det	13	SENT_47	[p2l909t2632r948b2655],
13	journal	NN	O	journal	prep_in	10	SENT_47	[p2l951t2632r1033b2661],
14	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	15	SENT_47	[p2l1039t2632r1056b2655],
15	permitted	VBN	O	permit	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1061t2632r1171b2661],
16	only	RB	O	only	advmod	15	SENT_47	[p2l1176t2632r1226b2661],
17	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1231t2632r1318b2661],
18	Rightslink	NNP	PERSON	Rightslink	prep_through	15	SENT_47	[p2l1324t2632r1440b2661],
19	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1445t2635r1465b2654],
20	http://pubs.acs.orypage/4authors/copyright/index.html	NN	O	http://pubs.acs.orypage/4authors/copyright/index.html	prep_at	15	SENT_47	[p2l1470t2632r2093b2661],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1470t2632r2093b2661],

1	Instructions	NNS	O	instruction	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l8t2812r328b2859],
2	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l342t2812r419b2859],
3	Authors	NNS	O	author	prep_for	1	SENT_48	[p2l429t2812r645b2859],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l659t2813r758b2859],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_48	[p2l771t2813r852b2859],
6	ACS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ACS	nn	9	SENT_48	[p2l864t2812r987b2859],
7	Journal	NNP	O	Journal	nn	9	SENT_48	[p2l1001t2813r1208b2859],
8	Publishing	NNP	O	Publishing	nn	9	SENT_48	[p2l1221t2812r1504b2872],
9	Agreement	NNP	O	Agreement	prep_for	1	SENT_48	[p2l1516t2812r1826b2872],
10	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1516t2812r1826b2872],
11	Visit	VB	O	visit	dep	1	SENT_48	[p2l7t2893r125b2942],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_48	[p2l136t2893r211b2942],
13	ACS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ACS	nn	15	SENT_48	[p2l223t2895r342b2942],
14	Web	NN	O	web	nn	15	SENT_48	[p2l356t2893r470b2942],
15	site	NN	O	site	dobj	11	SENT_48	[p2l486t2893r566b2942],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_48	[p2l580t2893r1398b2955],
17	http://paragonplus.acs.org/login	NN	O	http://paragonplus.acs.org/login	nn	18	SENT_48	[p2l580t2893r1398b2955],
18	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	11	SENT_48	[p2l580t2893r1398b2955],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l580t2893r1398b2955],

1	Please	VB	O	please	dep	2	SENT_49	[p2l1427t2893r1581b2942],
2	conform	VB	O	conform	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1595t2893r1807b2942],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1818t2900r1866b2942],
4	these	DT	O	these	det	5	SENT_49	[p2l1879t2893r2006b2942],
5	instructions	NNS	O	instruction	prep_to	2	SENT_49	[p2l9t2976r297b3024],
6	when	WRB	O	when	advmod	7	SENT_49	[p2l309t2976r447b3024],
7	submitting	VBG	O	submit	advcl	2	SENT_49	[p2l460t2976r724b3038],
8	manuscripts	NNS	O	manuscript	dobj	7	SENT_49	[p2l736t2976r1048b3038],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l736t2976r1048b3038],

1	Manuscript	NN	O	manuscript	nn	2	SENT_50	[p2l8t3061r319b3122],
2	Submission	NN	O	submission	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l333t3061r648b3109],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l333t3061r648b3109],
4	Submit	VB	O	submit	dep	2	SENT_50	[p2l11t3143r188b3191],
5	via	IN	O	via	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l198t3143r276b3191],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_50	[p2l286t3143r362b3191],
7	J	NN	O	j	prep_via	4	SENT_50	[p2l375t3145r400b3191],
8	oumal	JJ	O	oumal	amod	13	SENT_50	[p2l398t3143r558b3191],
9	Web	NN	O	web	nn	13	SENT_50	[p2l569t3143r684b3191],
10	site	NN	O	site	nn	13	SENT_50	[p2l700t3143r780b3191],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	13	SENT_50	[p2l794t3143r1659b3205],
12	http://pubs.acsorgﬁoumal/bichaw	NN	O	http://pubs.acsorgﬁoumal/bichaw	nn	13	SENT_50	[p2l794t3143r1659b3205],
13	)	NN	O	)	dep	7	SENT_50	[p2l794t3143r1659b3205],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l794t3143r1659b3205],

1	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	amod	2	SENT_51	[p2l7t3228r247b3288],
2	Papers	NNP	O	Papers	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l260t3228r438b3288],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l453t3228r550b3274],
4	Proofs	NNP	O	Proofs	conj_and	2	SENT_51	[p2l563t3227r745b3274],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l563t3227r745b3274],
6	Direct	NNP	O	Direct	nn	7	SENT_51	[p2l8t3309r158b3357],
7	correspondence	NN	O	correspondence	dep	2	SENT_51	[p2l170t3309r545b3370],
8	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l557t3315r603b3357],
9	J	NNP	O	J	nn	11	SENT_51	[p2l617t3311r642b3357],
10	ournal	JJ	O	ournal	amod	11	SENT_51	[p2l640t3309r792b3357],
11	Production	NNP	O	Production	prep_to	7	SENT_51	[p2l804t3309r1068b3357],
12	&	CC	O	&	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1080t3310r1128b3357],
13	Manufacturing	NNP	O	Manufacturing	prep_to	7	SENT_51	[p2l1141t3309r1499b3370],
14	Operations	NNP	O	Operations	nn	15	SENT_51	[p2l1512t3309r1772b3370],
15	(	NN	O	(	nsubj	16	SENT_51	[p2l1787t3309r1880b3370],
16	see	VB	O	see	rcmod	11	SENT_51	[p2l1787t3309r1880b3370],
17	above	IN	O	above	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1894t3309r2064b3370],
18	)	NN	O	)	prep_above	16	SENT_51	[p2l1894t3309r2064b3370],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1894t3309r2064b3370],

1	Journal	NNP	O	Journal	nn	2	SENT_52	[p2l7t3395r210b3440],
2	Policies	NNS	O	policy	dep	11	SENT_52	[p2l222t3394r428b3440],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l222t3394r428b3440],
4	The	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_52	[p2l9t3474r103b3523],
5	American	JJ	ORGANIZATION	american	amod	7	SENT_52	[p2l115t3474r356b3523],
6	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	7	SENT_52	[p2l368t3474r599b3523],
7	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	nsubj	11	SENT_52	[p2l614t3474r792b3536],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l804t3474r893b3523],
9	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	10	SENT_52	[p2l904t3474r957b3523],
10	Editors	NNP	O	Editors	nsubj	11	SENT_52	[p2l971t3474r1142b3523],
11	assume	VB	O	assume	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1156t3490r1333b3523],
12	no	DT	O	no	det	13	SENT_52	[p2l1345t3490r1407b3523],
13	responsibility	NN	O	responsibility	dobj	11	SENT_52	[p2l1419t3474r1741b3536],
14	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1753t3474r1823b3523],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_52	[p2l1833t3474r1907b3523],
16	statements	NNS	O	statement	prep_for	13	SENT_52	[p2l10t3564r258b3605],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l273t3557r361b3605],
18	opinions	NNS	O	opinion	conj_and	16	SENT_52	[p2l373t3557r577b3619],
19	advanced	VBN	O	advance	partmod	16	SENT_52	[p2l591t3557r820b3605],
20	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l830t3557r893b3619],
21	contributors	NNS	O	contributor	agent	19	SENT_52	[p2l905t3557r1200b3605],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l905t3557r1200b3605],

1	Registered	NNP	O	Registered	nsubj	20	SENT_53	[p2l1229t3557r1486b3619],
2	names	NNS	O	name	nn	1	SENT_53	[p2l1496t3573r1652b3605],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1666t3557r1755b3605],
4	trademarks	NNS	O	trademark	nn	1	SENT_53	[p2l1765t3557r2043b3615],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1765t3557r2043b3615],
6	etc.	FW	O	etc.	dep	1	SENT_53	[p2l2059t3564r2152b3615],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l2059t3564r2152b3615],
8	used	VBN	O	use	partmod	1	SENT_53	[p2l7t3640r120b3688],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l132t3640r179b3687],
10	this	DT	O	this	det	11	SENT_53	[p2l189t3640r274b3688],
11	publication	NN	O	publication	prep_in	8	SENT_53	[p2l286t3640r565b3702],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l286t3640r565b3702],
13	even	RB	O	even	advmod	8	SENT_53	[p2l581t3655r696b3688],
14	without	IN	O	without	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l706t3640r891b3688],
15	speciﬁc	NN	O	speciﬁc	nn	16	SENT_53	[p2l904t3640r1084b3702],
16	indication	NN	O	indication	prep_without	13	SENT_53	[p2l1098t3640r1335b3688],
17	thereof	RB	O	thereof	advmod	13	SENT_53	[p2l1346t3640r1526b3698],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1346t3640r1526b3698],
19	are	VBP	O	be	aux	20	SENT_53	[p2l1541t3655r1613b3688],
20	not	RB	O	not	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1625t3647r1704b3688],
21	to	TO	O	to	aux	23	SENT_53	[p2l1714t3647r1761b3688],
22	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	23	SENT_53	[p2l1773t3640r1831b3688],
23	considered	VBN	O	consider	xcomp	20	SENT_53	[p2l1845t3640r2104b3688],
24	unprotected	JJ	O	unprotected	acomp	23	SENT_53	[p2l7t3722r291b3784],
25	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l300t3722r364b3784],
26	law	NN	O	law	agent	23	SENT_53	[p2l376t3722r474b3771],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l376t3722r474b3771],

1	Change	NNP	O	Change	nsubj	12	SENT_54	[p3l9t19r209b79],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l223t19r278b66],
3	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	prep_of	1	SENT_54	[p3l284t19r460b65],
4	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l473t33r530b66],
5	Mailing	NNP	O	Mailing	nn	6	SENT_54	[p3l542t19r744b79],
6	Address	NNP	O	Address	prep_of	1	SENT_54	[p3l755t19r983b66],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l755t19r983b66],
8	For	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l8t102r94b149],
9	members	NNS	O	member	prep_for	12	SENT_54	[p3l104t100r328b149],
10	only	RB	O	only	advmod	12	SENT_54	[p3l342t100r460b162],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l342t100r460b162],
12	notify	VBP	O	notify	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l474t100r616b162],
13	Subscription	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Subscription	nn	15	SENT_54	[p3l631t100r930b162],
14	Services	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Services	nn	15	SENT_54	[p3l944t100r1142b149],
15	(	NN	O	(	nsubj	16	SENT_54	[p3l1156t100r1250b162],
16	see	VB	O	see	ccomp	12	SENT_54	[p3l1156t100r1250b162],
17	above	IN	O	above	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1263t100r1434b162],
18	)	NN	O	)	prep_above	16	SENT_54	[p3l1263t100r1434b162],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1263t100r1434b162],

1	Include	VB	O	include	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1463t100r1641b149],
2	both	DT	O	both	preconj	3	SENT_55	[p3l1653t100r1763b149],
3	old	JJ	O	old	amod	6	SENT_55	[p3l1775t100r1852b149],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1864t100r1953b149],
5	new	JJ	O	new	amod	6	SENT_55	[p3l1963t116r2068b149],
6	addresses	NNS	O	address	dobj	1	SENT_55	[p3l9t183r246b230],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l9t183r246b230],

1	New	NNP	O	New	nn	4	SENT_56	[p3l8t305r126b351],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l140t305r237b351],
3	Renewal	NNP	MISC	Renewal	conj_and	1	SENT_56	[p3l250t305r474b351],
4	Subscriptions	NNPS	MISC	Subscriptions	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l489t304r850b365],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l489t304r850b365],
6	Members	NNS	O	member	nsubj	7	SENT_56	[p3l8t386r238b434],
7	send	VBP	O	send	dep	4	SENT_56	[p3l254t386r364b434],
8	payment	NN	O	payment	dobj	7	SENT_56	[p3l373t393r585b447],
9	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l596t392r642b434],
10	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	12	SENT_56	[p3l654t386r896b434],
11	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	12	SENT_56	[p3l908t386r1139b434],
12	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	prep_to	7	SENT_56	[p3l1154t386r1342b447],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1154t386r1342b447],
14	P.O.	NNP	O	P.O.	nn	15	SENT_56	[p3l1356t387r1460b434],
15	Box	NNP	O	Box	appos	12	SENT_56	[p3l1475t388r1579b434],
16	182426	CD	NUMBER	182426	num	15	SENT_56	[p3l1598t387r1785b444],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1598t387r1785b444],
18	Columbus	NNP	LOCATION	Columbus	appos	12	SENT_56	[p3l1801t386r2062b444],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1801t386r2062b444],
20	OH	NN	LOCATION	oh	appos	12	SENT_56	[p3l9t470r99b517],
21	43218-2426	CD	NUMBER	43218-2426	num	20	SENT_56	[p3l111t470r414b517],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l111t470r414b517],

1	Institutions	NNS	O	institution	nsubj	2	SENT_57	[p3l443t468r706b517],
2	send	VBP	O	send	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l721t468r831b517],
3	payment	NN	O	payment	dobj	2	SENT_57	[p3l841t475r1053b530],
4	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1063t475r1109b517],
5	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	7	SENT_57	[p3l1122t468r1363b517],
6	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	7	SENT_57	[p3l1375t468r1606b517],
7	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	prep_to	2	SENT_57	[p3l1621t468r1809b530],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1621t468r1809b530],
9	P.O.	NNP	O	P.O.	nn	10	SENT_57	[p3l1823t470r1927b517],
10	Box	NNP	O	Box	appos	7	SENT_57	[p3l1943t471r2047b517],
11	182977	CD	NUMBER	182977	num	10	SENT_57	[p3l15t552r202b608],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l15t552r202b608],
13	Columbus	NNP	LOCATION	Columbus	appos	7	SENT_57	[p3l218t551r478b608],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l218t551r478b608],
15	OH	NN	LOCATION	oh	appos	7	SENT_57	[p3l494t552r584b599],
16	43218-2977	CD	NUMBER	43218-2977	num	15	SENT_57	[p3l596t552r899b598],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l596t552r899b598],

1	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	2	SENT_58	[p3l9t672r127b720],
2	Subscription	NN	O	subscription	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l144t672r468b733],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l483t673r581b720],
4	Ordering	NNP	O	Ordering	nn	5	SENT_58	[p3l595t672r836b733],
5	Information	NNP	O	Information	conj_and	2	SENT_58	[p3l849t672r1179b720],
6	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l849t672r1179b720],
7	ACS	NN	ORGANIZATION	ac	nn	8	SENT_58	[p3l7t755r127b802],
8	members	NNS	O	member	dep	2	SENT_58	[p3l141t754r365b802],
9	may	MD	O	may	aux	10	SENT_58	[p3l378t769r486b816],
10	purchase	VB	O	purchase	rcmod	8	SENT_58	[p3l496t754r710b816],
11	a	DT	O	a	det	13	SENT_58	[p3l724t769r752b802],
12	Web	NN	O	web	nn	13	SENT_58	[p3l762t754r880b802],
13	subscription	NN	O	subscription	dobj	10	SENT_58	[p3l895t754r1184b816],
14	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1196t754r1266b802],
15	$	$	MONEY	$	prep_for	10	SENT_58	[p3l1279t752r1379b806],
16	90	CD	MONEY	90	num	15	SENT_58	[p3l1279t752r1379b806],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1279t752r1379b806],

1	Contact	NN	O	contact	nn	3	SENT_59	[p3l1410t755r1597b802],
2	Member	NNP	O	Member	nn	3	SENT_59	[p3l1607t754r1818b802],
3	Services	NNP	O	Services	nsubj	5	SENT_59	[p3l1831t754r2029b802],
4	(	NN	O	(	dep	3	SENT_59	[p3l2044t754r2137b815],
5	see	VB	O	see	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l2044t754r2137b815],
6	above	IN	O	above	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l9t836r179b898],
7	)	NN	O	)	prep_above	5	SENT_59	[p3l9t836r179b898],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l9t836r179b898],

1	Institutional	JJ	O	institutional	amod	2	SENT_60	[p3l208t836r490b885],
2	subscribers	NNS	O	subscriber	nsubj	4	SENT_60	[p3l505t836r769b885],
3	may	MD	O	may	aux	4	SENT_60	[p3l781t852r890b898],
4	contact	VB	O	contact	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l902t843r1074b885],
5	Sales	NNS	O	sale	dobj	4	SENT_60	[p3l1088t836r1210b885],
6	Analysis	NNP	O	Analysis	nsubj	10	SENT_60	[p3l1223t836r1432b898],
7	&	CC	O	&	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1447t838r1495b885],
8	Support	NN	O	support	nsubj	10	SENT_60	[p3l1511t838r1699b898],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_60	[p3l1712t837r1805b898],
10	see	VBP	O	see	rcmod	5	SENT_60	[p3l1712t837r1805b898],
11	above	IN	O	above	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1819t836r1979b898],
12	)	NN	O	)	prep_above	10	SENT_60	[p3l1819t836r1979b898],
13	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1993t836r2063b885],
14	Web	NN	MISC	web	nn	18	SENT_60	[p3l8t919r125b968],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l139t919r228b968],
16	print	NN	O	print	nn	18	SENT_60	[p3l237t919r351b981],
17	subscription	NN	O	subscription	nn	18	SENT_60	[p3l364t919r653b981],
18	information	NN	O	information	prep_for	12	SENT_60	[p3l665t919r956b968],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l665t919r956b968],

1	Canadian	JJ	MISC	canadian	amod	2	SENT_61	[p3l9t1132r247b1180],
2	GST	NN	O	gst	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l259t1133r375b1180],
3	Reg	NN	PERSON	reg	dep	2	SENT_61	[p3l388t1134r497b1194],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l388t1134r497b1194],

1	No.	NN	O	no.	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l511t1134r599b1180],
2	127571347	CD	NUMBER	127571347	num	1	SENT_62	[p3l622t1133r876b1180],

1	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l11t1254r279b1373],
2	W	NNP	O	W	pobj	1	SENT_63	[p3l7t1375r280b1511],
3	©	CD	NUMBER	©	num	2	SENT_63	[p3l335t1361r382b1407],
4	Copyright	NN	O	copyright	nn	8	SENT_63	[p3l396t1359r640b1421],
5	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	8	SENT_63	[p3l651t1361r769b1407],
6	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	8	SENT_63	[p3l785t1360r1026b1407],
7	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	8	SENT_63	[p3l1038t1359r1269b1407],
8	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	dep	2	SENT_63	[p3l1285t1360r1462b1421],

1	Digital	NNP	O	Digital	nn	3	SENT_64	[p3l9t1662r182b1722],
2	Object	NNP	O	Object	nn	3	SENT_64	[p3l195t1662r369b1722],
3	Identiﬁer	NNP	O	Identiﬁer	nsubjpass	17	SENT_64	[p3l380t1662r620b1708],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_64	[p3l634t1662r803b1721],
5	DOI	NNP	O	DOI	dep	3	SENT_64	[p3l634t1662r803b1721],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	5	SENT_64	[p3l634t1662r803b1721],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l634t1662r803b1721],
8	The	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_64	[p3l10t1742r105b1790],
9	DOI	NN	O	dous	nn	11	SENT_64	[p3l117t1743r227b1790],
10	identiﬁcation	NN	O	identiﬁcation	nn	11	SENT_64	[p3l240t1742r553b1790],
11	system	NN	O	system	dep	3	SENT_64	[p3l566t1749r733b1803],
12	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l745t1742r815b1790],
13	digital	JJ	O	digital	amod	14	SENT_64	[p3l826t1742r974b1803],
14	media	NNS	O	media	prep_for	11	SENT_64	[p3l986t1742r1137b1790],
15	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	17	SENT_64	[p3l1147t1742r1227b1790],
16	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	17	SENT_64	[p3l1239t1742r1356b1790],
17	designed	VBN	O	design	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1368t1742r1582b1803],
18	to	TO	O	to	aux	19	SENT_64	[p3l1591t1749r1638b1790],
19	provide	VB	O	provide	xcomp	17	SENT_64	[p3l1649t1742r1833b1803],
20	persistent	JJ	O	persistent	amod	23	SENT_64	[p3l1845t1742r2072b1803],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l11t1824r99b1871],
22	reliable	JJ	O	reliable	conj_and	20	SENT_64	[p3l109t1824r285b1871],
23	identiﬁcation	NN	O	identiﬁcation	dobj	19	SENT_64	[p3l299t1824r611b1871],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l623t1824r681b1871],
25	digital	JJ	O	digital	amod	26	SENT_64	[p3l685t1824r834b1884],
26	objects	NNS	O	object	prep_of	23	SENT_64	[p3l847t1824r1024b1884],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l847t1824r1024b1884],

1	Information	NN	O	information	nsubjpass	17	SENT_65	[p3l1040t1824r1326b1871],
2	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1337t1839r1399b1871],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_65	[p3l1410t1824r1483b1871],
4	DOI	NNP	O	DOI	prep_on	1	SENT_65	[p3l1495t1825r1606b1871],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1619t1824r1707b1871],
6	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	8	SENT_65	[p3l1719t1824r1772b1871],
7	goveming	JJ	O	goveming	amod	8	SENT_65	[p3l1786t1824r2028b1885],
8	body	NN	O	body	prep_on	1	SENT_65	[p3l8t1905r143b1966],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l8t1905r143b1966],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_65	[p3l157t1905r230b1952],
11	Intemational	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Intemational	nn	13	SENT_65	[p3l243t1905r543b1952],
12	DOI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DOI	nn	13	SENT_65	[p3l555t1906r666b1952],
13	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Foundation	appos	1	SENT_65	[p3l677t1905r962b1962],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l677t1905r962b1962],
15	can	MD	O	can	aux	17	SENT_65	[p3l978t1920r1062b1952],
16	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	17	SENT_65	[p3l1072t1905r1131b1952],
17	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1145t1905r1286b1952],
18	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1298t1911r1341b1952],
19	http://wvvw.doi.org	NN	O	http://wvvw.doi.org	prep_at	17	SENT_65	[p3l1351t1905r1817b1966],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1351t1905r1817b1966],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_66	[p3l1834t1905r1928b1952],
2	DOI	NNP	O	DOI	nsubjpass	5	SENT_66	[p3l1940t1906r2051b1952],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_66	[p3l2064t1905r2101b1952],
4	prominently	RB	O	prominently	advmod	5	SENT_66	[p3l8t1986r303b2047],
5	displayed	VBN	O	display	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l315t1986r544b2047],
6	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l555t2002r617b2033],
7	each	DT	O	each	det	9	SENT_66	[p3l630t1986r740b2033],
8	published	VBN	O	publish	amod	9	SENT_66	[p3l750t1986r985b2047],
9	paper	NN	O	paper	prep_on	5	SENT_66	[p3l994t2002r1139b2047],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l994t2002r1139b2047],

1	Claims	NNS	O	claim	nsubj	5	SENT_67	[p3l11t2072r191b2118],
2	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l205t2072r281b2118],
3	Issues	NNS	O	issue	prep_for	1	SENT_67	[p3l293t2073r445b2118],
4	Not	RB	O	not	neg	3	SENT_67	[p3l458t2073r554b2118],
5	Received	VBN	O	receive	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l565t2072r812b2118],
6	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l565t2072r812b2118],
7	Claims	NNS	O	claim	nsubjpass	10	SENT_67	[p3l11t2152r180b2200],
8	will	MD	O	will	aux	10	SENT_67	[p3l192t2152r285b2199],
9	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_67	[p3l297t2152r355b2199],
10	honored	VBN	O	honor	parataxis	5	SENT_67	[p3l367t2152r567b2199],
11	only	RB	O	only	advmod	13	SENT_67	[p3l579t2152r686b2213],
12	if	IN	O	if	dep	13	SENT_67	[p3l697t2152r740b2199],
13	submitted	VBN	O	submit	conj_or	13	SENT_67	[p3l747t2152r982b2199],
14	Within	IN	O	within	dep	13	SENT_67	[p3l991t2152r1146b2199],
15	90	CD	DURATION	90	num	16	SENT_67	[p3l1158t2153r1218b2199],
16	days	NNS	NUMBER	day	pobj	14	SENT_67	[p3l1232t2152r1341b2213],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1355t2152r1412b2199],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_67	[p3l1416t2152r1489b2199],
19	issue	NN	O	issue	nn	20	SENT_67	[p3l1503t2152r1620b2199],
20	date	NN	O	date	prep_of	16	SENT_67	[p3l1634t2152r1732b2199],
21	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1746t2152r1816b2199],
22	subscribers	NNS	O	subscriber	prep_for	13	SENT_67	[p3l1828t2152r2092b2199],
23	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l2105t2152r2152b2199],
24	North	NNP	LOCATION	North	nn	25	SENT_67	[p3l7t2233r151b2281],
25	America	NNP	LOCATION	America	prep_in	22	SENT_67	[p3l162t2233r373b2281],
26	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l385t2249r436b2281],
27	within	IN	O	within	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l446t2233r600b2281],
28	180	CD	DURATION	180	num	29	SENT_67	[p3l618t2235r702b2281],
29	days	NNS	NUMBER	day	prep_within	13	SENT_67	[p3l716t2233r825b2294],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l839t2233r897b2281],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_67	[p3l900t2233r974b2281],
32	issue	NN	O	issue	nn	33	SENT_67	[p3l987t2233r1104b2281],
33	date	NN	O	date	prep_of	29	SENT_67	[p3l1118t2233r1216b2281],
34	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1230t2233r1300b2281],
35	all	DT	O	all	det	37	SENT_67	[p3l1311t2233r1369b2280],
36	other	JJ	O	other	amod	37	SENT_67	[p3l1382t2233r1505b2281],
37	subscribers	NNS	O	subscriber	prep_for	33	SENT_67	[p3l1518t2233r1792b2281],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1518t2233r1792b2281],

1	Contact	NN	O	contact	nn	2	SENT_68	[p3l1822t2235r2009b2281],
2	Sales	NNS	O	sale	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l2023t2233r2145b2281],
3	Analysis	NNP	O	Analysis	dep	2	SENT_68	[p3l9t2315r218b2375],
4	&	CC	O	&	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l232t2316r280b2362],
5	Support	NN	O	support	dep	2	SENT_68	[p3l296t2316r493b2375],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l296t2316r493b2375],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l523t2315r603b2362],
2	(614) 447-3674	CD	NUMBER	(614) 447-3674	num	1	SENT_69	[p3l757t2316r988b2362],[p3l617t2315r744b2375],
3	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1002t2330r1053b2362],
4	(888) 338-0012	CD	NUMBER	(888) 338-0012	conj_or	1	SENT_69	[p3l1208t2316r1450b2372],[p3l1065t2315r1192b2375],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1208t2316r1450b2372],
6	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	1	SENT_69	[p3l1464t2317r1557b2362],
7	(614) 447-5475	CD	NUMBER	(614) 447-5475	num	6	SENT_69	[p3l1711t2316r1955b2372],[p3l1570t2315r1697b2375],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1711t2316r1955b2372],
9	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	nn	10	SENT_69	[p3l1970t2315r2134b2362],
10	ACS_Pubs_Assist@acs.org	NN	O	acs_pubs_assist@acs.org	dep	6	SENT_69	[p3l9t2396r710b2457],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l9t2396r710b2457],

1	Back	RB	O	back	advcl	7	SENT_70	[p3l10t2482r145b2527],
2	Issue	NNP	O	Issue	nn	3	SENT_70	[p3l155t2482r284b2527],
3	Orders	NNS	O	order	pobj	1	SENT_70	[p3l298t2481r498b2527],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l298t2481r498b2527],
5	Single	JJ	O	single	amod	6	SENT_70	[p3l12t2561r164b2622],
6	issues	NNS	O	issue	nsubj	7	SENT_70	[p3l178t2561r322b2608],
7	ﬁom	VBP	O	ﬁom	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l337t2561r459b2608],
8	January	NNP	DATE	January	nsubj	12	SENT_70	[p3l470t2563r666b2622],
9	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	8	SENT_70	[p3l677t2562r793b2608],
10	forward	RB	O	forward	advmod	12	SENT_70	[p3l807t2561r1004b2608],
11	are	VBP	O	be	cop	12	SENT_70	[p3l1016t2576r1090b2608],
12	available	JJ	O	available	ccomp	7	SENT_70	[p3l1104t2561r1320b2608],
13	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1333t2561r1403b2608],
14	a	DT	O	a	det	15	SENT_70	[p3l1415t2576r1443b2608],
15	fee	NN	O	fee	prep_for	12	SENT_70	[p3l1455t2561r1527b2608],
16	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1542t2561r1664b2608],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_70	[p3l1674t2561r1750b2608],
18	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Office	prep_from	15	SENT_70	[p3l1763t2561r1921b2608],
19	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1934t2561r1991b2608],
20	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	nn	21	SENT_70	[p3l12t2642r195b2703],
21	Services	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Services	prep_of	18	SENT_70	[p3l209t2642r427b2690],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l209t2642r427b2690],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l444t2642r518b2690],
2	(800) 227-5558	CD	NUMBER	(800) 227-5558	num	1	SENT_71	[p3l672t2643r892b2690],[p3l532t2643r658b2703],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_71	[p3l908t2642r1037b2703],
4	US	NNP	LOCATION	US	nn	5	SENT_71	[p3l908t2642r1037b2703],
5	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_71	[p3l908t2642r1037b2703],
6	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l908t2642r1037b2703],
7	(202) 872-4600	CD	NUMBER	(202) 872-4600	number	8	SENT_71	[p3l1194t2643r1429b2690],[p3l1054t2642r1178b2703],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	1	SENT_71	[p3l1444t2642r1748b2703],
9	worldwide	JJ	O	worldwide	amod	10	SENT_71	[p3l1444t2642r1748b2703],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	8	SENT_71	[p3l1444t2642r1748b2703],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l1444t2642r1748b2703],
12	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	1	SENT_71	[p3l1762t2644r1854b2689],
13	(202) 8726067	CD	NUMBER	(202) 8726067	num	12	SENT_71	[p3l2008t2643r2115b2690, p3l11t2725r142b2781],[p3l1868t2643r1992b2703],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l2008t2643r2115b2690, p3l11t2725r142b2781],
15	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	nn	16	SENT_71	[p3l158t2723r327b2771],
16	help@acs.org	NN	O	help@acs.org	dep	12	SENT_71	[p3l338t2723r686b2784],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l338t2723r686b2784],

1	Bulk	NNP	O	Bulk	nn	3	SENT_72	[p3l10t2809r137b2855],
2	Reprint	NNP	O	Reprint	nn	3	SENT_72	[p3l148t2808r349b2868],
3	Orders	NNS	O	order	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l362t2809r562b2855],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l362t2809r562b2855],
5	For	IN	O	for	mark	9	SENT_72	[p3l9t2891r95b2936],
6	information	NN	O	information	nsubj	9	SENT_72	[p3l106t2888r398b2936],
7	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l410t2904r473b2936],
8	ordering	VBG	O	order	prepc_on	6	SENT_72	[p3l485t2888r694b2949],
9	reprints	VBZ	O	reprint	advcl	11	SENT_72	[p3l705t2888r907b2949],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l705t2888r907b2949],
11	see	VB	O	see	dep	3	SENT_72	[p3l924t2904r1000b2936],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_72	[p3l1012t2888r1087b2936],
13	speciﬁc	NN	O	speciﬁc	nn	14	SENT_72	[p3l1102t2888r1288b2949],
14	article	NN	O	article	dobj	11	SENT_72	[p3l1302t2888r1453b2936],
15	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1466t2904r1529b2936],
16	http://pubs.acs.org	NN	O	http://pubs.acs.org	prep_on	14	SENT_72	[p3l1539t2888r1982b2949],
17	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1996t2904r2047b2936],
18	instructions	NNS	O	instruction	prep_on	14	SENT_72	[p3l10t2970r298b3017],
19	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l313t2976r357b3017],
20	http://pubs.acs.org/page/copyright/perrnissions.html	NN	O	http://pubs.acs.org/page/copyright/perrnissions.html	prep_at	14	SENT_72	[p3l367t2970r1635b3031],
21	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1648t2985r1700b3017],
22	contact	NN	O	contact	prep_at	14	SENT_72	[p3l1711t2976r1889b3017],
23	Cierant	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cierant	nn	24	SENT_72	[p3l1901t2970r2081b3017],
24	Corporation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Corporation	dep	31	SENT_72	[p3l11t3051r310b3112],
25	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l323t3058r366b3098],
26	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	27	SENT_72	[p3l379t3051r742b3111],
27	866	CD	NUMBER	866	prep_at	24	SENT_72	[p3l379t3051r742b3111],
28	)	NN	O	)	dep	31	SENT_72	[p3l379t3051r742b3111],
29	-305	CD	NUMBER	-305	num	28	SENT_72	[p3l379t3051r742b3111],
30	-0111	CD	NUMBER	-0111	num	31	SENT_72	[p3l379t3051r742b3111],
31	9am	CD	TIME	9am	dep	34	SENT_72	[p3l762t3052r870b3098],
32	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l881t3058r928b3098],
33	5pm	CD	TIME	5pm	prep_to	31	SENT_72	[p3l944t3053r1053b3112],
34	EST.	NNP	O	EST.	dep	14	SENT_72	[p3l1065t3052r1181b3099],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1065t3052r1181b3099],

1	Supporting	VBG	O	support	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l12t3137r302b3197],
2	Information	NN	O	information	nn	4	SENT_73	[p3l314t3137r628b3183],
3	(	NN	O	(	nn	4	SENT_73	[p3l642t3137r751b3195],
4	S1	NN	O	s1	dobj	1	SENT_73	[p3l642t3137r751b3195],
5	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	4	SENT_73	[p3l642t3137r751b3195],
6	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l642t3137r751b3195],
7	S1	NN	O	s1	dep	4	SENT_73	[p3l12t3218r63b3265],
8	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l77t3217r199b3264],
9	1995	CD	DATE	1995	prep_from	7	SENT_73	[p3l217t3218r327b3264],
10	to	TO	DATE	to	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l342t3224r390b3264],
11	present	JJ	DATE	present	prep_to	1	SENT_73	[p3l401t3224r581b3278],
12	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	14	SENT_73	[p3l593t3217r631b3264],
13	available	JJ	O	available	amod	14	SENT_73	[p3l645t3217r861b3264],
14	free	JJ	O	free	aux	1	SENT_73	[p3l875t3217r970b3264],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l984t3217r1041b3264],
16	charge	NN	O	charge	prep_of	14	SENT_73	[p3l1046t3217r1208b3278],
17	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1222t3217r1344b3264],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_73	[p3l1355t3217r1430b3264],
19	journal	NN	O	journal	poss	22	SENT_73	[p3l1436t3217r1654b3278],
20	’s	POS	O	’s	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1436t3217r1654b3278],
21	home	NN	O	home	nn	22	SENT_73	[p3l1666t3217r1805b3264],
22	page	NN	O	page	prep_from	14	SENT_73	[p3l1816t3233r1933b3278],
23	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	26	SENT_73	[p3l11t3298r501b3359],
24	http://pubs.acs.org/j	NN	O	http://pubs.acs.org/j	nn	26	SENT_73	[p3l11t3298r501b3359],
25	ournal/bichaw	NN	O	ournal/bichaw	nn	26	SENT_73	[p3l506t3298r887b3359],
26	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	1	SENT_73	[p3l506t3298r887b3359],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l506t3298r887b3359],

1	For	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l916t3300r1001b3346],
2	information	NN	O	information	prep_for	7	SENT_74	[p3l1012t3298r1305b3346],
3	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1317t3314r1379b3346],
4	electronic	JJ	O	electronic	amod	5	SENT_74	[p3l1392t3298r1630b3346],
5	access	NN	O	access	prep_on	2	SENT_74	[p3l1644t3314r1813b3355],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1644t3314r1813b3355],
7	send	VB	O	send	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1830t3298r1943b3346],
8	e-mail	JJ	O	e-mail	dobj	7	SENT_74	[p3l1954t3298r2111b3346],
9	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l9t3386r57b3427],
10	support@services.acs.org	NN	O	support@services.acs.org	prep_to	7	SENT_74	[p3l72t3379r712b3440],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l72t3379r712b3440],

1	SI	NNP	O	SI	nsubj	6	SENT_75	[p3l744t3381r794b3427],
2	prior	RB	O	prior	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l805t3379r927b3440],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l937t3386r985b3427],
4	1995	CD	DATE	1995	prep_prior_to	6	SENT_75	[p3l1005t3381r1115b3427],
5	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	6	SENT_75	[p3l1132t3379r1170b3427],
6	available	JJ	O	available	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l1184t3379r1400b3427],
7	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l1414t3379r1484b3427],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_75	[p3l1495t3395r1523b3426],
9	fee	NN	O	fee	prep_for	6	SENT_75	[p3l1536t3379r1620b3437],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l1536t3379r1620b3437],
11	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l1636t3379r1758b3427],
12	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Office	prep_from	6	SENT_75	[p3l1770t3379r1928b3427],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l1941t3379r1998b3427],
14	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	nn	15	SENT_75	[p3l12t3461r195b3522],
15	Services	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Services	prep_of	12	SENT_75	[p3l209t3461r427b3508],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l209t3461r427b3508],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l457t3461r532b3508],
2	(800) 227-5558	CD	NUMBER	(800) 227-5558	num	1	SENT_76	[p3l685t3462r905b3508],[p3l545t3461r672b3521],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_76	[p3l921t3461r1051b3521],
4	US	NNP	LOCATION	US	nn	5	SENT_76	[p3l921t3461r1051b3521],
5	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_76	[p3l921t3461r1051b3521],
6	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l921t3461r1051b3521],
7	(202) 872-4600	CD	NUMBER	(202) 872-4600	number	8	SENT_76	[p3l1208t3462r1443b3508],[p3l1068t3461r1192b3521],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	1	SENT_76	[p3l1458t3461r1762b3521],
9	worldwide	JJ	O	worldwide	amod	10	SENT_76	[p3l1458t3461r1762b3521],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	8	SENT_76	[p3l1458t3461r1762b3521],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l1458t3461r1762b3521],
12	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	1	SENT_76	[p3l9t3544r102b3589],
13	(202) 872-6067	CD	NUMBER	(202) 872-6067	num	12	SENT_76	[p3l255t3543r497b3599],[p3l114t3542r239b3602],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l255t3543r497b3599],
15	E-mai1help@acs.org	NN	O	e-mai1help@acs.org	dep	12	SENT_76	[p3l512t3542r1041b3603],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l512t3542r1041b3603],

1	BIOCHEMISTRY	NN	O	biochemistry	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l49t99r863b193],
2	including	VBG	O	include	dep	1	SENT_77	[p4l82t202r207b237],
3	biophysical	JJ	O	biophysical	amod	4	SENT_77	[p4l220t202r375b237],
4	chemistry	NN	O	chemistry	pobj	2	SENT_77	[p4l387t202r524b237],
5	&	CC	O	&	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l532t204r551b232],
6	molecular	JJ	O	molecular	amod	7	SENT_77	[p4l562t202r699b231],
7	biology	NN	O	biology	conj_and	4	SENT_77	[p4l711t202r814b237],

1	Karen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Karen	nn	7	SENT_78	[p4l267t464r348b487],
2	Allen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Allen	nn	7	SENT_78	[p4l355t463r429b487],
3	Boston	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Boston	nn	7	SENT_78	[p4l227t503r319b526],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	7	SENT_78	[p4l332t503r468b533],
5	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	Jeffrey	nn	7	SENT_78	[p4l224t543r315b574],
6	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	nn	7	SENT_78	[p4l324t544r350b567],
7	Benovic	NNP	PERSON	Benovic	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l361t543r471b567],

1	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	Thomas	nn	3	SENT_79	[p4l158t583r261b607],
2	Jefferson	NNP	PERSON	Jefferson	nn	3	SENT_79	[p4l269t583r391b614],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l404t584r539b614],

1	Gary	NNP	PERSON	Gary	nn	5	SENT_80	[p4l234t624r300b655],
2	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	5	SENT_80	[p4l308t625r342b648],
3	Brudvig	NNP	PERSON	Brudvig	nn	5	SENT_80	[p4l353t624r462b655],
4	Yale	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Yale	nn	5	SENT_80	[p4l249t664r302b688],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l314t665r449b695],

1	Pia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pia	nn	3	SENT_81	[p4l9t839r83b881],
2	Adelroth	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Adelroth	nn	3	SENT_81	[p4l97t831r304b881],
3	Stockholm	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stockholm	_	0	SENT_81	[p4l9t899r248b941],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	8	SENT_81	[p4l271t900r507b953],
5	Natalie	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Natalie	nn	8	SENT_81	[p4l8t976r175b1018],
6	G.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	G.	nn	8	SENT_81	[p4l193t977r243b1018],
7	Ahn	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ahn	nn	8	SENT_81	[p4l259t976r359b1017],
8	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	3	SENT_81	[p4l15t1045r250b1097],
9	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_81	[p4l267t1044r322b1097],
10	Colorado	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Colorado	nn	12	SENT_81	[p4l12t1119r239b1166],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_81	[p4l12t1119r239b1166],
12	Boulder	NNP	LOCATION	Boulder	prep_of	8	SENT_81	[p4l259t1119r449b1160],

1	Johan	NNP	PERSON	Johan	nn	3	SENT_82	[p4l9t1226r144b1267],
2	Aqvist	NNP	PERSON	Aqvist	nn	3	SENT_82	[p4l155t1226r311b1279],
3	Uppsala	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Uppsala	_	0	SENT_82	[p4l15t1301r204b1353],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	8	SENT_82	[p4l226t1302r462b1353],
5	Fraser	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Fraser	nn	8	SENT_82	[p4l9t1405r155b1444],
6	A.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	A.	nn	8	SENT_82	[p4l165t1404r218b1444],
7	Armstrong	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Armstrong	nn	8	SENT_82	[p4l233t1404r484b1456],
8	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	3	SENT_82	[p4l15t1463r250b1515],
9	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_82	[p4l267t1461r322b1515],
10	Oxford	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oxford	nn	16	SENT_82	[p4l328t1461r490b1515],
11	David	NNP	ORGANIZATION	David	nn	16	SENT_82	[p4l9t1568r151b1610],
12	S.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	S.	nn	16	SENT_82	[p4l168t1569r208b1610],
13	Auld	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Auld	nn	16	SENT_82	[p4l223t1568r340b1610],
14	Harvard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Harvard	nn	16	SENT_82	[p4l7t1643r209b1685],
15	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	16	SENT_82	[p4l219t1643r413b1685],
16	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	prep_of	8	SENT_82	[p4l426t1643r585b1685],

1	Barbara	NNP	PERSON	Barbara	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l9t1750r193b1791],
2	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l204t1751r256b1791],
3	Baird	NNP	PERSON	Baird	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l275t1750r404b1791],
4	Cornell	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cornell	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l12t1824r188b1866],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l206t1826r443b1877],
6	James	NNP	ORGANIZATION	James	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l9t1933r149b1973],
7	R.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	R.	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l166t1933r215b1973],
8	Bamburg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bamburg	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l233t1931r447b1984],
9	Colorado	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Colorado	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l12t2006r229b2048],
10	State	NNP	ORGANIZATION	State	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l246t2007r362b2048],
11	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l382t2008r619b2059],
12	Dorothy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dorothy	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l9t2113r202b2167],
13	Beckett	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Beckett	nn	14	SENT_83	[p4l217t2114r394b2156],
14	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l15t2190r250b2242],
15	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l267t2188r322b2242],
16	Maryland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Maryland	nn	18	SENT_83	[p4l323t2188r556b2242],
17	Stephen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stephen	nn	18	SENT_83	[p4l12t2296r196b2349],
18	J	NNP	ORGANIZATION	J	prep_of	14	SENT_83	[p4l211t2298r233b2338],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l237t2331r243b2338],

1	Benkovic	JJ	O	benkovic	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l262t2296r483b2338],
2	The	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_84	[p4l13t2371r95b2412],
3	Pennsylvania	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pennsylvania	nn	10	SENT_84	[p4l109t2371r421b2424],
4	State	NNP	ORGANIZATION	State	nn	10	SENT_84	[p4l9t2447r124b2487],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	10	SENT_84	[p4l145t2447r381b2499],
6	Robert	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Robert	nn	10	SENT_84	[p4l9t2553r167b2595],
7	E.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	E.	nn	10	SENT_84	[p4l182t2555r228b2595],
8	Blankenship	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Blankenship	nn	10	SENT_84	[p4l246t2553r535b2607],
9	Washington	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Washington	nn	10	SENT_84	[p4l15t2628r278b2681],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	1	SENT_84	[p4l301t2629r537b2681],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l11t2705r52b2743],
12	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	13	SENT_84	[p4l68t2702r121b2743],
13	Louis	NNP	LOCATION	Louis	prep_in	10	SENT_84	[p4l140t2703r270b2743],

1	David	NNP	PERSON	David	nn	2	SENT_85	[p4l9t2809r151b2850],
2	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l166t2811r203b2850],
3	Bocian	NNP	PERSON	Bocian	nn	4	SENT_85	[p4l222t2809r386b2850],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	2	SENT_85	[p4l15t2885r250b2936],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l267t2883r322b2936],
6	California	NNP	ORGANIZATION	California	nn	8	SENT_85	[p4l328t2883r575b2936],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l328t2883r575b2936],
8	Riverside	NNP	LOCATION	Riverside	prep_of	4	SENT_85	[p4l7t2957r228b2998],

1	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	3	SENT_86	[p4l9t3066r42b3106],
2	Martin	NNP	PERSON	Martin	nn	3	SENT_86	[p4l61t3064r218b3105],
3	Bollinger	NNP	PERSON	Bollinger	_	0	SENT_86	[p4l234t3064r453b3117],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_87	[p4l13t3256r95b3297],
2	Pennsylvania	NNP	LOCATION	Pennsylvania	_	0	SENT_87	[p4l109t3256r421b3309],
3	State	NNP	O	State	nn	4	SENT_87	[p4l9t3332r124b3372],
4	University	NNP	O	University	dep	2	SENT_87	[p4l145t3332r381b3384],

1	ASSOCIATE	JJ	O	associate	amod	2	SENT_88	[p4l863t400r1099b429],
2	EDITORS	NNS	O	editor	_	0	SENT_88	[p4l1112t400r1296b429],

1	John	NNP	PERSON	John	nn	3	SENT_89	[p4l993t463r1055b487],
2	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	3	SENT_89	[p4l1062t463r1092b487],
3	Gerlt	NNP	PERSON	Gerlt	_	0	SENT_89	[p4l1103t463r1171b487],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_91	[p4l1095t502r1361b533],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_91	[p4l1095t502r1361b533],

1	Champaign	NNP	LOCATION	Champaign	_	0	SENT_92	[p4l1095t502r1361b533],

1	Catherine	NNP	PERSON	Catherine	nn	8	SENT_93	[p4l953t543r1081b567],
2	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	8	SENT_93	[p4l1088t544r1118b567],
3	Royer	NNP	PERSON	Royer	nn	8	SENT_93	[p4l1129t544r1211b574],
4	Université	NNP	PERSON	Université	nn	8	SENT_93	[p4l932t583r1067b607],
5	Montpellier	NNP	PERSON	Montpellier	nn	8	SENT_93	[p4l1075t583r1234b614],
6	Charles	NNP	PERSON	Charles	nn	8	SENT_93	[p4l955t624r1055b648],
7	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	8	SENT_93	[p4l1065t625r1092b648],
8	Sanders	NNP	PERSON	Sanders	_	0	SENT_93	[p4l1105t624r1208b648],

1	David	NNP	PERSON	David	nn	2	SENT_95	[p4l748t840r890b881],
2	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	_	0	SENT_95	[p4l905t841r954b881],
3	Davies	NNP	PERSON	Davies	nn	5	SENT_95	[p4l973t840r1132b881],
4	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	5	SENT_95	[p4l746t900r952b941],
5	Institutes	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Institutes	dep	2	SENT_95	[p4l964t901r1177b941],
6	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_95	[p4l1195t899r1250b953],
7	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	10	SENT_95	[p4l1251t899r1409b941],
8	Victoria	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Victoria	nn	10	SENT_95	[p4l748t977r935b1018],
9	DeRose	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DeRose	nn	10	SENT_95	[p4l950t978r1132b1018],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_of	5	SENT_95	[p4l753t1046r989b1098],
11	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_95	[p4l1006t1044r1061b1098],
12	Oregon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oregon	nn	19	SENT_95	[p4l1067t1045r1237b1098],
13	Jack	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jack	nn	19	SENT_95	[p4l749t1152r851b1193],
14	E.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	E.	nn	19	SENT_95	[p4l866t1154r911b1193],
15	Dixon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dixon	nn	19	SENT_95	[p4l931t1152r1075b1193],
16	Howard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Howard	nn	19	SENT_95	[p4l746t1226r938b1268],
17	Hughes	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hughes	nn	19	SENT_95	[p4l949t1226r1126b1279],
18	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	19	SENT_95	[p4l746t1301r939b1342],
19	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	prep_of	10	SENT_95	[p4l951t1303r1142b1342],

1	Debra	NNP	O	Debra	nn	3	SENT_96	[p4l748t1403r889b1445],
2	Dunaway-Mariano	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dunaway-Mariano	nn	3	SENT_96	[p4l905t1403r1341b1456],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l753t1464r990b1515],
4	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1006t1462r1061b1515],
5	New	NNP	ORGANIZATION	New	nn	9	SENT_96	[p4l1062t1463r1167b1504],
6	Mexico	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mexico	nn	9	SENT_96	[p4l1180t1463r1351b1504],
7	Irwin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Irwin	nn	9	SENT_96	[p4l749t1569r873b1611],
8	Fridovich	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Fridovich	nn	9	SENT_96	[p4l889t1569r1114b1611],
9	Duke	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Duke	prep_of	3	SENT_96	[p4l746t1644r869b1685],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	12	SENT_96	[p4l891t1645r1126b1697],
11	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	12	SENT_96	[p4l745t1718r939b1759],
12	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	3	SENT_96	[p4l956t1719r1112b1759],

1	Martin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Martin	nn	2	SENT_97	[p4l748t1825r906b1866],
2	Gellert	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Gellert	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l922t1825r1082b1866],
3	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	16	SENT_97	[p4l746t1899r952b1941],
4	Institutes	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Institutes	dep	3	SENT_97	[p4l964t1901r1177b1941],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l1195t1899r1250b1953],
6	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	10	SENT_97	[p4l1251t1899r1409b1941],
7	Marc	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Marc	nn	10	SENT_97	[p4l748t2009r868b2048],
8	M.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	M.	nn	10	SENT_97	[p4l885t2009r947b2048],
9	Greenberg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Greenberg	nn	10	SENT_97	[p4l967t2007r1209b2060],
10	Johns	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Johns	prep_of	3	SENT_97	[p4l745t2082r882b2123],
11	Hopkins	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hopkins	nn	16	SENT_97	[p4l896t2082r1090b2135],
12	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	16	SENT_97	[p4l1112t2083r1348b2135],
13	Angela	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Angela	nn	16	SENT_97	[p4l748t2189r915b2243],
14	M.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	M.	nn	16	SENT_97	[p4l931t2191r992b2231],
15	Gronenborn	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Gronenborn	nn	16	SENT_97	[p4l1012t2189r1291b2231],
16	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	2	SENT_97	[p4l753t2266r990b2317],
17	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l1006t2264r1061b2318],
18	Pittsburgh	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pittsburgh	nn	22	SENT_97	[p4l1062t2265r1305b2318],
19	Paul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Paul	nn	22	SENT_97	[p4l748t2372r850b2413],
20	J.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	J.	nn	22	SENT_97	[p4l866t2373r899b2413],
21	Hagerman	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hagerman	nn	22	SENT_97	[p4l918t2373r1159b2425],
22	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_of	16	SENT_97	[p4l753t2448r990b2499],
23	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l1006t2446r1061b2500],
24	California	NNP	ORGANIZATION	California	nn	32	SENT_97	[p4l751t2521r997b2574],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l751t2521r997b2574],
26	Davis	NNP	PERSON	Davis	appos	32	SENT_97	[p4l1017t2523r1153b2563],
27	Kathleen	NNP	PERSON	Kathleen	nn	32	SENT_97	[p4l748t2628r957b2670],
28	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	32	SENT_97	[p4l973t2630r1021b2670],
29	Hall	NNP	PERSON	Hall	nn	32	SENT_97	[p4l1040t2628r1139b2669],
30	Washington	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Washington	nn	32	SENT_97	[p4l755t2702r1017b2755],
31	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	32	SENT_97	[p4l1040t2704r1276b2755],
32	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	prep_of	22	SENT_97	[p4l748t2777r907b2818],
33	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l921t2777r977b2830],
34	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	nn	38	SENT_97	[p4l978t2777r1195b2818],
35	Jeffrey	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jeffrey	nn	38	SENT_97	[p4l749t2884r908b2937],
36	J.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	J.	nn	38	SENT_97	[p4l923t2885r956b2925],
37	Hayes	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hayes	nn	38	SENT_97	[p4l975t2885r1118b2937],
38	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_of	32	SENT_97	[p4l753t2959r990b3011],
39	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l1006t2958r1061b3011],
40	Rochester	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Rochester	nn	42	SENT_97	[p4l1062t2958r1297b2999],
41	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	42	SENT_97	[p4l745t3032r939b3074],
42	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	prep_of	38	SENT_97	[p4l956t3033r1112b3074],

1	George	NNP	PERSON	George	nn	5	SENT_98	[p4l749t3257r916b3310],
2	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	5	SENT_98	[p4l932t3258r969b3298],
3	Hess	NNP	PERSON	Hess	nn	5	SENT_98	[p4l987t3258r1098b3298],
4	Cornell	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cornell	nn	5	SENT_98	[p4l751t3331r926b3373],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l945t3333r1181b3384],

1	Vanderbilt	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Vanderbilt	nn	2	SENT_99	[p4l1157t129r1295b153],
2	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1304t129r1444b160],
3	EDITOR-IN-CHIEF	NN	O	editor-in-chief	dep	2	SENT_99	[p4l1167t91r1546b120],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1167t91r1546b120],
5	RICHARD	NNP	PERSON	RICHARD	nn	8	SENT_99	[p4l1571t91r1767b120],
6	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	8	SENT_99	[p4l1780t91r1818b120],
7	ARMSTRONG	NNP	PERSON	ARMSTRONG	nn	8	SENT_99	[p4l1828t91r2103b120],
8	School	NNP	O	School	dep	2	SENT_99	[p4l1454t129r1544b153],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1554t129r1585b153],
10	Medicine	NNP	O	Medicine	nn	12	SENT_99	[p4l1590t129r1722b158],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1590t129r1722b158],
12	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	prep_of	8	SENT_99	[p4l1732t130r1889b160],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1898t129r1929b153],
14	Biochemistry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biochemistry	prep_of	8	SENT_99	[p4l1934t129r2113b160],

1	832	CD	NUMBER	832	num	2	SENT_100	[p4l1341t163r1388b186],
2	RRB	NN	O	rrb	_	0	SENT_100	[p4l1398t163r1471b191],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_100	[p4l1398t163r1471b191],
4	Nashville	NNP	LOCATION	Nashville	nn	6	SENT_100	[p4l1480t162r1615b191],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_100	[p4l1480t162r1615b191],
6	Tennessee	NNP	LOCATION	Tennessee	appos	2	SENT_100	[p4l1625t163r1760b186],
7	37232-0146	CD	NUMBER	37232-0146	num	6	SENT_100	[p4l1771t163r1929b186],
8	(615) 343-3915	CD	NUMBER	(615) 343-3915	dep	2	SENT_100	[p4l1470t196r1604b224],[p4l1390t195r1460b226],
9	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_100	[p4l1470t196r1604b224],
10	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	8	SENT_100	[p4l1615t196r1664b219],
11	(202) 354-5420	CD	NUMBER	(202) 354-5420	num	10	SENT_100	[p4l1754t196r1880b219],[p4l1674t195r1744b226],

1	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	nn	2	SENT_101	[p4l1442t229r1532b252],
2	eic@biochem.acs.org	NN	O	eic@biochem.acs.org	_	0	SENT_101	[p4l1542t229r1828b259],

1	Mark	NNP	PERSON	Mark	nn	2	SENT_102	[p4l1689t463r1761b487],
2	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	_	0	SENT_102	[p4l1771t463r1794b487],
3	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	5	SENT_102	[p4l1805t464r1825b487],
4	Sansom	NNP	PERSON	Sansom	nn	5	SENT_102	[p4l1838t463r1941b487],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	2	SENT_102	[p4l1680t503r1816b533],
6	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_102	[p4l1825t502r1857b533],
7	Oxford	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oxford	nn	13	SENT_102	[p4l1860t502r1953b533],
8	Ming-Daw	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ming-Daw	nn	13	SENT_102	[p4l1710t543r1856b574],
9	Tsai	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tsai	nn	13	SENT_102	[p4l1865t543r1918b567],
10	Academia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Academia	nn	13	SENT_102	[p4l1700t583r1834b607],
11	Sinica	NNP	PERSON	Sinica	nn	13	SENT_102	[p4l1844t583r1926b607],
12	Leslie	NNP	PERSON	Leslie	nn	13	SENT_102	[p4l1723t624r1804b648],
13	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	Wilson	prep_of	5	SENT_102	[p4l1812t624r1907b648],

1	Masao	NNP	PERSON	Masao	nn	3	SENT_104	[p4l1487t842r1640b882],
2	lkeda-Saito	NNP	O	lkeda-Saito	nn	3	SENT_104	[p4l1657t840r1922b882],
3	Tohoku	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tohoku	_	0	SENT_104	[p4l1490t901r1654b943],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	8	SENT_104	[p4l1676t903r1912b955],
5	Barbara	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barbara	nn	8	SENT_104	[p4l1487t980r1670b1023],
6	Imperiali	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Imperiali	nn	8	SENT_104	[p4l1686t980r1897b1034],
7	Massachusetts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Massachusetts	nn	8	SENT_104	[p4l1484t1050r1824b1092],
8	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	3	SENT_104	[p4l1838t1052r2030b1092],
9	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_104	[p4l1488t1127r1543b1180],
10	Technology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Technology	nn	15	SENT_104	[p4l1550t1127r1812b1180],
11	Matthew	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Matthew	nn	15	SENT_104	[p4l1487t1235r1693b1277],
12	P.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	P.	nn	15	SENT_104	[p4l1708t1237r1744b1277],
13	Jacobson	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jacobson	nn	15	SENT_104	[p4l1763t1235r1975b1277],
14	California	NNP	ORGANIZATION	California	nn	15	SENT_104	[p4l1490t1312r1727b1365],
15	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	prep_of	8	SENT_104	[p4l1741t1314r1933b1353],
16	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_104	[p4l1938t1312r2017b1365],
17	Quantitative	JJ	ORGANIZATION	quantitative	amod	18	SENT_104	[p4l1489t1385r1776b1436],
18	Biosciences	NNS	ORGANIZATION	bioscience	prep_for	15	SENT_104	[p4l1790t1386r2064b1425],
19	Robert	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Robert	nn	25	SENT_104	[p4l1487t1476r1645b1518],
20	L.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	L.	nn	25	SENT_104	[p4l1660t1478r1705b1518],
21	J	NNP	O	J	nn	25	SENT_104	[p4l1725t1478r1746b1518],
22	emigan	NN	O	emigan	nn	25	SENT_104	[p4l1748t1476r1920b1530],
23	Iowa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Iowa	nn	25	SENT_104	[p4l1485t1555r1601b1595],
24	State	NNP	ORGANIZATION	State	nn	25	SENT_104	[p4l1617t1554r1733b1595],
25	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	3	SENT_104	[p4l1754t1555r1990b1606],

1	Lewis	NNP	PERSON	Lewis	nn	2	SENT_105	[p4l1487t1662r1627b1703],
2	E.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	E.	_	0	SENT_105	[p4l1644t1664r1689b1703],
3	Kay	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kay	nn	4	SENT_105	[p4l1708t1664r1804b1715],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	2	SENT_105	[p4l1492t1739r1729b1791],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_105	[p4l1745t1738r1800b1791],
6	Toronto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Toronto	nn	13	SENT_105	[p4l1807t1739r1981b1779],
7	Jeffery	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jeffery	nn	13	SENT_105	[p4l1487t1846r1647b1900],
8	W.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	W.	nn	13	SENT_105	[p4l1660t1848r1720b1888],
9	Kelly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kelly	nn	13	SENT_105	[p4l1739t1846r1868b1900],
10	The	NNP	ORGANIZATION	The	nn	13	SENT_105	[p4l1490t1923r1573b1964],
11	Scripps	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Scripps	nn	13	SENT_105	[p4l1588t1924r1761b1976],
12	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	13	SENT_105	[p4l1775t1923r1989b1964],
13	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	prep_of	4	SENT_105	[p4l1484t2001r1676b2041],

1	Clara	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Clara	nn	3	SENT_106	[p4l1488t2109r1613b2151],
2	Kielkopf	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kielkopf	nn	3	SENT_106	[p4l1627t2109r1839b2162],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_106	[p4l1492t2187r1729b2239],
4	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_106	[p4l1745t2185r1800b2239],
5	Rochester	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Rochester	prep_of	3	SENT_106	[p4l1801t2185r2036b2227],

1	Claude	NNP	PERSON	Claude	nn	6	SENT_107	[p4l1488t2295r1649b2336],
2	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	6	SENT_107	[p4l1666t2297r1715b2336],
3	Klee	NNP	PERSON	Klee	nn	6	SENT_107	[p4l1734t2295r1842b2336],
4	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	6	SENT_107	[p4l1485t2371r1691b2413],
5	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	6	SENT_107	[p4l1708t2372r1877b2413],
6	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	_	0	SENT_107	[p4l1888t2373r2080b2413],

1	Judith	NNP	PERSON	Judith	nn	4	SENT_108	[p4l1487t2480r1628b2522],
2	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	4	SENT_108	[p4l1644t2482r1680b2522],
3	Klinman	NNP	PERSON	Klinman	nn	4	SENT_108	[p4l1699t2480r1901b2522],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1492t2558r1729b2610],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1745t2557r1800b2610],
6	California	NNP	ORGANIZATION	California	prep_of	4	SENT_108	[p4l1806t2557r2053b2610],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1806t2557r2053b2610],
8	Berkeley	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Berkeley	nn	11	SENT_108	[p4l1485t2633r1690b2686],
9	Elizabeth	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Elizabeth	nn	11	SENT_108	[p4l1488t2741r1706b2783],
10	Komives	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Komives	nn	11	SENT_108	[p4l1721t2741r1928b2783],
11	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	4	SENT_108	[p4l1492t2819r1729b2871],
12	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1745t2818r1800b2871],
13	California	NNP	ORGANIZATION	California	prep_of	11	SENT_108	[p4l1806t2818r2053b2871],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1806t2818r2053b2871],
15	San	NNP	ORGANIZATION	San	nn	20	SENT_108	[p4l1487t2895r1571b2935],
16	Diego	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Diego	nn	20	SENT_108	[p4l1586t2896r1728b2947],
17	John	NNP	ORGANIZATION	John	nn	20	SENT_108	[p4l1487t3002r1596b3044],
18	W.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	W.	nn	20	SENT_108	[p4l1610t3004r1670b3044],
19	Kozarich	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kozarich	nn	20	SENT_108	[p4l1689t3001r1901b3043],
20	ActivXBiosciences	NNP	O	ActivXBiosciences	appos	4	SENT_108	[p4l1483t3078r1938b3125],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1483t3078r1938b3125],
22	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	appos	4	SENT_108	[p4l1957t3079r2042b3119],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1957t3079r2042b3119],

1	John	NNP	PERSON	John	nn	2	SENT_109	[p4l1487t3304r1596b3345],
2	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1611t3305r1663b3345],
3	Lipscomb	NNP	PERSON	Lipscomb	nn	4	SENT_109	[p4l1683t3303r1913b3357],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	2	SENT_109	[p4l1492t3382r1729b3433],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1745t3380r1800b3433],
6	Minnesota	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Minnesota	prep_of	4	SENT_109	[p4l1801t3382r2046b3422],

1	James	NNP	PERSON	James	nn	2	SENT_110	[p5l9t74r149b113],
2	U.	NNP	PERSON	U.	_	0	SENT_110	[p5l165t73r217b113],
3	Bowie	NNP	PERSON	Bowie	nn	4	SENT_110	[p5l237t72r386b113],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	2	SENT_110	[p5l15t148r250b200],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_110	[p5l267t147r322b200],
6	California	NNP	ORGANIZATION	California	nn	13	SENT_110	[p5l328t147r575b200],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_110	[p5l328t147r575b200],
8	Los	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Los	appos	13	SENT_110	[p5l7t223r91b263],
9	Angeles	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Angeles	nn	13	SENT_110	[p5l103t221r289b275],
10	David	NNP	ORGANIZATION	David	nn	13	SENT_110	[p5l9t328r151b370],
11	L.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	L.	nn	13	SENT_110	[p5l166t330r211b370],
12	Brautigan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Brautigan	nn	13	SENT_110	[p5l230t328r459b382],
13	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_of	4	SENT_110	[p5l15t405r250b457],
14	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_110	[p5l267t403r322b457],
15	I/zrginia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	I/zrginia	nn	16	SENT_110	[p5l332t405r510b457],
16	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	prep_of	13	SENT_110	[p5l9t478r168b520],
17	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_110	[p5l183t478r238b532],
18	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	prep_of	16	SENT_110	[p5l239t478r457b520],

1	Laura	NNP	PERSON	Laura	nn	3	SENT_111	[p5l9t696r144b737],
2	Busenlehner	NNP	PERSON	Busenlehner	nn	3	SENT_111	[p5l159t695r450b737],
3	The	NNP	ORGANIZATION	The	_	0	SENT_111	[p5l13t770r95b811],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	22	SENT_111	[p5l116t771r352b823],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_111	[p5l368t770r424b823],
6	Alabama	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Alabama	nn	10	SENT_111	[p5l422t769r634b811],
7	Richard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Richard	nn	10	SENT_111	[p5l9t877r193b919],
8	A.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	A.	nn	10	SENT_111	[p5l204t878r256b919],
9	Cerione	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cerione	nn	10	SENT_111	[p5l276t877r458b919],
10	Cornell	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cornell	prep_of	4	SENT_111	[p5l12t951r188b993],
11	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l206t953r443b1005],
12	Benjamin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Benjamin	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l9t1060r235b1113],
13	F.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	F.	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l250t1061r287b1101],
14	Cravatt	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cravatt	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l307t1061r477b1102],
15	The	NNP	ORGANIZATION	The	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l12t1129r95b1170],
16	Scripps	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Scripps	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l110t1130r283b1182],
17	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l297t1129r511b1170],
18	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l7t1205r198b1245],
19	Valerie	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Valerie	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l9t1310r172b1352],
20	D.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	D.	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l188t1312r240b1352],
21	Daggett	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Daggett	nn	22	SENT_111	[p5l259t1312r443b1364],
22	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	3	SENT_111	[p5l15t1370r250b1421],
23	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_111	[p5l267t1368r322b1421],
24	Washington	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Washington	prep_of	22	SENT_111	[p5l332t1368r595b1421],

1	Stefan	NNP	PERSON	Stefan	nn	3	SENT_112	[p5l751t73r896b114],
2	Highsmith	NNP	PERSON	Highsmith	nn	3	SENT_112	[p5l911t72r1156b126],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_112	[p5l753t149r990b200],
4	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_112	[p5l1006t147r1061b200],
5	the	DT	ORGANIZATION	the	det	11	SENT_112	[p5l1066t147r1134b189],
6	Paciﬁc	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Paciﬁc	nn	11	SENT_112	[p5l1148t147r1313b200],
7	Donald	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Donald	nn	11	SENT_112	[p5l748t255r919b296],
8	Hilvert	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hilvert	nn	11	SENT_112	[p5l933t255r1098b296],
9	E	NNP	ORGANIZATION	E	nn	11	SENT_112	[p5l746t330r784b370],
10	T	NN	ORGANIZATION	t	nn	11	SENT_112	[p5l787t330r821b370],
11	H	NN	ORGANIZATION	h	prep_of	3	SENT_112	[p5l814t330r862b370],
12	Zurich	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Zurich	nn	16	SENT_112	[p5l871t329r1024b370],
13	Richard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Richard	nn	16	SENT_112	[p5l748t437r932b479],
14	H.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	H.	nn	16	SENT_112	[p5l946t438r998b479],
15	Himes	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Himes	nn	16	SENT_112	[p5l1018t437r1167b479],
16	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	3	SENT_112	[p5l753t513r990b565],
17	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_112	[p5l1006t512r1061b565],
18	Kansas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kansas	prep_of	16	SENT_112	[p5l1062t513r1234b554],

1	Dick	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dick	nn	10	SENT_113	[p5l748t728r861b770],
2	Hoekstra	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hoekstra	nn	10	SENT_113	[p5l876t728r1085b770],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	10	SENT_113	[p5l753t804r989b856],
4	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	10	SENT_113	[p5l1002t803r1196b844],
5	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	nn	10	SENT_113	[p5l751t879r907b919],
6	Groningen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Groningen	nn	10	SENT_113	[p5l924t879r1167b931],
7	Hazel	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hazel	nn	10	SENT_113	[p5l748t985r882b1027],
8	M.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	M.	nn	10	SENT_113	[p5l898t986r960b1027],
9	Holden	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Holden	nn	10	SENT_113	[p5l979t985r1149b1027],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_113	[p5l753t1062r990b1114],
11	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_113	[p5l1006t1060r1061b1114],
12	Wisconsin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wisconsin	nn	19	SENT_113	[p5l1071t1062r1308b1108],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_113	[p5l1071t1062r1308b1108],
14	Madison	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Madison	appos	19	SENT_113	[p5l745t1129r949b1171],
15	Tony	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tony	nn	19	SENT_113	[p5l749t1238r866b1290],
16	E.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	E.	nn	19	SENT_113	[p5l881t1238r927b1278],
17	Hugli	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hugli	nn	19	SENT_113	[p5l946t1236r1077b1290],
18	Torrey	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Torrey	nn	19	SENT_113	[p5l751t1313r898b1364],
19	Pines	NNS	ORGANIZATION	pine	prep_of	10	SENT_113	[p5l911t1313r1040b1353],
20	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	10	SENT_113	[p5l1054t1312r1246b1353],
21	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_113	[p5l737t1369r816b1422],
22	Molecular	JJ	ORGANIZATION	molecular	amod	23	SENT_113	[p5l828t1369r1073b1410],
23	Studies	NNS	ORGANIZATION	study	prep_for	20	SENT_113	[p5l1087t1369r1253b1411],

1	Hung-Wen	JJ	O	hung-wen	amod	2	SENT_114	[p5l1487t125r1740b176],
2	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_114	[p5l1756t123r1885b176],
3	Ben	NNP	PERSON	Ben	nn	6	SENT_114	[p5l1756t123r1885b176],
4	)	NNP	O	)	nn	6	SENT_114	[p5l1756t123r1885b176],
5	Liu	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Liu	nn	6	SENT_114	[p5l1902t123r1982b165],
6	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	2	SENT_114	[p5l1492t201r1729b253],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_114	[p5l1745t199r1799b253],
8	Texas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Texas	nn	12	SENT_114	[p5l1807t201r1932b241],
9	atAustin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	atAustin	nn	12	SENT_114	[p5l1949t200r2152b241],
10	Erwin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Erwin	nn	12	SENT_114	[p5l1487t308r1628b350],
11	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	nn	12	SENT_114	[p5l1644t308r1824b350],
12	Stony	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stony	prep_of	6	SENT_114	[p5l1487t386r1615b439],
13	Brook	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Brook	nn	17	SENT_114	[p5l1629t385r1772b427],
14	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	17	SENT_114	[p5l1790t387r2027b439],
15	Michael	NNP	PERSON	Michael	nn	17	SENT_114	[p5l1487t495r1676b536],
16	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	17	SENT_114	[p5l1688t496r1741b536],
17	Marletta	NNP	PERSON	Marletta	dep	2	SENT_114	[p5l1760t495r1956b536],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_115	[p5l1490t680r1573b722],
2	Scripps	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Scripps	nn	5	SENT_115	[p5l1588t681r1761b733],
3	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	5	SENT_115	[p5l1775t680r1989b722],
4	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	nn	5	SENT_115	[p5l1485t758r1676b798],
5	Richard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Richard	_	0	SENT_115	[p5l1487t866r1671b908],
6	E.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	E.	nn	10	SENT_115	[p5l1686t868r1731b908],
7	McCarty	NNP	ORGANIZATION	McCarty	nn	10	SENT_115	[p5l1750t867r1956b919],
8	Johns	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Johns	nn	10	SENT_115	[p5l1484t942r1621b984],
9	Hopkins	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hopkins	nn	10	SENT_115	[p5l1635t942r1829b996],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	5	SENT_115	[p5l1850t944r2087b996],
11	Thomas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Thomas	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1488t1052r1672b1094],
12	J.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	J.	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1689t1054r1722b1094],
13	Mclntosh	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mclntosh	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1740t1052r1962b1094],
14	Duke	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Duke	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1485t1123r1608b1164],
15	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1629t1125r1865b1176],
16	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1484t1199r1678b1240],
17	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1695t1200r1851b1240],
18	Christopher	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Christopher	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1488t1308r1762b1361],
19	Miller	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Miller	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1776t1308r1921b1349],
20	Brandeis	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Brandeis	nn	21	SENT_115	[p5l1485t1368r1695b1409],
21	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	5	SENT_115	[p5l1717t1369r1953b1421],

1	Narla	NNP	PERSON	Narla	nn	5	SENT_116	[p5l7t1617r202b1679],
2	Mohandas	NNP	PERSON	Mohandas	nn	5	SENT_116	[p5l225t1617r583b1680],
3	Joachim	NNP	PERSON	Joachim	nn	5	SENT_116	[p5l1117t1617r1405b1680],
4	Seelig	NNP	PERSON	Seelig	nn	5	SENT_116	[p5l1432t1617r1644b1697],
5	Lindsley	NNP	PERSON	Lindsley	_	0	SENT_116	[p5l6t1731r304b1811],
6	F	NN	O	f	dep	5	SENT_116	[p5l323t1733r384b1792],
7	Kimball	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kimball	nn	11	SENT_116	[p5l408t1731r693b1792],
8	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	11	SENT_116	[p5l1124t1740r1477b1817],
9	ofBasel	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ofBasel	nn	11	SENT_116	[p5l1502t1737r1784b1817],
10	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	11	SENT_116	[p5l7t1846r326b1908],
11	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	5	SENT_116	[p5l348t1848r635b1908],

1	Shu-ou	FW	O	shu-ou	nn	2	SENT_117	[p5l1120t1908r1366b1970],
2	Shan	FW	O	shan	_	0	SENT_117	[p5l1393t1908r1562b1970],

1	Adrian	NNP	PERSON	Adrian	nn	5	SENT_118	[p5l9t2009r250b2070],
2	Mulhouand	NNP	PERSON	Mulhouand	nn	5	SENT_118	[p5l273t2009r678b2070],
3	California	NNP	ORGANIZATION	California	nn	5	SENT_118	[p5l1121t2029r1476b2109],
4	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	nn	5	SENT_118	[p5l1496t2032r1784b2091],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_118	[p5l18t2125r371b2201],
6	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_118	[p5l395t2122r477b2201],
7	Bristol	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bristol	nn	11	SENT_118	[p5l480t2122r721b2184],
8	Offechnology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Offechnology	nn	11	SENT_118	[p5l1118t2149r1602b2229],
9	Robert	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Robert	nn	11	SENT_118	[p5l10t2261r246b2323],
10	K.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	K.	nn	11	SENT_118	[p5l268t2263r346b2323],
11	Nakamoto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nakamoto	prep_of	5	SENT_118	[p5l372t2261r733b2323],
12	Yunyu	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Yunyu	nn	14	SENT_118	[p5l1116t2297r1343b2375],
13	Shi	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Shi	nn	14	SENT_118	[p5l1370t2295r1478b2358],
14	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	5	SENT_118	[p5l18t2378r371b2455],
15	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_118	[p5l395t2376r477b2455],
16	Virginia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Virginia	nn	17	SENT_118	[p5l493t2378r761b2455],
17	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_of	14	SENT_118	[p5l1124t2419r1477b2496],
18	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_118	[p5l1502t2416r1584b2496],
19	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	nn	24	SENT_118	[p5l1589t2418r1854b2479],
20	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	&	_	0	SENT_118	[p5l1880t2418r1940b2479],
21	Gary	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Gary	nn	24	SENT_118	[p5l11t2540r182b2619],
22	L.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	L.	nn	24	SENT_118	[p5l205t2542r274b2601],
23	Nelsestuen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nelsestuen	nn	24	SENT_118	[p5l299t2539r683b2601],
24	Technology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Technology	prep_of	17	SENT_118	[p5l1122t2538r1513b2618],
25	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_118	[p5l1537t2538r1619b2618],
26	China	NNP	ORGANIZATION	China	nn	27	SENT_118	[p5l1630t2538r1835b2601],
27	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_of	24	SENT_118	[p5l18t2656r371b2733],
28	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_118	[p5l395t2653r477b2733],
29	Minnesota	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Minnesota	prep_of	27	SENT_118	[p5l480t2656r847b2716],

1	Marcia	NNP	PERSON	Marcia	nn	6	SENT_119	[p5l10t2818r256b2880],
2	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	nn	6	SENT_119	[p5l278t2820r346b2880],
3	Newcomer	NNP	PERSON	Newcomer	nn	6	SENT_119	[p5l372t2820r757b2880],
4	Louisiana	NNP	PERSON	Louisiana	nn	6	SENT_119	[p5l6t2912r355b2973],
5	State	NNP	PERSON	State	nn	6	SENT_119	[p5l379t2911r552b2973],
6	Universitv	NNP	PERSON	Universitv	_	0	SENT_119	[p5l583t2912r937b2975],

1	Daniel	NNP	PERSON	Daniel	nn	5	SENT_120	[p5l10t3095r240b3157],
2	D.	NNP	O	D.	nn	5	SENT_120	[p5l263t3097r342b3157],
3	Oprian	NNP	O	Oprian	nn	5	SENT_120	[p5l371t3095r611b3175],
4	Brandeis	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Brandeis	nn	5	SENT_120	[p5l7t3209r321b3272],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_120	[p5l354t3212r707b3289],

1	Paul	NNP	PERSON	Paul	nn	2	SENT_121	[p5l10t3374r163b3436],
2	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	_	0	SENT_121	[p5l186t3377r259b3436],
3	Ortiz	NNP	PERSON	Ortiz	nn	5	SENT_121	[p5l289t3374r464b3436],
4	de	IN	PERSON	de	amod	5	SENT_121	[p5l490t3373r567b3436],
5	Montellano	NNP	PERSON	Montellano	dep	2	SENT_121	[p5l592t3373r990b3436],

1	Edward	NNP	PERSON	Edward	_	0	SENT_123	[p5l1117t2709r1386b2772],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	1	SENT_123	[p5l1409t2712r1452b2772],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_123	[p5l1409t2712r1452b2772],

1	Solomon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Solomon	nn	3	SENT_124	[p5l1485t2709r1794b2772],
2	Stanford	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stanford	nn	3	SENT_124	[p5l1116t2831r1416b2911],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_124	[p5l1443t2833r1796b2911],

1	Reinhard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Reinhard	nn	3	SENT_125	[p5l1116t3001r1434b3064],
2	Stemer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stemer	nn	3	SENT_125	[p5l1461t3003r1708b3064],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_125	[p5l1124t3125r1477b3202],
4	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_125	[p5l1502t3122r1584b3202],
5	Regensburg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Regensburg	prep_of	3	SENT_125	[p5l1586t3122r2003b3202],

1	Witold	NNP	PERSON	Witold	nn	3	SENT_126	[p5l1116t3293r1354b3356],
2	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	nn	3	SENT_126	[p5l1376t3295r1454b3356],
3	Surewicz	NNP	PERSON	Surewicz	_	0	SENT_126	[p5l1487t3293r1805b3356],

1	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	4	SENT_127	[p5l1124t3604r1477b3681],
2	Case	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Case	nn	4	SENT_127	[p5l1121t3416r1288b3477],
3	Western	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Western	nn	4	SENT_127	[p5l1321t3417r1584b3477],
4	Reserve	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Reserve	_	0	SENT_127	[p5l1608t3417r1884b3477],

1	Neil	NNP	PERSON	Neil	nn	5	SENT_128	[p6l7t87r157b149],
2	Osheroff	NNP	PERSON	Osheroff	nn	5	SENT_128	[p6l183t87r497b149],
3	Vanderbilt	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Vanderbilt	nn	5	SENT_128	[p6l20t201r373b264],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	5	SENT_128	[p6l402t204r755b281],
5	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	_	0	SENT_128	[p6l10t316r248b378],
6	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_128	[p6l269t316r352b396],
7	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	nn	11	SENT_128	[p6l354t316r680b377],
8	Krzysztof	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Krzysztof	nn	11	SENT_128	[p6l10t479r361b559],
9	Palczewski	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Palczewski	nn	11	SENT_128	[p6l375t479r763b542],
10	Case	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Case	nn	11	SENT_128	[p6l14t596r182b656],
11	Western	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Western	prep_of	5	SENT_128	[p6l215t597r479b656],
12	Reserve	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Reserve	nn	16	SENT_128	[p6l502t597r778b656],
13	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	16	SENT_128	[p6l18t709r371b786],
14	Arthur	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Arthur	nn	16	SENT_128	[p6l9t869r241b931],
15	Pardi	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pardi	nn	16	SENT_128	[p6l263t869r445b931],
16	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	5	SENT_128	[p6l18t986r371b1063],
17	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	prep	16	SENT_128	[p6l395t983r477b1063],

1	Colorado	NNP	LOCATION	Colorado	_	0	SENT_129	[p6l14t1160r355b1232],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_129	[p6l14t1160r355b1232],
3	Boulder	NNP	LOCATION	Boulder	appos	1	SENT_129	[p6l384t1160r668b1222],

1	Daniel	NNP	PERSON	Daniel	nn	5	SENT_130	[p6l10t1323r240b1386],
2	Raleigh	NNP	PERSON	Raleigh	nn	5	SENT_130	[p6l264t1323r533b1403],
3	Stony	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stony	nn	5	SENT_130	[p6l10t1439r202b1517],
4	Brook	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Brook	nn	5	SENT_130	[p6l222t1438r437b1500],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_130	[p6l464t1440r818b1517],
6	Frank	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Frank	nn	14	SENT_130	[p6l10t1601r212b1664],
7	M.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	M.	nn	14	SENT_130	[p6l234t1604r327b1664],
8	Raushel	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Raushel	nn	14	SENT_130	[p6l356t1601r633b1664],
9	Texas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Texas	nn	14	SENT_130	[p6l15t1719r202b1779],
10	A&M	NNP	ORGANIZATION	A&M	nn	14	SENT_130	[p6l220t1717r425b1779],
11	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	14	SENT_130	[p6l448t1719r801b1796],
12	Ivan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ivan	nn	14	SENT_130	[p6l11t1881r163b1942],
13	Rayment	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Rayment	nn	14	SENT_130	[p6l186t1881r500b1959],
14	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	5	SENT_130	[p6l18t1996r371b2073],
15	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_130	[p6l395t1993r477b2073],
16	Wisconsin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wisconsin	nn	22	SENT_130	[p6l493t1996r847b2065],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_130	[p6l493t1996r847b2065],
18	Madison	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Madison	appos	22	SENT_130	[p6l6t2107r310b2169],
19	John	NNP	ORGANIZATION	John	nn	22	SENT_130	[p6l10t2218r173b2281],
20	P.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	P.	nn	22	SENT_130	[p6l196t2220r249b2281],
21	Richard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Richard	nn	22	SENT_130	[p6l279t2218r553b2281],
22	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_of	14	SENT_130	[p6l18t2334r371b2412],
23	at	IN	ORGANIZATION	at	_	0	SENT_130	[p6l395t2343r463b2394],
24	Buffalo	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Buffalo	nn	30	SENT_130	[p6l480t2332r736b2412],
25	J.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	J.	nn	30	SENT_130	[p6l10t2470r58b2531],
26	Evan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Evan	nn	30	SENT_130	[p6l88t2470r265b2531],
27	Sadler	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sadler	nn	30	SENT_130	[p6l292t2468r510b2531],
28	Washington	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Washington	nn	30	SENT_130	[p6l19t2555r413b2635],
29	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	30	SENT_130	[p6l447t2557r801b2635],
30	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	prep_at	22	SENT_130	[p6l10t2646r248b2708],
31	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_130	[p6l269t2646r352b2726],
32	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l354t2646r680b2708],
33	Nicole	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nicole	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l7t2771r239b2833],
34	Sampson	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sampson	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l268t2772r582b2851],
35	Stony	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stony	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l9t2886r202b2964],
36	Brook	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Brook	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l221t2885r437b2946],
37	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l464t2887r818b2964],
38	Harold	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Harold	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l10t3042r250b3104],
39	A.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	A.	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l267t3044r346b3104],
40	Scheraga	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Scheraga	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l379t3042r693b3122],
41	Cornell	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cornell	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l14t3157r276b3219],
42	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l305t3159r659b3237],
43	Franz	NNP	PERSON	Franz	nn	44	SENT_130	[p6l10t3323r206b3383],
44	X.	NNP	PERSON	X.	prep_of	30	SENT_130	[p6l229t3323r308b3383],
45	Schmid	NNP	PERSON	Schmid	nn	47	SENT_130	[p6l340t3321r601b3383],
46	Universitéit	NNP	PERSON	Universitéit	nn	47	SENT_130	[p6l18t3410r402b3470],
47	Bayreuth	NNP	PERSON	Bayreuth	dep	44	SENT_130	[p6l420t3408r735b3488],

1	Dan	NNP	PERSON	Dan	nn	2	SENT_131	[p6l1116t30r1261b90],
2	Tawﬁk	NNP	PERSON	Tawﬁk	_	0	SENT_131	[p6l1282t28r1527b90],
3	Weizmann	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Weizmann	nn	4	SENT_131	[p6l1126t152r1467b211],
4	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	2	SENT_131	[p6l1488t152r1776b211],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_131	[p6l1800t149r1883b229],
6	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	prep_of	4	SENT_131	[p6l1888t150r2153b211],

1	Robert	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Robert	nn	2	SENT_132	[p6l1116t318r1352b381],
2	Tycko	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tycko	_	0	SENT_132	[p6l1375t319r1586b398],
3	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	4	SENT_132	[p6l1113t440r1422b503],
4	Institutes	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Institutes	dep	2	SENT_132	[p6l1439t443r1759b503],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_132	[p6l1785t440r1867b520],
6	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	prep_of	4	SENT_132	[p6l1870t440r2105b503],

1	J	NNP	O	J	nn	3	SENT_133	[p6l1117t614r1149b674],
2	ayant	NNP	O	ayant	nn	3	SENT_133	[p6l1152t620r1338b691],
3	B.	NNP	O	B.	_	0	SENT_133	[p6l1361t614r1434b673],
4	Udgaonkar	NNP	O	Udgaonkar	nn	6	SENT_133	[p6l1461t611r1849b691],
5	National	NNP	O	National	nn	6	SENT_133	[p6l1113t731r1422b794],
6	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	3	SENT_133	[p6l1447t732r1674b794],
7	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_133	[p6l1682t731r1801b811],
8	Biological	NNP	O	Biological	nn	9	SENT_133	[p6l1114t851r1480b931],
9	Sciences	NNPS	O	Sciences	prep_for	6	SENT_133	[p6l1500t852r1797b914],

1	John	NNP	PERSON	John	nn	3	SENT_134	[p6l1117t1022r1280b1083],
2	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	3	SENT_134	[p6l1302t1024r1380b1083],
3	Viles	NNP	PERSON	Viles	_	0	SENT_134	[p6l1406t1021r1582b1083],

1	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_135	[p6l1124t1208r1477b1285],
2	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_135	[p6l1502t1205r1584b1285],
3	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	prep_of	1	SENT_135	[p6l1586t1205r1852b1267],

1	Gerhard	NNP	PERSON	Gerhard	nn	5	SENT_136	[p6l1118t1375r1401b1438],
2	Wagner	NNP	PERSON	Wagner	nn	5	SENT_136	[p6l1422t1378r1690b1455],
3	Harvard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Harvard	nn	5	SENT_136	[p6l1113t1497r1416b1559],
4	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	5	SENT_136	[p6l1431t1497r1720b1559],
5	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	_	0	SENT_136	[p6l1740t1497r1979b1559],

1	Bonnie	NNP	PERSON	Bonnie	nn	2	SENT_137	[p6l1116t1668r1365b1730],
2	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	_	0	SENT_137	[p6l1384t1669r1463b1730],
3	Wallace	NNP	PERSON	Wallace	nn	4	SENT_137	[p6l1489t1668r1764b1730],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	2	SENT_137	[p6l1124t1792r1477b1869],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_137	[p6l1502t1789r1584b1869],
6	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	prep_of	4	SENT_137	[p6l1586t1789r1851b1851],

1	Marten	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Marten	nn	3	SENT_138	[p6l1117t1958r1366b2021],
2	Wikstrom	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wikstrom	nn	3	SENT_138	[p6l1388t1958r1731b2021],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_138	[p6l1124t2083r1477b2160],
4	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_138	[p6l1502t2080r1584b2160],
5	Helsinki	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Helsinki	nn	9	SENT_138	[p6l1586t2080r1879b2142],
6	W.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	W.	nn	9	SENT_138	[p6l1116t2199r1206b2260],
7	David	NNP	ORGANIZATION	David	nn	9	SENT_138	[p6l1234t2197r1446b2260],
8	Wilson	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wilson	nn	9	SENT_138	[p6l1488t2197r1736b2260],
9	Georgia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Georgia	prep_of	3	SENT_138	[p6l1121t2319r1400b2398],
10	State	NNP	ORGANIZATION	State	nn	14	SENT_138	[p6l1425t2319r1597b2381],
11	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	14	SENT_138	[p6l1628t2320r1982b2398],
12	Stephen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stephen	nn	14	SENT_138	[p6l1120t2460r1396b2540],
13	Withers	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Withers	nn	14	SENT_138	[p6l1417t2461r1685b2523],
14	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	3	SENT_138	[p6l1124t2557r1477b2635],
15	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_138	[p6l1502t2555r1584b2635],
16	British	NNP	ORGANIZATION	British	nn	24	SENT_138	[p6l1586t2555r1823b2617],
17	Columbia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Columbia	nn	24	SENT_138	[p6l1121t2653r1456b2715],
18	Peter	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Peter	nn	24	SENT_138	[p6l1116t2787r1295b2847],
19	E.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	E.	nn	24	SENT_138	[p6l1317t2787r1385b2847],
20	Wright	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wright	nn	24	SENT_138	[p6l1411t2784r1655b2864],
21	The	NNP	ORGANIZATION	The	nn	24	SENT_138	[p6l1122t2905r1245b2967],
22	Scripps	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Scripps	nn	24	SENT_138	[p6l1268t2906r1527b2984],
23	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	24	SENT_138	[p6l1548t2905r1867b2967],
24	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	prep_of	14	SENT_138	[p6l1113t3023r1400b3083],
