1	AMERICAN	NNP	O	AMERICAN	nn	2	SENT_1	[p1l1558t116r1747b152],
2	JOURNAL	NNP	O	JOURNAL	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1776t116r1949b152],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1776t116r1949b152],

1	OF	IN	O	of	dep	5	SENT_2	[p1l1972t116r2010b137],
2	medical	JJ	O	medical	amod	3	SENT_2	[p1l1559t143r1762b194],
3	genetics	NNS	O	genetics	pobj	1	SENT_2	[p1l1782t150r2011b210],
4	Neuropsychiatric	NNP	O	Neuropsychiatric	nn	5	SENT_2	[p1l1561t220r1849b260],
5	Genetics	NNP	O	Genetics	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1865t220r2011b250],

1	BRIEF	JJ	O	brief	amod	3	SENT_3	[p1l129t113r266b154],
2	RESEARCH	NN	O	research	nn	3	SENT_3	[p1l291t113r535b155],
3	COMMUNICATION	NN	O	communication	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l562t113r954b155],

1	Association	NNP	O	Association	dep	11	SENT_4	[p1l78t330r456b386],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l489t330r554b386],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_4	[p1l579t345r610b385],
4	Variant	JJ	O	variant	prep_of	1	SENT_4	[p1l639t330r871b386],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l904t330r956b385],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_4	[p1l986t331r1091b386],
7	Muscarinic	NNP	O	Muscarinic	nn	8	SENT_4	[p1l1125t330r1474b386],
8	Acetylcholine	NNP	O	Acetylcholine	prep_in	4	SENT_4	[p1l78t416r519b492],
9	Receptor	NN	O	receptor	dep	11	SENT_4	[p1l553t417r842b491],
10	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	9	SENT_4	[p1l871t416r906b472],
11	Gene	NNP	O	Gene	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l940t416r1099b472],
12	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	11	SENT_4	[p1l1137t409r1420b486],
13	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	dep	11	SENT_4	[p1l1137t409r1420b486],
14	]	CD	NUMBER	]	num	13	SENT_4	[p1l1137t409r1420b486],
15	With	IN	O	with	dep	11	SENT_4	[p1l1454t416r1595b472],
16	Nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	17	SENT_4	[p1l85t503r349b559],
17	Addiction	NN	O	addiction	pobj	15	SENT_4	[p1l376t503r677b559],

1	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	nn	2	SENT_5	[p1l78t612r111b645],
2	Mobascher	NNP	PERSON	Mobascher	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l130t600r393b651],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l130t600r393b651],
4	”	CD	NUMBER	”	num	6	SENT_5	[p1l130t600r393b651],
5	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	6	SENT_5	[p1l412t612r446b645],
6	Rujescu	NNP	PERSON	Rujescu	appos	2	SENT_5	[p1l465t600r674b656],
7	,3	CD	NUMBER	,3	num	11	SENT_5	[p1l465t600r674b656],
8	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	11	SENT_5	[p1l465t600r674b656],
9	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	11	SENT_5	[p1l465t600r674b656],
10	K.	NNP	O	K.	nn	11	SENT_5	[p1l692t612r724b645],
11	Mittelstral3	NNP	O	Mittelstral3	dep	6	SENT_5	[p1l744t600r983b651],
12	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	num	13	SENT_5	[p1l744t600r983b651],
13	I.	NN	PERSON	i.	amod	6	SENT_5	[p1l1002t612r1021b645],
14	Gieg	NNP	PERSON	Gieg	nn	15	SENT_5	[p1l1040t600r1251b656],
15	|	NNP	O	|	dep	13	SENT_5	[p1l1040t600r1251b656],
16	ing	VBG	O	ing	dep	15	SENT_5	[p1l1040t600r1251b656],
17	,3	CD	NUMBER	,3	num	18	SENT_5	[p1l1040t600r1251b656],
18	’	CD	NUMBER	’	nsubj	21	SENT_5	[p1l1040t600r1251b656],
19	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	21	SENT_5	[p1l1040t600r1251b656],
20	c.	NN	O	c.	nn	21	SENT_5	[p1l1268t612r1299b645],
21	Lamina	NNP	PERSON	Lamina	xcomp	16	SENT_5	[p1l1318t600r1515b651],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1318t600r1515b651],
23	“	NNP	O	“	nn	25	SENT_5	[p1l1318t600r1515b651],
24	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	25	SENT_5	[p1l1534t612r1567b645],
25	Nitz	NNP	PERSON	Nitz	appos	21	SENT_5	[p1l1586t600r1689b651],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1586t600r1689b651],
27	‘	NNP	O	‘	nn	29	SENT_5	[p1l1586t600r1689b651],
28	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	29	SENT_5	[p1l1708t612r1744b645],
29	Brenner	NNP	PERSON	Brenner	appos	21	SENT_5	[p1l1763t600r1942b651],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1763t600r1942b651],
31	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	32	SENT_5	[p1l1763t600r1942b651],
32	c.	NN	O	c.	appos	21	SENT_5	[p1l81t666r113b699],
33	Fehr	NNP	PERSON	Fehr	nn	36	SENT_5	[p1l132t654r243b705],
34	,8	CD	NUMBER	,8	num	36	SENT_5	[p1l132t654r243b705],
35	L.P.	NNP	O	L.P.	nn	36	SENT_5	[p1l262t666r327b699],
36	Breitnng	NNP	O	Breitnng	dep	32	SENT_5	[p1l347t654r536b710],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l347t654r536b710],
38	’	NNP	O	’	nn	42	SENT_5	[p1l347t654r536b710],
39	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	42	SENT_5	[p1l553t666r583b699],
40	Gal	NNP	O	Gal	nn	42	SENT_5	[p1l602t654r778b705],
41	|	NNP	O	|	nn	42	SENT_5	[p1l602t654r778b705],
42	inat	NN	O	inat	appos	21	SENT_5	[p1l602t654r778b705],
43	,9	CD	NUMBER	,9	num	45	SENT_5	[p1l602t654r778b705],
44	n.	NN	O	n.	nn	45	SENT_5	[p1l798t666r831b699],
45	Rothenbacher	NNP	PERSON	Rothenbacher	dep	42	SENT_5	[p1l850t654r1146b705],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l850t654r1146b705],
47	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l850t654r1146b705],

1	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	nn	2	SENT_6	[p1l1165t666r1195b699],
2	Raum	NNP	PERSON	Raum	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1215t654r1351b705],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1215t654r1351b705],
4	’	NNP	O	’	nn	6	SENT_6	[p1l1215t654r1351b705],
5	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	6	SENT_6	[p1l1370t666r1405b699],
6	Muller	NNP	PERSON	Muller	appos	2	SENT_6	[p1l1424t654r1568b705],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1424t654r1568b705],
8	’	NNP	O	’	nn	10	SENT_6	[p1l1424t654r1568b705],
9	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	10	SENT_6	[p1l1583t666r1616b699],
10	Ruppert	NNP	PERSON	Ruppert	appos	2	SENT_6	[p1l1635t654r1833b710],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1635t654r1833b710],
12	”	CD	NUMBER	”	appos	2	SENT_6	[p1l1635t654r1833b710],
13	A.M.	NNP	O	A.M.	nn	14	SENT_6	[p1l78t720r154b753],
14	Hartmann	NNP	PERSON	Hartmann	dep	12	SENT_6	[p1l174t708r422b759],
15	,3	CD	NUMBER	,3	number	16	SENT_6	[p1l174t708r422b759],
16	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	2	SENT_6	[p1l174t708r422b759],
17	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	24	SENT_6	[p1l174t708r422b759],
18	H.J.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	H.J.	nn	24	SENT_6	[p1l439t720r508b753],
19	M6	NNP	O	M6	nn	24	SENT_6	[p1l527t709r671b759],
20	|	NN	O	|	nn	24	SENT_6	[p1l527t709r671b759],
21	ler	NN	O	ler	nn	24	SENT_6	[p1l527t709r671b759],
22	,4	CD	NUMBER	,4	num	24	SENT_6	[p1l527t709r671b759],
23	A.	NN	O	a.	nn	24	SENT_6	[p1l685t720r718b753],
24	car	NN	O	car	dep	16	SENT_6	[p1l736t709r844b759],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l736t709r844b759],
26	“	CD	NUMBER	“	num	27	SENT_6	[p1l736t709r844b759],
27	ch	NN	O	ch	appos	2	SENT_6	[p1l862t720r918b753],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l862t720r918b753],

1	Gieger	NNP	PERSON	Gieger	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l936t709r1086b764],
2	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l936t709r1086b764],
3	H.E.	NNP	PERSON	H.E.	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1105t720r1176b753],
4	Wichmann	NNP	PERSON	Wichmann	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1192t709r1420b759],
5	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1192t709r1420b759],
6	T.	NNP	O	T.	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1437t720r1466b753],
7	|	NNP	O	|	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1485t709r1582b764],
8	l	NN	O	l	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1485t709r1582b764],
9	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1485t709r1582b764],
10	ig	NN	O	ig	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1485t709r1582b764],
11	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1485t709r1582b764],
12	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l82t774r116b807],
13	Dahmen	NNP	PERSON	Dahmen	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l136t762r320b813],
14	,8	CD	NUMBER	,8	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l136t762r320b813],
15	and	CC	O	and	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l338t775r405b807],
16	G.	NNP	O	G.	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l424t774r458b807],
17	Winterer1	NNP	O	Winterer1	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l474t762r703b807],
18	’	NN	O	’	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l474t762r703b807],
19	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l474t762r703b807],
20	*	CD	NUMBER	*	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l474t762r703b807],
21	1Department	NN	O	1department	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l82t829r255b869],
22	of	IN	O	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l268t837r294b861],
23	Psychiatry	NNP	O	Psychiatry	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l305t837r458b869],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l305t837r458b869],
25	Neuropsychiatric	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Neuropsychiatric	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l472t837r704b869],
26	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l717t838r842b861],
27	Laboratory	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Laboratory	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l856t838r1012b869],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l856t838r1012b869],
29	Heinrich-Heine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heinrich-Heine	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1026t837r1224b861],
30	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1238t837r1381b869],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1238t837r1381b869],
32	Duesseldorf	NNP	LOCATION	Duesseldorf	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1395t837r1563b865],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1395t837r1563b865],
34	Germany	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Germany	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1577t837r1697b869],
35	Zlnstitute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Zlnstitute	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l80t883r208b915],
36	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l222t891r248b915],
37	Neurosciences	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Neurosciences	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l260t891r458b915],
38	and	CC	O	and	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l471t892r519b915],
39	Biophysics	NNP	O	Biophysics	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l534t891r688b923],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l534t891r688b923],
41	Helmholtz	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Helmholtz	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l703t892r838b915],
42	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l852t892r976b915],
43	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l990t891r1084b919],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l990t891r1084b919],
45	Juelich	NNP	PERSON	Juelich	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1096t891r1200b919],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1096t891r1200b919],
47	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1214t891r1334b923],
48	3Department	NNP	O	3Department	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l80t937r255b977],
49	of	IN	O	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l268t945r294b969],
50	Psychiatry	NNP	O	Psychiatry	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l305t945r458b977],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l305t945r458b977],
52	Division	NNP	O	Division	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l472t945r575b969],
53	of	IN	O	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l589t945r616b969],
54	Molecular	JJ	O	molecular	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l627t946r757b969],
55	and	CC	O	and	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l770t946r817b969],
56	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l832t945r927b969],
57	Neurobiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Neurobiology	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l941t945r1126b977],
58	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l941t945r1126b977],
59	Ludwig-Maximilians-University	NNP	PERSON	Ludwig-Maximilians-University	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1140t945r1564b977],
60	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1140t945r1564b977],
61	Munich	NNP	LOCATION	Munich	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1578t945r1681b973],
62	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1578t945r1681b973],
63	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1695t945r1815b977],
64	‘	NNP	O	‘	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l79t991r255b1031],
65	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l79t991r255b1031],
66	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l268t1000r294b1023],
67	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l305t1000r458b1031],
68	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l305t1000r458b1031],
69	Ludwig-Maximilians-University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ludwig-Maximilians-University	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l472t1000r895b1031],
70	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l472t1000r895b1031],
71	Munich	NNP	LOCATION	Munich	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l910t1000r1012b1028],
72	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l910t1000r1012b1028],
73	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1026t999r1146b1031],
74	5He	NNP	O	5He	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l81t1045r231b1077],
75	|	NN	O	|	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l81t1045r231b1077],
76	mho	NN	O	mho	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l81t1045r231b1077],
77	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l81t1045r231b1077],
78	tz	NN	O	tz	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l81t1045r231b1077],
79	Zentrum	NNP	PERSON	Zentrum	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l243t1054r355b1077],
80	Miinchen	NNP	PERSON	Miinchen	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l370t1052r499b1082],
81	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l370t1052r499b1082],
82	German	NNP	ORGANIZATION	German	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l513t1053r616b1077],
83	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l630t1054r754b1077],
84	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l768t1053r856b1077],
85	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l867t1053r903b1077],
86	Environmental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Environmental	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l917t1053r1112b1077],
87	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1127t1054r1213b1077],
88	[	NNP	O	[	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1229t1050r1341b1083],
89	GmbH	NN	O	gmbh	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1229t1050r1341b1083],
90	]	NN	O	]	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1229t1050r1341b1083],
91	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1229t1050r1341b1083],
92	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1355t1053r1468b1077],
93	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1482t1053r1508b1077],
94	Epidemiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Epidemiology	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1519t1053r1708b1085],
95	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1519t1053r1708b1085],
96	Neuherberg	NNP	LOCATION	Neuherberg	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1722t1054r1886b1085],
97	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1722t1054r1886b1085],
98	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1900t1053r2020b1085],
99	6Department	NNP	O	6Department	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l80t1099r255b1139],
100	of	IN	O	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l268t1108r294b1131],
101	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l305t1108r407b1131],
102	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l421t1108r544b1136],
103	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l421t1108r544b1136],
104	Molecular	JJ	O	molecular	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l559t1108r689b1131],
105	and	CC	O	and	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l701t1108r749b1131],
106	Clinical	JJ	O	clinical	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l764t1108r859b1131],
107	Pharmacology	NN	O	pharmacology	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l873t1108r1074b1139],
108	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l873t1108r1074b1139],
109	Division	NN	O	division	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1088t1108r1191b1131],
110	of	IN	O	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1205t1108r1232b1131],
111	Genetic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	genetic	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1243t1108r1343b1131],
112	Epidemiology	NN	ORGANIZATION	epidemiology	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1357t1108r1545b1140],
113	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1357t1108r1545b1140],
114	Innsbruck	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Innsbruck	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l81t1151r215b1175],
115	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l228t1151r329b1175],
116	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l343t1151r487b1183],
117	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l343t1151r487b1183],
118	Innsbruck	NNP	LOCATION	Innsbruck	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l501t1151r642b1179],
119	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l501t1151r642b1179],
120	Austria	NNP	LOCATION	Austria	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l653t1151r748b1175],
121	7Division	NNP	O	7Division	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l81t1197r198b1229],
122	of	IN	O	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l212t1205r239b1229],
123	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l249t1205r344b1229],
124	Epidemiology	NN	ORGANIZATION	epidemiology	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l359t1205r539b1237],
125	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l553t1205r601b1229],
126	Aging	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Aging	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l614t1205r688b1237],
127	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l701t1205r833b1233],
128	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l701t1205r833b1233],
129	German	NNP	O	German	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l847t1205r950b1229],
130	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l964t1205r1056b1229],
131	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1069t1205r1194b1229],
132	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1208t1205r1302b1233],
133	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1208t1205r1302b1233],
134	Heidelberg	NNP	LOCATION	Heidelberg	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1316t1205r1467b1237],
135	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1316t1205r1467b1237],
136	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1481t1205r1601b1237],
137	ﬂDepartment	NNP	O	ﬂDepartment	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l80t1251r255b1290],
138	of	IN	O	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l268t1259r294b1283],
139	Psychiatry	NNP	O	Psychiatry	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l305t1259r458b1291],
140	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l305t1259r458b1291],
141	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l471t1259r606b1291],
142	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l620t1259r647b1283],
143	Mainz	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mainz	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l658t1259r743b1287],
144	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l658t1259r743b1287],
145	Mainz	NNP	LOCATION	Mainz	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l757t1259r843b1287],
146	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l757t1259r843b1287],
147	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l857t1259r977b1291],
148	9Department	NN	O	9department	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l80t1305r255b1345],
149	of	IN	O	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l268t1313r294b1337],
150	Psychiatry	NNP	O	Psychiatry	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l305t1313r458b1345],
151	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l305t1313r458b1345],
152	Charité	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Charité	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l471t1310r566b1337],
153	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l580t1313r715b1345],
154	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l730t1313r848b1337],
155	Berlin	NNP	LOCATION	Berlin	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l862t1313r946b1341],
156	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l862t1313r946b1341],
157	Campus	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Campus	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l960t1313r1067b1345],
158	Mitte	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mitte	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1081t1313r1155b1341],
159	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1081t1313r1155b1341],
160	Berlin	NNP	LOCATION	Berlin	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1169t1313r1252b1341],
161	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1169t1313r1252b1341],
162	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1266t1313r1386b1345],
163	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l82t1359r225b1391],
164	°	CD	ORGANIZATION	°	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l82t1359r225b1391],
165	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l82t1359r225b1391],
166	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l239t1367r362b1391],
167	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l377t1367r463b1391],
168	GmbH	NN	ORGANIZATION	gmbh	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l477t1367r562b1395],
169	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l477t1367r562b1395],
170	Munich	NNP	LOCATION	Munich	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l577t1367r680b1395],
171	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l577t1367r680b1395],
172	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l693t1367r814b1399],
173	“	NNP	O	“	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l82t1413r223b1445],
174	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l82t1413r223b1445],
175	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l235t1421r271b1445],
176	Human	JJ	ORGANIZATION	human	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l284t1421r378b1445],
177	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l392t1421r516b1449],
178	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l392t1421r516b1449],
179	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l530t1421r665b1453],
180	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l678t1421r705b1445],
181	Hamburg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hamburg	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l716t1421r839b1453],
182	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l851t1421r953b1445],
183	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l967t1421r1054b1445],
184	Eppendorf	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Eppendorf	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1067t1421r1212b1453],
185	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1067t1421r1212b1453],
186	Hamburg	NNP	LOCATION	Hamburg	dep	188	SENT_7	[p1l1226t1421r1355b1453],
187	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1226t1421r1355b1453],
188	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1369t1421r1489b1453],

1	Received	VBN	O	receive	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l81t1495r188b1517],
2	P	NN	O	p	dobj	1	SENT_8	[p1l201t1496r214b1517],
3	January	NNP	DATE	January	tmod	2	SENT_8	[p1l225t1496r324b1524],
4	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	3	SENT_8	[p1l337t1495r407b1521],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l337t1495r407b1521],
6	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	amod	7	SENT_8	[p1l418t1496r529b1524],
7	15	CD	DATE	15	dep	2	SENT_8	[p1l543t1496r571b1517],
8	June	NNP	DATE	June	tmod	1	SENT_8	[p1l582t1496r640b1517],
9	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	8	SENT_8	[p1l653t1495r715b1517],

1	Genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	2	SENT_9	[p1l80t1603r194b1629],
2	factors	NNS	O	factor	nsubj	3	SENT_9	[p1l212t1602r313b1629],
3	contribute	VBP	O	contribute	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l333t1603r490b1629],
4	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l508t1607r538b1629],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_9	[p1l557t1603r604b1629],
6	overall	JJ	O	overall	amod	7	SENT_9	[p1l623t1603r724b1629],
7	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_to	3	SENT_9	[p1l743t1602r800b1629],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l818t1602r850b1629],
9	developing	VBG	O	develop	amod	11	SENT_9	[p1l866t1602r1030b1637],
10	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	11	SENT_9	[p1l79t1646r202b1672],
11	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_of	7	SENT_9	[p1l220t1646r370b1676],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l220t1646r370b1676],
13	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	17	SENT_9	[p1l388t1646r479b1672],
14	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	17	SENT_9	[p1l496t1647r520b1672],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_9	[p1l537t1646r584b1672],
16	major	JJ	O	major	amod	17	SENT_9	[p1l602t1646r691b1680],
17	cause	NN	O	cause	rcmod	11	SENT_9	[p1l709t1655r789b1672],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l807t1646r839b1672],
19	preventable	JJ	O	preventable	amod	20	SENT_9	[p1l853t1646r1029b1680],
20	deaths	NNS	O	death	prep_of	17	SENT_9	[p1l80t1689r176b1715],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l195t1690r224b1715],
22	western	JJ	O	western	amod	23	SENT_9	[p1l242t1693r359b1715],
23	countries	NNS	O	country	prep_in	20	SENT_9	[p1l378t1690r525b1715],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l378t1690r525b1715],

1	However	RB	O	however	advmod	11	SENT_10	[p1l545t1691r686b1719],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l545t1691r686b1719],
3	knowledge	NN	O	knowledge	nsubj	11	SENT_10	[p1l705t1689r866b1723],
4	regarding	VBG	O	regard	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l885t1689r1030b1723],
5	speciﬁc	NN	O	speciﬁc	nn	6	SENT_10	[p1l80t1732r189b1766],
6	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	prep_regarding	3	SENT_10	[p1l208t1732r443b1767],
7	inﬂuencing	VBG	O	inﬂuencing	partmod	6	SENT_10	[p1l462t1732r632b1767],
8	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	9	SENT_10	[p1l651t1732r780b1767],
9	phenotypes	NNS	O	phenotype	dobj	7	SENT_10	[p1l797t1732r969b1767],
10	remains	VBZ	O	remain	cop	11	SENT_10	[p1l988t1741r1029b1758, p1l79t1776r170b1802],
11	scarce	JJ	O	scarce	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l183t1785r281b1802],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l183t1785r281b1802],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l295t1777r328b1801],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_11	[p1l340t1775r387b1802],
3	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	4	SENT_11	[p1l400t1780r511b1809],
4	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	6	SENT_11	[p1l525t1775r607b1810],
5	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	6	SENT_11	[p1l618t1785r658b1802],
6	provide	VBP	O	provide	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l671t1775r786b1809],
7	evidence	NN	O	evidence	dobj	6	SENT_11	[p1l800t1775r928b1802],
8	that	IN	O	that	complm	36	SENT_11	[p1l941t1775r1001b1802],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	16	SENT_11	[p1l1014t1785r1030b1802],
10	common	JJ	O	common	amod	16	SENT_11	[p1l80t1828r212b1845],
11	single	JJ	O	single	amod	16	SENT_11	[p1l226t1818r312b1853],
12	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	16	SENT_11	[p1l326t1819r483b1845],
13	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	nn	16	SENT_11	[p1l496t1819r718b1853],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_11	[p1l734t1819r820b1850],
15	SNP	NN	O	snp	nn	16	SENT_11	[p1l734t1819r820b1850],
16	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	36	SENT_11	[p1l734t1819r820b1850],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l835t1819r865b1845],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_11	[p1l878t1819r925b1845],
19	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	20	SENT_11	[p1l940t1817r963b1845],
20	’	NN	O	’	prep_in	16	SENT_11	[p1l940t1817r963b1845],
21	untranslated	JJ	O	untranslated	amod	22	SENT_11	[p1l978t1828r1029b1845, p1l79t1862r230b1888],
22	region	NN	O	region	dep	20	SENT_11	[p1l238t1863r333b1896],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l342t1862r374b1888],
24	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	prep_of	22	SENT_11	[p1l381t1863r509b1892],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l381t1863r509b1892],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_11	[p1l517t1862r564b1888],
27	gene	NN	O	gene	appos	22	SENT_11	[p1l572t1871r640b1896],
28	coding	VBG	O	code	partmod	27	SENT_11	[p1l649t1862r750b1896],
29	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l757t1862r801b1888],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_11	[p1l809t1862r856b1888],
31	muscarinic	JJ	O	muscarinic	amod	33	SENT_11	[p1l863t1863r1030b1888],
32	acetylcholine	NN	O	acetylcholine	nn	33	SENT_11	[p1l80t1905r276b1940],
33	receptor	NN	O	receptor	prep_for	28	SENT_11	[p1l290t1910r415b1939],
34	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	20	SENT_11	[p1l429t1908r445b1931],
35	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	36	SENT_11	[p1l459t1906r482b1931],
36	associated	VBN	O	associate	ccomp	6	SENT_11	[p1l496t1905r649b1931],
37	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l661t1905r728b1931],
38	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	39	SENT_11	[p1l742t1906r864b1931],
39	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_with	36	SENT_11	[p1l879t1905r1028b1931],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l879t1905r1028b1931],

1	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	nsubjpass	3	SENT_12	[p1l82t1950r202b1975],
2	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_12	[p1l211t1958r266b1975],
3	deﬁned	VBN	O	deﬁned	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l278t1948r388b1975],
4	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l398t1958r427b1975],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_12	[p1l439t1958r454b1975],
6	candidate	NN	O	candidate	nn	7	SENT_12	[p1l465t1948r610b1975],
7	gene	NN	O	gene	prep_as	3	SENT_12	[p1l621t1958r689b1983],
8	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l699t1948r744b1975],
9	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	10	SENT_12	[p1l754t1949r876b1975],
10	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_for	7	SENT_12	[p1l888t1948r1030b1975],
11	based	VBN	O	base	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l79t1991r164b2018],
12	on	IN	O	on	prepc_based_on	3	SENT_12	[p1l174t2001r212b2018],
13	previous	JJ	O	previous	amod	14	SENT_12	[p1l220t1992r349b2025],
14	evidence	NN	O	evidence	pobj	3	SENT_12	[p1l360t1991r488b2018],
15	that	IN	O	that	nsubj	16	SENT_12	[p1l497t1991r557b2018],
16	linked	VBN	O	link	rcmod	14	SENT_12	[p1l566t1991r661b2018],
17	variations	NNS	O	variation	dobj	16	SENT_12	[p1l669t1992r820b2018],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l829t1992r859b2017],
19	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	prep_in	16	SENT_12	[p1l871t1993r992b2018],
20	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l999t1996r1029b2018],
21	alcohol	NN	O	alcohol	nn	24	SENT_12	[p1l80t2035r188b2061],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l195t2035r251b2061],
23	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	24	SENT_12	[p1l257t2035r327b2069],
24	dependence	NN	O	dependence	prep_to	16	SENT_12	[p1l334t2035r518b2069],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l334t2035r518b2069],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_13	[p1l525t2036r549b2061],
2	total	NN	O	total	nsubjpass	14	SENT_13	[p1l555t2035r623b2061],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l630t2035r662b2061],
4	more	JJR	O	more	mwe	5	SENT_13	[p1l666t2044r744b2061],
5	than	IN	O	than	quantmod	6	SENT_13	[p1l750t2035r818b2061],
6	5,500	CD	NUMBER	5,500	num	7	SENT_13	[p1l825t2037r903b2065],
7	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_of	2	SENT_13	[p1l910t2035r1029b2069],
8	representative	JJ	O	representative	amod	7	SENT_13	[p1l80t2079r292b2112],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l306t2078r338b2104],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_13	[p1l348t2078r395b2104],
11	German	JJ	MISC	german	amod	12	SENT_13	[p1l409t2079r530b2104],
12	population	NN	O	population	prep_of	8	SENT_13	[p1l543t2078r708b2112],
13	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	14	SENT_13	[p1l721t2087r792b2104],
14	genotyped	VBN	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l806t2078r961b2113],
15	and	CC	O	and	advmod	14	SENT_13	[p1l975t2078r1030b2104],

1	How	WRB	O	how	advmod	3	SENT_14	[p1l1227t1612r1295b1639],
2	to	TO	O	to	aux	3	SENT_14	[p1l1308t1615r1339b1639],
3	Cite	VB	O	cite	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1356t1611r1416b1639],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	8	SENT_14	[p1l1430t1611r1492b1639],
5	Article	NN	O	article	dep	8	SENT_14	[p1l1506t1611r1618b1639],
6	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1506t1611r1618b1639],
7	Mobascher	NNP	O	Mobascher	nn	8	SENT_14	[p1l1225t1656r1385b1683],
8	A	NNP	O	A	dobj	3	SENT_14	[p1l1395t1658r1426b1687],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1395t1658r1426b1687],
10	Rujescu	NNP	PERSON	Rujescu	nn	11	SENT_14	[p1l1438t1657r1550b1691],
11	D	NNP	PERSON	D	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1562t1658r1594b1687],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1562t1658r1594b1687],
13	Mittelstraﬁ	NNP	PERSON	Mittelstraﬁ	nn	14	SENT_14	[p1l1606t1656r1766b1683],
14	K	NNP	PERSON	K	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1778t1658r1808b1687],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1778t1658r1808b1687],
16	Giegling	NNP	O	Giegling	nn	20	SENT_14	[p1l1226t1700r1345b1734],
17	I	PRP	O	I	dep	20	SENT_14	[p1l1354t1702r1372b1730],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1354t1702r1372b1730],
19	Lamina	NNP	PERSON	Lamina	dep	20	SENT_14	[p1l1381t1701r1489b1726],
20	C	NNP	O	C	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1498t1701r1527b1730],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1498t1701r1527b1730],
22	Nitz	NNP	PERSON	Nitz	nn	23	SENT_14	[p1l1536t1701r1598b1726],
23	B	NNP	O	B	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1606t1702r1633b1730],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1606t1702r1633b1730],
25	Brenner	NNP	PERSON	Brenner	nn	26	SENT_14	[p1l1642t1702r1757b1726],
26	H	NNP	O	H	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1765t1702r1799b1730],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1765t1702r1799b1730],
28	Fehr	NNP	PERSON	Fehr	nn	29	SENT_14	[p1l1808t1700r1873b1726],
29	C	NNP	O	C	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1226t1744r1255b1773],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1226t1744r1255b1773],
31	Breitling	NNP	O	Breitling	nn	32	SENT_14	[p1l1268t1743r1392b1778],
32	LP	NN	O	lp	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1403t1745r1449b1773],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1403t1745r1449b1773],
34	Gallinat	NNP	O	Gallinat	nn	35	SENT_14	[p1l1462t1743r1575b1769],
35	I	NNP	O	I	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1587t1745r1605b1774],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1587t1745r1605b1774],
37	Rothenbacher	NNP	PERSON	Rothenbacher	nn	38	SENT_14	[p1l1618t1743r1819b1769],
38	D	NNP	O	D	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1831t1745r1863b1773],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1831t1745r1863b1773],
40	Raum	NNP	PERSON	Raum	nn	41	SENT_14	[p1l1225t1788r1312b1812],
41	E	NNP	O	E	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1323t1788r1349b1817],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1323t1788r1349b1817],
43	Miiller	NNP	PERSON	Miiller	nn	44	SENT_14	[p1l1361t1786r1459b1812],
44	H	NNP	PERSON	H	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1470t1788r1504b1817],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1470t1788r1504b1817],
46	Ruppert	NNP	PERSON	Ruppert	nn	47	SENT_14	[p1l1517t1788r1635b1820],
47	A	NNP	O	A	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1645t1788r1676b1817],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1645t1788r1676b1817],
49	Hartmann	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hartmann	nn	50	SENT_14	[p1l1689t1788r1840b1812],
50	AM	NNP	ORGANIZATION	AM	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1224t1831r1287b1860],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1224t1831r1287b1860],
52	Moller	NNP	PERSON	Moller	nn	53	SENT_14	[p1l1296t1830r1393b1856],
53	HI	NNP	O	HI	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1401t1831r1447b1860],
54	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1401t1831r1447b1860],
55	Gal	NNP	O	Gal	nn	56	SENT_14	[p1l1456t1829r1505b1856],
56	A	NNP	O	A	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1512t1831r1542b1860],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1512t1831r1542b1860],
58	Gieger	NNP	PERSON	Gieger	nn	59	SENT_14	[p1l1552t1830r1645b1864],
59	Ch	NNP	O	Ch	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1653t1830r1702b1860],
60	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1653t1830r1702b1860],
61	Wichmann	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wichmann	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1710t1829r1872b1856],
62	HE	PRP	ORGANIZATION	he	dep	61	SENT_14	[p1l1225t1875r1279b1903],
63	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1225t1875r1279b1903],
64	Illig	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Illig	nn	65	SENT_14	[p1l1292t1873r1347b1907],
65	T	NN	ORGANIZATION	t	appos	62	SENT_14	[p1l1358t1874r1386b1903],
66	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1358t1874r1386b1903],
67	Dahmen	NNP	PERSON	Dahmen	nn	71	SENT_14	[p1l1399t1873r1523b1899],
68	N	NNP	PERSON	N	nn	71	SENT_14	[p1l1534t1875r1568b1903],
69	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1534t1875r1568b1903],
70	Winterer	NNP	O	Winterer	appos	71	SENT_14	[p1l1579t1874r1710b1899],
71	G.	NNP	O	G.	appos	8	SENT_14	[p1l1722t1874r1752b1899],
72	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	71	SENT_14	[p1l1765t1875r1840b1899],
73	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1765t1875r1840b1899],

1	Association	NNP	O	Association	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1224t1917r1392b1942],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1403t1916r1435b1942],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_15	[p1l1443t1925r1457b1942],
4	Variant	JJ	O	variant	amod	17	SENT_15	[p1l1467t1917r1577b1942],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1588t1917r1616b1942],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_15	[p1l1627t1916r1671b1942],
7	Muscarinic	NNP	O	Muscarinic	nn	9	SENT_15	[p1l1683t1917r1844b1942],
8	Acetylcholine	NNP	O	Acetylcholine	nn	9	SENT_15	[p1l1224t1959r1420b1994],
9	Receptor	NN	O	receptor	prep_in	4	SENT_15	[p1l1432t1961r1561b1993],
10	2	CD	NUMBER	2	tmod	4	SENT_15	[p1l1572t1962r1587b1985],
11	Gene	NNP	O	Gene	nn	17	SENT_15	[p1l1600t1960r1673b1985],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_15	[p1l1686t1959r1828b1991],
13	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	dep	17	SENT_15	[p1l1686t1959r1828b1991],
14	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	13	SENT_15	[p1l1686t1959r1828b1991],
15	With	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1224t2002r1298b2029],
16	Nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	prep_with	13	SENT_15	[p1l1310t2003r1434b2029],
17	Addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_of	1	SENT_15	[p1l1445t2002r1598b2029],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1445t2002r1598b2029],

1	Am	VBP	O	be	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1224t2058r1277b2082],
2	I	PRP	O	I	nsubj	3	SENT_16	[p1l1288t2058r1299b2087],
3	Med	VBD	O	med	ccomp	1	SENT_16	[p1l1310t2056r1376b2083],
4	Genet	NNP	O	Genet	nn	9	SENT_16	[p1l1388t2058r1472b2083],
5	Part	NNP	O	Part	nn	9	SENT_16	[p1l1483t2058r1543b2083],
6	B	NNP	O	B	nn	9	SENT_16	[p1l1554t2058r1573b2082],
7	153B	NN	O	153b	nn	9	SENT_16	[p1l1588t2058r1796b2083],
8	:684	CD	NUMBER	:684	num	9	SENT_16	[p1l1588t2058r1796b2083],
9	—	NN	O	—	dobj	3	SENT_16	[p1l1588t2058r1796b2083],
10	690	CD	NUMBER	690	dep	9	SENT_16	[p1l1588t2058r1796b2083],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1588t2058r1796b2083],

1	Additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	3	SENT_17	[p1l79t2270r218b2294],
2	Supporting	VBG	O	support	amod	3	SENT_17	[p1l229t2271r375b2302],
3	Information	NN	O	information	nsubjpass	6	SENT_17	[p1l385t2270r545b2294],
4	may	MD	O	may	aux	6	SENT_17	[p1l555t2279r610b2302],
5	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_17	[p1l619t2271r648b2294],
6	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l659t2270r736b2294],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l746t2271r771b2294],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_17	[p1l781t2271r821b2294],
9	online	JJ	O	online	amod	10	SENT_17	[p1l832t2271r913b2294],
10	version	NN	O	version	prep_in	6	SENT_17	[p1l922t2271r1017b2294],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1027t2270r1056b2294],
12	this	DT	O	this	det	13	SENT_17	[p1l1062t2271r1109b2294],
13	article	NN	O	article	prep_of	10	SENT_17	[p1l1119t2270r1204b2294],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1119t2270r1204b2294],

1	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l80t2311r155b2334],
2	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l161t2318r269b2341],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l161t2318r269b2341],
4	German	NNP	O	German	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l276t2311r381b2334],
5	Federal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Federal	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l387t2310r480b2334],
6	Ministry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ministry	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l485t2311r598b2341],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l602t2310r631b2334],
8	Education	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Education	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l633t2310r765b2334],
9	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l771t2310r819b2334],
10	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l824t2310r938b2334],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l946t2310r1057b2339],
12	BMBF	NN	O	bmbf	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l946t2310r1057b2339],
13	)	NN	O	)	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l946t2310r1057b2339],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l946t2310r1057b2339],
15	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1064t2311r1139b2334],
16	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1144t2318r1253b2341],
17	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1144t2318r1253b2341],
18	State	NN	O	state	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1260t2311r1322b2334],
19	of	IN	O	of	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1328t2310r1356b2334],
20	Bavaria	NNP	LOCATION	Bavaria	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1358t2311r1454b2334],
21	and	CC	O	and	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1460t2310r1507b2334],
22	the	DT	O	the	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1513t2310r1552b2334],
23	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1557t2310r1671b2334],
24	Genome	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genome	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1676t2311r1785b2334],
25	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1791t2310r1905b2334],
26	Network	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Network	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1910t2310r2025b2334],
27	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l81t2350r197b2378],
28	NGFN	NNP	O	NGFN	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l81t2350r197b2378],
29	)	NN	O	)	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l81t2350r197b2378],
30	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l81t2350r197b2378],
31	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l215t2351r290b2374],
32	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l307t2358r416b2381],
33	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l307t2358r416b2381],
34	BMBF	NN	O	bmbf	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l434t2352r523b2377],
35	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l434t2352r523b2377],
36	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l542t2351r616b2374],
37	number	NN	O	number	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l633t2350r742b2374],
38	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l633t2350r742b2374],
39	01EB0113	NN	O	01eb0113	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l761t2352r896b2377],
40	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l761t2352r896b2377],
41	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l915t2351r990b2374],
42	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1007t2358r1115b2381],
43	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1007t2358r1115b2381],
44	DFG	NN	O	dfg	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1134t2351r1202b2377],
45	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1134t2351r1202b2377],
46	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1221t2351r1296b2374],
47	number	NN	O	number	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1313t2350r1421b2374],
48	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1313t2350r1421b2374],
49	Wi2997/1	NN	O	wi2997/1	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1439t2351r1601b2377],
50	-1	CD	NUMBER	-1	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1439t2351r1601b2377],
51	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1439t2351r1601b2377],
52	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1619t2351r1694b2374],
53	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1711t2358r1819b2381],
54	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1711t2358r1819b2381],
55	Project	NNP	O	Project	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1838t2351r1929b2381],
56	Berlin	NNP	O	Berlin	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1946t2350r2024b2374],
57	Neuroimaging	NNP	O	Neuroimaging	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l79t2390r268b2421],
58	Center	NNP	O	Center	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l284t2391r377b2417],
59	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l284t2391r377b2417],
60	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l394t2391r469b2413],
61	number	NN	O	number	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l484t2389r593b2413],
62	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l484t2389r593b2413],
63	01G00208	NN	O	01g00208	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l610t2391r747b2417],
64	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l610t2391r747b2417],
65	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l764t2391r839b2413],
66	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l855t2398r963b2420],
67	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l855t2398r963b2420],
68	Baden	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Baden	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l980t2389r1060b2413],
69	Wiirttemberg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wiirttemberg	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1075t2389r1252b2421],
70	Ministry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ministry	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1267t2390r1380b2421],
71	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1395t2389r1423b2413],
72	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1435t2389r1556b2417],
73	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1435t2389r1556b2417],
74	Science	NNP	O	Science	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1573t2390r1667b2413],
75	and	CC	O	and	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1683t2389r1731b2413],
76	Arts	NNS	O	art	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1745t2391r1807b2417],
77	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1745t2391r1807b2417],
78	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1823t2391r1898b2413],
79	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1914t2398r2022b2420],
80	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1914t2398r2022b2420],
81	Helmholtz	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Helmholtz	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l80t2429r218b2453],
82	Zentrum	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Zentrum	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l227t2430r343b2453],
83	Miinchen	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Miinchen	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l353t2429r478b2453],
84	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l490t2429r593b2458],
85	KORA	NNP	O	KORA	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l490t2429r593b2458],
86	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l490t2429r593b2458],
87	ESTHER	NNP	PERSON	ESTHER	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l604t2429r738b2458],
88	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l604t2429r738b2458],
89	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l604t2429r738b2458],
90	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l750t2430r825b2453],
91	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l835t2437r943b2460],
92	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l835t2437r943b2460],
93	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l955t2430r1064b2453],
94	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1075t2429r1189b2453],
95	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1200t2430r1293b2456],
96	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1200t2430r1293b2456],
97	Munich/Germany	NNP	O	Munich/Germany	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1304t2429r1539b2460],
98	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1550t2429r1690b2458],
99	NCOOP	NN	O	ncoop	dep	100	SENT_18	[p1l1550t2429r1690b2458],
100	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1550t2429r1690b2458],
101	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1550t2429r1690b2458],

1	*	NN	O	*	nn	2	SENT_19	[p1l80t2469r306b2500],
2	Correspondence	NN	O	correspondence	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l80t2469r306b2500],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l316t2473r349b2493],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l316t2473r349b2493],
5	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	12	SENT_19	[p1l80t2510r108b2532],
6	Winterer	NNP	PERSON	Winterer	nn	12	SENT_19	[p1l116t2509r240b2536],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l116t2509r240b2536],
8	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	12	SENT_19	[p1l248t2510r323b2536],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l248t2510r323b2536],
10	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	12	SENT_19	[p1l332t2508r412b2536],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l332t2508r412b2536],
12	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	prep_to	2	SENT_19	[p1l420t2510r577b2539],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l585t2508r614b2532],
14	Psychiatry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Psychiatry	prep_of	12	SENT_19	[p1l618t2508r758b2539],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l618t2508r758b2539],
16	Laboratory	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Laboratory	appos	12	SENT_19	[p1l767t2508r911b2539],
17	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l917t2508r946b2532],
18	Neuropsychiatric	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Neuropsychiatric	nn	19	SENT_19	[p1l950t2508r1174b2539],
19	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	prep_of	16	SENT_19	[p1l1182t2508r1303b2536],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1182t2508r1303b2536],
21	Heinrich-Heine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heinrich-Heine	nn	22	SENT_19	[p1l1311t2508r1516b2532],
22	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	12	SENT_19	[p1l1524t2509r1665b2539],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1524t2509r1665b2539],
24	Bergische	NNP	PERSON	Bergische	nn	25	SENT_19	[p1l1674t2508r1796b2539],
25	Landstr	NNP	PERSON	Landstr	appos	22	SENT_19	[p1l1804t2508r1908b2532],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1804t2508r1908b2532],

1	2	CD	NUMBER	2	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1918t2511r1939b2536],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1918t2511r1939b2536],
3	40629	CD	NUMBER	40629	num	6	SENT_20	[p1l1947t2510r2023b2532],
4	Duesseldorf	NNP	LOCATION	Duesseldorf	nn	6	SENT_20	[p1l80t2548r240b2575],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l80t2548r240b2575],
6	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	appos	1	SENT_20	[p1l251t2549r377b2579],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l251t2549r377b2579],

1	E	NN	O	e	nn	3	SENT_21	[p1l389t2548r481b2572],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	3	SENT_21	[p1l389t2548r481b2572],
3	mail	NN	O	mail	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l389t2548r481b2572],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l389t2548r481b2572],
5	georg.winterer@uni—duesseldorﬂde	VB	O	georg.winterer@uni—duesseldorﬂde	dep	3	SENT_21	[p1l493t2548r947b2579],
6	Published	VBN	O	publish	dep	5	SENT_21	[p1l80t2587r207b2611],
7	online	JJ	O	online	amod	9	SENT_21	[p1l218t2588r298b2611],
8	30	CD	NUMBER	30	num	9	SENT_21	[p1l309t2590r338b2611],
9	Iuly	NNP	O	Iuly	dobj	6	SENT_21	[p1l349t2587r400b2619],
10	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	9	SENT_21	[p1l409t2590r469b2611],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l480t2588r505b2611],
12	Wiley	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wiley	nn	15	SENT_21	[p1l515t2587r591b2619],
13	InterScience	NNP	ORGANIZATION	InterScience	nn	15	SENT_21	[p1l601t2588r759b2611],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_21	[p1l771t2587r1156b2619],
15	www.interscience.wiley.com	NNP	O	www.interscience.wiley.com	prep_in	9	SENT_21	[p1l771t2587r1156b2619],
16	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	17	SENT_21	[p1l771t2587r1156b2619],
17	DOI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	DOI	dep	15	SENT_21	[p1l80t2629r137b2651],
18	10.1002	CD	NUMBER	10.1002	num	17	SENT_21	[p1l150t2627r428b2658],
19	/	:	O	/	punct	20	SENT_21	[p1l150t2627r428b2658],
20	ajmg	NN	O	ajmg	dep	15	SENT_21	[p1l150t2627r428b2658],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l150t2627r428b2658],

1	b.	NN	O	b.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l150t2627r428b2658],
2	31011	CD	NUMBER	31011	num	1	SENT_22	[p1l150t2627r428b2658],

1	©	RB	O	©	dep	2	SENT_23	[p1l81t2770r106b2795],
2	2009	CD	DATE	2009	dep	5	SENT_23	[p1l118t2772r187b2795],
3	Wiley-Liss	NNP	O	Wiley-Liss	nn	5	SENT_23	[p1l198t2769r364b2804],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l198t2769r364b2804],
5	Inc.	NNP	O	Inc.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l377t2771r432b2795],
6	684	CD	NUMBER	684	dep	5	SENT_23	[p1l1964t2767r2023b2795],

1	MOBASCHER	NNP	O	MOBASCHER	nn	3	SENT_24	[p1l6t2945r253b2974],
2	ET	NNP	O	ET	nn	3	SENT_24	[p1l266t2945r312b2974],
3	AL.	NNP	O	AL.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l324t2945r381b2974],
4	685	CD	NUMBER	685	dep	3	SENT_24	[p1l6t2995r65b3023],

1	assessed	VBN	O	assess	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l9t80r284b139],
2	regarding	VBG	O	regard	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l313t80r641b157],
3	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	5	SENT_25	[p2l668t80r830b139],
4	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	5	SENT_25	[p2l860t80r1150b157],
5	habits	NNS	O	habit	prep_regarding	1	SENT_25	[p2l1177t80r1401b139],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1177t80r1401b139],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_26	[p2l1433t80r1561b139],
2	impact	NN	O	impact	nsubjpass	13	SENT_26	[p2l1591t82r1823b156],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1853t80r1926b139],
4	three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	5	SENT_26	[p2l1948t80r2120b139],
5	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	prep_of	2	SENT_26	[p2l10t180r184b235],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l213t178r280b234],
7	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	prep_in	5	SENT_26	[p2l316t180r586b235],
8	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l613t197r698b235],
9	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	11	SENT_26	[p2l728t176r1017b253],
10	behavior/nicotine	NN	O	behavior/nicotine	nn	11	SENT_26	[p2l1044t176r1645b237],
11	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_on	7	SENT_26	[p2l1676t176r1995b235],
12	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_26	[p2l2022t197r2146b235],
13	investigated	VBN	O	investigate	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l9t272r415b349],
14	using	VBG	O	use	xcomp	13	SENT_26	[p2l435t274r618b349],
15	logistic	JJ	O	logistic	amod	17	SENT_26	[p2l636t272r879b349],
16	regression	NN	O	regression	nn	17	SENT_26	[p2l900t274r1246b349],
17	models	NNS	O	model	dobj	14	SENT_26	[p2l1267t272r1507b331],
18	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1530t292r1602b331],
19	a	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_26	[p2l1622t292r1657b331],
20	quasi	NNS	O	quasus	dobj	14	SENT_26	[p2l1678t274r2147b348],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1678t274r2147b348],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1678t274r2147b348],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1678t274r2147b348],

1	Poisson	NNP	PERSON	Poisson	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1678t274r2147b348],
2	regression	NN	O	regression	nn	3	SENT_28	[p2l9t371r355b446],
3	model	NN	O	model	dep	1	SENT_28	[p2l409t368r638b437],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l409t368r638b437],
5	respectively	RB	O	respectively	advmod	3	SENT_28	[p2l695t368r1108b446],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l695t368r1108b446],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_29	[p2l1165t373r1277b427],
2	found	VBD	O	find	dep	20	SENT_29	[p2l1332t368r1534b427],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_29	[p2l1588t368r1693b427],
4	T	NN	O	t	nn	5	SENT_29	[p2l1748t371r1796b426],
5	allele	NN	O	allele	dobj	2	SENT_29	[p2l1852t368r2025b427],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l2081t368r2154b427],
7	SNP	NN	O	snp	prep_of	5	SENT_29	[p2l10t469r152b524],
8	rs324650	CD	NUMBER	rs324650	num	7	SENT_29	[p2l168t471r467b524],
9	to	TO	O	to	aux	11	SENT_29	[p2l482t476r548b524],
10	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_29	[p2l564t465r641b524],
11	associated	VBN	O	associate	xcomp	2	SENT_29	[p2l658t465r1000b524],
12	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1012t465r1165b524],
13	an	DT	O	a	det	15	SENT_29	[p2l1180t486r1260b524],
14	increased	VBN	O	increase	amod	15	SENT_29	[p2l1275t465r1593b524],
15	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_with	11	SENT_29	[p2l1608t465r1736b524],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1750t465r1823b524],
17	smoking	NN	O	smoking	prep_of	15	SENT_29	[p2l1832t465r2146b542],
18	/	:	O	/	punct	20	SENT_29	[p2l1832t465r2146b542],
19	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	20	SENT_29	[p2l8t563r283b620],
20	dependence	NN	O	dependence	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l342t561r738b637],
21	according	VBG	O	accord	dep	20	SENT_29	[p2l796t561r1127b638],
22	to	TO	O	to	pcomp	21	SENT_29	[p2l1182t571r1248b620],
23	three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	25	SENT_29	[p2l1305t561r1478b620],
24	different	JJ	O	different	amod	25	SENT_29	[p2l1536t561r1828b620],
25	models	NNS	O	model	pobj	22	SENT_29	[p2l1885t561r2144b629],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1885t561r2144b629],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_29	[p2l8t657r113b716],
28	recessive	JJ	O	recessive	amod	29	SENT_29	[p2l152t660r447b716],
29	models	NNS	O	model	appos	25	SENT_29	[p2l485t657r726b716],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l766t657r838b716],
31	regular	JJ	O	regular	amod	34	SENT_29	[p2l870t657r1112b735],
32	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1150t678r1223b716],
33	heavy	JJ	O	heavy	amod	34	SENT_29	[p2l1259t657r1455b735],
34	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_of	29	SENT_29	[p2l1491t657r1770b716],
35	vs.	CC	O	vs.	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1806t678r1893b716],
36	neversmokers	NNS	O	neversmoker	appos	25	SENT_29	[p2l1934t678r2145b716, p2l10t754r287b813],
37	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	38	SENT_29	[p2l315t754r497b825],
38	odds	NNS	O	odds	rcmod	36	SENT_29	[p2l315t754r497b825],
39	ratio	NN	O	ratio	dep	38	SENT_29	[p2l520t756r679b813],
40	1.17	CD	NUMBER	1.17	num	39	SENT_29	[p2l707t760r838b813],
41	in	IN	O	in	dep	38	SENT_29	[p2l861t756r928b812],
42	both	CC	O	both	dep	36	SENT_29	[p2l948t754r1105b813],
43	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	conj	36	SENT_29	[p2l1127t754r1426b831],
44	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	43	SENT_29	[p2l1127t754r1426b831],
45	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1455t754r1580b813],
46	according	VBG	O	accord	conj_and	44	SENT_29	[p2l1601t754r1932b831],
47	to	TO	O	to	pcomp	46	SENT_29	[p2l1953t765r2019b813],
48	the	DT	O	the	det	50	SENT_29	[p2l2041t754r2146b813],
49	Fagerstrom	NNP	PERSON	Fagerstrom	nn	50	SENT_29	[p2l10t852r394b927],
50	index	NN	O	index	pobj	47	SENT_29	[p2l412t850r600b909],
51	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l616t850r688b909],
52	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	53	SENT_29	[p2l698t852r974b909],
53	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_of	50	SENT_29	[p2l993t850r1329b909],
54	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l993t850r1329b909],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1351t855r1423b908],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_30	[p2l1440t850r1545b909],
3	analysis	NN	O	analysis	prep_in	11	SENT_30	[p2l1564t850r1827b927],
4	stratiﬁed	VBN	O	stratiﬁed	partmod	3	SENT_30	[p2l1846t850r2147b909],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l7t946r91b1023],
6	gender	NN	O	gender	agent	4	SENT_30	[p2l112t946r342b1023],
7	this	DT	O	this	det	8	SENT_30	[p2l365t946r490b1005],
8	association	NN	O	association	nsubjpass	11	SENT_30	[p2l515t948r888b1005],
9	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_30	[p2l910t967r1035b1005],
10	only	RB	O	only	advmod	11	SENT_30	[p2l1060t946r1209b1023],
11	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1230t946r1431b1005],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1455t948r1522b1004],
13	females	NNS	O	female	prep_in	11	SENT_30	[p2l1545t946r1817b1005],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1545t946r1817b1005],

1	Our	PRP$	O	we	poss	2	SENT_31	[p2l1846t950r1981b1005],
2	data	NNS	O	datum	nsubj	3	SENT_31	[p2l2004t946r2148b1005],
3	provide	VBP	O	provide	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l8t1042r265b1118],
4	further	JJ	O	further	amod	5	SENT_31	[p2l306t1042r547b1101],
5	evidence	NN	O	evidence	dobj	3	SENT_31	[p2l588t1042r877b1101],
6	that	IN	O	that	complm	12	SENT_31	[p2l916t1042r1051b1101],
7	variations	NNS	O	variation	nsubjpass	12	SENT_31	[p2l1089t1044r1426b1101],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1468t1044r1535b1100],
9	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	prep_in	7	SENT_31	[p2l1581t1045r1851b1101],
10	may	MD	O	may	aux	12	SENT_31	[p2l1888t1062r2033b1119],
11	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	12	SENT_31	[p2l2068t1042r2146b1101],
12	associated	VBN	O	associate	conj_or	12	SENT_31	[p2l9t1138r352b1197],
13	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l393t1138r546b1197],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_31	[p2l590t1138r695b1197],
15	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	16	SENT_31	[p2l741t1141r979b1216],
16	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_with	12	SENT_31	[p2l1024t1138r1153b1197],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1197t1138r1269b1197],
18	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_of	16	SENT_31	[p2l1308t1138r1627b1197],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1672t1141r1739b1196],
20	general	JJ	O	general	prep_in	12	SENT_31	[p2l1785t1138r2030b1216],
21	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l2075t1159r2147b1197],
22	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l7t1235r158b1294],
23	certain	JJ	O	certain	amod	25	SENT_31	[p2l190t1237r423b1294],
24	personality	NN	O	personality	nn	25	SENT_31	[p2l452t1235r834b1312],
25	traits	NNS	O	trait	prep_with	12	SENT_31	[p2l861t1237r1037b1294],
26	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	27	SENT_31	[p2l1068t1235r1202b1294],
27	predispose	VBP	O	predispose	rcmod	25	SENT_31	[p2l1232t1235r1594b1311],
28	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1625t1246r1691b1294],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_31	[p2l1723t1235r1828b1294],
30	development	NN	O	development	prep_to	27	SENT_31	[p2l1860t1235r2144b1311, p2l8t1341r182b1390],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l217t1331r289b1390],
32	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_of	30	SENT_31	[p2l317t1331r653b1390],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l317t1331r653b1390],

1	Alternatively	RB	O	alternatively	advmod	7	SENT_32	[p2l689t1331r1145b1408],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l689t1331r1145b1408],
3	variations	NNS	O	variation	nsubj	16	SENT_32	[p2l1179t1333r1517b1390],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1552t1333r1619b1389],
5	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	prep_in	3	SENT_32	[p2l1659t1334r1929b1390],
6	could	MD	O	could	aux	7	SENT_32	[p2l1961t1331r2148b1390],
7	modulate	VB	O	modulate	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l8t1427r327b1486],
8	presynaptic	JJ	O	presynaptic	amod	9	SENT_32	[p2l366t1430r758b1505],
9	auto-regulation	NN	O	auto-regulation	dobj	7	SENT_32	[p2l798t1427r1325b1505],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1364t1430r1431b1485],
11	cholinergic	JJ	O	cholinergic	amod	12	SENT_32	[p2l1471t1427r1847b1505],
12	systems	NNS	O	system	prep_in	7	SENT_32	[p2l1888t1438r2146b1505],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l9t1524r134b1583],
14	may	MD	O	may	aux	16	SENT_32	[p2l148t1545r292b1601],
15	thereby	RB	O	thereby	advmod	16	SENT_32	[p2l305t1524r563b1601],
16	affect	VB	O	affect	conj_and	7	SENT_32	[p2l576t1524r761b1583],
17	an	DT	O	a	det	18	SENT_32	[p2l777t1545r857b1583],
18	individual	JJ	O	individual	poss	20	SENT_32	[p2l873t1524r1269b1583],
19	’s	POS	O	’s	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l873t1524r1269b1583],
20	response	NN	O	response	nsubj	24	SENT_32	[p2l1285t1544r1581b1600],
21	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1596t1535r1663b1583],
22	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	prep_to	20	SENT_32	[p2l1679t1526r1955b1583],
23	more	RBR	O	more	advmod	24	SENT_32	[p2l1971t1545r2146b1583],
24	speciﬁcally	RB	O	speciﬁcally	xcomp	16	SENT_32	[p2l10t1620r394b1697],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l10t1620r394b1697],

1	©	RB	O	©	advmod	2	SENT_33	[p2l433t1636r475b1679],
2	2009	CD	DATE	2009	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l497t1638r613b1678],
3	Wiley-Liss	NNP	O	Wiley-Liss	dep	2	SENT_33	[p2l631t1634r911b1692],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l631t1634r911b1692],
5	Inc.	NNP	O	Inc.	appos	3	SENT_33	[p2l933t1637r1025b1678],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l933t1637r1025b1678],

1	Key	NN	O	key	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l13t1818r143b1903],
2	words	NNS	O	word	dep	1	SENT_34	[p2l176t1818r416b1881],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l176t1818r416b1881],
4	smoking	NN	O	smoking	dep	1	SENT_34	[p2l472t1822r778b1899],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l472t1822r778b1899],
6	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	dep	4	SENT_34	[p2l806t1824r1081b1881],
7	addiction	NN	O	addiction	dep	6	SENT_34	[p2l1108t1822r1445b1891],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1108t1822r1445b1891],
9	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	dep	4	SENT_34	[p2l1474t1826r1746b1881],

1	Smoking	NN	O	smoking	nsubj	9	SENT_35	[p2l79t2017r367b2094],
2	due	JJ	O	due	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l395t2017r511b2075],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l539t2028r602b2075],
4	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	5	SENT_35	[p2l632t2019r895b2075],
5	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_due_to	1	SENT_35	[p2l925t2017r1232b2075],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	9	SENT_35	[p2l1261t2019r1307b2075],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_35	[p2l1335t2017r1435b2075],
8	major	JJ	O	major	amod	9	SENT_35	[p2l1463t2019r1655b2094],
9	cause	NN	O	cause	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1684t2038r1855b2075],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1884t2016r1956b2075],
11	early	JJ	O	early	amod	14	SENT_35	[p2l1975t2017r2144b2094],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1975t2017r2144b2094],
13	preventable	JJ	O	preventable	amod	14	SENT_35	[p2l8t2113r383b2189],
14	deaths	NNS	O	death	prep_of	9	SENT_35	[p2l414t2113r619b2172],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l650t2115r712b2171],
16	western	JJ	O	western	amod	17	SENT_35	[p2l740t2125r989b2172],
17	societies	NNS	O	society	prep_in	9	SENT_35	[p2l1019t2115r1285b2172],
18	[	VBP	O	[	dep	17	SENT_35	[p2l1324t2113r1590b2184],
19	Frieden	NNP	PERSON	Frieden	dobj	18	SENT_35	[p2l1324t2113r1590b2184],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1621t2113r1740b2172],
21	Bloomberg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bloomberg	conj_and	19	SENT_35	[p2l1769t2113r2144b2190],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1769t2113r2144b2190],
23	2007	CD	DATE	2007	conj_and	19	SENT_35	[p2l9t2214r178b2276],
24	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l9t2214r178b2276],
25	WHO	WP	O	who	dep	31	SENT_35	[p2l229t2212r425b2268],
26	Report	NNP	O	Report	dep	31	SENT_35	[p2l479t2213r701b2285],
27	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l751t2230r834b2267],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_35	[p2l883t2209r983b2267],
29	global	JJ	O	global	amod	30	SENT_35	[p2l1033t2209r1227b2286],
30	tobacco	NN	O	tobacco	prep_on	26	SENT_35	[p2l1276t2209r1526b2267],
31	epidemic	JJ	O	epidemic	rcmod	9	SENT_35	[p2l1580t2209r1891b2285],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1580t2209r1891b2285],
33	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	34	SENT_35	[p2l1944t2209r2143b2279],
34	]	NN	O	]	dep	9	SENT_35	[p2l1944t2209r2143b2279],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1944t2209r2143b2279],

1	Environmental	NNP	O	Environmental	nsubj	7	SENT_36	[p2l9t2305r496b2364],
2	as	RB	O	as	advmod	3	SENT_36	[p2l519t2326r579b2364],
3	well	RB	O	well	advmod	7	SENT_36	[p2l601t2305r729b2364],
4	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l753t2326r812b2364],
5	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	6	SENT_36	[p2l837t2307r1063b2382],
6	factors	NNS	O	factor	prep_as	3	SENT_36	[p2l1086t2305r1301b2364],
7	play	VBP	O	play	dep	19	SENT_36	[p2l1324t2305r1460b2382],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_36	[p2l1482t2326r1513b2364],
9	role	NN	O	role	dobj	7	SENT_36	[p2l1536t2305r1658b2364],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1682t2307r1745b2363],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_36	[p2l1767t2305r1866b2364],
12	etiology	NN	O	etiology	prep_in	7	SENT_36	[p2l1891t2305r2149b2382],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l10t2401r81b2460],
14	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	15	SENT_36	[p2l92t2403r355b2460],
15	dependence	NN	O	dependence	prep_of	12	SENT_36	[p2l377t2401r759b2477],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l781t2401r900b2460],
17	twin	JJ	O	twin	amod	18	SENT_36	[p2l919t2403r1063b2460],
18	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	12	SENT_36	[p2l1084t2401r1305b2460],
19	suggest	VBP	O	suggest	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1327t2413r1559b2478],
20	a	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_36	[p2l1580t2422r1612b2460],
21	heritability	NN	O	heritability	dobj	19	SENT_36	[p2l1631t2401r1988b2478],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l2006t2401r2078b2460],
23	at	IN	O	at	quantmod	25	SENT_36	[p2l2089t2413r2147b2460],
24	least	JJS	O	least	mwe	23	SENT_36	[p2l8t2498r150b2556],
25	50	CD	PERCENT	50	num	26	SENT_36	[p2l167t2503r306b2558],
26	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_of	21	SENT_36	[p2l167t2503r306b2558],
27	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	28	SENT_36	[p2l333t2498r433b2568],
28	Li	NNP	O	Li	nsubj	19	SENT_36	[p2l333t2498r433b2568],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l333t2498r433b2568],
30	2006	CD	DATE	2006	num	31	SENT_36	[p2l452t2498r651b2568],
31	]	NN	O	]	appos	28	SENT_36	[p2l452t2498r651b2568],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l452t2498r651b2568],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_37	[p2l668t2501r721b2555],
2	number	NN	O	number	nsubj	6	SENT_37	[p2l735t2498r993b2556],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1009t2497r1080b2556],
4	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	2	SENT_37	[p2l1087t2498r1308b2556],
5	have	VBP	O	have	aux	6	SENT_37	[p2l1324t2498r1471b2556],
6	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1487t2498r1681b2556],
7	an	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_37	[p2l1698t2519r1773b2556],
8	association	NN	O	association	dobj	6	SENT_37	[p2l1790t2500r2147b2556],
9	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l7t2593r273b2652],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_37	[p2l292t2593r392b2652],
11	CHRNA3-CHRNA5	NN	O	chrna3-chrna5	prep_between	8	SENT_37	[p2l419t2597r1401b2652],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l419t2597r1401b2652],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l419t2597r1401b2652],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l419t2597r1401b2652],

1	CHRNB4	NN	O	chrnb4	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l419t2597r1401b2652],
2	nicotinic	JJ	O	nicotinic	amod	7	SENT_39	[p2l1418t2595r1705b2652],
3	acetylcholine	NN	O	acetylcholine	nn	7	SENT_39	[p2l1725t2593r2146b2670],
4	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nn	7	SENT_39	[p2l10t2701r278b2765],
5	subunit	NN	O	subunit	nn	7	SENT_39	[p2l326t2689r572b2748],
6	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	7	SENT_39	[p2l620t2710r765b2766],
7	cluster	NN	O	cluster	dep	1	SENT_39	[p2l815t2689r1027b2748],
8	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1075t2710r1158b2748],
9	chromosome	NN	O	chromosome	prep_on	7	SENT_39	[p2l1207t2689r1632b2748],
10	15q24/25	CD	NUMBER	15q24/25	num	9	SENT_39	[p2l1688t2692r1976b2765],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l2028t2689r2147b2748],
12	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	14	SENT_39	[p2l10t2785r287b2862],
13	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	14	SENT_39	[p2l320t2785r541b2855],
14	Bierut	NNP	PERSON	Bierut	conj_and	9	SENT_39	[p2l320t2785r541b2855],
15	et	FW	O	et	nn	16	SENT_39	[p2l567t2796r622b2843],
16	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	1	SENT_39	[p2l648t2785r736b2852],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l648t2785r736b2852],
18	2007	CD	DATE	2007	appos	16	SENT_39	[p2l764t2790r933b2852],
19	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l764t2790r933b2852],
20	2008	CD	DATE	2008	appos	16	SENT_39	[p2l961t2790r1130b2852],
21	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l961t2790r1130b2852],
22	Saccone	NNP	PERSON	Saccone	dep	16	SENT_39	[p2l1159t2788r1417b2844],
23	et	FW	O	et	nn	24	SENT_39	[p2l1443t2796r1498b2843],
24	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	22	SENT_39	[p2l1524t2785r1612b2852],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1524t2785r1612b2852],
26	2007	CD	DATE	2007	appos	24	SENT_39	[p2l1640t2790r1809b2852],
27	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1640t2790r1809b2852],
28	Berrettini	NNP	PERSON	Berrettini	dep	16	SENT_39	[p2l1837t2787r2146b2843],
29	et	FW	O	et	nn	30	SENT_39	[p2l10t2893r65b2940],
30	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	28	SENT_39	[p2l113t2881r202b2949],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l113t2881r202b2949],
32	2008	CD	DATE	2008	appos	30	SENT_39	[p2l253t2887r421b2948],
33	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l253t2887r421b2948],
34	Chanock	NNP	LOCATION	Chanock	dep	16	SENT_39	[p2l473t2881r762b2940],
35	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l809t2881r928b2940],
36	Hunter	NNP	PERSON	Hunter	conj_and	34	SENT_39	[p2l976t2886r1229b2949],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l976t2886r1229b2949],
38	2008	CD	DATE	2008	appos	34	SENT_39	[p2l1279t2887r1449b2949],
39	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1279t2887r1449b2949],
40	Hung	NNP	O	Hung	dep	16	SENT_39	[p2l1499t2885r1684b2958],
41	et	FW	O	et	nn	42	SENT_39	[p2l1732t2893r1788b2940],
42	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	40	SENT_39	[p2l1836t2881r1924b2949],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1836t2881r1924b2949],
44	2008	CD	DATE	2008	appos	42	SENT_39	[p2l1975t2887r2144b2949],
45	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1975t2887r2144b2949],
46	Thorgeirsson	NNP	O	Thorgeirsson	dep	16	SENT_39	[p2l9t2977r436b3054],
47	et	FW	O	et	nn	48	SENT_39	[p2l454t2988r509b3035],
48	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	46	SENT_39	[p2l526t2977r614b3045],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l526t2977r614b3045],
50	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	51	SENT_39	[p2l634t2977r833b3047],
51	]	NN	O	]	appos	1	SENT_39	[p2l634t2977r833b3047],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l634t2977r833b3047],

1	Furthermore	RB	O	furthermore	advmod	20	SENT_40	[p2l853t2977r1286b3044],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l853t2977r1286b3044],
3	CHRNA4	NN	O	chrna4	nsubjpass	20	SENT_40	[p2l1311t2980r1630b3044],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1311t2980r1630b3044],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_40	[p2l1648t2977r1748b3035],
6	gene	NN	O	gene	appos	3	SENT_40	[p2l1765t2998r1910b3054],
7	coding	VBG	O	code	partmod	6	SENT_40	[p2l1928t2977r2147b3054],
8	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l9t3073r102b3132],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_40	[p2l130t3073r230b3132],
10	0c4	NN	O	0c4	nn	12	SENT_40	[p2l261t3073r626b3132],
11	—	NN	O	—	nn	12	SENT_40	[p2l261t3073r626b3132],
12	subunit	NN	O	subunit	prep_for	7	SENT_40	[p2l261t3073r626b3132],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l657t3073r728b3132],
14	nicotinic	JJ	O	nicotinic	amod	16	SENT_40	[p2l749t3075r1035b3132],
15	acetylcholine	NN	O	acetylcholine	nn	16	SENT_40	[p2l1066t3073r1486b3150],
16	receptors	NNS	O	receptor	prep_of	12	SENT_40	[p2l1517t3085r1831b3149],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1517t3085r1831b3149],
18	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	20	SENT_40	[p2l1862t3073r1966b3132],
19	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_40	[p2l1995t3073r2146b3132],
20	linked	VBN	O	link	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l8t3169r209b3228],
21	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l252t3181r316b3228],
22	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	23	SENT_40	[p2l362t3171r625b3228],
23	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_to	20	SENT_40	[p2l671t3169r979b3228],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1024t3169r1143b3228],
25	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	27	SENT_40	[p2l1189t3169r1465b3246],
26	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	27	SENT_40	[p2l1518t3169r1694b3246],
27	Feng	NNP	O	Feng	conj_and	23	SENT_40	[p2l1518t3169r1694b3246],
28	et	FW	O	et	nn	29	SENT_40	[p2l1739t3181r1795b3228],
29	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	23	SENT_40	[p2l1839t3169r1928b3237],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1839t3169r1928b3237],
31	2004	CD	DATE	2004	appos	29	SENT_40	[p2l1975t3175r2144b3237],
32	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1975t3175r2144b3237],
33	Li	NNP	PERSON	Li	dep	29	SENT_40	[p2l10t3267r71b3323],
34	et	FW	O	et	nn	35	SENT_40	[p2l104t3276r160b3323],
35	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	33	SENT_40	[p2l193t3265r282b3332],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l193t3265r282b3332],
37	2005	CD	DATE	2005	appos	35	SENT_40	[p2l317t3270r486b3332],
38	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l317t3270r486b3332],
39	Hutchison	NNP	PERSON	Hutchison	dep	29	SENT_40	[p2l522t3265r865b3323],
40	et	FW	O	et	nn	41	SENT_40	[p2l898t3276r954b3323],
41	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	39	SENT_40	[p2l987t3265r1076b3332],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l987t3265r1076b3332],
43	2007	CD	DATE	2007	appos	41	SENT_40	[p2l1111t3270r1281b3333],
44	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1111t3270r1281b3333],
45	Breitling	NNP	O	Breitling	dep	29	SENT_40	[p2l1316t3265r1594b3342],
46	et	FW	O	et	nn	47	SENT_40	[p2l1628t3276r1683b3323],
47	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	45	SENT_40	[p2l1716t3265r1805b3332],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1716t3265r1805b3332],
49	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1840t3267r1903b3323],
50	press	NN	O	press	nn	51	SENT_40	[p2l1935t3265r2143b3341],
51	]	NN	O	]	prep_in	23	SENT_40	[p2l1935t3265r2143b3341],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1935t3265r2143b3341],

1	However	RB	O	however	advmod	22	SENT_41	[p2l9t3366r318b3429],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l9t3366r318b3429],
3	other	JJ	O	other	amod	4	SENT_41	[p2l358t3361r528b3420],
4	genes	NNS	O	gene	nsubjpass	22	SENT_41	[p2l566t3382r738b3438],
5	involved	VBN	O	involve	partmod	4	SENT_41	[p2l777t3361r1053b3420],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1091t3363r1153b3419],
7	dopaminergic	JJ	O	dopaminergic	amod	10	SENT_41	[p2l1192t3361r1641b3438],
8	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1679t3382r1748b3420],
9	GABAergic	JJ	O	gabaergic	conj_or	7	SENT_41	[p2l1786t3363r2147b3438],
10	neurotransmission	NN	O	neurotransmission	prep_in	5	SENT_41	[p2l9t3459r617b3516],
11	as	RB	O	as	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l634t3478r693b3516],
12	well	RB	O	well	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l707t3457r836b3516],
13	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l852t3478r911b3516],
14	genes	NNS	O	gene	prep_in	5	SENT_41	[p2l927t3478r1101b3534],
15	involved	VBN	O	involve	partmod	14	SENT_41	[p2l1117t3457r1394b3516],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1409t3459r1471b3515],
17	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	18	SENT_41	[p2l1487t3459r1750b3516],
18	metabolism	NN	O	metabolism	prep_in	15	SENT_41	[p2l1766t3457r2146b3516],
19	have	VBP	O	have	aux	22	SENT_41	[p2l8t3554r155b3612],
20	also	RB	O	also	advmod	22	SENT_41	[p2l178t3554r299b3612],
21	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	22	SENT_41	[p2l321t3554r472b3612],
22	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l496t3554r821b3612],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l841t3554r985b3612],
24	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	25	SENT_41	[p2l1007t3554r1285b3631],
25	[	NN	O	[	prep_with	22	SENT_41	[p2l1315t3554r1430b3624],
26	for	IN	O	for	mark	29	SENT_41	[p2l1315t3554r1430b3624],
27	recent	JJ	O	recent	amod	28	SENT_41	[p2l1452t3565r1649b3612],
28	reviews	NNS	O	review	nsubj	29	SENT_41	[p2l1671t3556r1906b3612],
29	see	VBP	O	see	advcl	22	SENT_41	[p2l1930t3575r2022b3612],
30	Ho	NNP	O	Ho	dobj	29	SENT_41	[p2l2045t3558r2144b3612],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l10t3650r128b3709],
32	Tyndale	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tyndale	conj_and	30	SENT_41	[p2l154t3650r430b3727],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l154t3650r430b3727],
34	2007	CD	DATE	2007	appos	30	SENT_41	[p2l459t3656r628b3718],
35	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l459t3656r628b3718],
36	Benowitz	NNP	PERSON	Benowitz	dep	30	SENT_41	[p2l657t3652r974b3718],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l657t3652r974b3718],
38	2008	CD	DATE	2008	appos	36	SENT_41	[p2l1002t3656r1172b3718],
39	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1002t3656r1172b3718],
40	Ray	NNP	PERSON	Ray	dep	30	SENT_41	[p2l1200t3654r1322b3727],
41	et	FW	O	et	nn	42	SENT_41	[p2l1346t3661r1402b3709],
42	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	40	SENT_41	[p2l1428t3650r1516b3717],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1428t3650r1516b3717],
44	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	45	SENT_41	[p2l1545t3650r1743b3721],
45	]	NN	O	]	appos	30	SENT_41	[p2l1545t3650r1743b3721],
46	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1545t3650r1743b3721],

1	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	dep	15	SENT_42	[p2l84t3750r364b3814],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l84t3750r364b3814],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_42	[p2l414t3747r514b3805],
4	gene	NN	O	gene	appos	1	SENT_42	[p2l564t3768r709b3824],
5	coding	VBG	O	code	partmod	4	SENT_42	[p2l760t3747r979b3824],
6	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1028t3747r1121b3805],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_42	[p2l1169t3747r1268b3805],
8	muscarinic	JJ	O	muscarinic	amod	10	SENT_42	[p2l1318t3749r1676b3805],
9	acetylcholine	NN	O	acetylcholine	nn	10	SENT_42	[p2l1725t3747r2145b3824],
10	receptor	NN	O	receptor	prep_for	5	SENT_42	[p3l10t33r278b97],
11	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	10	SENT_42	[p3l300t27r333b79],
12	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	15	SENT_42	[p3l356t21r460b80],
13	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	15	SENT_42	[p3l483t21r821b98],
14	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	15	SENT_42	[p3l838t21r990b80],
15	identiﬁed	VBN	O	identiﬁed	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1012t21r1322b80],
16	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1344t42r1404b80],
17	a	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_42	[p3l1427t42r1460b80],
18	risk	NN	O	risk	nn	19	SENT_42	[p3l1482t21r1600b80],
19	gene	NN	O	gene	prep_as	15	SENT_42	[p3l1620t42r1766b98],
20	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1788t21r1881b80],
21	alcoholism	NN	O	alcoholism	prep_for	19	SENT_42	[p3l1903t21r2143b80, p3l8t117r143b176],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l188t119r250b175],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_42	[p3l294t117r393b176],
24	collaborative	JJ	O	collaborative	amod	25	SENT_42	[p3l439t117r854b176],
25	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	15	SENT_42	[p3l899t117r1076b194],
26	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1118t138r1200b176],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_42	[p3l1243t117r1343b176],
28	genetics	NNS	O	genetics	prep_on	25	SENT_42	[p3l1388t119r1642b194],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1688t117r1759b176],
30	alcoholism	NN	O	alcoholism	nn	32	SENT_42	[p3l1795t117r2146b176],
31	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	32	SENT_42	[p3l18t214r276b284],
32	COGA	NNP	LOCATION	COGA	prep_of	28	SENT_42	[p3l18t214r276b284],
33	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l18t214r276b284],
34	Wang	NNP	PERSON	Wang	dep	32	SENT_42	[p3l319t218r513b291],
35	et	FW	O	et	nn	36	SENT_42	[p3l555t225r610b272],
36	al.	FW	O	al.	nsubjpass	15	SENT_42	[p3l653t214r741b281],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l653t214r741b281],
38	2004	CD	DATE	2004	num	39	SENT_42	[p3l786t214r985b284],
39	]	NN	O	]	appos	36	SENT_42	[p3l786t214r985b284],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l786t214r985b284],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_43	[p3l1030t214r1169b272],
2	ﬁnding	NN	O	ﬁnding	nsubjpass	5	SENT_43	[p3l1213t213r1445b291],
3	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_43	[p3l1485t235r1602b272],
4	later	RB	O	later	advmod	5	SENT_43	[p3l1644t214r1787b272],
5	replicated	VBN	O	replicate	dep	25	SENT_43	[p3l1830t214r2146b290],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l10t310r128b369],
7	subsequent	JJ	O	subsequent	amod	8	SENT_43	[p3l179t310r540b386],
8	research	NN	O	research	nsubj	9	SENT_43	[p3l590t310r855b369],
9	suggested	VBD	O	suggest	dep	25	SENT_43	[p3l905t310r1213b387],
10	that	IN	O	that	complm	18	SENT_43	[p3l1262t310r1389b369],
11	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	12	SENT_43	[p3l1439t312r1665b387],
12	variations	NNS	O	variation	nsubjpass	18	SENT_43	[p3l1713t312r2032b369],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l2084t312r2146b368],
14	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	prep_in	12	SENT_43	[p3l15t410r280b465],
15	may	MD	O	may	aux	18	SENT_43	[p3l316t427r454b483],
16	also	RB	O	also	advmod	18	SENT_43	[p3l490t406r611b465],
17	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	18	SENT_43	[p3l650t406r723b465],
18	associated	VBN	O	associate	ccomp	9	SENT_43	[p3l763t406r1089b465],
19	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1125t406r1269b465],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_43	[p3l1307t406r1407b465],
21	abuse	NN	O	abuse	prep_with	18	SENT_43	[p3l1446t406r1625b465],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1665t406r1736b465],
23	illicit	JJ	O	illicit	amod	24	SENT_43	[p3l1766t406r1928b465],
24	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_of	21	SENT_43	[p3l1968t406r2145b483],
25	[	VBP	O	[	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l18t503r163b573],
26	Luo	NNP	PERSON	Luo	dobj	25	SENT_43	[p3l18t503r163b573],
27	et	FW	O	et	nn	28	SENT_43	[p3l206t514r261b561],
28	al.	FW	O	al.	nsubj	25	SENT_43	[p3l302t503r390b570],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l302t503r390b570],
30	2005	CD	DATE	2005	appos	28	SENT_43	[p3l432t508r602b570],
31	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l432t508r602b570],
32	Dick	NNP	PERSON	Dick	dep	30	SENT_43	[p3l644t503r797b561],
33	et	FW	O	et	nn	34	SENT_43	[p3l835t514r891b561],
34	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	32	SENT_43	[p3l931t503r1020b570],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l931t503r1020b570],
36	2007b	JJ	O	2007b	amod	37	SENT_43	[p3l1062t503r1301b573],
37	]	NN	O	]	appos	34	SENT_43	[p3l1062t503r1301b573],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1062t503r1301b573],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1345t507r1413b561],
2	fact	NN	O	fact	prep_in	7	SENT_44	[p3l1453t502r1585b570],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1453t502r1585b570],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_44	[p3l1626t503r1726b561],
5	latter	JJ	O	latter	amod	6	SENT_44	[p3l1764t503r1933b561],
6	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	7	SENT_44	[p3l1973t503r2149b580],
7	suggested	VBD	O	suggest	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l10t599r318b676],
8	that	IN	O	that	complm	20	SENT_44	[p3l340t599r467b658],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_44	[p3l488t599r587b658],
10	association	NN	O	association	nsubjpass	20	SENT_44	[p3l611t601r967b658],
11	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l988t599r1254b658],
12	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	prep_between	10	SENT_44	[p3l1283t602r1548b658],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1568t599r1687b658],
14	alcoholism	NN	O	alcoholism	prep_between	10	SENT_44	[p3l1710t599r2061b658],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l2084t601r2146b657],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_44	[p3l8t695r108b753],
17	COGA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	COGA	nn	18	SENT_44	[p3l131t698r350b754],
18	sample	NN	O	sample	prep_in	12	SENT_44	[p3l372t695r595b771],
19	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_44	[p3l615t716r732b753],
20	driven	VBN	O	drive	ccomp	7	SENT_44	[p3l755t695r961b753],
21	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l980t695r1060b772],
22	a	DT	O	a	det	23	SENT_44	[p3l1079t716r1111b753],
23	subsample	NN	O	subsample	agent	20	SENT_44	[p3l1133t695r1471b771],
24	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1491t695r1635b753],
25	comorbid	NN	O	comorbid	nn	27	SENT_44	[p3l1657t695r1974b753],
26	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	27	SENT_44	[p3l1997t695r2147b772],
27	abuse	NN	O	abuse	prep_with	23	SENT_44	[p3l10t792r205b851],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l10t792r205b851],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_45	[p3l77t888r200b947],
2	comorbidity	NN	O	comorbidity	nsubj	13	SENT_45	[p3l239t888r644b965],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l680t888r751b947],
4	alcoholism	NN	O	alcoholism	prep_of	2	SENT_45	[p3l780t888r1149b956],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l780t888r1149b956],
6	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	7	SENT_45	[p3l1190t888r1341b965],
7	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_of	2	SENT_45	[p3l1379t888r1686b947],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1725t888r1844b947],
9	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	10	SENT_45	[p3l1882t890r2146b947],
10	abuse	NN	O	abuse	conj_and	4	SENT_45	[p3l10t984r189b1042],
11	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	13	SENT_45	[p3l210t986r256b1042],
12	high	JJ	O	high	amod	13	SENT_45	[p3l277t984r420b1061],
13	[	NN	O	[	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l449t984r575b1061],
14	e.g.	FW	O	e.g.	nsubj	35	SENT_45	[p3l449t984r575b1061],
15	Bien	NNP	PERSON	Bien	dep	14	SENT_45	[p3l600t986r743b1042],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l765t984r883b1042],
17	Burge	NNP	PERSON	Burge	dep	14	SENT_45	[p3l904t988r1110b1061],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l904t988r1110b1061],
19	1990	CD	DATE	1990	num	20	SENT_45	[p3l1140t984r1333b1054],
20	]	NN	O	]	appos	14	SENT_45	[p3l1140t984r1333b1054],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1140t984r1333b1054],
22	a	DT	O	a	det	23	SENT_45	[p3l1357t1005r1389b1042],
23	phenomenon	NN	O	phenomenon	appos	14	SENT_45	[p3l1408t984r1843b1060],
24	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	27	SENT_45	[p3l1863t984r1990b1042],
25	may	MD	O	may	aux	27	SENT_45	[p3l2011t1005r2149b1061],
26	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	27	SENT_45	[p3l7t1080r80b1139],
27	mediated	VBN	O	mediate	rcmod	23	SENT_45	[p3l99t1080r400b1139],
28	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l414t1080r494b1157],
29	an	DT	O	a	det	31	SENT_45	[p3l509t1101r584b1139],
30	overlapping	VBG	O	overlap	amod	31	SENT_45	[p3l603t1080r988b1157],
31	set	NN	O	set	agent	27	SENT_45	[p3l1005t1092r1090b1139],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1108t1080r1179b1139],
33	risk	NN	O	risk	nn	34	SENT_45	[p3l1188t1080r1307b1139],
34	genes	NNS	O	gene	prep_of	31	SENT_45	[p3l1322t1101r1495b1157],
35	[	VBP	O	[	rcmod	13	SENT_45	[p3l1522t1080r1774b1151],
36	Grucza	NNP	O	Grucza	dobj	35	SENT_45	[p3l1522t1080r1774b1151],
37	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1792t1080r1911b1139],
38	Bierut	NNP	PERSON	Bierut	dobj	35	SENT_45	[p3l1928t1082r2144b1148],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1928t1082r2144b1148],
40	2006	CD	DATE	2006	num	41	SENT_45	[p3l9t1177r182b1248],
41	]	NN	O	]	appos	36	SENT_45	[p3l9t1177r182b1248],
42	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l197t1225r207b1236],

1	Therefore	RB	O	therefore	dep	23	SENT_46	[p3l227t1177r543b1236],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l560t1177r678b1236],
3	in	IN	O	in	dep	23	SENT_46	[p3l694t1179r757b1235],
4	View	NNP	O	View	pobj	3	SENT_46	[p3l771t1179r920b1236],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l935t1177r1006b1236],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_46	[p3l1012t1177r1111b1236],
7	notion	NN	O	notion	prep_of	4	SENT_46	[p3l1128t1179r1344b1236],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1362t1177r1432b1236],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_46	[p3l1440t1198r1472b1236],
10	common	JJ	O	common	amod	11	SENT_46	[p3l1489t1198r1780b1236],
11	molecularl	NN	O	molecularl	prep_of	7	SENT_46	[p3l1797t1177r2145b1238],
12	neurobiological	JJ	O	neurobiological	amod	13	SENT_46	[p3l9t1273r517b1350],
13	pathway	NN	O	pathway	nsubj	23	SENT_46	[p3l544t1273r818b1350],
14	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l844t1273r936b1331],
15	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_for	13	SENT_46	[p3l964t1273r1272b1331],
16	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	18	SENT_46	[p3l1299t1273r1426b1331],
17	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	18	SENT_46	[p3l1454t1275r1501b1331],
18	shared	VBN	O	share	rcmod	15	SENT_46	[p3l1530t1273r1741b1331],
19	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1766t1273r1846b1350],
20	different	JJ	O	different	amod	22	SENT_46	[p3l1872t1272r2146b1332],
21	addictive	JJ	O	addictive	amod	22	SENT_46	[p3l10t1369r301b1428],
22	substances	NNS	O	substance	agent	18	SENT_46	[p3l342t1369r682b1428],
23	[	VBP	O	[	dep	30	SENT_46	[p3l731t1369r999b1440],
24	Nestler	NNP	PERSON	Nestler	dobj	23	SENT_46	[p3l731t1369r999b1440],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l731t1369r999b1440],
26	2005	CD	DATE	2005	num	27	SENT_46	[p3l1040t1369r1240b1440],
27	]	NN	O	]	appos	24	SENT_46	[p3l1040t1369r1240b1440],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1040t1369r1240b1440],
29	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	30	SENT_46	[p3l1280t1390r1368b1428],
30	sought	VBD	O	seek	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1408t1369r1625b1446],
31	to	TO	O	to	aux	32	SENT_46	[p3l1663t1381r1726b1428],
32	address	VB	O	address	xcomp	30	SENT_46	[p3l1769t1369r2007b1428],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	34	SENT_46	[p3l2046t1369r2146b1428],
34	question	NN	O	question	dobj	32	SENT_46	[p3l10t1467r287b1541],
35	whether	IN	O	whether	complm	42	SENT_46	[p3l318t1465r581b1523],
36	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubjpass	42	SENT_46	[p3l613t1465r1123b1542],
37	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1158t1467r1220b1523],
38	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	prep_in	36	SENT_46	[p3l1259t1468r1524b1524],
39	may	MD	O	may	aux	42	SENT_46	[p3l1554t1486r1693b1542],
40	also	RB	O	also	advmod	42	SENT_46	[p3l1724t1465r1844b1523],
41	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	42	SENT_46	[p3l1878t1465r1952b1523],
42	associated	VBN	O	associate	ccomp	32	SENT_46	[p3l1985t1486r2143b1523, p3l10t1561r199b1620],
43	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l224t1561r368b1620],
44	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	47	SENT_46	[p3l394t1561r672b1638],
45	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l698t1561r817b1620],
46	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	conj_and	44	SENT_46	[p3l843t1563r1106b1620],
47	dependence	NN	O	dependence	prep_with	42	SENT_46	[p3l1134t1561r1532b1637],
48	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1134t1561r1532b1637],

1	Thus	RB	O	thus	advmod	4	SENT_47	[p3l78t1657r257b1725],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l78t1657r257b1725],
3	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	4	SENT_47	[p3l301t1678r389b1716],
4	investigated	VBD	O	investigate	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l434t1657r817b1735],
5	CHRM2	NN	O	chrm2	nn	6	SENT_47	[p3l868t1661r1133b1716],
6	genotype	NN	O	genotype	dobj	4	SENT_47	[p3l1175t1669r1483b1735],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1175t1669r1483b1735],
8	extent	NN	O	extent	appos	6	SENT_47	[p3l1532t1669r1728b1716],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1773t1657r1844b1716],
10	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	11	SENT_47	[p3l1879t1660r2143b1716],
11	dependence	NN	O	dependence	prep_of	8	SENT_47	[p3l10t1754r392b1830],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l424t1754r542b1813],
13	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	14	SENT_47	[p3l573t1754r851b1831],
14	habits	NNS	O	habit	conj_and	11	SENT_47	[p3l880t1754r1072b1813],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1104t1756r1167b1812],
16	5,561	CD	NUMBER	5,561	num	17	SENT_47	[p3l1199t1759r1363b1822],
17	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_in	4	SENT_47	[p3l1401t1754r1652b1831],
18	(	JJ	O	(	amod	17	SENT_47	[p3l1688t1754r1954b1825],
19	derived	VBN	O	derive	partmod	17	SENT_47	[p3l1688t1754r1954b1825],
20	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1984t1754r2142b1813],
21	three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	23	SENT_47	[p3l8t1850r171b1909],
22	subsamples	NNS	O	subsample	nn	23	SENT_47	[p3l191t1850r557b1926],
23	R1	NN	O	r1	prep_from	19	SENT_47	[p3l578t1850r822b1921],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l578t1850r822b1921],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l578t1850r822b1921],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l578t1850r822b1921],

1	R3	NN	O	r3	nn	2	SENT_49	[p3l578t1850r822b1921],
2	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	3	SENT_49	[p3l578t1850r822b1921],
3	recruited	VBN	O	recruit	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l847t1850r1138b1909],
4	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1158t1850r1316b1909],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_49	[p3l1335t1850r1434b1909],
6	general	JJ	O	general	amod	7	SENT_49	[p3l1454t1850r1684b1927],
7	population	NN	O	population	prep_from	3	SENT_49	[p3l1702t1850r2061b1926],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l2081t1852r2143b1908],
9	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	prep_in	7	SENT_49	[p3l10t1949r324b2023],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l10t1949r324b2023],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l78t2047r146b2101],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_50	[p3l174t2043r273b2101],
3	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	4	SENT_50	[p3l302t2054r538b2119],
4	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	11	SENT_50	[p3l568t2043r758b2120],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l568t2043r758b2120],
6	“	CD	NUMBER	“	num	9	SENT_50	[p3l792t2042r1109b2120],
7	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	9	SENT_50	[p3l792t2042r1109b2120],
8	status	NN	O	status	nn	9	SENT_50	[p3l1138t2042r1358b2101],
9	”	NN	O	”	nsubjpass	11	SENT_50	[p3l1138t2042r1358b2101],
10	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_50	[p3l1389t2064r1506b2101],
11	deﬁned	VBN	O	deﬁned	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l1537t2042r1776b2102],
12	as	IN	O	as	mark	13	SENT_50	[p3l1805t2064r1864b2101],
13	follows	VBZ	O	follow	advcl	11	SENT_50	[p3l1894t2042r2139b2101],
14	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l1894t2042r2139b2101],
15	people	NNS	O	people	nn	16	SENT_50	[p3l9t2139r222b2216],
16	smoking	NN	O	smoking	dobj	13	SENT_50	[p3l262t2139r539b2217],
17	at	IN	O	at	quantmod	19	SENT_50	[p3l578t2151r636b2198],
18	least	JJS	O	least	mwe	17	SENT_50	[p3l673t2139r815b2198],
19	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	20	SENT_50	[p3l855t2160r970b2198],
20	cigarette	NN	O	cigarette	nsubjpass	24	SENT_50	[p3l1011t2142r1282b2217],
21	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l1321t2160r1426b2216],
22	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	20	SENT_50	[p3l1466t2139r1580b2217],
23	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	24	SENT_50	[p3l1614t2160r1764b2198],
24	deﬁned	VBN	O	deﬁned	rcmod	16	SENT_50	[p3l1804t2139r2043b2198],
25	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l2083t2160r2142b2198],
26	regular	JJ	O	regular	amod	27	SENT_50	[p3l10t2236r236b2313],
27	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_as	24	SENT_50	[p3l288t2236r569b2295],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l288t2236r569b2295],

1	People	NNS	O	people	nsubjpass	10	SENT_51	[p3l625t2236r840b2312],
2	smoking	VBG	O	smoke	partmod	1	SENT_51	[p3l892t2236r1169b2313],
3	20	CD	NUMBER	20	num	6	SENT_51	[p3l1220t2242r1293b2295],
4	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l1347t2257r1415b2295],
5	more	JJR	O	more	num	6	SENT_51	[p3l1466t2257r1634b2295],
6	cigarettes	NNS	O	cigarette	dobj	2	SENT_51	[p3l1687t2238r1987b2313],
7	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l2039t2256r2143b2312],
8	day	NN	DURATION	day	prep_per	6	SENT_51	[p3l10t2332r124b2409],
9	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_51	[p3l147t2353r297b2391],
10	deﬁned	VBN	O	deﬁned	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l326t2332r564b2391],
11	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l593t2353r653b2391],
12	heavy	JJ	O	heavy	amod	13	SENT_51	[p3l680t2332r866b2409],
13	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	prep_as	10	SENT_51	[p3l892t2332r1174b2391],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l892t2332r1174b2391],

1	Never-smoking	JJ	O	never-smoking	amod	2	SENT_52	[p3l1204t2332r1706b2409],
2	controls	NNS	O	control	nsubj	3	SENT_52	[p3l1735t2332r1996b2391],
3	had	VBD	O	have	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l2024t2332r2143b2391],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_52	[p3l10t2449r42b2487],
5	life	NN	O	life	nn	8	SENT_52	[p3l58t2428r333b2487],
6	—	NN	O	—	nn	8	SENT_52	[p3l58t2428r333b2487],
7	time	NN	O	time	nn	8	SENT_52	[p3l58t2428r333b2487],
8	history	NN	O	history	dobj	3	SENT_52	[p3l350t2428r577b2506],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l593t2428r664b2487],
10	no	DT	O	no	quantmod	13	SENT_52	[p3l673t2449r753b2487],
11	more	JJR	O	more	quantmod	13	SENT_52	[p3l773t2449r941b2487],
12	than	IN	O	than	quantmod	13	SENT_52	[p3l959t2428r1104b2487],
13	100	CD	NUMBER	100	num	14	SENT_52	[p3l1129t2434r1234b2487],
14	cigarettes	NNS	O	cigarette	prep_of	8	SENT_52	[p3l1254t2431r1571b2506],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1254t2431r1571b2506],

1	In	IN	O	in	dep	6	SENT_53	[p3l1593t2433r1660b2486],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_53	[p3l1677t2428r1776b2487],
3	MONICA	NNP	O	MONICA	pobj	1	SENT_53	[p3l1793t2432r2141b2490],
4	/	:	O	/	punct	6	SENT_53	[p3l1793t2432r2141b2490],
5	KORA	NN	ORGANIZATION	kora	nn	6	SENT_53	[p3l10t2529r224b2584],
6	study	NN	O	study	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l256t2525r433b2602],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_53	[p3l467t2525r573b2596],
8	R1	NN	O	r1	nsubjpass	22	SENT_53	[p3l467t2525r573b2596],
9	sample	NN	O	sample	nn	10	SENT_53	[p3l612t2525r860b2601],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	8	SENT_53	[p3l612t2525r860b2601],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l900t2525r1018b2584],
12	NCOOP	NN	O	ncoop	nn	13	SENT_53	[p3l1049t2529r1326b2584],
13	study	NN	O	study	dep	8	SENT_53	[p3l1360t2525r1538b2602],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_53	[p3l1571t2525r1681b2596],
15	R2	NN	O	r2	nn	16	SENT_53	[p3l1571t2525r1681b2596],
16	sample	NN	O	sample	dep	8	SENT_53	[p3l1717t2525r1965b2601],
17	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	20	SENT_53	[p3l1717t2525r1965b2601],
18	only	RB	O	only	advmod	20	SENT_53	[p3l2004t2525r2146b2602],
19	current	JJ	DATE	current	amod	20	SENT_53	[p3l10t2634r247b2680],
20	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	dep	16	SENT_53	[p3l297t2622r562b2680],
21	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	22	SENT_53	[p3l611t2643r762b2680],
22	considered	VBN	O	consider	rcmod	6	SENT_53	[p3l813t2622r1179b2680],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l813t2622r1179b2680],

1	However	RB	O	however	advmod	28	SENT_54	[p3l1233t2626r1541b2689],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1233t2626r1541b2689],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1593t2624r1656b2679],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_54	[p3l1705t2622r1805b2680],
5	ESTHER	NNP	O	ESTHER	nn	6	SENT_54	[p3l1855t2625r2145b2680],
6	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	28	SENT_54	[p3l10t2717r186b2795],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	9	SENT_54	[p3l219t2718r328b2788],
8	R3	NN	O	r3	nn	9	SENT_54	[p3l219t2718r328b2788],
9	sample	NN	O	sample	nsubj	28	SENT_54	[p3l363t2717r611b2794],
10	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	12	SENT_54	[p3l363t2717r611b2794],
11	former	JJ	O	former	amod	12	SENT_54	[p3l648t2717r872b2776],
12	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	nsubjpass	15	SENT_54	[p3l902t2717r1167b2776],
13	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	15	SENT_54	[p3l1197t2738r1348b2776],
14	also	RB	O	also	advmod	15	SENT_54	[p3l1380t2717r1500b2776],
15	considered	VBN	O	consider	rcmod	9	SENT_54	[p3l1534t2717r1901b2785],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1534t2717r1901b2785],
17	if	IN	O	if	mark	23	SENT_54	[p3l1934t2717r1986b2775],
18	they	PRP	O	they	nsubj	23	SENT_54	[p3l2007t2717r2146b2795],
19	had	VBD	O	have	aux	23	SENT_54	[p3l8t2814r128b2872],
20	been	VBN	O	be	cop	23	SENT_54	[p3l167t2814r318b2872],
21	regular	JJ	O	regular	amod	23	SENT_54	[p3l360t2814r587b2891],
22	heavy	JJ	O	heavy	amod	23	SENT_54	[p3l627t2814r813b2891],
23	smokers	NNS	O	smoker	advcl	15	SENT_54	[p3l853t2814r1117b2872],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1159t2816r1221b2872],
25	the	DT	DATE	the	det	27	SENT_54	[p3l1262t2814r1362b2872],
26	past	JJ	DATE	past	amod	27	SENT_54	[p3l1403t2825r1533b2890],
27	(	CD	NUMBER	(	prep_in	23	SENT_54	[p3l1579t2814r1697b2885],
28	see	VBP	O	see	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1579t2814r1697b2885],
29	also	RB	O	also	advmod	28	SENT_54	[p3l1740t2814r1860b2872],
30	below	IN	O	below	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1902t2814r2139b2884],
31	)	NN	O	)	prep_below	28	SENT_54	[p3l1902t2814r2139b2884],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1902t2814r2139b2884],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l10t2914r77b2967],
2	a	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_55	[p3l118t2930r151b2968],
3	subset	NN	O	subset	prep_in	24	SENT_55	[p3l191t2909r389b2968],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l431t2909r502b2968],
5	participants	NNS	O	participant	prep_of	3	SENT_55	[p3l533t2912r917b2986],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l959t2909r1031b2968],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_55	[p3l1062t2909r1161b2968],
8	R1	NN	O	r1	nn	11	SENT_55	[p3l1202t2914r1282b2968],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1330t2909r1448b2968],
10	R2	NN	O	r2	nn	11	SENT_55	[p3l1489t2914r1573b2968],
11	subsamples	NNS	O	subsample	prep_of	5	SENT_55	[p3l1617t2909r2000b2986],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1617t2909r2000b2986],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_55	[p3l2043t2909r2142b2968],
14	Fagerstrom	NNP	PERSON	Fagerstrom	nn	15	SENT_55	[p3l10t3009r376b3083],
15	test	NN	O	test	nsubjpass	24	SENT_55	[p3l410t3018r521b3065],
16	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l556t3006r649b3065],
17	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	18	SENT_55	[p3l683t3008r945b3065],
18	dependence	NN	O	dependence	prep_for	15	SENT_55	[p3l982t3006r1363b3082],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	21	SENT_55	[p3l1404t3006r1660b3077],
20	FTND	NN	O	ftnd	nn	21	SENT_55	[p3l1404t3006r1660b3077],
21	)	NN	O	)	dep	18	SENT_55	[p3l1404t3006r1660b3077],
22	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	24	SENT_55	[p3l1699t3027r1816b3065],
23	also	RB	O	also	advmod	24	SENT_55	[p3l1853t3006r1973b3065],
24	performed	VBN	O	perform	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l2009t3026r2139b3082, p3l9t3102r260b3161],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l2009t3026r2139b3082, p3l9t3102r260b3161],

1	Detailed	JJ	O	detailed	amod	2	SENT_56	[p3l303t3102r572b3161],
2	characteristics	NNS	O	characteristic	nsubjpass	9	SENT_56	[p3l611t3102r1066b3161],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1106t3102r1177b3161],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_56	[p3l1205t3102r1305b3161],
5	three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	7	SENT_56	[p3l1342t3102r1505b3161],
6	study	NN	O	study	nn	7	SENT_56	[p3l1544t3102r1720b3179],
7	populations	NNS	O	population	prep_of	2	SENT_56	[p3l1755t3102r2141b3178],
8	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_56	[p3l10t3219r105b3256],
9	shown	VBN	O	show	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l132t3198r340b3256],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l367t3201r429b3256],
11	Table	NNP	MISC	Table	nn	12	SENT_56	[p3l454t3198r631b3257],
12	I.	NNP	MISC	I.	prep_in	9	SENT_56	[p3l658t3203r697b3256],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_57	[p3l78t3294r200b3353],
2	three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	3	SENT_57	[p3l255t3294r417b3353],
3	population	NN	O	population	nsubjpass	9	SENT_57	[p3l471t3294r1315b3370],
4	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	6	SENT_57	[p3l471t3294r1315b3370],
5	representative	JJ	O	representative	amod	6	SENT_57	[p3l471t3294r1315b3370],
6	subsamples	NNS	O	subsample	dep	3	SENT_57	[p3l1371t3294r1737b3370],
7	have	VBP	O	have	aux	9	SENT_57	[p3l1791t3294r1938b3353],
8	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_57	[p3l1991t3294r2142b3353],
9	described	VBN	O	describe	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l10t3391r316b3449],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l342t3393r405b3449],
11	more	JJR	O	more	amod	12	SENT_57	[p3l433t3412r601b3449],
12	detail	NN	O	detail	prep_in	9	SENT_57	[p3l630t3391r806b3449],
13	elsewhere	RB	O	elsewhere	rcmod	12	SENT_57	[p3l834t3391r1141b3449],
14	[	RB	O	[	advmod	15	SENT_57	[p3l1178t3391r1339b3461],
15	Low	JJ	O	low	dep	13	SENT_57	[p3l1178t3391r1339b3461],
16	et	FW	O	et	nn	17	SENT_57	[p3l1365t3402r1420b3449],
17	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	12	SENT_57	[p3l1448t3391r1536b3458],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1448t3391r1536b3458],
19	2004	CD	DATE	2004	appos	17	SENT_57	[p3l1566t3397r1736b3458],
20	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1566t3397r1736b3458],
21	Holle	NNP	PERSON	Holle	dep	17	SENT_57	[p3l1766t3391r1940b3449],
22	et	FW	O	et	nn	23	SENT_57	[p3l1969t3403r2024b3449],
23	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	21	SENT_57	[p3l2052t3391r2141b3458],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l2052t3391r2141b3458],
25	2005	CD	DATE	2005	appos	23	SENT_57	[p3l10t3492r179b3554],
26	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l10t3492r179b3554],
27	Wichmann	NNP	PERSON	Wichmann	dep	17	SENT_57	[p3l205t3486r568b3545],
28	et	FW	O	et	nn	29	SENT_57	[p3l596t3498r652b3545],
29	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	27	SENT_57	[p3l678t3486r766b3554],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l678t3486r766b3554],
31	2005	CD	DATE	2005	appos	29	SENT_57	[p3l795t3492r964b3554],
32	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l795t3492r964b3554],
33	Twardella	NNP	O	Twardella	dep	17	SENT_57	[p3l992t3486r1311b3545],
34	et	FW	O	et	nn	35	SENT_57	[p3l1337t3498r1393b3545],
35	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	33	SENT_57	[p3l1419t3486r1507b3554],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1419t3486r1507b3554],
37	2006	CD	DATE	2006	num	38	SENT_57	[p3l1536t3487r1734b3557],
38	]	NN	O	]	appos	12	SENT_57	[p3l1536t3487r1734b3557],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1536t3487r1734b3557],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l78t24r146b78],
2	brief	NN	O	brief	prep_in	11	SENT_58	[p4l165t20r331b87],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l165t20r331b87],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_58	[p4l354t20r453b78],
5	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	nn	9	SENT_58	[p4l475t19r600b78],
6	sample	NN	O	sample	nn	9	SENT_58	[p4l621t20r845b96],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	9	SENT_58	[p4l871t20r1008b91],
8	R1	NN	O	r1	nn	9	SENT_58	[p4l871t20r1008b91],
9	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	11	SENT_58	[p4l871t20r1008b91],
10	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_58	[p4l1033t41r1150b78],
11	derived	VBN	O	derive	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1173t20r1411b78],
12	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1432t20r1591b78],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_58	[p4l1612t20r1711b78],
14	S3	NN	O	s3	prep_from	11	SENT_58	[p4l1733t23r1831b81],
15	/	:	O	/	punct	16	SENT_58	[p4l1733t23r1831b81],
16	F3	NN	O	f3	dep	14	SENT_58	[p4l1836t24r1910b78],
17	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_58	[p4l1939t20r2141b91],
18	1994	CD	DATE	1994	dep	16	SENT_58	[p4l1939t20r2141b91],
19	/	:	DATE	/	punct	16	SENT_58	[p4l1939t20r2141b91],
20	1995	CD	DATE	1995	dep	39	SENT_58	[p4l16t122r158b175],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l209t116r328b175],
22	10	CD	DATE	10	num	23	SENT_58	[p4l381t122r447b175],
23	years	NNS	DATE	year	npadvmod	24	SENT_58	[p4l494t137r656b194],
24	later	RBR	DATE	later	advmod	20	SENT_58	[p4l703t116r869b187],
25	)	RB	O	)	dep	31	SENT_58	[p4l703t116r869b187],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l923t116r1042b175],
27	S4	NN	O	s4	dep	31	SENT_58	[p4l1090t120r1163b175],
28	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	29	SENT_58	[p4l1215t117r1599b187],
29	1999/2001	CD	NUMBER	1999/2001	dep	27	SENT_58	[p4l1215t117r1599b187],
30	)	NN	O	)	nn	31	SENT_58	[p4l1215t117r1599b187],
31	surveys	NNS	O	survey	conj_and	20	SENT_58	[p4l1653t137r1886b194],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1935t116r2006b175],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	34	SENT_58	[p4l2043t116r2142b175],
34	MONICA/KORA	NN	O	monica/kora	prep_of	20	SENT_58	[p4l9t216r577b274],
35	study	NN	O	study	dep	39	SENT_58	[p4l627t213r803b290],
36	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	35	SENT_58	[p4l855t213r1275b289],
37	Cooperative	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cooperative	nn	39	SENT_58	[p4l855t213r1275b289],
38	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	39	SENT_58	[p4l1326t213r1544b272],
39	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	44	SENT_58	[p4l1595t213r1880b272],
40	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1931t215r1993b271],
41	the	DT	O	the	det	43	SENT_58	[p4l2043t213r2142b272],
42	Augsburg	NNP	LOCATION	Augsburg	nn	43	SENT_58	[p4l7t309r320b386],
43	Region	NNP	LOCATION	Region	prep_in	39	SENT_58	[p4l358t309r608b386],
44	)	NN	O	)	dep	16	SENT_58	[p4l358t309r608b386],
45	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	49	SENT_58	[p4l649t309r844b368],
46	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	49	SENT_58	[p4l881t311r928b368],
47	a	DT	O	a	det	49	SENT_58	[p4l966t330r998b368],
48	research	NN	O	research	nn	49	SENT_58	[p4l1034t309r1299b368],
49	platform	NN	O	platform	rcmod	14	SENT_58	[p4l1335t309r1619b385],
50	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1656t309r1748b368],
51	population	NN	O	population	prep_for	49	SENT_58	[p4l1784t309r2143b385],
52	based	VBN	O	base	partmod	51	SENT_58	[p4l7t404r188b463],
53	health	NN	O	health	nn	54	SENT_58	[p4l225t404r423b463],
54	research	NN	O	research	dobj	52	SENT_58	[p4l461t404r741b463],
55	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l461t404r741b463],

1	Out	IN	O	out	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l783t408r909b463],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l947t404r1018b463],
3	9,117	CD	NUMBER	9,117	num	4	SENT_59	[p4l1046t410r1216b472],
4	participants	NNS	O	participant	prep_out_of	27	SENT_59	[p4l1254t407r1638b481],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l1677t404r1748b463],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_59	[p4l1775t404r1874b463],
7	S3	NN	O	s3	nn	10	SENT_59	[p4l1913t408r1983b463],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l2024t404r2143b463],
9	S4	NN	O	s4	nn	10	SENT_59	[p4l10t505r83b560],
10	surveys	NNS	O	survey	prep_of	4	SENT_59	[p4l123t522r356b578],
11	drawn	VBN	O	draw	partmod	10	SENT_59	[p4l397t501r599b560],
12	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l638t501r797b560],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_59	[p4l834t501r934b560],
14	southern	JJ	O	southern	amod	16	SENT_59	[p4l973t501r1260b560],
15	German	JJ	MISC	german	amod	16	SENT_59	[p4l1300t505r1561b560],
16	population	NN	O	population	prep_from	11	SENT_59	[p4l1599t501r1958b577],
17	aged	JJ	O	aged	amod	16	SENT_59	[p4l1997t501r2143b578],
18	25-84	CD	NUMBER	25-84	num	19	SENT_59	[p4l10t603r205b656],
19	years	NNS	NUMBER	year	tmod	17	SENT_59	[p4l258t618r438b674],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l258t618r438b674],
21	N	NN	O	n	nsubjpass	27	SENT_59	[p4l493t602r551b655],
22	=	JJ	O	=	amod	21	SENT_59	[p4l570t624r624b644],
23	1,412	CD	NUMBER	1,412	num	24	SENT_59	[p4l650t603r813b665],
24	subjects	NNS	O	subject	dep	22	SENT_59	[p4l870t597r1122b674],
25	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	27	SENT_59	[p4l1174t618r1324b656],
26	randomly	RB	O	randomly	advmod	27	SENT_59	[p4l1379t597r1696b674],
27	selected	VBN	O	select	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l1748t597r1997b656],
28	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l2051t597r2143b656],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_59	[p4l9t693r108b752],
30	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	31	SENT_59	[p4l141t705r378b770],
31	study	NN	O	study	prep_for	27	SENT_59	[p4l413t693r602b771],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l413t693r602b771],

1	See	VB	O	see	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l641t697r743b752],
2	Keil	NNP	O	Keil	nsubj	5	SENT_60	[p4l777t693r903b752],
3	et	FW	O	et	nn	5	SENT_60	[p4l938t705r994b752],
4	al.	FW	O	al.	nn	5	SENT_60	[p4l1029t693r1096b752],
5	[	FW	O	[	ccomp	1	SENT_60	[p4l1143t694r1364b764],
6	1998	CD	DATE	1998	num	7	SENT_60	[p4l1143t694r1364b764],
7	]	CD	NUMBER	]	dobj	5	SENT_60	[p4l1143t694r1364b764],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l1143t694r1364b764],
9	Holle	NNP	PERSON	Holle	appos	7	SENT_60	[p4l1401t693r1577b752],
10	et	FW	O	et	nn	12	SENT_60	[p4l1612t705r1667b752],
11	al.	FW	O	al.	nn	12	SENT_60	[p4l1702t693r1770b752],
12	[	FW	O	[	rcmod	9	SENT_60	[p4l1816t694r2037b764],
13	2005	CD	DATE	2005	number	14	SENT_60	[p4l1816t694r2037b764],
14	]	CD	NUMBER	]	dobj	12	SENT_60	[p4l1816t694r2037b764],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l1816t694r2037b764],
16	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l2075t714r2143b752],
17	Wichmann	NNP	PERSON	Wichmann	conj_or	14	SENT_60	[p4l7t790r372b848],
18	et	FW	O	et	dep	17	SENT_60	[p4l393t801r448b848],
19	al.	FW	O	al.	nn	20	SENT_60	[p4l469t790r537b848],
20	[	FW	O	[	dep	17	SENT_60	[p4l569t790r765b860],
21	2005	CD	DATE	2005	num	22	SENT_60	[p4l569t790r765b860],
22	]	NN	O	]	dep	20	SENT_60	[p4l569t790r765b860],
23	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l795t789r888b848],
24	a	DT	O	a	det	26	SENT_60	[p4l909t811r940b848],
25	further	JJ	O	further	amod	26	SENT_60	[p4l960t789r1187b848],
26	description	NN	O	description	prep_for	12	SENT_60	[p4l1207t790r1570b866],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l1592t790r1663b848],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_60	[p4l1674t790r1773b848],
29	MONICA	NNP	O	MONICA	prep_of	5	SENT_60	[p4l1793t793r2141b851],
30	/	:	O	/	punct	33	SENT_60	[p4l1793t793r2141b851],
31	KORA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	KORA	nn	33	SENT_60	[p4l10t890r224b945],
32	study	NN	O	study	nn	33	SENT_60	[p4l250t886r426b964],
33	procedures	NNS	O	procedure	dep	29	SENT_60	[p4l448t886r807b963],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l834t886r953b945],
35	characteristics	NNS	O	characteristic	dep	29	SENT_60	[p4l979t886r1451b945],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p4l979t886r1451b945],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_61	[p4l78t983r200b1042],
2	second	JJ	ORDINAL	second	amod	6	SENT_61	[p4l226t983r447b1042],
3	sample	NN	O	sample	nn	6	SENT_61	[p4l472t983r696b1059],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_61	[p4l725t983r862b1054],
5	R2	NN	O	r2	nn	6	SENT_61	[p4l725t983r862b1054],
6	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	8	SENT_61	[p4l725t983r862b1054],
7	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_61	[p4l890t1004r1007b1042],
8	recruited	VBN	O	recruit	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l1033t983r1323b1042],
9	within	IN	O	within	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l1346t983r1556b1042],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_61	[p4l1580t983r1679b1042],
11	framework	NN	O	framework	prep_within	8	SENT_61	[p4l1704t983r2058b1042],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l2081t983r2152b1042],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_61	[p4l8t1079r108b1138],
14	cooperation	NN	O	cooperation	nn	15	SENT_61	[p4l139t1081r528b1155],
15	study	NN	O	study	prep_of	11	SENT_61	[p4l558t1079r735b1156],
16	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l762t1100r844b1138],
17	nicotine	NN	O	nicotine	nn	18	SENT_61	[p4l874t1081r1137b1138],
18	addiction	NN	O	addiction	prep_on	15	SENT_61	[p4l1168t1079r1474b1138],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	21	SENT_61	[p4l1509t1079r1836b1150],
20	NCOOP	NN	O	ncoop	nn	21	SENT_61	[p4l1509t1079r1836b1150],
21	)	NN	O	)	dobj	8	SENT_61	[p4l1509t1079r1836b1150],
22	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	24	SENT_61	[p4l1871t1079r1998b1138],
23	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	24	SENT_61	[p4l2025t1100r2142b1138],
24	performed	VBN	O	perform	rcmod	21	SENT_61	[p4l9t1175r351b1252],
25	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l379t1178r441b1233],
26	ﬁve	JJ	O	ﬁve	amod	28	SENT_61	[p4l468t1175r580b1234],
27	German	JJ	MISC	german	amod	28	SENT_61	[p4l609t1179r870b1234],
28	cities	NNS	O	city	prep_in	24	SENT_61	[p4l899t1178r1076b1234],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p4l899t1178r1076b1234],
