1	Journal	NNP	O	Journal	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1225t81r1378b110],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1390t81r1428b110],
3	Medical	NNP	O	Medical	nn	4	SENT_1	[p1l1436t81r1589b110],
4	Virology	NNP	O	Virology	prep_of	1	SENT_1	[p1l1600t81r1767b117],
5	83:871	CD	NUMBER	83:871	num	6	SENT_1	[p1l1778t82r1976b110],
6	—	NN	O	—	dep	1	SENT_1	[p1l1778t82r1976b110],
7	878	CD	NUMBER	878	number	8	SENT_1	[p1l1778t82r1976b110],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	6	SENT_1	[p1l1989t81r2100b114],
9	2011	CD	DATE	2011	num	10	SENT_1	[p1l1989t81r2100b114],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	8	SENT_1	[p1l1989t81r2100b114],

1	Association	NNP	O	Association	dep	14	SENT_2	[p1l58t248r509b305],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l534t248r610b305],
3	IL28B	NNP	O	IL28B	nn	4	SENT_2	[p1l631t249r856b305],
4	Variants	NNS	O	variant	prep_of	1	SENT_2	[p1l882t248r1217b305],
5	With	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1240t248r1424b305],
6	Response	NN	O	response	prep_with	1	SENT_2	[p1l1449t249r1814b319],
7	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1840t253r1914b305],
8	Pegylated-Interferon	NNP	O	Pegylated-Interferon	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l61t330r878b401],
9	Alpha	NNP	O	Alpha	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l900t330r1131b401],
10	Plus	NNP	O	Plus	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l1155t330r1324b387],
11	Ribavirin	NNP	O	Ribavirin	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l1349t330r1723b387],
12	Combination	NNP	O	Combination	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l62t412r565b469],
13	Therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_to	6	SENT_2	[p1l589t412r917b483],
14	Reveals	VBZ	O	reveal	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l940t412r1239b469],
15	Intersubgenotypic	JJ	O	intersubgenotypic	amod	16	SENT_2	[p1l1265t412r1980b483],
16	Differences	NNS	O	difference	dobj	14	SENT_2	[p1l61t494r503b551],
17	Between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l528t495r862b551],
18	Genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	prep_between	14	SENT_2	[p1l888t494r1294b565],
19	2a	NN	O	2a	nsubj	14	SENT_2	[p1l1319t497r1406b551],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1432t494r1576b551],
21	2b	NN	O	2b	nsubj	14	SENT_2	[p1l1600t494r1686b551],

1	Naoya	NNP	PERSON	Naoya	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l60t655r189b692],
2	Sakamoto	NNP	PERSON	Sakamoto	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l203t654r414b690],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l203t654r414b690],
4	MD	NNP	O	MD	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l428t663r487b690],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l428t663r487b690],
6	PhD	NNP	O	PhD	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l505t645r643b691],
7	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l505t645r643b691],
8	’	NN	O	’	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l505t645r643b691],
9	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l505t645r643b691],
10	*	CD	NUMBER	*	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l505t645r643b691],
11	Mina	NNP	PERSON	Mina	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l658t654r762b684],
12	Nakagawa	NNP	PERSON	Nakagawa	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l775t647r1015b692],
13	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l775t647r1015b692],
14	Yasuhito	NNP	PERSON	Yasuhito	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1028t654r1210b684],
15	Tanaka	NNP	PERSON	Tanaka	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1224t647r1405b690],
16	,3	CD	NUMBER	,3	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1224t647r1405b690],
17	Yuko	NNP	PERSON	Yuko	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1416t654r1522b684],
18	Sekine-Osajima	NNP	PERSON	Sekine-Osajima	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1538t647r1882b692],
19	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1538t647r1882b692],
20	Mayumi	NNP	PERSON	Mayumi	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l60t698r225b736],
21	Ueyama	NNP	PERSON	Ueyama	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l238t691r430b736],
22	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l238t691r430b736],
23	Masayuki	NNP	PERSON	Masayuki	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l444t698r642b736],
24	Kurosaki	NNP	PERSON	Kurosaki	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l655t691r871b734],
25	,4	CD	NUMBER	,4	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l655t691r871b734],
26	Nao	NNP	O	Nao	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l884t698r964b728],
27	Nishida	NNP	O	Nishida	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l977t691r1164b734],
28	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l977t691r1164b734],
29	Akihiro	NNP	PERSON	Akihiro	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1175t698r1333b728],
30	Tamori	NNP	PERSON	Tamori	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1346t691r1523b734],
31	,6	CD	NUMBER	,6	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1346t691r1523b734],
32	Nishimura-Sakurai	NNP	O	Nishimura-Sakurai	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1536t698r1930b728],
33	Yuki	NNP	PERSON	Yuki	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1941t691r2065b734],
34	,1	NNP	O	,1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1941t691r2065b734],
35	Yasuhiro	NNP	PERSON	Yasuhiro	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l59t741r244b772],
36	Itsui	NNP	PERSON	Itsui	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l258t734r406b777],
37	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l258t734r406b777],
38	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l258t734r406b777],
39	7	CD	NUMBER	7	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l258t734r406b777],
40	Seishin	NNP	PERSON	Seishin	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l421t741r570b772],
41	Azuma	NNP	PERSON	Azuma	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l582t734r749b777],
42	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l582t734r749b777],
43	Sei	NNP	O	Sei	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l765t741r825b772],
44	Kakinuma	NNP	O	Kakinuma	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l839t734r1104b777],
45	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l839t734r1104b777],
46	’	NN	O	’	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l839t734r1104b777],
47	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l839t734r1104b777],
48	Shuhei	NNP	PERSON	Shuhei	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1119t741r1261b772],
49	Hige	NNP	PERSON	Hige	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1274t734r1397b779],
50	,8	CD	NUMBER	,8	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1274t734r1397b779],
51	Yoshito	NNP	PERSON	Yoshito	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1409t741r1564b772],
52	Itoh	NNP	PERSON	Itoh	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1577t735r1690b778],
53	,9	CD	NUMBER	,9	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1577t735r1690b778],
54	Eiji	NNP	PERSON	Eiji	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1703t741r1775b779],
55	Tanaka	NNP	PERSON	Tanaka	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1788t734r1986b777],
56	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1788t734r1986b777],
57	°	CD	NUMBER	°	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1788t734r1986b777],
58	Yoichi	NNP	PERSON	Yoichi	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l59t785r190b815],
59	Hiasa	NNP	PERSON	Hiasa	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l203t778r363b821],
60	,11	CD	NUMBER	,11	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l203t778r363b821],
61	Namiki	NNP	PERSON	Namiki	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l377t785r526b815],
62	Izumi	NNP	PERSON	Izumi	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l540t778r685b821],
63	,4	CD	NUMBER	,4	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l540t778r685b821],
64	Katsushi	NNP	PERSON	Katsushi	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l698t785r878b815],
65	Tokunaga	NNP	PERSON	Tokunaga	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l891t778r1124b823],
66	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l891t778r1124b823],
67	Masashi	NNP	PERSON	Masashi	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1136t785r1304b815],
68	Mizokami	NNP	PERSON	Mizokami	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1317t778r1736b821],
69	,12	CD	NUMBER	,12	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1317t778r1736b821],
70	Mamoru	NNP	PERSON	Mamoru	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1317t778r1736b821],
71	Watanabe1	NNP	PERSON	Watanabe1	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1747t778r1966b815],
72	and	CC	O	and	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1981t785r2057b815],
73	the	DT	O	the	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l60t829r125b859],
74	Ochanomizu-Liver	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ochanomizu-Liver	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l139t829r519b859],
75	Conference	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Conference	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l533t829r765b859],
76	Study	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Study	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l780t829r899b867],
77	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l911t829r1040b867],
78	1Department	NN	O	1department	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l61t878r279b921],
79	of	IN	O	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l291t885r327b920],
80	Gastroenterology	NNP	O	Gastroenterology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l335t885r623b921],
81	and	CC	O	and	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l635t884r702b913],
82	Hepatology	NNP	O	Hepatology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l713t885r913b921],
83	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l713t885r913b921],
84	Tokyo	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tokyo	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l930t885r1029b921],
85	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1040t884r1178b913],
86	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1191t885r1258b913],
87	Dental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dental	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1269t885r1384b913],
88	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1400t885r1583b921],
89	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1400t885r1583b921],
90	Tokyo	NNP	LOCATION	Tokyo	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1600t885r1707b921],
91	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1600t885r1707b921],
92	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1721t885r1830b921],
93	2Department	NNP	O	2Department	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l59t920r279b962],
94	for	IN	O	for	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l289t926r339b962],
95	Hepatitis	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hepatitis	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l349t927r506b962],
96	Control	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Control	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l522t926r656b961],
97	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l522t926r656b961],
98	Tokyo	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tokyo	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l673t927r772b962],
99	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l783t926r921b955],
100	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l934t926r1001b955],
101	Dental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dental	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1011t927r1127b955],
102	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1143t927r1326b962],
103	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1143t927r1326b962],
104	Tokyo	NNP	LOCATION	Tokyo	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1343t927r1450b962],
105	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1343t927r1450b962],
106	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1464t927r1573b962],
107	3Depart	NNP	O	3Depart	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l60t962r193b1005],
108	nt	NN	O	nt	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l244t973r279b997],
109	of	IN	O	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l291t969r327b1005],
110	Virology	NNP	O	Virology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l334t969r476b1005],
111	&	CC	O	&	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l491t969r518b998],
112	Liver	NN	O	liver	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l531t969r622b998],
113	Unit	NN	O	unit	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l637t969r719b1003],
114	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l637t969r719b1003],
115	Nagoya	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nagoya	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l733t969r864b1005],
116	City	NNP	ORGANIZATION	City	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l877t969r946b1005],
117	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l962t969r1137b1005],
118	Graduate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Graduate	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1151t969r1312b998],
119	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1325t969r1438b998],
120	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1450t969r1487b1005],
121	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1491t969r1629b998],
122	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1643t969r1793b1003],
123	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1643t969r1793b1003],
124	M	NN	O	m	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l58t1011r96b1038],
125	izuho	NN	O	izuho	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l96t1010r199b1039],
126	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l96t1010r199b1039],
127	Nagoya	NNP	LOCATION	Nagoya	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l255t1011r393b1046],
128	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l255t1011r393b1046],
129	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l407t1011r517b1046],
130	4Division	NN	O	4division	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l60t1045r217b1081],
131	of	IN	O	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l230t1052r267b1088],
132	Gastroenterology	NNP	O	Gastroenterology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l274t1052r562b1088],
133	and	CC	O	and	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l575t1052r642b1081],
134	Hepatology	NNP	O	Hepatology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l652t1052r852b1088],
135	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l652t1052r852b1088],
136	Musashino	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Musashino	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l866t1052r1056b1081],
137	Red	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Red	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1068t1052r1136b1081],
138	Cross	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cross	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1149t1052r1241b1081],
139	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1254t1052r1409b1088],
140	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1254t1052r1409b1088],
141	Tokyo	NNP	LOCATION	Tokyo	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1426t1052r1533b1088],
142	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1426t1052r1533b1088],
143	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1547t1053r1656b1088],
144	5Department	NN	O	5department	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l60t1087r279b1130],
145	of	IN	O	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l291t1094r327b1129],
146	Human	JJ	O	human	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l332t1094r463b1122],
147	Genetics	NNP	O	Genetics	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l477t1094r627b1128],
148	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l477t1094r627b1128],
149	Graduate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Graduate	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l644t1094r805b1122],
150	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l818t1094r931b1122],
151	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l944t1094r980b1129],
152	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l984t1094r1149b1128],
153	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l984t1094r1149b1128],
154	The	NNP	ORGANIZATION	The	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1166t1094r1228b1122],
155	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1244t1094r1419b1130],
156	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1432t1094r1468b1129],
157	Tokyo	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tokyo	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1476t1094r1583b1130],
158	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1476t1094r1583b1130],
159	Tokyo	NNP	LOCATION	Tokyo	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1600t1094r1707b1130],
160	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1600t1094r1707b1130],
161	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1721t1094r1830b1130],
162	6Department	NNP	O	6Department	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l60t1129r279b1171],
163	of	IN	O	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l291t1135r327b1171],
164	Hepatology	NNP	O	Hepatology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l332t1136r532b1171],
165	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l332t1136r532b1171],
166	Osaka	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Osaka	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l549t1135r656b1164],
167	City	NNP	ORGANIZATION	City	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l670t1135r738b1171],
168	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l754t1136r929b1171],
169	Graduate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Graduate	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l943t1135r1104b1164],
170	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1117t1135r1230b1164],
171	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1243t1135r1279b1171],
172	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1283t1135r1448b1169],
173	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1283t1135r1448b1169],
174	Osaka	NNP	LOCATION	Osaka	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1465t1135r1579b1169],
175	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1465t1135r1579b1169],
176	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1593t1136r1702b1171],
177	7Department	NNP	O	7Department	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l62t1170r279b1212],
178	of	IN	O	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l291t1177r327b1212],
179	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l332t1177r473b1205],
180	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l484t1177r649b1211],
181	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l484t1177r649b1211],
182	Soka	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Soka	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l664t1177r748b1205],
183	Municipal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Municipal	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l759t1177r938b1212],
184	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l949t1177r1104b1212],
185	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l949t1177r1104b1212],
186	Saitama	NNP	LOCATION	Saitama	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1120t1177r1274b1211],
187	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1120t1177r1274b1211],
188	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1288t1177r1397b1212],
189	8Department	NN	O	8department	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l60t1212r279b1254],
190	of	IN	O	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l291t1218r327b1254],
191	Internal	JJ	ORGANIZATION	internal	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l332t1218r473b1247],
192	Medicine	NN	ORGANIZATION	medicine	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l484t1218r649b1252],
193	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l484t1218r649b1252],
194	Hokkaido	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hokkaido	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l663t1218r829b1247],
195	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l845t1219r1020b1254],
196	Graduate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Graduate	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1034t1218r1196b1247],
197	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1209t1218r1321b1247],
198	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1334t1218r1370b1254],
199	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1375t1218r1539b1252],
200	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1375t1218r1539b1252],
201	Sapporo	NNP	LOCATION	Sapporo	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1555t1218r1704b1254],
202	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1555t1218r1704b1254],
203	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1718t1219r1827b1254],
204	9Molecular	NNP	O	9Molecular	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l60t1253r248b1288],
205	Gastroenterology	NNP	O	Gastroenterology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l261t1260r549b1296],
206	and	CC	O	and	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l562t1260r629b1288],
207	Hepatology	NNP	O	Hepatology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l639t1260r839b1296],
208	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l639t1260r839b1296],
209	Kyoto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kyoto	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l854t1260r950b1296],
210	Prefectural	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Prefectural	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l962t1260r1152b1295],
211	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1169t1260r1343b1296],
212	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1356t1260r1392b1295],
213	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1397t1260r1561b1294],
214	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1397t1260r1561b1294],
215	Kyoto	NNP	LOCATION	Kyoto	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1575t1260r1680b1296],
216	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1575t1260r1680b1296],
217	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1694t1260r1803b1296],
218	10Department	NNP	O	10Department	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l61t1295r294b1338],
219	of	IN	O	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l306t1302r343b1338],
220	Medicine	NNP	MISC	Medicine	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l347t1302r511b1336],
221	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l347t1302r511b1336],
222	Shinshu	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Shinshu	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l527t1302r670b1331],
223	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l687t1302r862b1338],
224	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l875t1302r988b1331],
225	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1000t1302r1037b1338],
226	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1041t1302r1205b1336],
227	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1041t1302r1205b1336],
228	Matsumoto	NNP	PERSON	Matsumoto	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1219t1302r1421b1336],
229	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1219t1302r1421b1336],
230	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1435t1302r1544b1338],
231	”	NNP	O	”	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l61t1337r294b1379],
232	Department	NNP	O	Department	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l61t1337r294b1379],
233	of	IN	O	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l306t1343r343b1379],
234	Gastroenterology	NNP	O	Gastroenterology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l350t1343r638b1379],
235	and	CC	O	and	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l651t1343r717b1372],
236	Metabology	NNP	O	Metabology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l728t1343r932b1379],
237	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l728t1343r932b1379],
238	Ehime	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ehime	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l946t1343r1058b1372],
239	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1074t1344r1249b1379],
240	Graduate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Graduate	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1263t1343r1424b1372],
241	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1437t1343r1550b1372],
242	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1563t1343r1599b1379],
243	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1603t1343r1768b1377],
244	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1603t1343r1768b1377],
245	Ehime	NNP	O	Ehime	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1782t1343r1902b1377],
246	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1782t1343r1902b1377],
247	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1916t1344r2025b1379],
248	12Research	NNP	O	12Research	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l61t1379r244b1414],
249	Center	NNP	O	Center	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l259t1385r370b1414],
250	for	IN	O	for	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l380t1385r430b1421],
251	Hepatitis	NNP	O	Hepatitis	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l440t1386r597b1421],
252	and	CC	O	and	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l611t1385r677b1414],
253	Immunology	NNP	O	Immunology	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l688t1385r912b1421],
254	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l688t1385r912b1421],
255	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	International	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l926t1385r1156b1414],
256	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1167t1385r1305b1414],
257	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1319t1385r1431b1414],
258	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1442t1385r1478b1421],
259	Japan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Japan	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1483t1386r1593b1421],
260	Konodai	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Konodai	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1605t1385r1748b1414],
261	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1761t1385r1915b1421],
262	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1761t1385r1915b1421],
263	Ichikawa	NNP	PERSON	Ichikawa	dep	265	SENT_3	[p1l1930t1385r2097b1419],
264	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1930t1385r2097b1419],
265	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l58t1427r168b1463],

1	Genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	2	SENT_4	[p1l119t1677r434b1744],
2	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubjpass	13	SENT_4	[p1l488t1678r1147b1760],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1199t1677r1280b1744],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_4	[p1l1324t1678r1454b1744],
5	interleukin	NN	O	interleukin	nn	6	SENT_4	[p1l1509t1678r1944b1744],
6	28B	NN	O	28b	prep_of	2	SENT_4	[p1l1999t1678r2149b1744],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	8	SENT_4	[p1l119t1779r400b1853],
8	|	CD	NUMBER	|	dep	6	SENT_4	[p1l119t1779r400b1853],
9	L28B	NN	O	l28b	nn	11	SENT_4	[p1l119t1779r400b1853],
10	)	NN	O	)	nn	11	SENT_4	[p1l119t1779r400b1853],
11	locus	NN	O	locus	dep	8	SENT_4	[p1l462t1779r676b1846],
12	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_4	[p1l733t1798r858b1846],
13	associated	VBN	O	associate	dep	20	SENT_4	[p1l915t1779r1353b1846],
14	closely	RB	O	closely	advmod	13	SENT_4	[p1l1411t1779r1701b1862],
15	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1751t1779r1928b1846],
16	outcomes	NNS	O	outcome	prep_with	13	SENT_4	[p1l1989t1787r2151b1846, p1l116t1900r389b1948],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l411t1881r492b1948],
18	pegy	JJ	O	pegy	amod	19	SENT_4	[p1l512t1881r1365b1965],
19	|	NN	O	|	prep_of	16	SENT_4	[p1l512t1881r1365b1965],
20	ated	VBD	O	ate	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l512t1881r1365b1965],
21	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	24	SENT_4	[p1l512t1881r1365b1965],
22	interferon	NN	O	interferon	nn	24	SENT_4	[p1l512t1881r1365b1965],
23	(	NN	O	(	nn	24	SENT_4	[p1l1392t1881r1794b1956],
24	PEG	NN	O	peg	nsubj	28	SENT_4	[p1l1392t1881r1794b1956],
25	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	26	SENT_4	[p1l1392t1881r1794b1956],
26	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	28	SENT_4	[p1l1392t1881r1794b1956],
27	FN	NN	O	fn	nn	28	SENT_4	[p1l1392t1881r1794b1956],
28	)	NN	O	)	xcomp	20	SENT_4	[p1l1392t1881r1794b1956],
29	plus	CC	O	plus	prep	28	SENT_4	[p1l1822t1882r1992b1964],
30	ribavirin	NNP	O	ribavirin	nn	32	SENT_4	[p1l2017t1882r2151b1948, p1l117t1984r344b2050],
31	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	32	SENT_4	[p1l376t1984r602b2058],
32	RBV	NN	O	rbv	dep	29	SENT_4	[p1l376t1984r602b2058],
33	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	35	SENT_4	[p1l376t1984r602b2058],
34	combination	NN	O	combination	nn	35	SENT_4	[p1l628t1984r1153b2050],
35	therapy	NN	O	therapy	nsubj	20	SENT_4	[p1l1178t1984r1519b2066],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1178t1984r1519b2066],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_5	[p1l1544t1984r1699b2050],
2	aim	NN	O	aim	nn	5	SENT_5	[p1l1724t1984r1872b2050],
3	ofthis	NN	O	ofthi	nn	5	SENT_5	[p1l1901t1983r2151b2050],
4	study	NN	O	study	nn	5	SENT_5	[p1l116t2085r346b2168],
5	wasto	NN	O	wasto	nsubj	6	SENT_5	[p1l362t2093r625b2152],
6	investigate	VBP	O	investigate	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l651t2085r1104b2168],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_5	[p1l1123t2085r1253b2152],
8	relationship	NN	O	relationship	dobj	6	SENT_5	[p1l1279t2085r1772b2168],
9	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1798t2085r2146b2152],
10	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	12	SENT_5	[p1l121t2189r342b2255],
11	L28B	NN	O	l28b	nn	12	SENT_5	[p1l121t2189r342b2255],
12	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	prep_between	8	SENT_5	[p1l370t2189r980b2271],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1010t2189r1158b2255],
14	responses	NNS	O	response	prep_between	8	SENT_5	[p1l1190t2207r1612b2271],
15	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1632t2197r1711b2255],
16	therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_to	6	SENT_5	[p1l1734t2189r2055b2271],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l2081t2189r2146b2254],
18	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	16	SENT_5	[p1l120t2290r449b2373],
19	infected	VBN	O	infect	partmod	18	SENT_5	[p1l487t2289r813b2357],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l848t2290r1025b2357],
21	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	19	SENT_5	[p1l1066t2298r1456b2373],
22	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	21	SENT_5	[p1l1493t2292r1556b2356],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1493t2292r1556b2356],

1	One	CD	NUMBER	one	num	4	SENT_6	[p1l1596t2289r1762b2357],
2	hundred	CD	NUMBER	hundred	number	3	SENT_6	[p1l1802t2290r2147b2357],
3	twenty	CD	NUMBER	twenty	amod	4	SENT_6	[p1l113t2392r613b2475],
4	—	NN	O	—	nsubjpass	28	SENT_6	[p1l113t2392r613b2475],
5	nine	CD	NUMBER	nine	num	9	SENT_6	[p1l113t2392r613b2475],
6	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	9	SENT_6	[p1l644t2392r952b2459],
7	hepatitis	NN	O	hepatitis	nn	9	SENT_6	[p1l987t2392r1340b2475],
8	C	NN	O	c	nn	9	SENT_6	[p1l1372t2391r1424b2459],
9	patients	NNS	O	patient	dep	4	SENT_6	[p1l1458t2392r1787b2475],
10	infected	VBN	O	infect	partmod	9	SENT_6	[p1l1822t2391r2147b2459],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l114t2494r290b2561],
12	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	10	SENT_6	[p1l362t2502r753b2577],
13	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	12	SENT_6	[p1l821t2496r887b2571],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l821t2496r887b2571],
15	77	CD	NUMBER	77	num	16	SENT_6	[p1l954t2497r1045b2560],
16	patients	NNS	O	patient	conj_and	12	SENT_6	[p1l1117t2494r1446b2577],
17	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1511t2494r1686b2561],
18	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	19	SENT_6	[p1l1759t2502r2150b2577],
19	2a	NN	O	2a	prep_with	16	SENT_6	[p1l117t2598r206b2663],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l246t2596r394b2663],
21	52	CD	NUMBER	52	num	22	SENT_6	[p1l435t2598r525b2663],
22	patients	NNS	O	patient	conj_and	12	SENT_6	[p1l567t2596r895b2679],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l930t2596r1106b2663],
24	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	25	SENT_6	[p1l1148t2604r1538b2679],
25	2b	NN	O	2b	prep_with	22	SENT_6	[p1l1577t2596r1697b2672],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1577t2596r1697b2672],
27	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	28	SENT_6	[p1l1733t2615r1937b2663],
28	analyzed	VBN	O	analyze	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1974t2615r2151b2663, p1l121t2698r350b2781],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1974t2615r2151b2663, p1l121t2698r350b2781],

1	Clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	4	SENT_7	[p1l380t2697r678b2765],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l708t2698r857b2765],
3	laboratory	JJ	O	laboratory	conj_and	1	SENT_7	[p1l889t2699r1319b2781],
4	parameters	NNS	O	parameter	nsubjpass	19	SENT_7	[p1l1345t2706r1841b2781],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1345t2706r1841b2781],
6	including	VBG	O	include	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1871t2698r2151b2765, p1l120t2801r241b2884],
7	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	8	SENT_7	[p1l329t2801r631b2884],
8	variation	NN	O	variation	prep_including	4	SENT_7	[p1l711t2801r1076b2867],
9	near	IN	O	near	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1167t2819r1347b2867],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_7	[p1l1424t2801r1555b2867],
11	|	NN	O	|	nn	12	SENT_7	[p1l1643t2801r1864b2867],
12	L28B	NN	O	l28b	prep_near	8	SENT_7	[p1l1643t2801r1864b2867],
13	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	16	SENT_7	[p1l1949t2819r2150b2884],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_7	[p1l119t2902r620b2978],
15	rs8099917	NN	O	rs8099917	nn	16	SENT_7	[p1l119t2902r620b2978],
16	)	NN	O	)	dep	12	SENT_7	[p1l119t2902r620b2978],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l119t2902r620b2978],
18	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	19	SENT_7	[p1l690t2921r893b2969],
19	assessed	VBN	O	assess	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l967t2902r1364b2969],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l967t2902r1364b2969],

1	Drug	NN	O	drug	nn	2	SENT_8	[p1l1444t2902r1639b2985],
2	adherence	NN	O	adherence	nsubjpass	4	SENT_8	[p1l1715t2902r2150b2969],
3	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_8	[p1l114t3023r278b3071],
4	monitored	VBN	O	monitor	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l368t3004r798b3071],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l890t3004r955b3070],
6	each	DT	O	each	det	7	SENT_8	[p1l1045t3004r1232b3071],
7	patient	NN	O	patient	prep_in	4	SENT_8	[p1l1325t3004r1631b3087],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1325t3004r1631b3087],

1	Univariate	NNP	O	Univariate	nsubjpass	13	SENT_9	[p1l1724t3004r2150b3071],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l117t3107r266b3173],
3	multivariate	JJ	O	multivariate	amod	5	SENT_9	[p1l338t3107r835b3173],
4	statistical	JJ	O	statistical	amod	5	SENT_9	[p1l901t3107r1289b3173],
5	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	nsubjpass	13	SENT_9	[p1l1360t3107r1720b3189],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1786t3106r1867b3173],
7	these	DT	O	these	det	8	SENT_9	[p1l1925t3107r2150b3173],
8	parameters	NNS	O	parameter	prep_of	5	SENT_9	[p1l120t3216r592b3291],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l633t3208r781b3275],
10	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	11	SENT_9	[p1l825t3208r1109b3275],
11	responses	NNS	O	response	prep_of	5	SENT_9	[p1l1159t3227r1581b3291],
12	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_9	[p1l1619t3227r1823b3275],
13	carried	VBN	O	carry	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1864t3208r2147b3275],
14	out	RP	O	out	prt	13	SENT_9	[p1l117t3318r271b3377],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l117t3318r271b3377],

1	Univariate	JJ	O	univariate	amod	2	SENT_10	[p1l305t3310r731b3377],
2	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	nsubj	3	SENT_10	[p1l758t3310r1118b3393],
3	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1144t3310r1468b3377],
4	that	IN	O	that	complm	10	SENT_10	[p1l1494t3310r1656b3377],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_10	[p1l1681t3329r1720b3377],
6	sustained	JJ	O	sustained	amod	8	SENT_10	[p1l1748t3310r2147b3377],
7	virological	JJ	O	virological	amod	8	SENT_10	[p1l114t3413r550b3496],
8	response	NN	O	response	nsubjpass	10	SENT_10	[p1l590t3431r966b3495],
9	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_10	[p1l995t3431r1159b3479],
10	correlated	VBN	O	correlate	ccomp	3	SENT_10	[p1l1190t3413r1608b3479],
11	significantly	RB	O	significantly	advmod	10	SENT_10	[p1l1643t3412r2153b3496],
12	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l114t3515r290b3581],
13	|	NN	O	|	nn	15	SENT_10	[p1l333t3515r554b3581],
14	L28B	NN	O	l28b	nn	15	SENT_10	[p1l333t3515r554b3581],
15	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	prep_with	10	SENT_10	[p1l593t3515r1232b3597],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l593t3515r1232b3597],
17	as	RB	O	as	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1270t3533r1356b3581],
18	well	RB	O	well	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1389t3515r1554b3581],
19	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1595t3533r1681b3581],
20	age	NN	O	age	prep_with	10	SENT_10	[p1l1717t3533r1887b3598],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1717t3533r1887b3598],
22	white	JJ	O	white	amod	24	SENT_10	[p1l1921t3515r2150b3581],
23	blood	NN	O	blood	nn	24	SENT_10	[p1l120t3616r352b3683],
24	cell	NN	O	cell	conj_and	20	SENT_10	[p1l397t3616r530b3683],
25	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l578t3616r727b3683],
26	neutrophil	NN	O	neutrophil	nn	27	SENT_10	[p1l777t3616r1201b3699],
27	counts	NNS	O	count	conj_and	20	SENT_10	[p1l1248t3624r1551b3693],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1248t3624r1551b3693],
29	adherence	NN	O	adherence	nn	31	SENT_10	[p1l1595t3616r2030b3683],
30	to	TO	O	to	dep	31	SENT_10	[p1l2070t3624r2149b3683],
31	RBV	NN	O	rbv	conj_and	20	SENT_10	[p1l120t3719r312b3795],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l120t3719r312b3795],
33	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l356t3719r505b3785],
34	rapid	JJ	O	rapid	amod	36	SENT_10	[p1l554t3719r759b3801],
35	virological	JJ	O	virological	amod	36	SENT_10	[p1l802t3719r1238b3802],
36	response	NN	O	response	conj_and	20	SENT_10	[p1l1288t3737r1687b3801],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1288t3737r1687b3801],

1	Subgroup	NN	O	subgroup	nn	2	SENT_11	[p1l1733t3718r2150b3802],
2	analysis	NN	O	analysis	nsubj	3	SENT_11	[p2l117t17r453b99],
3	revealed	VBD	O	reveal	_	0	SENT_11	[p2l484t17r832b83],
4	that	IN	O	that	complm	10	SENT_11	[p2l859t17r1020b83],
5	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	10	SENT_11	[p2l1049t17r1378b99],
6	infected	VBN	O	infect	partmod	5	SENT_11	[p2l1408t16r1733b83],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_11	[p2l1760t17r1937b83],
8	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	6	SENT_11	[p2l1968t35r2151b100, p2l117t126r348b201],
9	2b	RB	O	2b	advmod	10	SENT_11	[p2l381t118r477b185],
10	achieved	VBD	O	achieve	ccomp	3	SENT_11	[p2l511t119r878b185],
11	significantly	RB	O	significantly	advmod	12	SENT_11	[p2l914t117r1425b201],
12	lower	JJR	O	lower	amod	16	SENT_11	[p2l1458t118r1689b185],
13	rapid	JJ	O	rapid	amod	16	SENT_11	[p2l1723t119r1928b201],
14	virological	JJ	O	virological	amod	16	SENT_11	[p2l1961t118r2151b185, p2l121t221r385b304],
15	response	NN	O	response	nn	16	SENT_11	[p2l427t239r804b303],
16	rates	NNS	O	rate	dobj	10	SENT_11	[p2l842t228r1039b287],
17	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_11	[p2l1069t221r1250b287],
18	those	DT	O	those	prep_than	16	SENT_11	[p2l1284t221r1515b287],
19	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_11	[p2l1545t221r1721b287],
20	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	21	SENT_11	[p2l1759t228r2150b304],
21	2a	NN	O	2a	prep_with	10	SENT_11	[p2l117t325r230b390],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p2l117t325r230b390],

1	Patients	NNS	O	patient	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l276t324r604b390],
2	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l639t324r816b390],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_12	[p2l855t324r985b390],
4	|	NN	O	|	nn	5	SENT_12	[p2l1027t324r1532b406],
5	L28B	NN	O	l28b	prep_with	1	SENT_12	[p2l1027t324r1532b406],
6	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	8	SENT_12	[p2l1027t324r1532b406],
7	major	JJ	O	major	amod	8	SENT_12	[p2l1027t324r1532b406],
8	allele	NN	O	allele	nsubj	9	SENT_12	[p2l1568t324r1784b390],
9	showed	VBD	O	show	rcmod	5	SENT_12	[p2l1823t324r2147b390],
10	higher	JJR	O	higher	amod	13	SENT_12	[p2l121t425r386b508],
11	virus	NN	O	virus	nn	13	SENT_12	[p2l426t425r630b492],
12	clearance	NN	O	clearance	nn	13	SENT_12	[p2l673t425r1069b492],
13	rates	NNS	O	rate	dobj	9	SENT_12	[p2l1118t433r1315b492],
14	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_12	[p2l1360t433r1433b492],
15	each	DT	O	each	det	17	SENT_12	[p2l1476t425r1663b492],
16	time	NN	O	time	nn	17	SENT_12	[p2l1708t425r1893b492],
17	point	NN	O	point	prep_at	13	SENT_12	[p2l1940t425r2152b508],

1	©	RB	O	©	advmod	2	SENT_13	[p2l6t632r64b690],
2	2011	CD	DATE	2011	_	0	SENT_13	[p2l95t628r284b690],
3	WILEY-LISS	NNP	O	WILEY-LISS	dep	2	SENT_13	[p2l311t626r881b702],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p2l311t626r881b702],
5	INC.	NNP	O	INC.	appos	3	SENT_13	[p2l910t626r1103b690],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p2l910t626r1103b690],

1	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l115t724r287b787],
2	those	DT	O	those	prep_than	16	SENT_14	[p2l326t724r544b787],
3	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l581t724r747b787],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_14	[p2l786t724r910b787],
5	|	NN	O	|	nn	6	SENT_14	[p2l952t724r1435b787],
6	L28B	NN	O	l28b	prep_with	2	SENT_14	[p2l952t724r1435b787],
7	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	9	SENT_14	[p2l952t724r1435b787],
8	minor	JJ	O	minor	amod	9	SENT_14	[p2l952t724r1435b787],
9	allele	NN	O	allele	nsubj	16	SENT_14	[p2l1472t724r1699b796],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l1472t724r1699b796],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l1739t724r1880b787],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_14	[p2l1918t724r2041b787],
13	differences	NNS	O	difference	conj_and	9	SENT_14	[p2l119t819r554b883],
14	were	VBD	O	be	cop	16	SENT_14	[p2l620t837r813b883],
15	more	RBR	O	more	advmod	16	SENT_14	[p2l885t837r1086b883],
16	profound	JJ	O	profound	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l1158t819r1519b898],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l1593t820r1656b882],
18	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	16	SENT_14	[p2l1731t820r2042b898],
19	infected	VBN	O	infect	partmod	18	SENT_14	[p2l121t916r429b980],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l466t917r632b980],
21	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	22	SENT_14	[p2l673t924r1042b996],
22	2b	NN	O	2b	prep_with	19	SENT_14	[p2l1079t917r1170b980],
23	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l1203t917r1375b980],
24	those	DT	O	those	prep_than	19	SENT_14	[p2l1412t917r1630b980],
25	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l1663t917r1830b980],
26	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	27	SENT_14	[p2l1870t934r2042b996, p2l119t1021r337b1092],
27	2a	NN	O	2a	prep_with	24	SENT_14	[p2l367t1014r473b1077],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p2l367t1014r473b1077],

1	Furthermore	RB	O	furthermore	advmod	10	SENT_15	[p2l508t1013r1025b1086],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l508t1013r1025b1086],
3	both	DT	O	both	det	4	SENT_15	[p2l1057t1013r1228b1077],
4	rapid	JJ	O	rapid	nsubjpass	10	SENT_15	[p2l1264t1013r1458b1092],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1490t1013r1630b1077],
6	sustained	JJ	O	sustained	amod	8	SENT_15	[p2l1661t1013r2039b1077],
7	virological	JJ	O	virological	amod	8	SENT_15	[p2l116t1111r527b1190],
8	responses	NNS	O	response	conj_and	4	SENT_15	[p2l594t1128r993b1189],
9	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_15	[p2l1048t1128r1240b1174],
10	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1299t1111r1714b1174],
11	significantly	RB	O	significantly	advmod	10	SENT_15	[p2l1774t1110r2042b1190, p2l118t1208r354b1286],
12	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l369t1208r535b1271],
13	|	NN	O	|	nn	15	SENT_15	[p2l563t1208r772b1271],
14	L28B	NN	O	l28b	nn	15	SENT_15	[p2l563t1208r772b1271],
15	alleles	NNS	O	allele	prep_with	10	SENT_15	[p2l794t1208r1041b1271],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1064t1208r1126b1270],
17	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	15	SENT_15	[p2l1153t1208r1464b1286],
18	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p2l1481t1208r1647b1271],
19	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	17	SENT_15	[p2l1672t1215r2042b1287],

1	Abbreviations	NNS	O	abbreviation	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l87t1446r562b1501],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l87t1446r562b1501],
3	HCV	NN	O	hcv	dep	1	SENT_16	[p2l606t1446r781b1513],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l606t1446r781b1513],
5	hepatitis	NN	O	hepatitis	appos	1	SENT_16	[p2l823t1446r1112b1514],
6	C	NN	O	c	nn	7	SENT_16	[p2l1153t1446r1198b1501],
7	virus	NN	O	virus	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l1237t1447r1422b1513],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1237t1447r1422b1513],
9	HCC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	HCC	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l1464t1446r1640b1513],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1464t1446r1640b1513],
11	hepatocellular	JJ	O	hepatocellular	amod	12	SENT_16	[p2l1681t1446r2152b1514],
12	carcinoma	NN	O	carcinoma	appos	9	SENT_16	[p2l9t1528r362b1593],
13	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l9t1528r362b1593],
14	IFN	NN	ORGANIZATION	ifn	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l432t1528r579b1593],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l432t1528r579b1593],
16	interferon	NN	O	interferon	appos	14	SENT_16	[p2l648t1527r995b1593],
17	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l648t1527r995b1593],
18	PEG-IFN	NN	O	peg-ifn	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l1064t1527r1390b1593],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1064t1527r1390b1593],
20	pegylated-interferon	NN	O	pegylated-interferon	appos	18	SENT_16	[p2l1458t1527r2149b1595],
21	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1458t1527r2149b1595],
22	RBV	NN	O	rbv	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l9t1608r176b1673],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l9t1608r176b1673],
24	ribavirin	NNP	O	ribavirin	appos	22	SENT_16	[p2l207t1606r514b1673],
25	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l207t1606r514b1673],
26	IL28B	NN	O	il28b	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l545t1608r765b1673],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l545t1608r765b1673],
28	interleukin	NN	O	interleukin	nn	29	SENT_16	[p2l796t1606r1165b1661],
29	28B	NN	O	28b	appos	26	SENT_16	[p2l1193t1608r1337b1673],
30	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1193t1608r1337b1673],
31	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l1369t1607r1564b1673],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1369t1607r1564b1673],
33	single	JJ	O	single	amod	35	SENT_16	[p2l1596t1607r1787b1675],
34	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	35	SENT_16	[p2l1815t1607r2152b1661],
35	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	appos	31	SENT_16	[p2l8t1686r527b1755],
36	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l8t1686r527b1755],
37	BMI	NNP	O	BMI	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l553t1688r715b1753],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l553t1688r715b1753],
39	body	NN	O	body	nn	41	SENT_16	[p2l741t1687r896b1755],
40	mass	NN	O	mass	nn	41	SENT_16	[p2l919t1705r1084b1741],
41	index	NN	O	index	appos	37	SENT_16	[p2l1108t1687r1304b1753],
42	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1108t1687r1304b1753],
43	ALT	NNP	O	ALT	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l1328t1687r1491b1753],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1328t1687r1491b1753],
45	alanine	NN	O	alanine	nn	46	SENT_16	[p2l1521t1687r1762b1741],
46	transaminase	NN	O	transaminase	appos	43	SENT_16	[p2l1786t1688r2150b1741, p2l11t1785r131b1833],
47	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1786t1688r2150b1741, p2l11t1785r131b1833],
48	ISDR	NNP	O	ISDR	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l167t1766r360b1833],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l167t1766r360b1833],
50	the	DT	O	the	det	52	SENT_16	[p2l395t1766r500b1821],
51	interferon	NN	O	interferon	nn	52	SENT_16	[p2l532t1766r861b1821],
52	sensitivity	NN	O	sensitivity	appos	48	SENT_16	[p2l895t1767r1236b1834],
53	determining	VBG	O	determine	partmod	5	SENT_16	[p2l1267t1766r1672b1834],
54	region	NN	O	region	dobj	53	SENT_16	[p2l1701t1767r1924b1834],
55	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1701t1767r1924b1834],
56	ITPA	NNP	O	ITPA	dep	5	SENT_16	[p2l1960t1767r2149b1833],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p2l1960t1767r2149b1833],
58	inosine	NN	O	inosine	nn	59	SENT_16	[p2l9t1848r242b1901],
59	triphosphatase	NN	O	triphosphatase	appos	56	SENT_16	[p2l266t1847r758b1915],

1	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	nn	2	SENT_17	[p2l91t1940r285b1995],
2	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l308t1959r574b2008],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l308t1959r574b2008],
4	Ministry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ministry	dep	2	SENT_17	[p2l598t1941r885b2008],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l906t1940r970b1995],
6	Education	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Education	prep_of	4	SENT_17	[p2l985t1940r1334b2007],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l985t1940r1334b2007],
8	Culture	NNP	O	Culture	prep_of	4	SENT_17	[p2l1362t1940r1630b2007],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1362t1940r1630b2007],
10	Sports	NNP	O	Sports	prep_of	4	SENT_17	[p2l1658t1940r1883b2008],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1658t1940r1883b2008],
12	Science	NNP	O	Science	prep_of	4	SENT_17	[p2l1911t1940r2151b1995],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l11t2021r131b2075],
14	Technology-Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Technology-Japan	conj_and	6	SENT_17	[p2l152t2021r766b2089],
15	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l152t2021r766b2089],
16	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	2	SENT_17	[p2l793t2021r987b2075],
17	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	16	SENT_17	[p2l1010t2039r1276b2089],
18	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1010t2039r1276b2089],
19	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	nn	20	SENT_17	[p2l1299t2022r1502b2089],
20	Society	NNP	LOCATION	Society	dep	2	SENT_17	[p2l1525t2021r1758b2089],
21	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1778t2021r1868b2075],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_17	[p2l1889t2021r1993b2075],
23	Promotion	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Promotion	prep_for	20	SENT_17	[p2l2016t2022r2150b2075, p2l9t2101r234b2155],
24	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l254t2100r317b2155],
25	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	nn	27	SENT_17	[p2l332t2100r589b2167],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l332t2100r589b2167],
27	Ministry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ministry	prep_of	23	SENT_17	[p2l610t2101r896b2169],
28	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l915t2100r978b2155],
29	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	prep_of	27	SENT_17	[p2l990t2100r1232b2167],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l990t2100r1232b2167],
31	Labour	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Labour	prep_of	27	SENT_17	[p2l1255t2100r1490b2155],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1511t2100r1631b2155],
33	Welfare-Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Welfare-Japan	prep_of	27	SENT_17	[p2l1647t2100r2149b2169],
34	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1647t2100r2149b2169],
35	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	2	SENT_17	[p2l11t2180r205b2235],
36	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	35	SENT_17	[p2l222t2199r487b2249],
37	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l222t2199r487b2249],
38	Japan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Japan	nn	41	SENT_17	[p2l504t2182r707b2249],
39	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	41	SENT_17	[p2l723t2180r948b2235],
40	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	nn	41	SENT_17	[p2l966t2181r1240b2235],
41	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Foundation	dep	2	SENT_17	[p2l1256t2181r1651b2247],
42	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1256t2181r1651b2247],
43	Grant	NNP	O	Grant	nn	44	SENT_17	[p2l1672t2180r1866b2235],
44	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	41	SENT_17	[p2l1882t2199r2148b2249],
45	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1882t2199r2148b2249],
46	Miyakawa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Miyakawa	nn	47	SENT_17	[p2l8t2260r352b2328],
47	Memorial	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Memorial	dep	2	SENT_17	[p2l414t2260r731b2315],
48	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	49	SENT_17	[p2l795t2260r1095b2315],
49	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Foundation	dep	47	SENT_17	[p2l1159t2260r1553b2327],
50	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1159t2260r1553b2327],
51	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	2	SENT_17	[p2l1623t2260r1817b2315],
52	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	51	SENT_17	[p2l1882t2279r2148b2328],
53	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1882t2279r2148b2328],
54	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	55	SENT_17	[p2l9t2341r295b2395],
55	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	2	SENT_17	[p2l319t2342r606b2395],
56	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l630t2341r694b2395],
57	Biomedical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biomedical	nn	58	SENT_17	[p2l709t2341r1073b2395],
58	Innovation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Innovation	prep_of	55	SENT_17	[p2l1098t2342r1469b2395],
59	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p2l1098t2342r1469b2395],

1	Naoya	NNP	PERSON	Naoya	nn	2	SENT_18	[p2l90t2436r299b2503],
2	Sakamoto	NNP	PERSON	Sakamoto	nsubj	6	SENT_18	[p2l330t2435r652b2489],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l685t2435r805b2489],
4	Mina	NNP	PERSON	Mina	nn	5	SENT_18	[p2l833t2436r1006b2489],
5	Nakagawa	NNP	PERSON	Nakagawa	nsubj	6	SENT_18	[p2l1035t2435r1386b2503],
6	contributed	VBD	O	contribute	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l1415t2435r1792b2489],
7	equally	RB	O	equally	advmod	6	SENT_18	[p2l1823t2435r2062b2503],
8	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l2090t2440r2151b2489],
9	this	DT	O	this	det	10	SENT_18	[p2l8t2514r132b2569],
10	work	NN	O	work	prep_to	6	SENT_18	[p2l156t2515r335b2569],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l156t2515r335b2569],

1	*	NN	O	*	nn	2	SENT_19	[p2l92t2608r649b2677],
2	Correspondence	NN	O	correspondence	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l92t2608r649b2677],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l677t2613r753b2663],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l677t2613r753b2663],
5	Naoya	NNP	PERSON	Naoya	nn	12	SENT_19	[p2l785t2609r995b2676],
6	Sakamoto	NNP	PERSON	Sakamoto	nn	12	SENT_19	[p2l1023t2608r1363b2675],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1023t2608r1363b2675],
8	MD	NNP	O	MD	appos	12	SENT_19	[p2l1392t2609r1530b2675],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1392t2609r1530b2675],
10	PhD	NNP	O	PhD	appos	12	SENT_19	[p2l1562t2608r1722b2675],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1562t2608r1722b2675],
12	Department	NNP	O	Department	prep_to	2	SENT_19	[p2l1753t2609r2152b2677],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l9t2689r73b2743],
14	Gastroenterology	NNP	O	Gastroenterology	prep_of	12	SENT_19	[p2l98t2689r662b2757],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l693t2689r814b2743],
16	Hepatology	NNP	O	Hepatology	prep_of	12	SENT_19	[p2l843t2689r1230b2757],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l843t2689r1230b2757],
18	Tokyo	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tokyo	nn	19	SENT_19	[p2l1263t2689r1460b2757],
19	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	appos	12	SENT_19	[p2l1490t2689r1749b2743],
20	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1780t2689r1900b2743],
21	Dental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dental	nn	22	SENT_19	[p2l1930t2689r2152b2743],
22	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	12	SENT_19	[p2l8t2770r374b2837],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l8t2770r374b2837],
24	1-5-45	CD	DATE	1-5-45	num	25	SENT_19	[p2l406t2770r602b2823],
25	Yushima	NNP	O	Yushima	appos	19	SENT_19	[p2l624t2768r936b2835],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l624t2768r936b2835],
27	Bunkyo-ku	NN	O	bunkyo-ku	appos	19	SENT_19	[p2l962t2768r1343b2837],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l962t2768r1343b2837],
29	Tokyo	NNP	LOCATION	Tokyo	appos	19	SENT_19	[p2l1370t2768r1567b2837],
30	113-8519	CD	NUMBER	113-8519	num	29	SENT_19	[p2l1596t2770r1905b2835],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1596t2770r1905b2835],
32	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	appos	19	SENT_19	[p2l1930t2770r2148b2837],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1930t2770r2148b2837],

1	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l9t2848r244b2903],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l9t2848r244b2903],
3	nsakamoto.gast@tmd.ac.jp	NN	O	nsakamoto.gast@tmd.ac.jp	dep	1	SENT_20	[p2l272t2848r1157b2916],

1	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	amod	2	SENT_21	[p2l87t2942r383b3011],
2	10	CD	DATE	10	dep	5	SENT_21	[p2l412t2945r481b2997],
3	January	NNP	DATE	January	dep	2	SENT_21	[p2l504t2943r781b3010],
4	2011	CD	DATE	2011	dep	5	SENT_21	[p2l805t2945r956b2997],
5	DOI	NNP	O	DOI	dep	8	SENT_21	[p2l90t3036r226b3091],
6	10.1002	CD	NUMBER	10.1002	dep	5	SENT_21	[p2l257t3036r863b3104],
7	/	:	O	/	punct	8	SENT_21	[p2l257t3036r863b3104],
8	jmv	NN	O	jmv	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l257t3036r863b3104],
9	.22038	CD	NUMBER	.22038	num	8	SENT_21	[p2l257t3036r863b3104],
10	Published	VBN	O	publish	partmod	8	SENT_21	[p2l90t3117r416b3171],
11	online	NN	O	online	dep	10	SENT_21	[p2l440t3117r640b3171],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l664t3118r727b3170],
13	Wiley	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wiley	nn	15	SENT_21	[p2l749t3117r939b3185],
14	Online	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Online	nn	15	SENT_21	[p2l963t3117r1182b3171],
15	Library	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Library	prep_in	10	SENT_21	[p2l1207t3117r1456b3185],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_21	[p2l92t3196r904b3264],
17	Wileyonlinelibrary.com	NNP	O	Wileyonlinelibrary.com	dep	15	SENT_21	[p2l92t3196r904b3264],
18	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	17	SENT_21	[p2l92t3196r904b3264],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l92t3196r904b3264],

1	2b	NN	O	2b	_	0	SENT_22	[p3l120t64r231b127],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p3l120t64r231b127],

1	|	NN	O	|	nn	3	SENT_23	[p3l272t64r480b127],
2	L28B	NN	O	l28b	nn	3	SENT_23	[p3l272t64r480b127],
3	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	nsubj	5	SENT_23	[p3l518t64r1094b142],
4	was	VBD	O	be	cop	5	SENT_23	[p3l1129t82r1284b127],
5	predictive	JJ	O	predictive	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l1320t64r1705b142],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l1740t63r1816b127],
7	PEGIFN	NN	O	pegifn	prep_of	5	SENT_23	[p3l1849t63r2037b127, p3l123t160r244b222],
8	plus	CC	O	plus	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l272t160r432b238],
9	RBV	NN	O	rbv	nn	12	SENT_23	[p3l457t160r617b222],
10	combination	NN	O	combination	nn	12	SENT_23	[p3l636t160r1130b223],
11	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nn	12	SENT_23	[p3l1152t167r1539b223],
12	outcomes	NNS	O	outcome	conj_plus	5	SENT_23	[p3l1559t167r1947b223],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l1971t160r2033b222],
14	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	12	SENT_23	[p3l122t257r432b334],
15	infected	VBN	O	infect	partmod	14	SENT_23	[p3l458t256r765b319],
16	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l788t257r954b319],
17	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	15	SENT_23	[p3l981t264r1350b335],
18	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	17	SENT_23	[p3l1373t258r1411b318],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l1436t257r1601b329],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l1436t257r1601b329],
21	especially	RB	O	especially	dep	15	SENT_23	[p3l1626t257r2036b334],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l1626t257r2036b334],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l116t352r282b415],
24	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	25	SENT_23	[p3l311t359r679b430],
25	2b	NN	O	2b	prep_with	15	SENT_23	[p3l704t352r816b415],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p3l704t352r816b415],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l847t352r908b414],
2	conclusion	NN	O	conclusion	prep_in	9	SENT_24	[p3l935t352r1386b424],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l935t352r1386b424],
4	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	5	SENT_24	[p3l1414t352r1651b415],
5	L	NN	O	l	nsubj	9	SENT_24	[p3l1414t352r1651b415],
6	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	8	SENT_24	[p3l1414t352r1651b415],
7	28B	NN	O	28b	nn	8	SENT_24	[p3l1414t352r1651b415],
8	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	dep	5	SENT_24	[p3l1679t352r2037b430, p3l122t448r358b526],
9	affects	VBZ	O	affect	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l392t447r647b511],
10	responses	NNS	O	response	nsubj	12	SENT_24	[p3l680t466r1078b526],
11	to	TO	O	to	aux	12	SENT_24	[p3l1103t456r1178b511],
12	PEG	VB	O	peg	xcomp	9	SENT_24	[p3l1212t447r1801b511],
13	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	14	SENT_24	[p3l1212t447r1801b511],
14	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	16	SENT_24	[p3l1212t447r1801b511],
15	FN	NN	O	fn	nn	16	SENT_24	[p3l1212t447r1801b511],
16	—	NN	O	—	dobj	12	SENT_24	[p3l1212t447r1801b511],
17	based	VBN	O	base	partmod	16	SENT_24	[p3l1212t447r1801b511],
18	treatment	NN	O	treatment	dobj	17	SENT_24	[p3l1830t456r2037b511, p3l123t552r320b607],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l363t545r425b606],
20	difficult-to-treat	JJ	O	difficult-to-treat	amod	22	SENT_24	[p3l470t544r1084b607],
21	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	22	SENT_24	[p3l1128t544r1293b607],
22	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	18	SENT_24	[p3l1335t545r1665b622],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p3l1335t545r1665b622],

1	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	2	SENT_25	[p3l1709t545r1782b607],
2	Med	NNP	O	Med	_	0	SENT_25	[p3l1824t545r2036b607],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p3l1824t545r2036b607],

1	Virol	NNP	PERSON	Virol	_	0	SENT_26	[p3l129t640r357b703],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p3l129t640r357b703],

1	33:3	CD	NUMBER	33:3	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l385t642r582b703],
2	71-3	CD	NUMBER	71-3	num	3	SENT_27	[p3l591t642r794b703],
3	73	CD	NUMBER	73	dep	1	SENT_27	[p3l802t642r928b712],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l802t642r928b712],
5	201	CD	NUMBER	201	number	6	SENT_27	[p3l951t642r1115b703],
6	1	CD	NUMBER	1	appos	3	SENT_27	[p3l1136t643r1199b702],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p3l1136t643r1199b702],

1	©	RB	O	©	advmod	2	SENT_28	[p3l1292t654r1341b702],
2	2011	CD	DATE	2011	_	0	SENT_28	[p3l1364t651r1515b703],
3	Wiley-Liss	NNP	O	Wiley-Liss	dep	2	SENT_28	[p3l1534t649r1896b716],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p3l1534t649r1896b716],
5	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	appos	3	SENT_28	[p3l1918t650r2035b703],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p3l1918t650r2035b703],

1	KEY	JJ	O	key	amod	2	SENT_29	[p3l117t800r311b861],
2	WORDS	NNS	O	word	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l351t798r720b862],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l351t798r720b862],
4	hepatitis	NN	O	hepatitis	nn	6	SENT_29	[p3l816t800r1149b877],
5	C	NN	O	c	nn	6	SENT_29	[p3l1201t799r1249b862],
6	virus	NN	O	virus	dep	2	SENT_29	[p3l1297t800r1490b862],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	9	SENT_29	[p3l1542t799r1786b872],
8	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	9	SENT_29	[p3l1542t799r1786b872],
9	)	NN	O	)	dep	6	SENT_29	[p3l1542t799r1786b872],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l1542t799r1786b872],
11	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	12	SENT_29	[p3l1836t800r2037b862, p3l816t896r925b959],
12	hepatitis	NN	O	hepatitis	dep	6	SENT_29	[p3l995t896r1328b974],
13	C	NN	O	c	dep	12	SENT_29	[p3l1396t894r1468b969],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l1396t894r1468b969],
15	genotype	NN	O	genotype	dep	6	SENT_29	[p3l1537t903r1905b975],
16	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	15	SENT_29	[p3l1974t897r2036b969],
17	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l1974t897r2036b969],
18	PEG	NN	O	peg	dep	6	SENT_29	[p3l816t991r1136b1055],
19	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	20	SENT_29	[p3l816t991r1136b1055],
20	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	21	SENT_29	[p3l816t991r1136b1055],
21	FN	NN	O	fn	dep	18	SENT_29	[p3l816t991r1136b1055],
22	plus	CC	O	plus	prep	21	SENT_29	[p3l1226t992r1387b1070],
23	RBV	NN	O	rbv	nn	24	SENT_29	[p3l1473t992r1634b1054],
24	therapy	NN	O	therapy	dep	22	SENT_29	[p3l1712t992r2036b1070],
25	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l1712t992r2036b1070],
26	combination	NN	O	combination	dep	6	SENT_29	[p3l812t1089r1307b1151],
27	therapv	NN	O	therapv	dep	26	SENT_29	[p3l1391t1089r1715b1166],
28	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l1391t1089r1715b1166],
29	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	30	SENT_29	[p3l1803t1089r2036b1161],
30	L28B	NN	O	l28b	dep	6	SENT_29	[p3l1803t1089r2036b1161],
31	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_29	[p3l1803t1089r2036b1161],
32	interferon-A3	NN	O	interferon-a3	dep	30	SENT_29	[p3l816t1184r1322b1247],

1	INTRODUCTION	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_30	[p3l702t1530r1454b1595],

1	Hepatitis	NNP	O	Hepatitis	nn	6	SENT_31	[p3l96t1677r456b1757],
2	C	NNP	O	C	nn	6	SENT_31	[p3l494t1676r548b1741],
3	virus	NN	O	virus	nn	6	SENT_31	[p3l583t1677r782b1741],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_31	[p3l822t1676r1060b1749],
5	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	6	SENT_31	[p3l822t1676r1060b1749],
6	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	15	SENT_31	[p3l822t1676r1060b1749],
7	infects	VBZ	O	infect	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l1100t1676r1354b1741],
8	around	IN	O	around	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l1392t1676r1667b1741],
9	170	CD	NUMBER	170	number	10	SENT_31	[p3l1708t1679r1836b1741],
10	million	CD	NUMBER	million	num	11	SENT_31	[p3l1874t1676r2145b1741],
11	people	NNS	O	people	prep_around	7	SENT_31	[p3l9t1774r256b1855],
12	Worldwide	NNP	O	Worldwide	dep	11	SENT_31	[p3l287t1774r689b1839],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l723t1774r865b1838],
14	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	15	SENT_31	[p3l896t1775r957b1839],
15	characterized	VBN	O	characterize	conj_and	7	SENT_31	[p3l989t1774r1516b1839],
16	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l1544t1774r1636b1855],
17	a	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_31	[p3l1669t1796r1712b1838],
18	high	JJ	O	high	amod	19	SENT_31	[p3l1741t1774r1914b1855],
19	probability	NN	O	probability	agent	15	SENT_31	[p3l1945t1774r2143b1855, p3l12t1870r259b1951],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l288t1870r363b1935],
21	developing	VBG	O	develop	prepc_of	19	SENT_31	[p3l384t1870r803b1951],
22	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	23	SENT_31	[p3l829t1870r1112b1935],
23	inﬂammation	NN	O	inﬂammation	dobj	21	SENT_31	[p3l1141t1870r1664b1935],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l1696t1870r1838b1935],
25	fibrosis	NN	O	fibrosis	conj_and	23	SENT_31	[p3l1866t1870r2145b1935],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l11t1967r86b2032],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_31	[p3l107t1967r230b2032],
28	liver	NN	O	liver	prep_of	23	SENT_31	[p3l261t1967r456b2046],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l261t1967r456b2046],
30	leading	VBG	O	lead	dep	21	SENT_31	[p3l491t1967r779b2048],
31	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l805t1973r877b2032],
32	end-stage	JJ	O	end-stage	amod	34	SENT_31	[p3l908t1967r1280b2048],
33	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	34	SENT_31	[p3l1312t1967r1487b2032],
34	failure	NN	O	failure	prep_to	30	SENT_31	[p3l1517t1967r1773b2032],
35	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l1806t1967r1948b2032],
36	hepatocellular	JJ	O	hepatocellular	amod	39	SENT_31	[p3l1978t1967r2143b2048, p3l12t2065r425b2129],
37	carcinoma	NN	O	carcinoma	nn	39	SENT_31	[p3l472t2066r872b2129],
38	(	NN	O	(	nn	39	SENT_31	[p3l921t2065r1160b2137],
39	HCC	NN	O	hcc	prep_to	30	SENT_31	[p3l921t2065r1160b2137],
40	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	41	SENT_31	[p3l921t2065r1160b2137],
41	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	42	SENT_31	[p3l1215t2065r1454b2143],
42	Alter	NNP	O	Alter	dep	39	SENT_31	[p3l1215t2065r1454b2143],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l1215t2065r1454b2143],
44	1997	CD	DATE	1997	dobj	21	SENT_31	[p3l1512t2067r1710b2143],
45	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l1512t2067r1710b2143],
46	Sakamoto	NNP	PERSON	Sakamoto	dep	44	SENT_31	[p3l1763t2065r2145b2129],
47	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l12t2160r154b2225],
48	Watanabe	NNP	PERSON	Watanabe	dep	44	SENT_31	[p3l169t2160r585b2239],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l169t2160r585b2239],
50	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	51	SENT_31	[p3l608t2161r837b2233],
51	]	NN	O	]	appos	46	SENT_31	[p3l608t2161r837b2233],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l608t2161r837b2233],

1	Since	IN	O	since	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l864t2160r1069b2225],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_32	[p3l1087t2160r1210b2225],
3	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	nn	4	SENT_32	[p3l1229t2160r1387b2225],
4	report	NN	O	report	prep_since	14	SENT_32	[p3l1404t2166r1643b2241],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1661t2161r1736b2223],
6	1986	CD	DATE	1986	prep_in	4	SENT_32	[p3l1761t2163r1957b2239],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1761t2163r1957b2239],
8	type	NN	O	type	nsubj	14	SENT_32	[p3l1979t2166r2145b2241],
9	I	CD	NUMBER	i	num	10	SENT_32	[p3l11t2258r40b2321],
10	interferons	NNS	O	interferon	dep	8	SENT_32	[p3l75t2257r503b2322],
11	have	VBP	O	have	aux	14	SENT_32	[p3l537t2257r721b2322],
12	been	VBN	O	be	cop	14	SENT_32	[p3l753t2257r935b2322],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_32	[p3l968t2257r1092b2322],
14	mainstay	NN	O	mainstay	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1126t2258r1488b2338],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1521t2257r1596b2322],
16	HCV	NN	O	hcv	prep_of	14	SENT_32	[p3l1621t2257r1813b2322],
17	therapy	NN	O	therapy	nn	19	SENT_32	[p3l1842t2257r2146b2338],
18	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	19	SENT_32	[p3l15t2354r451b2435],
19	Hoofnagle	NNP	PERSON	Hoofnagle	dep	16	SENT_32	[p3l15t2354r451b2435],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l15t2354r451b2435],
21	1994	CD	DATE	1994	num	22	SENT_32	[p3l481t2356r705b2427],
22	]	NN	O	]	appos	16	SENT_32	[p3l481t2356r705b2427],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l481t2356r705b2427],

1	Current	JJ	DATE	current	amod	2	SENT_33	[p3l731t2354r1041b2419],
2	standards	NNS	O	standard	nsubj	5	SENT_33	[p3l1062t2354r1447b2419],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1466t2354r1541b2419],
4	care	NN	O	care	prep_of	2	SENT_33	[p3l1553t2377r1713b2419],
5	consist	VBP	O	consist	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1732t2356r1997b2419],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l2017t2354r2093b2419],
7	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_33	[p3l2104t2377r2147b2419],
8	combination	NN	O	combination	prep_of	5	SENT_33	[p3l11t2451r487b2516],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l531t2451r606b2516],
10	ribavirin	NNP	O	ribavirin	prep_of	8	SENT_33	[p3l640t2451r983b2516],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_33	[p3l1030t2451r1259b2524],
12	RBV	NN	O	rbv	nn	13	SENT_33	[p3l1030t2451r1259b2524],
13	)	NN	O	)	dobj	5	SENT_33	[p3l1030t2451r1259b2524],
14	plus	CC	O	plus	advmod	15	SENT_33	[p3l1305t2451r1467b2532],
15	pegylated	VBN	O	pegylate	partmod	13	SENT_33	[p3l1510t2451r1887b2532],
16	interferon	NN	O	interferon	nn	18	SENT_33	[p3l1930t2452r2143b2516, p3l10t2548r209b2613],
17	(	NN	O	(	nn	18	SENT_33	[p3l243t2548r914b2629],
18	PEG-IFN	NN	O	peg-ifn	dobj	15	SENT_33	[p3l243t2548r914b2629],
19	)	SYM	O	)	dep	21	SENT_33	[p3l243t2548r914b2629],
20	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l243t2548r914b2629],
21	alpha	NN	O	alpha	dep	18	SENT_33	[p3l243t2548r914b2629],
22	for	IN	O	for	dep	21	SENT_33	[p3l944t2548r1049b2613],
23	48	CD	DURATION	48	num	24	SENT_33	[p3l1080t2551r1169b2613],
24	Weeks	NNS	DURATION	week	pobj	22	SENT_33	[p3l1200t2548r1437b2613],
25	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1468t2548r1573b2613],
26	infection	NN	O	infection	prep_for	22	SENT_33	[p3l1604t2548r1941b2613],
27	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1971t2548r2145b2613],
28	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	prep_with	26	SENT_33	[p3l10t2651r397b2726],
29	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	28	SENT_33	[p3l433t2648r466b2709],
30	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l501t2645r644b2710],
31	4	CD	NUMBER	4	conj_and	28	SENT_33	[p3l672t2648r735b2724],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l672t2648r735b2724],
33	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l770t2645r913b2710],
34	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l941t2645r1046b2710],
35	24	CD	DURATION	24	num	36	SENT_33	[p3l1077t2648r1165b2709],
36	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	prep_for	22	SENT_33	[p3l1194t2645r1431b2710],
37	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1460t2645r1566b2710],
38	the	DT	O	the	det	40	SENT_33	[p3l1594t2645r1718b2710],
39	other	JJ	O	other	amod	40	SENT_33	[p3l1748t2645r1952b2710],
40	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	prep_for	36	SENT_33	[p3l1981t2666r2144b2726, p3l11t2748r256b2823],
41	[	VBP	O	[	dep	21	SENT_33	[p3l281t2743r605b2815],
42	Zeuzem	NNP	O	Zeuzem	nsubj	44	SENT_33	[p3l281t2743r605b2815],
43	et	FW	O	et	nn	44	SENT_33	[p3l624t2748r695b2807],
44	a1.	FW	O	a1.	xcomp	41	SENT_33	[p3l716t2742r827b2821],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l716t2742r827b2821],
46	2000	CD	DATE	2000	appos	44	SENT_33	[p3l852t2745r1054b2821],
47	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l852t2745r1054b2821],
48	Fried	NNP	O	Fried	dep	44	SENT_33	[p3l1077t2742r1286b2807],
49	et	FW	O	et	nn	50	SENT_33	[p3l1305t2748r1376b2807],
50	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	48	SENT_33	[p3l1396t2742r1507b2821],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1396t2742r1507b2821],
52	2002	CD	DATE	2002	num	53	SENT_33	[p3l1532t2743r1761b2815],
53	]	NN	O	]	appos	44	SENT_33	[p3l1532t2743r1761b2815],
54	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1532t2743r1761b2815],

1	Although	IN	O	although	mark	4	SENT_34	[p3l1782t2742r2145b2823],
2	this	DT	O	this	det	3	SENT_34	[p3l9t2839r156b2904],
3	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nsubj	4	SENT_34	[p3l191t2845r583b2904],
4	improved	VBD	O	improve	advcl	13	SENT_34	[p3l617t2839r981b2920],
5	substantially	RB	O	substantially	advmod	4	SENT_34	[p3l1017t2839r1525b2920],
6	sustained	JJ	O	sustained	amod	9	SENT_34	[p3l1560t2839r1934b2904],
7	virological	JJ	O	virological	amod	9	SENT_34	[p3l1966t2840r2143b2904, p3l10t2936r259b3017],
8	response	NN	O	response	nn	9	SENT_34	[p3l306t2959r645b3017],
9	rates	NNS	O	rate	dobj	4	SENT_34	[p3l693t2942r908b3015],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l693t2942r908b3015],
11	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	13	SENT_34	[p3l960t2938r1016b3001],
12	may	MD	O	may	aux	13	SENT_34	[p3l1063t2959r1229b3017],
13	result	VB	O	result	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1275t2936r1502b3001],
14	also	RB	O	also	advmod	13	SENT_34	[p3l1552t2936r1699b3001],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1748t2938r1822b3000],
16	serious	JJ	O	serious	amod	18	SENT_34	[p3l1872t2938r2145b3001],
17	adverse	JJ	O	adverse	amod	18	SENT_34	[p3l12t3033r309b3098],
18	effects	NNS	O	effect	prep_in	13	SENT_34	[p3l328t3033r573b3098],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l595t3033r737b3098],
20	a	DT	O	a	det	22	SENT_34	[p3l756t3055r798b3098],
21	considerable	JJ	O	considerable	amod	22	SENT_34	[p3l816t3033r1300b3098],
22	proportion	NN	O	proportion	nsubj	25	SENT_34	[p3l1318t3034r1726b3114],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1745t3033r1820b3098],
24	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_of	22	SENT_34	[p3l1829t3034r2145b3114],
25	require	VBP	O	require	conj_and	13	SENT_34	[p3l10t3131r292b3211],
26	early	JJ	O	early	amod	27	SENT_34	[p3l323t3130r519b3211],
27	discontinuation	NN	O	discontinuation	dobj	25	SENT_34	[p3l549t3130r1153b3195],
28	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1184t3130r1259b3195],
29	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_of	27	SENT_34	[p3l1279t3136r1689b3195],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1279t3136r1689b3195],

1	Patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	5	SENT_35	[p3l1725t3131r2048b3195],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l2079t3130r2154b3195],
3	African	JJ	MISC	african	amod	4	SENT_35	[p3l7t3227r296b3292],
4	origin	NN	O	origin	prep_of	1	SENT_35	[p3l341t3229r567b3308],
5	have	VBP	O	have	dep	10	SENT_35	[p3l611t3227r794b3292],
6	even	RB	O	even	advmod	9	SENT_35	[p3l839t3250r1017b3292],
7	poorer	JJR	O	poorer	amod	9	SENT_35	[p3l1060t3250r1308b3308],
8	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nn	9	SENT_35	[p3l1351t3233r1742b3292],
9	outcomes	NNS	O	outcome	dobj	5	SENT_35	[p3l1786t3233r2145b3292],
10	[	VBP	O	[	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l15t3325r271b3397],
11	Rosen	NNP	PERSON	Rosen	nsubj	10	SENT_35	[p3l15t3325r271b3397],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l292t3324r434b3389],
13	Gretch	NNP	PERSON	Gretch	conj_and	11	SENT_35	[p3l454t3324r736b3403],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l454t3324r736b3403],
15	1999	CD	DATE	1999	num	16	SENT_35	[p3l765t3325r989b3397],
16	]	NN	O	]	appos	11	SENT_35	[p3l765t3325r989b3397],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l765t3325r989b3397],

1	Given	VBN	O	give	prep	19	SENT_36	[p3l1016t3324r1242b3389],
2	this	DT	O	this	det	3	SENT_36	[p3l1260t3324r1406b3389],
3	situation	NN	O	situation	dep	1	SENT_36	[p3l1427t3325r1790b3403],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1427t3325r1790b3403],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_36	[p3l1816t3346r1858b3389],
6	precise	JJ	O	precise	amod	7	SENT_36	[p3l1874t3325r2145b3405],
7	assessment	NN	O	assessment	nsubj	19	SENT_36	[p3l12t3427r453b3486],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l479t3421r554b3486],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_36	[p3l570t3421r693b3486],
10	likely	JJ	O	likely	amod	12	SENT_36	[p3l720t3421r935b3502],
11	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nn	12	SENT_36	[p3l958t3427r1350b3486],
12	outcomes	NNS	O	outcome	prep_of	7	SENT_36	[p3l1376t3427r1735b3486],
13	before	IN	O	before	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1759t3421r1996b3486],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_36	[p3l2021t3421r2145b3486],
15	initiation	NN	O	initiation	prep_before	12	SENT_36	[p3l10t3520r370b3583],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l406t3518r481b3583],
17	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_of	15	SENT_36	[p3l506t3524r897b3583],
18	may	MD	O	may	aux	19	SENT_36	[p3l932t3541r1097b3599],
19	improve	VB	O	improve	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1130t3520r1444b3599],
20	substantially	RB	O	substantially	advmod	19	SENT_36	[p3l1481t3518r1989b3599],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_36	[p3l2021t3518r2145b3583],
22	quality	NN	O	quality	dobj	19	SENT_36	[p3l12t3616r284b3697],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l313t3616r388b3680],
24	antiviral	JJ	O	antiviral	amod	25	SENT_36	[p3l411t3616r746b3680],
25	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_of	22	SENT_36	[p3l774t3621r1184b3680],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l774t3621r1184b3680],

1	Recently	RB	DATE	recently	advmod	6	SENT_37	[p3l96t3712r451b3793],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l96t3712r451b3793],
3	several	JJ	O	several	amod	4	SENT_37	[p3l489t3712r764b3777],
4	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	6	SENT_37	[p3l797t3712r1071b3777],
5	have	VBP	O	have	aux	6	SENT_37	[p3l1102t3712r1286b3777],
6	reported	VBN	O	report	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l1317t3712r1647b3793],
7	that	IN	O	that	complm	27	SENT_37	[p3l1677t3712r1838b3777],
8	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	9	SENT_37	[p3l1870t3713r2146b3793],
9	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubj	27	SENT_37	[p4l9t15r604b96],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l625t15r701b80],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_37	[p4l712t15r836b80],
12	IL28B	NN	O	il28b	nn	13	SENT_37	[p4l857t17r1095b80],
13	locus	NN	O	locus	prep_of	9	SENT_37	[p4l1119t15r1332b95],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1119t15r1332b95],
15	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	16	SENT_37	[p4l1356t15r1587b80],
16	encodes	VBZ	O	encode	rcmod	9	SENT_37	[p4l1609t15r1908b80],
17	interferon	NN	O	interferon	dobj	16	SENT_37	[p4l1930t17r2143b80, p4l10t113r328b177],
18	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1930t17r2143b80, p4l10t113r328b177],
19	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	17	SENT_37	[p4l1930t17r2143b80, p4l10t113r328b177],
20	\	CD	NUMBER	\	number	21	SENT_37	[p4l1930t17r2143b80, p4l10t113r328b177],
21	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	25	SENT_37	[p4l1930t17r2143b80, p4l10t113r328b177],
22	(	NN	O	(	nn	25	SENT_37	[p4l353t113r815b186],
23	interleukin	NN	O	interleukin	nn	25	SENT_37	[p4l353t113r815b186],
24	28B	NN	O	28b	nn	25	SENT_37	[p4l835t113r1032b191],
25	)	NN	O	)	dep	19	SENT_37	[p4l835t113r1032b191],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l835t113r1032b191],
27	are	VBP	O	be	ccomp	6	SENT_37	[p4l1058t135r1178b177],
28	associated	VBN	O	associate	dep	27	SENT_37	[p4l1200t112r1596b177],
29	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1613t113r1787b177],
30	response	NN	O	response	prep_with	28	SENT_37	[p4l1805t135r2145b194],
31	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l9t215r81b273],
32	interferon-based	JJ	O	interferon-based	amod	33	SENT_37	[p4l101t209r743b273],
33	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_to	28	SENT_37	[p4l762t215r1153b273],
34	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1173t209r1248b273],
35	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	37	SENT_37	[p4l1260t209r1542b273],
36	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	37	SENT_37	[p4l1563t209r1754b273],
37	infections	NNS	O	infection	prep_of	33	SENT_37	[p4l1770t209r2145b273],
38	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l9t305r183b370],
39	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	28	SENT_37	[p4l216t311r564b386],
40	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	41	SENT_37	[p4l603t308r636b369],
41	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	42	SENT_37	[p4l677t305r805b378],
42	Ge	NNP	O	Ge	dep	39	SENT_37	[p4l677t305r805b378],
43	et	FW	O	et	nn	44	SENT_37	[p4l838t311r909b370],
44	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	39	SENT_37	[p4l943t305r1054b384],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l943t305r1054b384],
46	2009	CD	DATE	2009	appos	44	SENT_37	[p4l1091t308r1294b384],
47	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1091t308r1294b384],
48	Suppiah	NNP	O	Suppiah	dep	44	SENT_37	[p4l1333t305r1653b386],
49	et	FW	O	et	nn	50	SENT_37	[p4l1686t311r1757b370],
50	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	48	SENT_37	[p4l1791t305r1902b384],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1791t305r1902b384],
52	2009	CD	DATE	2009	appos	50	SENT_37	[p4l1939t308r2142b384],
53	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l1939t308r2142b384],
54	Tanaka	NNP	PERSON	Tanaka	dep	44	SENT_37	[p4l10t402r307b467],
55	et	FW	O	et	nn	56	SENT_37	[p4l334t409r405b467],
56	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	54	SENT_37	[p4l436t403r547b482],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l436t403r547b482],
58	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	59	SENT_37	[p4l580t404r786b475],
59	]	NN	O	]	appos	39	SENT_37	[p4l580t404r786b475],
60	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l821t402r964b467],
61	also	RB	O	also	conj_and	28	SENT_37	[p4l993t403r1141b467],
62	spontaneous	JJ	O	spontaneous	amod	63	SENT_37	[p4l1173t408r1655b484],
63	clearance	NN	O	clearance	dep	28	SENT_37	[p4l1684t403r2049b467],
64	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l2079t403r2154b467],
65	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	67	SENT_37	[p4l11t499r202b563],
66	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	67	SENT_37	[p4l232t499r563b571],
67	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	Thomas	prep_of	63	SENT_37	[p4l232t499r563b571],
68	et	FW	O	et	nn	69	SENT_37	[p4l593t505r664b563],
69	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	67	SENT_37	[p4l695t499r806b577],
70	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l695t499r806b577],
71	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	72	SENT_37	[p4l840t500r1069b571],
72	]	NN	O	]	appos	67	SENT_37	[p4l840t500r1069b571],
73	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p4l840t500r1069b571],

1	While	IN	O	while	mark	9	SENT_38	[p4l92t595r321b660],
2	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	4	SENT_38	[p4l363t595r646b660],
3	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	4	SENT_38	[p4l687t595r879b660],
4	infections	NNS	O	infection	nsubjpass	9	SENT_38	[p4l916t595r1291b660],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l1333t595r1507b660],
6	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	4	SENT_38	[p4l1548t601r1896b676],
7	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	6	SENT_38	[p4l1939t598r1979b659],
8	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_38	[p4l2024t618r2145b660],
9	associated	VBN	O	associate	advcl	16	SENT_38	[p4l12t692r409b757],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l426t692r600b757],
11	good	JJ	O	good	amod	13	SENT_38	[p4l620t693r795b773],
12	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nn	13	SENT_38	[p4l812t699r1204b757],
13	outcome	NN	O	outcome	prep_with	9	SENT_38	[p4l1223t699r1563b772],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l1223t699r1563b772],
15	there	EX	O	there	expl	16	SENT_38	[p4l1585t692r1789b757],
16	are	VBP	O	be	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l1811t715r1932b757],
17	some	DT	O	some	det	19	SENT_38	[p4l1952t715r2145b757],
18	refractory	JJ	O	refractory	amod	19	SENT_38	[p4l10t790r397b871],
19	cases	NNS	O	case	nsubj	16	SENT_38	[p4l421t812r621b855],
20	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l648t810r908b871],
21	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_among	19	SENT_38	[p4l927t791r1244b871],
22	infected	VBN	O	infect	partmod	21	SENT_38	[p4l1268t790r1576b855],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l1599t790r1773b855],
24	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	22	SENT_38	[p4l1798t796r2145b871],
25	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	24	SENT_38	[p4l11t889r73b965],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l11t889r73b965],
27	similar	JJ	O	similar	acomp	22	SENT_38	[p4l106t886r379b951],
28	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l404t892r475b951],
29	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_to	27	SENT_38	[p4l503t892r850b967],
30	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	29	SENT_38	[p4l884t889r939b951],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p4l884t889r939b951],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_39	[p4l971t886r1118b951],
2	aims	NNS	O	aim	nsubj	6	SENT_39	[p4l1147t888r1328b951],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l1356t886r1431b951],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	5	SENT_39	[p4l1448t886r1594b951],
5	study	NN	O	study	prep_of	2	SENT_39	[p4l1623t886r1836b967],
6	Were	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l1861t909r2047b951],
7	to	TO	O	to	aux	8	SENT_39	[p4l2073t892r2145b951],
8	analyze	VB	O	analyze	ccomp	6	SENT_39	[p4l12t984r307b1064],
9	retrospectively	RB	O	retrospectively	advmod	8	SENT_39	[p4l342t984r920b1065],
10	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	13	SENT_39	[p4l956t984r1232b1048],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l1270t984r1412b1048],
12	virological	JJ	O	virological	conj_and	10	SENT_39	[p4l1446t984r1849b1064],
13	factors	NNS	O	factor	dobj	8	SENT_39	[p4l1884t984r2145b1048],
14	associated	VBN	O	associate	partmod	13	SENT_39	[p4l12t1081r409b1146],
15	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l451t1081r626b1146],
16	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nn	17	SENT_39	[p4l670t1087r1062b1146],
17	response	NN	O	response	prep_with	14	SENT_39	[p4l1106t1103r1446b1162],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l1491t1082r1565b1144],
19	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	17	SENT_39	[p4l1610t1082r1927b1162],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l1971t1081r2145b1146],
21	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	23	SENT_39	[p4l11t1177r294b1242],
22	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	23	SENT_39	[p4l312t1178r502b1242],
23	infection	NN	O	infection	prep_with	14	SENT_39	[p4l517t1178r853b1242],
24	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l871t1178r1045b1242],
25	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	23	SENT_39	[p4l1063t1184r1410b1259],
26	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	25	SENT_39	[p4l1429t1181r1469b1241],
27	who	WP	O	who	nsubjpass	29	SENT_39	[p4l1488t1177r1645b1242],
28	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	29	SENT_39	[p4l1662t1200r1848b1242],
29	treated	VBN	O	treat	rcmod	13	SENT_39	[p4l1865t1177r2146b1242],
30	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l9t1275r183b1340],
31	PEG-IFN	NN	O	peg-ifn	prep_with	29	SENT_39	[p4l221t1275r588b1340],
32	plus	CC	O	plus	prep	31	SENT_39	[p4l624t1275r787b1356],
33	RBV	NN	O	rbv	nn	35	SENT_39	[p4l825t1276r1007b1340],
34	combination	NN	O	combination	nn	35	SENT_39	[p4l1041t1275r1517b1340],
35	therapy	NN	O	therapy	dep	32	SENT_39	[p4l1554t1275r1858b1356],
36	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l1896t1275r2038b1339],
37	to	TO	O	to	aux	38	SENT_39	[p4l2073t1281r2145b1340],
38	clarify	VB	O	clarify	conj_and	8	SENT_39	[p4l11t1372r257b1453],
39	the	DT	O	the	det	40	SENT_39	[p4l291t1372r415b1437],
40	relationship	NN	O	relationship	dobj	38	SENT_39	[p4l451t1372r920b1453],
41	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l954t1372r1277b1437],
42	IL28B	NN	O	il28b	nn	43	SENT_39	[p4l1314t1373r1552b1437],
43	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	prep_between	40	SENT_39	[p4l1589t1372r2146b1453],
44	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l12t1469r154b1533],
45	the	DT	O	the	det	46	SENT_39	[p4l182t1469r306b1533],
46	response	NN	O	response	conj_and	43	SENT_39	[p4l335t1491r674b1550],
47	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l703t1475r774b1533],
48	combination	NN	O	combination	nn	49	SENT_39	[p4l805t1468r1280b1533],
49	therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_to	38	SENT_39	[p4l1309t1469r1630b1550],
50	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p4l1309t1469r1630b1550],

1	PATIENTS	NNS	O	patient	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l474t1677r949b1741],
2	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_40	[p4l973t1678r1177b1741],
3	METHODS	NNS	O	method	conj_and	1	SENT_40	[p4l1204t1677r1679b1741],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_41	[p4l94t1823r242b1888],
2	authors	NNS	O	author	nsubj	3	SENT_41	[p4l290t1823r586b1888],
3	analyzed	VBN	O	analyze	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l635t1823r979b1904],
4	retrospectively	RB	O	retrospectively	amod	10	SENT_41	[p4l1023t1823r1601b1904],
5	129	CD	NUMBER	129	num	6	SENT_41	[p4l1653t1826r1782b1888],
6	patients	NNS	O	patient	dep	4	SENT_41	[p4l1828t1824r2145b1904],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l9t1921r183b1986],
8	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	9	SENT_41	[p4l246t1921r529b1985],
9	HCV	NN	O	hcv	prep_with	4	SENT_41	[p4l591t1921r781b1986],
10	infection	NN	O	infection	dobj	3	SENT_41	[p4l841t1921r1177b1986],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l1238t1921r1412b1986],
12	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	10	SENT_41	[p4l1474t1927r1821b2002],
13	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	12	SENT_41	[p4l1885t1924r1924b1984],
14	who	WP	O	who	rcmod	10	SENT_41	[p4l1988t1921r2145b1985],

1	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	2	SENT_42	[p4l6t2094r63b2147],
2	Med	NNP	O	Med	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l91t2092r248b2147],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l91t2092r248b2147],

1	Virol	NNP	PERSON	Virol	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l280t2093r454b2147],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l280t2093r454b2147],

1	DOI	NNP	O	DOI	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l486t2092r622b2147],
2	10.1002	CD	NUMBER	10.1002	num	1	SENT_44	[p4l653t2092r1043b2160],
3	/	:	O	/	punct	4	SENT_44	[p4l653t2092r1043b2160],
4	jmv	NN	O	jmv	dep	1	SENT_44	[p4l653t2092r1043b2160],

1	Sakamoto	NNP	PERSON	Sakamoto	_	0	SENT_45	[p4l1576t2191r1938b2252],
2	et	FW	O	et	nn	3	SENT_45	[p4l1964t2197r2032b2252],
3	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	1	SENT_45	[p4l2058t2191r2140b2252],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p4l2058t2191r2140b2252],

1	received	VBN	O	receive	csubj	18	SENT_46	[p4l9t2365r329b2430],
2	combination	NN	O	combination	nn	3	SENT_46	[p4l396t2365r872b2430],
3	therapy	NN	O	therapy	dobj	1	SENT_46	[p4l939t2365r1243b2446],
4	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1307t2365r1481b2430],
5	PEG-IFN	NN	O	peg-ifn	prep_with	3	SENT_46	[p4l1549t2365r1915b2430],
6	plus	CC	O	plus	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1982t2365r2144b2446],
7	RBV	NN	O	rbv	dobj	1	SENT_46	[p4l10t2463r191b2526],
8	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l226t2462r548b2526],
9	December	NNP	DATE	December	prep_between	7	SENT_46	[p4l589t2462r975b2526],
10	2004	CD	DATE	2004	num	9	SENT_46	[p4l1015t2465r1197b2526],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1239t2462r1381b2526],
12	December	NNP	DATE	December	conj_and	1	SENT_46	[p4l1421t2462r1807b2526],
13	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	12	SENT_46	[p4l1847t2465r2028b2526],
14	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l2071t2468r2145b2526],
15	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	17	SENT_46	[p4l16t2561r97b2623],
16	multicenter	JJ	O	multicenter	amod	17	SENT_46	[p4l120t2558r574b2623],
17	hospitals	NNS	O	hospital	prep_at	12	SENT_46	[p4l595t2558r944b2639],
18	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l969t2558r1170b2631],
19	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	20	SENT_46	[p4l969t2558r1170b2631],
20	units	NNS	O	unit	dobj	18	SENT_46	[p4l1189t2559r1388b2623],
21	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1409t2558r1583b2623],
22	hepatologists	NNS	O	hepatologist	prep_with	18	SENT_46	[p4l1604t2558r2141b2639],
23	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	22	SENT_46	[p4l1604t2558r2141b2639],
24	throughout	IN	O	throughout	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l8t2655r447b2736],
25	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	prep_throughout	22	SENT_46	[p4l504t2656r763b2736],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l504t2656r763b2736],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	2	SENT_47	[p4l824t2655r937b2719],
2	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	3	SENT_47	[p4l995t2656r1312b2736],
3	had	VBD	O	have	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1371t2655r1515b2720],
4	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	6	SENT_47	[p4l1575t2655r1857b2720],
5	active	JJ	O	active	amod	6	SENT_47	[p4l1919t2656r2144b2720],
6	hepatitis	NN	O	hepatitis	dobj	3	SENT_47	[p4l9t2752r352b2833],
7	conﬁrmed	VBD	O	conﬁrmed	rcmod	6	SENT_47	[p4l376t2752r761b2817],
8	histologically	RB	O	histologically	advmod	7	SENT_47	[p4l783t2752r1297b2833],
9	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1321t2774r1397b2817],
10	clinically	RB	O	clinically	conj_or	8	SENT_47	[p4l1421t2752r1770b2833],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1794t2752r1936b2817],
12	were	VBD	O	be	cop	13	SENT_47	[p4l1959t2774r2144b2817],
13	positive	JJ	O	positive	rcmod	6	SENT_47	[p4l8t2850r308b2930],
14	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l336t2849r442b2914],
15	anti-HCV	JJ	O	anti-hcv	amod	16	SENT_47	[p4l472t2849r847b2914],
16	antibodies	NNS	O	antibody	prep_for	13	SENT_47	[p4l874t2849r1271b2914],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1302t2849r1444b2914],
18	serum	NN	O	serum	nn	20	SENT_47	[p4l1473t2871r1714b2914],
19	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	20	SENT_47	[p4l1742t2849r1933b2914],
20	RNA	NN	O	rna	prep_for	13	SENT_47	[p4l1958t2849r2148b2914],
21	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l7t2946r99b3027],
22	quantitative	JJ	O	quantitative	amod	25	SENT_47	[p4l150t2947r627b3027],
23	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l677t2968r753b3011],
24	qualitative	JJ	O	qualitative	amod	25	SENT_47	[p4l804t2946r1222b3027],
25	assays	NNS	O	assay	prep_by	13	SENT_47	[p4l1275t2968r1543b3027],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1275t2968r1543b3027],

1	Patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubjpass	58	SENT_48	[p4l1598t2947r1921b3011],
2	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1970t2946r2144b3011],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_48	[p4l11t3066r53b3108],
4	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	5	SENT_48	[p4l90t3045r389b3124],
5	test	NN	O	test	prep_with	1	SENT_48	[p4l427t3049r571b3108],
6	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l609t3043r715b3108],
7	serum	NN	O	serum	nn	11	SENT_48	[p4l754t3066r994b3108],
8	hepatitis	NN	O	hepatitis	nn	11	SENT_48	[p4l1032t3043r1374b3124],
9	B	NN	O	b	nn	11	SENT_48	[p4l1411t3045r1467b3107],
10	surface	NN	O	surface	nn	11	SENT_48	[p4l1510t3043r1788b3108],
11	antigen	NN	O	antigen	prep_for	5	SENT_48	[p4l1828t3045r2140b3124],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1828t3045r2140b3124],
13	coinfection	NN	O	coinfection	appos	11	SENT_48	[p4l10t3140r426b3205],
14	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l450t3140r624b3205],
15	other	JJ	O	other	amod	17	SENT_48	[p4l651t3140r854b3205],
16	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	17	SENT_48	[p4l880t3140r1070b3205],
17	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	prep_with	13	SENT_48	[p4l1093t3146r1499b3221],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1093t3146r1499b3221],
19	coinfection	NN	O	coinfection	nsubjpass	58	SENT_48	[p4l1529t3140r1946b3205],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1970t3140r2145b3205],
21	human	JJ	O	human	amod	23	SENT_48	[p4l9t3237r283b3302],
22	immunodeﬁciency	NN	O	immunodeﬁciency	nn	23	SENT_48	[p4l316t3237r1022b3318],
23	virus	NN	O	virus	prep_with	19	SENT_48	[p4l1052t3238r1271b3316],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1052t3238r1271b3316],
25	other	JJ	O	other	amod	26	SENT_48	[p4l1308t3237r1512b3302],
26	causes	NNS	O	cause	nsubjpass	58	SENT_48	[p4l1545t3259r1797b3302],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1831t3237r1906b3302],
28	hepatocellular	JJ	O	hepatocellular	amod	29	SENT_48	[p4l1930t3237r2143b3318, p4l8t3334r377b3399],
29	injury	NN	O	injury	prep_of	26	SENT_48	[p4l440t3336r676b3415],
30	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	29	SENT_48	[p4l742t3334r944b3408],
31	such	JJ	O	such	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l742t3334r944b3408],
32	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1010t3357r1090b3399],
33	alcoholism	NN	O	alcoholism	prep_such_as	29	SENT_48	[p4l1156t3334r1584b3413],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1156t3334r1584b3413],
35	autoimmune	JJ	O	autoimmune	amod	36	SENT_48	[p4l1654t3336r2144b3399],
36	hepatitis	NN	O	hepatitis	conj_or	33	SENT_48	[p4l9t3432r371b3513],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l9t3432r371b3513],
38	primary	JJ	O	primary	amod	40	SENT_48	[p4l396t3433r712b3513],
39	biliary	JJ	O	biliary	amod	40	SENT_48	[p4l730t3432r986b3512],
40	cirrhosis	NN	O	cirrhosis	prep_such_as	29	SENT_48	[p4l1007t3431r1360b3511],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1007t3431r1360b3511],
42	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1386t3454r1463b3496],
43	a	DT	O	a	det	44	SENT_48	[p4l1485t3454r1527b3496],
44	history	NN	O	history	prep_such_as	29	SENT_48	[p4l1546t3432r1820b3512],
45	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1840t3432r1916b3496],
46	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_of	44	SENT_48	[p4l1927t3438r2142b3496, p4l9t3534r208b3593],
47	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l230t3528r404b3593],
48	hepatotoxic	JJ	O	hepatotoxic	amod	49	SENT_48	[p4l428t3528r875b3609],
49	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_with	46	SENT_48	[p4l898t3528r1164b3609],
50	)	RB	O	)	advmod	46	SENT_48	[p4l898t3528r1164b3609],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l898t3528r1164b3609],
52	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1195t3528r1337b3593],
53	a	DT	O	a	det	54	SENT_48	[p4l1362t3550r1404b3593],
54	need	NN	O	need	conj_and	1	SENT_48	[p4l1427t3528r1609b3593],
55	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1632t3528r1737b3593],
56	hemodialysis	NN	O	hemodialysis	prep_for	54	SENT_48	[p4l1760t3528r2142b3593, p4l6t3627r155b3706],
57	Were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	58	SENT_48	[p4l184t3648r369b3690],
58	excluded	VBN	O	exclude	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l400t3625r757b3690],
59	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l400t3625r757b3690],

1	Study	NNP	O	Study	nn	2	SENT_49	[p5l789t64r1044b145],
2	Design	NNP	O	Design	_	0	SENT_49	[p5l1067t64r1368b145],

1	Each	DT	O	each	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l94t211r287b275],
2	patient	NN	O	patient	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l320t212r599b292],
3	was	VBD	O	be	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l631t233r780b276],
4	treated	VBN	O	treat	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l812t211r1093b276],
5	with	IN	O	with	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1124t211r1299b276],
6	combination	NN	O	combination	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1333t211r1809b276],
7	therapy	NN	O	therapy	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1841t211r2146b292],
8	with	IN	O	with	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l8t307r182b372],
9	PEG-IFN-oz2b	NN	O	peg-ifn-oz2b	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l216t307r754b372],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l791t308r1256b388],
11	Peg-Intron	NNP	MISC	Peg-Intron	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l791t308r1256b388],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l791t308r1256b388],
13	Schering-Plough	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Schering-Plough	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1295t307r1939b388],
14	Nordic	JJ	O	nordic	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1972t309r2143b372, p5l10t404r119b469],
15	Biotech	NNP	O	Biotech	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l139t405r450b484],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l139t405r450b484],
17	Stockholm	NNP	LOCATION	Stockholm	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l478t404r903b484],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l478t404r903b484],
19	Sweden	NNP	LOCATION	Sweden	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l931t405r1249b484],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l931t405r1249b484],
21	at	IN	O	at	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1276t411r1350b469],
22	a	DT	O	a	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1373t427r1415b469],
23	dose	NN	O	dose	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1436t405r1603b469],
24	of	IN	O	of	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1625t405r1701b469],
25	1.2-1	CD	NUMBER	1.2-1	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1719t407r1988b469],
26	.5	CD	NUMBER	.5	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1719t407r1988b469],
27	p.	NN	O	p.	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l2027t404r2147b486],
28	g	NN	O	g	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l2027t404r2147b486],
29	/	:	O	/	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l2027t404r2147b486],
30	kg	NN	O	kg	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l9t502r105b583],
31	subcutaneously	RB	O	subcutaneously	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l167t502r769b583],
32	once	RB	DATE	once	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l833t524r1003b566],
33	a	DT	DURATION	a	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1069t524r1111b566],
34	week	NN	DURATION	week	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1173t502r1396b575],
35	)	NN	O	)	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1173t502r1396b575],
36	or	CC	O	or	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1464t524r1540b566],
37	PEG-IFN-oz2a	NN	O	peg-ifn-oz2a	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1604t502r2146b567],
38	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l12t598r369b679],
39	Pegasys	NNS	O	pegasy	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l12t598r369b679],
40	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l12t598r369b679],
41	Roche	NNP	PERSON	Roche	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l435t598r686b677],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l435t598r686b677],
43	Basel	NNP	LOCATION	Basel	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l751t598r983b677],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l751t598r983b677],
45	Switzerland	NNP	LOCATION	Switzerland	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1052t598r1538b677],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l1052t598r1538b677],
47	at	IN	O	at	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1606t604r1680b663],
48	a	DT	O	a	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1744t620r1786b663],
49	dose	NN	O	dose	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1848t598r2016b663],
50	of	IN	O	of	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l2078t598r2154b663],
51	180	CD	NUMBER	180	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l16t698r144b760],
52	pug	NN	O	pug	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l182t716r280b777],
53	subcutaneously	RB	O	subcutaneously	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l299t696r900b776],
54	once	RB	DATE	once	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l920t718r1090b760],
55	a	DT	DURATION	a	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1114t718r1156b760],
56	week	NN	DURATION	week	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1174t696r1398b769],
57	)	NN	O	)	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1174t696r1398b769],
58	plus	CC	O	plus	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1420t696r1583b777],
59	RBV	NN	O	rbv	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1604t697r1786b760],
60	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1806t696r2140b775],
61	Rebetol	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Rebetol	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1806t696r2140b775],
62	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l1806t696r2140b775],
63	Schering-Plough	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Schering-Plough	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l12t793r656b874],
64	Nordic	JJ	O	nordic	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l707t793r965b858],
65	Biotech	NN	O	biotech	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1014t793r1306b858],
66	or	CC	O	or	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1357t815r1434b857],
67	Copegus	NN	O	copegus	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1485t793r1831b874],
68	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l1485t793r1831b874],
69	Roche	NNP	LOCATION	Roche	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1885t793r2141b866],
70	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1885t793r2141b866],
71	600	CD	NUMBER	600	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l11t892r401b968],
72	—	NN	O	—	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l11t892r401b968],
73	1,000	CD	NUMBER	1,000	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l11t892r401b968],
74	mg	NN	O	mg	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l435t910r556b970],
75	daily	JJ	SET	daily	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l610t889r801b970],
76	depending	VBG	O	depend	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l858t889r1263b970],
77	on	IN	O	on	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1318t911r1408b954],
78	the	DT	O	the	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1464t889r1588b954],
79	body	NN	O	body	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1644t889r1827b970],
80	weight	NN	O	weight	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1882t889r2145b970],
81	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l12t986r219b1060],
82	b.w.	NN	O	b.w.	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l12t986r219b1060],
83	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l12t986r219b1060],
84	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l270t987r447b1059],
85	b.w.	NN	O	b.w.	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l270t987r447b1059],
86	<	JJR	O	<	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l502t989r650b1053],
87	60	CD	NUMBER	60	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l502t989r650b1053],
88	kg	NN	O	kg	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l683t986r795b1067],
89	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l683t986r795b1067],
90	600	CD	NUMBER	600	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l846t989r980b1051],
91	mg	NN	O	mg	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1013t1007r1133b1067],
92	po	NN	O	po	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1174t1009r1261b1068],
93	daily	RB	SET	daily	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1307t987r1517b1067],
94	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l1307t987r1517b1067],
95	b.	FW	O	b.	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1563t987r1717b1051],
96	w	FW	O	w	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1563t987r1717b1051],
97	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l1563t987r1717b1051],
98	60-80	CD	NUMBER	60-80	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1768t989r1994b1051],
99	kg	NN	O	kg	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l2028t987r2139b1067],
100	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l2028t987r2139b1067],
101	800	CD	NUMBER	800	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l11t1086r144b1149],
102	mg	NN	O	mg	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l178t1104r298b1165],
103	po	NN	O	po	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l339t1106r426b1165],
104	daily	RB	SET	daily	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l472t1084r682b1165],
105	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l472t1084r682b1165],
106	b.w.	FW	O	b.w.	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l728t1084r882b1149],
107	>	JJR	O	>	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l936t1086r1085b1150],
108	80	CD	NUMBER	80	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l936t1086r1085b1150],
109	kg	NN	O	kg	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1117t1084r1229b1165],
110	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l1117t1084r1229b1165],
111	1,000	CD	NUMBER	1,000	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1285t1086r1484b1163],
112	mg	NN	O	mg	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1517t1104r1638b1165],
113	po	NN	O	po	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1678t1106r1766b1165],
114	daily	RB	SET	daily	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l1812t1084r2022b1165],
115	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l1812t1084r2022b1165],
116	in	IN	O	in	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l2070t1085r2144b1147],
117	two	CD	NUMBER	two	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l8t1187r146b1245],
118	divided	JJ	O	divided	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l191t1181r474b1245],
119	doses	NNS	O	dose	dep	120	SENT_50	[p5l518t1181r771b1253],
120	)	RB	O	)	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l518t1181r771b1253],
121	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p5l518t1181r771b1253],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_51	[p5l820t1181r967b1245],
2	duration	NN	O	duration	nsubjpass	8	SENT_51	[p5l1012t1181r1346b1245],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1391t1181r1466b1245],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_51	[p5l1500t1181r1624b1245],
5	combination	NN	O	combination	nn	6	SENT_51	[p5l1669t1181r2144b1245],
6	therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_of	2	SENT_51	[p5l8t1277r312b1359],
7	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_51	[p5l338t1300r486b1342],
8	set	VBN	O	set	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l515t1284r623b1342],
9	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l652t1284r726b1342],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	13	SENT_51	[p5l754t1300r796b1342],
11	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	13	SENT_51	[p5l824t1278r1171b1342],
12	24	CD	DURATION	24	num	13	SENT_51	[p5l1198t1280r1286b1341],
13	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	prep_at	8	SENT_51	[p5l1312t1278r1569b1357],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1312t1278r1569b1357],
15	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1598t1277r1728b1342],
16	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nn	17	SENT_51	[p5l1753t1284r2145b1342],
17	reduction	NN	O	reduction	nsubjpass	21	SENT_51	[p5l9t1375r377b1440],
18	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l407t1397r483b1439],
19	discontinuation	NN	O	discontinuation	nsubjpass	21	SENT_51	[p5l512t1375r1116b1440],
20	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	21	SENT_51	[p5l1144t1397r1293b1440],
21	permitted	VBN	O	permit	conj_but	8	SENT_51	[p5l1321t1375r1705b1456],
22	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1731t1375r1823b1456],
23	doctor	NN	O	doctor	poss	25	SENT_51	[p5l1851t1375r2144b1440],
24	’s	POS	O	’s	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l1851t1375r2144b1440],
25	decision	NN	O	decision	agent	21	SENT_51	[p5l10t1471r339b1535],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p5l10t1471r339b1535],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_52	[p5l361t1471r508b1535],
2	rates	NNS	O	rate	nsubjpass	11	SENT_52	[p5l525t1477r720b1535],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l738t1471r814b1535],
4	PE	NN	O	pe	nn	5	SENT_52	[p5l823t1472r933b1534],
5	G-IFN	NN	O	g-ifn	prep_of	2	SENT_52	[p5l942t1471r1189b1535],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l1209t1471r1351b1535],
7	RBV	NN	O	rbv	nn	8	SENT_52	[p5l1368t1472r1550b1535],
8	administration	NN	O	administration	prep_of	2	SENT_52	[p5l1566t1471r2144b1535],
9	achieved	VBN	O	achieve	partmod	5	SENT_52	[p5l11t1567r348b1632],
10	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_52	[p5l374t1590r559b1632],
11	calculated	VBN	O	calculate	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l587t1567r981b1632],
12	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l1010t1590r1090b1632],
13	percentages	NNS	O	percentage	prep_as	11	SENT_52	[p5l1116t1574r1580b1649],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l1608t1568r1684b1632],
15	actual	JJ	O	actual	amod	17	SENT_52	[p5l1704t1568r1941b1632],
16	total	JJ	O	total	amod	17	SENT_52	[p5l1967t1568r2145b1632],
17	dose	NN	O	dose	prep_of	13	SENT_52	[p5l10t1665r177b1729],
18	administered	VBN	O	administer	partmod	17	SENT_52	[p5l205t1665r718b1729],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l743t1665r819b1729],
20	a	DT	O	a	det	23	SENT_52	[p5l838t1686r880b1729],
21	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	23	SENT_52	[p5l907t1665r1254b1729],
22	total	NN	O	total	nn	23	SENT_52	[p5l1278t1665r1456b1729],
23	dose	NN	O	dose	prep_of	18	SENT_52	[p5l1483t1665r1650b1729],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l1677t1665r1752b1729],
25	24	CD	DURATION	24	num	26	SENT_52	[p5l1770t1667r1858b1727],
26	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	prep_of	23	SENT_52	[p5l1884t1665r2140b1743],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l1884t1665r2140b1743],
28	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l11t1760r384b1841],
29	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	18	SENT_52	[p5l408t1766r480b1825],
30	body	NN	O	body	nn	31	SENT_52	[p5l506t1760r689b1841],
31	weight	NN	O	weight	pobj	18	SENT_52	[p5l715t1760r978b1841],
32	before	IN	O	before	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l1003t1760r1241b1825],
33	therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_before	31	SENT_52	[p5l1268t1760r1590b1841],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p5l1268t1760r1590b1841],

1	During	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l1624t1761r1903b1841],
2	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_during	6	SENT_53	[p5l1927t1766r2142b1825, p5l9t1863r227b1936],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l1927t1766r2142b1825, p5l9t1863r227b1936],
4	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubjpass	6	SENT_53	[p5l253t1858r570b1938],
5	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_53	[p5l591t1879r777b1922],
6	assessed	VBN	O	assess	conj_and	6	SENT_53	[p5l801t1857r1131b1922],
7	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l1154t1879r1234b1922],
8	outpatients	NNS	O	outpatient	prep_as	6	SENT_53	[p5l1257t1858r1699b1938],
9	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l1724t1863r1798b1922],
10	weeks	NNS	DURATION	week	prep_at	8	SENT_53	[p5l1819t1857r2055b1922],
11	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	10	SENT_53	[p5l2079t1860r2140b1936],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l2079t1860r2140b1936],
13	4	CD	NUMBER	4	conj_and	10	SENT_53	[p5l10t1957r72b2034],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l10t1957r72b2034],
15	6	CD	NUMBER	6	prep_at	8	SENT_53	[p5l101t1957r162b2034],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l101t1957r162b2034],
17	8	CD	NUMBER	8	prep_at	8	SENT_53	[p5l191t1957r252b2034],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l191t1957r252b2034],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l282t1955r424b2019],
20	then	RB	O	then	advmod	10	SENT_53	[p5l446t1955r622b2020],
21	every	DT	SET	every	det	23	SENT_53	[p5l646t1977r857b2036],
22	4	CD	SET	4	num	23	SENT_53	[p5l879t1957r922b2018],
23	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	conj_and	10	SENT_53	[p5l944t1955r1181b2020],
24	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l1205t1955r1310b2019],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_53	[p5l1332t1955r1456b2020],
26	duration	NN	O	duration	prep_for	6	SENT_53	[p5l1480t1955r1814b2020],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l1838t1955r1914b2019],
28	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_of	26	SENT_53	[p5l1927t1961r2142b2020, p5l9t2057r208b2116],
29	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l240t2051r382b2116],
30	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l414t2057r487b2116],
31	every	DT	SET	every	det	33	SENT_53	[p5l518t2073r729b2132],
32	4	CD	SET	4	num	33	SENT_53	[p5l758t2054r800b2115],
33	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	prep_at	6	SENT_53	[p5l830t2051r1067b2116],
34	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l1099t2051r1282b2116],
35	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_53	[p5l1310t2051r1434b2116],
36	end	NN	O	end	prep_after	6	SENT_53	[p5l1465t2051r1604b2116],
37	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l1634t2051r1710b2116],
38	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_of	36	SENT_53	[p5l1730t2057r2139b2116],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p5l1730t2057r2139b2116],

1	Biochemical	JJ	MISC	biochemical	nsubjpass	6	SENT_54	[p5l8t2148r480b2213],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p5l510t2148r652b2213],
3	hematological	JJ	O	hematological	amod	4	SENT_54	[p5l680t2148r1219b2229],
4	testing	NN	O	testing	conj_and	1	SENT_54	[p5l1247t2149r1518b2229],
5	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_54	[p5l1542t2170r1690b2213],
6	carried	VBN	O	carry	_	0	SENT_54	[p5l1720t2148r1994b2213],
7	out	RP	O	out	prt	6	SENT_54	[p5l2022t2154r2145b2213],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p5l9t2247r84b2309],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_54	[p5l106t2268r148b2310],
10	central	JJ	O	central	amod	11	SENT_54	[p5l168t2246r440b2311],
11	laboratory	NN	O	laboratory	prep_in	6	SENT_54	[p5l460t2246r880b2327],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p5l460t2246r880b2327],

1	Serum	NN	O	serum	nn	3	SENT_55	[p5l908t2246r1162b2311],
2	HCV	NN	O	hcv	nn	3	SENT_55	[p5l1182t2246r1373b2311],
3	RNA	NN	O	rna	nsubjpass	5	SENT_55	[p5l1391t2246r1580b2311],
4	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_55	[p5l1596t2268r1745b2311],
5	measured	VBN	O	measure	conj_and	5	SENT_55	[p5l1765t2246r2146b2311],
6	before	IN	O	before	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l7t2342r245b2407],
7	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_before	5	SENT_55	[p5l277t2348r689b2421],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l277t2348r689b2421],
9	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l726t2342r988b2423],
10	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_during	5	SENT_55	[p5l1017t2348r1408b2407],
11	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1443t2348r1517b2407],
12	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	14	SENT_55	[p5l1550t2345r1593b2405],
13	weekly	JJ	SET	weekly	amod	14	SENT_55	[p5l1625t2342r1897b2423],
14	intervals	NNS	O	interval	prep_at	10	SENT_55	[p5l1929t2343r2142b2407, p5l7t2439r183b2518],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1929t2343r2142b2407, p5l7t2439r183b2518],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l251t2439r393b2504],
17	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l455t2439r637b2504],
18	therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_after	5	SENT_55	[p5l697t2439r1002b2520],
19	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1063t2445r1138b2504],
20	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	22	SENT_55	[p5l1199t2442r1241b2503],
21	weekly	JJ	SET	weekly	amod	22	SENT_55	[p5l1301t2439r1573b2520],
22	intervals	NNS	O	interval	prep_at	5	SENT_55	[p5l1633t2439r1978b2504],
23	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l2040t2439r2145b2504],
24	24	CD	DURATION	24	num	25	SENT_55	[p5l10t2539r98b2599],
25	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	prep_for	22	SENT_55	[p5l127t2536r384b2615],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l127t2536r384b2615],
27	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l415t2536r507b2617],
28	quantitative	JJ	O	quantitative	amod	31	SENT_55	[p5l537t2537r1014b2617],
29	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1044t2558r1121b2601],
30	qualitative	JJ	O	qualitative	conj_or	28	SENT_55	[p5l1151t2536r1570b2617],
31	assays	NNS	O	assay	agent	5	SENT_55	[p5l1602t2558r1870b2617],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1602t2558r1870b2617],

1	Patient	NN	O	patient	nn	2	SENT_56	[p5l660t2731r983b2795],
2	Evaluation	NN	O	evaluation	_	0	SENT_56	[p5l1010t2731r1494b2795],
