1	pharméceuiics	NNS	O	pharméceuiics	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1648t139r2105b286],

1	Vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	6	SENT_2	[p1l373t373r564b413],
2	E	NN	O	e	nn	6	SENT_2	[p1l589t373r619b412],
3	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	nn	6	SENT_2	[p1l640t372r785b413],
4	P-Glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	nn	6	SENT_2	[p1l809t372r1190b424],
5	Inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	nn	6	SENT_2	[p1l1215t373r1452b413],
6	Mechanism	NN	O	mechanism	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1477t373r1782b413],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1477t373r1782b413],
8	Influence	NN	O	influence	dep	6	SENT_2	[p1l345t439r578b479],
9	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l599t448r660b479],
10	Conformational	NNP	O	Conformational	nn	11	SENT_2	[p1l684t438r1078b479],
11	Flexibility	NNP	O	Flexibility	prep_on	8	SENT_2	[p1l1104t439r1362b490],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1104t439r1362b490],
13	Intracellular	JJ	O	intracellular	amod	14	SENT_2	[p1l1386t439r1689b479],
14	ATP	NN	O	atp	appos	11	SENT_2	[p1l1709t439r1814b478],

1	Levels	NNS	O	level	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l505t505r682b553],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l505t505r682b553],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l704t505r796b545],
4	Role	NN	O	role	conj_and	1	SENT_3	[p1l821t505r933b545],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l954t504r1003b545],
6	Time	NNP	O	Time	prep_of	4	SENT_3	[p1l1022t504r1147b545],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1168t505r1260b545],
8	Site	NN	O	site	prep_of	4	SENT_3	[p1l1282t504r1379b545],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1400t504r1448b545],
10	Access	NN	O	access	nn	11	SENT_3	[p1l1468t505r1655b545],
11	articles	NNS	O	article	prep_of	1	SENT_3	[p1l31t215r318b277],

1	Eva-Maria	NNP	PERSON	Eva-Maria	nn	2	SENT_4	[p1l346t635r540b665],
2	Collnot	NNP	PERSON	Collnot	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l556t628r740b672],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l556t628r740b672],
4	*	CD	NUMBER	*	num	5	SENT_4	[p1l556t628r740b672],
5	’	NN	O	’	appos	2	SENT_4	[p1l556t628r740b672],
6	l	NN	O	l	tmod	5	SENT_4	[p1l556t628r740b672],
7	Christiane	NNP	PERSON	Christiane	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l757t635r941b665],
8	Baldesf	NNP	PERSON	Baldesf	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l956t628r1099b672],
9	‘	NNP	O	‘	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l956t628r1099b672],
10	Ulrich	NNP	PERSON	Ulrich	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l1114t635r1227b665],
11	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l1242t636r1276b665],
12	Schaeferf	NNP	PERSON	Schaeferf	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l1292t628r1471b672],
13	‘	NNP	O	‘	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l1292t628r1471b672],
14	Kevin	NNP	PERSON	Kevin	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l1487t635r1592b665],
15	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l1606t636r1636b669],
16	Edgar	NNP	PERSON	Edgar	dep	2	SENT_4	[p1l1652t628r1811b673],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1652t628r1811b673],
18	”	CD	NUMBER	”	appos	16	SENT_4	[p1l1652t628r1811b673],

1	Michael	NNP	PERSON	Michael	nn	3	SENT_5	[p1l649t684r791b714],
2	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	3	SENT_5	[p1l806t685r840b714],
3	Wempe	NNP	PERSON	Wempe	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l856t677r1037b722],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l856t677r1037b722],
5	*	CD	NUMBER	*	num	6	SENT_5	[p1l856t677r1037b722],
6	’”	NN	O	’”	conj_and	3	SENT_5	[p1l856t677r1037b722],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1053t685r1118b714],
8	Claus-Michael	NNP	PERSON	Claus-Michael	nn	9	SENT_5	[p1l1135t684r1391b714],
9	Lehrl	NNP	PERSON	Lehrl	conj_and	3	SENT_5	[p1l1407t677r1508b714],

1	66123	CD	NUMBER	66123	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l331t815r428b843],
2	Saarbriicken	NNP	O	Saarbriicken	nn	8	SENT_7	[p1l442t815r650b848],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l442t815r650b848],
4	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	appos	8	SENT_7	[p1l669t816r820b851],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l669t816r820b851],
6	Eastman	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Eastman	appos	8	SENT_7	[p1l837t816r975b844],
7	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	8	SENT_7	[p1l992t815r1141b844],
8	Company	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Company	dep	1	SENT_7	[p1l1157t816r1311b851],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1157t816r1311b851],
10	Kingsport	NNP	LOCATION	Kingsport	nn	14	SENT_7	[p1l1329t816r1493b851],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1329t816r1493b851],
12	Tennessee	NNP	LOCATION	Tennessee	appos	14	SENT_7	[p1l1513t816r1679b848],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1513t816r1679b848],
14	Virginia	NNP	LOCATION	Virginia	appos	8	SENT_7	[p1l1699t816r1827b851],

1	Tech	NNP	O	Tech	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l395t863r475b896],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l395t863r475b896],
3	230	CD	NUMBER	230	num	5	SENT_8	[p1l493t863r552b891],
4	Cheatham	NNP	PERSON	Cheatham	nn	5	SENT_8	[p1l568t863r728b892],
5	Hall	NNP	PERSON	Hall	conj_and	1	SENT_8	[p1l741t863r817b896],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l741t863r817b896],
7	Blacksburg	NNP	LOCATION	Blacksburg	conj_and	1	SENT_8	[p1l834t863r1021b899],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l834t863r1021b899],
9	Virginia	NNP	LOCATION	Virginia	conj_and	1	SENT_8	[p1l1041t864r1176b899],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1041t864r1176b899],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1194t863r1254b891],
12	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	conj_and	1	SENT_8	[p1l1265t864r1456b899],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1469t863r1505b899],
14	Pharmaceutical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceutical	prep_of	1	SENT_8	[p1l1512t863r1765b891],

1	Sciences	NNPS	O	Sciences	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l590t912r732b944],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l590t912r732b944],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	1	SENT_9	[p1l753t912r915b947],
4	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	3	SENT_9	[p1l930t911r965b947],
5	Colorado	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Colorado	nn	6	SENT_9	[p1l975t911r1124b940],
6	Denver	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Denver	pobj	4	SENT_9	[p1l1137t912r1261b944],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1137t912r1261b944],
8	Aurora	NNP	LOCATION	Aurora	nn	10	SENT_9	[p1l1277t912r1399b944],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1277t912r1399b944],
10	Colorado	NNP	LOCATION	Colorado	dep	1	SENT_9	[p1l1419t911r1567b940],

1	Received	VBN	O	receive	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l350t987r493b1014],
2	August	NNP	DATE	August	tmod	1	SENT_10	[p1l507t987r616b1021],
3	5	CD	DATE	5	num	2	SENT_10	[p1l629t988r655b1018],
4	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l629t988r655b1018],
5	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	2	SENT_10	[p1l670t987r755b1018],
6	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l670t987r755b1018],
7	Revised	VBN	O	revise	parataxis	1	SENT_10	[p1l773t987r896b1014],
8	Manuscript	NNP	O	Manuscript	nn	9	SENT_10	[p1l912t987r1082b1020],
9	Received	NNP	O	Received	dobj	7	SENT_10	[p1l1098t987r1241b1014],
10	January	NNP	DATE	January	tmod	9	SENT_10	[p1l1255t987r1380b1021],
11	14	CD	DATE	14	num	10	SENT_10	[p1l1395t987r1438b1018],
12	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1395t987r1438b1018],
13	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	10	SENT_10	[p1l1454t987r1539b1018],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1454t987r1539b1018],
15	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	amod	16	SENT_10	[p1l1554t987r1699b1020],
16	March	NNP	DATE	March	dep	9	SENT_10	[p1l1715t987r1809b1014],

1	Abstract	JJ	O	abstract	nsubj	9	SENT_11	[p1l255t1178r433b1209],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l255t1178r433b1209],
3	Previous	JJ	O	previous	amod	4	SENT_11	[p1l451t1180r601b1209],
4	work	NN	O	work	dep	1	SENT_11	[p1l613t1180r696b1209],
5	conducted	VBN	O	conduct	partmod	4	SENT_11	[p1l708t1180r888b1209],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l903t1180r929b1208],
7	our	PRP$	O	we	poss	8	SENT_11	[p1l943t1187r999b1209],
8	laboratories	NNS	O	laboratory	prep_in	5	SENT_11	[p1l1012t1180r1215b1209],
9	established	VBD	O	establish	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1228t1180r1425b1209],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_11	[p1l1438t1180r1491b1209],
11	notion	NN	O	notion	dobj	9	SENT_11	[p1l1506t1180r1609b1209],
12	that	IN	O	that	complm	13	SENT_11	[p1l1622t1180r1687b1209],
13	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	dep	9	SENT_11	[p1l1699t1179r1804b1209],
14	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	13	SENT_11	[p1l1820t1180r1903b1209],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_11	[p1l256t1231r520b1269],
16	D-o	NN	O	d-o	dep	13	SENT_11	[p1l256t1231r520b1269],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l256t1231r520b1269],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l256t1231r520b1269],
2	tocopheryl	NN	O	tocopheryl	nn	7	SENT_12	[p1l256t1231r520b1269],
3	polyethylene	NN	O	polyethylene	nn	7	SENT_12	[p1l547t1231r766b1269],
4	glycol	NN	O	glycol	nn	7	SENT_12	[p1l791t1231r889b1269],
5	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	7	SENT_12	[p1l917t1232r1000b1261],
6	succinate	JJ	O	succinate	amod	7	SENT_12	[p1l1025t1231r1212b1269],
7	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	13	SENT_12	[p1l1025t1231r1212b1269],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1025t1231r1212b1269],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_12	[p1l1239t1239r1259b1261],
10	nonionic	JJ	O	nonionic	amod	11	SENT_12	[p1l1285t1231r1429b1261],
11	surfactant	NN	O	surfactant	appos	7	SENT_12	[p1l1454t1231r1634b1266],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1454t1231r1634b1266],
13	modulates	VBZ	O	modulate	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1662t1231r1841b1261],
14	Pglycoprotein	NNP	O	Pglycoprotein	nsubj	19	SENT_12	[p1l1868t1231r1903b1260, p1l255t1283r465b1320],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	14	SENT_12	[p1l485t1282r590b1320],
16	P-gp	JJ	O	p-gp	amod	19	SENT_12	[p1l485t1282r590b1320],
17	)	NN	O	)	nn	19	SENT_12	[p1l485t1282r590b1320],
18	efflux	NN	O	efflux	nn	19	SENT_12	[p1l609t1282r702b1312],
19	transport	NN	O	transport	xcomp	13	SENT_12	[p1l718t1284r873b1320],
20	via	IN	O	via	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l890t1283r939b1312],
21	P-gp	JJ	O	p-gp	amod	23	SENT_12	[p1l958t1283r1037b1320],
22	ATPase	NN	O	atpase	nn	23	SENT_12	[p1l1054t1283r1193b1312],
23	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	prep_via	19	SENT_12	[p1l1212t1283r1374b1312],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1212t1283r1374b1312],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_13	[p1l1393t1283r1459b1312],
2	current	JJ	DATE	current	dep	5	SENT_13	[p1l1477t1284r1599b1312],
3	in	FW	O	in	nn	4	SENT_13	[p1l1617t1283r1646b1311],
4	vitro	FW	O	vitro	dep	2	SENT_13	[p1l1665t1283r1737b1312],
5	research	NN	O	research	nsubjpass	10	SENT_13	[p1l1753t1283r1902b1312],
6	using	VBG	O	use	partmod	5	SENT_13	[p1l256t1334r346b1371],
7	Caco-2	NN	O	caco-2	nn	8	SENT_13	[p1l364t1333r489b1363],
8	cells	NNS	O	cell	dobj	6	SENT_13	[p1l505t1334r582b1363],
9	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_13	[p1l598t1341r667b1363],
10	conducted	VBN	O	conduct	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l683t1334r863b1363],
11	to	TO	O	to	aux	13	SENT_13	[p1l879t1336r911b1363],
12	further	RB	O	further	advmod	13	SENT_13	[p1l927t1333r1041b1363],
13	explore	VB	O	explore	xcomp	10	SENT_13	[p1l1056t1334r1183b1371],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_13	[p1l1199t1334r1253b1363],
15	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	18	SENT_13	[p1l1271t1334r1350b1371],
16	ATPase	NN	MISC	atpase	nn	18	SENT_13	[p1l1366t1334r1505b1363],
17	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	nn	18	SENT_13	[p1l1523t1334r1675b1363],
18	mechanism	NN	O	mechanism	dobj	13	SENT_13	[p1l1694t1334r1901b1363],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1694t1334r1901b1363],

1	Using	VBG	O	use	partmod	14	SENT_14	[p1l257t1385r353b1422],
2	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_14	[p1l369t1392r389b1414],
3	monoclonal	JJ	O	monoclonal	amod	5	SENT_14	[p1l404t1385r602b1414],
4	CD243	NN	O	cd243	nn	5	SENT_14	[p1l618t1384r739b1414],
5	P-gp	NN	O	p-gp	dobj	1	SENT_14	[p1l755t1385r834b1422],
6	antibody	NN	O	antibody	nn	11	SENT_14	[p1l849t1385r997b1422],
7	shift	NN	O	shift	nn	11	SENT_14	[p1l1011t1384r1082b1414],
8	assay	NN	O	assay	nn	11	SENT_14	[p1l1096t1392r1198b1422],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_14	[p1l1213t1384r1335b1422],
10	UIC2	NN	O	uic2	nn	11	SENT_14	[p1l1213t1384r1335b1422],
11	)	NN	O	)	dep	5	SENT_14	[p1l1213t1384r1335b1422],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1213t1384r1335b1422],
13	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	14	SENT_14	[p1l1351t1392r1400b1414],
14	probed	VBD	O	probe	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1415t1385r1535b1422],
15	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	17	SENT_14	[p1l1552t1385r1631b1422],
16	conformational	JJ	O	conformational	amod	17	SENT_14	[p1l1646t1384r1902b1414],
17	changes	NNS	O	change	nsubj	18	SENT_14	[p1l255t1436r402b1474],
18	induced	VBD	O	induce	ccomp	14	SENT_14	[p1l420t1436r555b1466],
19	via	IN	O	via	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l572t1436r621b1466],
20	TPGS	NNP	O	TPGS	prep_via	18	SENT_14	[p1l637t1435r743b1466],
21	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	20	SENT_14	[p1l763t1436r855b1466],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l763t1436r855b1466],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l876t1436r903b1465],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_15	[p1l921t1436r974b1466],
3	presence	NN	O	presence	prep_in	12	SENT_15	[p1l992t1443r1152b1473],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1169t1435r1200b1466],
5	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	prep_of	3	SENT_15	[p1l1216t1435r1321b1466],
6	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	5	SENT_15	[p1l1341t1436r1433b1471],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1341t1436r1433b1471],
8	UIC2	NN	O	uic2	nn	9	SENT_15	[p1l1454t1435r1540b1466],
9	binding	NN	O	binding	nsubjpass	12	SENT_15	[p1l1558t1436r1682b1474],
10	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	12	SENT_15	[p1l1699t1443r1768b1466],
11	slightly	RB	O	slightly	advmod	12	SENT_15	[p1l1785t1436r1904b1474],
12	decreased	VBN	O	decrease	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l255t1488r447b1518],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l255t1488r447b1518],

1	TPGS	NNS	O	tpg	nsubj	5	SENT_16	[p1l467t1487r573b1518],
2	1000	CD	DATE	1000	dep	1	SENT_16	[p1l595t1488r678b1518],
3	does	VBZ	O	do	aux	5	SENT_16	[p1l698t1488r781b1518],
4	not	RB	O	not	neg	5	SENT_16	[p1l802t1490r854b1518],
5	appear	VB	O	appear	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l873t1495r995b1525],
6	to	TO	O	to	aux	10	SENT_16	[p1l1012t1490r1044b1518],
7	be	VB	O	be	cop	10	SENT_16	[p1l1064t1488r1105b1518],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_16	[p1l1124t1495r1144b1518],
9	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	10	SENT_16	[p1l1165t1488r1245b1526],
10	substrate	NN	O	substrate	xcomp	5	SENT_16	[p1l1264t1488r1434b1523],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1264t1488r1434b1523],
12	nor	CC	O	nor	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1456t1495r1511b1518],
13	does	VBZ	O	do	aux	15	SENT_16	[p1l1529t1488r1613b1518],
14	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	15	SENT_16	[p1l1633t1488r1650b1517],
15	function	VB	O	function	conj_nor	5	SENT_16	[p1l1668t1487r1804b1518],
16	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1825t1495r1864b1518],
17	a	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_16	[p1l1884t1495r1904b1518],
18	competitive	JJ	O	competitive	amod	19	SENT_16	[p1l255t1539r451b1577],
19	inhibitor	NN	O	inhibitor	prep_as	15	SENT_16	[p1l465t1539r600b1569],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l612t1539r638b1568],
21	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	24	SENT_16	[p1l653t1539r732b1577],
22	substrate	NN	O	substrate	nn	24	SENT_16	[p1l744t1539r903b1569],
23	efflux	NN	O	efflux	nn	24	SENT_16	[p1l915t1539r1007b1569],
24	transport	NN	O	transport	prep_in	19	SENT_16	[p1l1018t1541r1181b1577],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1018t1541r1181b1577],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_17	[p1l1194t1539r1260b1569],
2	reduction	NN	O	reduction	nsubj	38	SENT_17	[p1l1274t1539r1430b1569],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1445t1539r1471b1568],
4	UIC2	NN	O	uic2	nn	5	SENT_17	[p1l1485t1539r1571b1569],
5	binding	NN	O	binding	prep_in	2	SENT_17	[p1l1584t1539r1707b1577],
6	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1719t1539r1786b1569],
7	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	prep_with	5	SENT_17	[p1l1798t1539r1904b1569],
8	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	7	SENT_17	[p1l258t1591r340b1620],
9	was	VBD	O	be	cop	38	SENT_17	[p1l352t1597r420b1620],
10	markedly	RB	O	markedly	advmod	11	SENT_17	[p1l433t1590r590b1628],
11	weaker	JJR	O	weaker	amod	38	SENT_17	[p1l600t1590r727b1620],
12	than	IN	O	than	amod	38	SENT_17	[p1l737t1590r811b1620],
13	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l823t1590r890b1620],
14	orthovanadate	NN	O	orthovanadate	prep_with	12	SENT_17	[p1l903t1590r1161b1625],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l903t1590r1161b1625],
16	data	NNS	O	datum	appos	14	SENT_17	[p1l1175t1590r1250b1620],
17	ruling	VBG	O	rule	partmod	16	SENT_17	[p1l1263t1590r1354b1628],
18	out	RP	O	out	prt	17	SENT_17	[p1l1367t1592r1420b1620],
19	trapping	NN	O	trapping	nn	20	SENT_17	[p1l1430t1590r1570b1628],
20	P-gp	NN	O	p-gp	dobj	17	SENT_17	[p1l1585t1590r1663b1628],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1677t1590r1703b1619],
22	a	DT	O	a	det	24	SENT_17	[p1l1716t1597r1736b1620],
23	transition	NN	O	transition	nn	24	SENT_17	[p1l1747t1590r1903b1620],
24	state	NN	O	state	prep_in	20	SENT_17	[p1l255t1644r338b1672],
25	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l357t1642r396b1680],
26	direct	JJ	O	direct	amod	27	SENT_17	[p1l413t1642r508b1672],
27	interaction	NN	O	interaction	agent	17	SENT_17	[p1l527t1642r704b1672],
28	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l722t1642r790b1672],
29	one	CD	NUMBER	one	prep_with	27	SENT_17	[p1l809t1649r872b1672],
30	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l890t1649r924b1672],
31	both	DT	O	both	agent	17	SENT_17	[p1l942t1642r1014b1672],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1033t1642r1065b1672],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_17	[p1l1081t1642r1134b1672],
34	P-gp	JJ	O	p-gp	amod	36	SENT_17	[p1l1154t1642r1233b1680],
35	ATP	NN	O	atp	nn	36	SENT_17	[p1l1250t1642r1325b1672],
36	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	prep_of	31	SENT_17	[p1l1344t1642r1521b1672],
37	binding	NN	O	binding	nn	38	SENT_17	[p1l1539t1642r1663b1680],
38	domains	NNS	O	domain	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1681t1642r1838b1672],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1681t1642r1838b1672],

1	An	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_18	[p1l1857t1642r1902b1671],
2	intracellular	JJ	O	intracellular	amod	5	SENT_18	[p1l256t1694r456b1723],
3	ATP	NN	O	atp	nn	5	SENT_18	[p1l467t1694r542b1723],
4	depletion	NN	O	depletion	nn	5	SENT_18	[p1l555t1694r712b1731],
5	mechanism	NN	O	mechanism	nsubjpass	8	SENT_18	[p1l727t1694r925b1723],
6	could	MD	O	could	aux	8	SENT_18	[p1l938t1694r1030b1723],
7	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_18	[p1l1044t1694r1085b1723],
8	ruled	VBN	O	rule	conj_and	8	SENT_18	[p1l1099t1694r1182b1723],
9	out	RP	O	out	prt	8	SENT_18	[p1l1196t1696r1249b1723],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1262t1694r1288b1723],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_18	[p1l1301t1694r1355b1723],
12	UIC2	NN	O	uic2	nn	13	SENT_18	[p1l1369t1693r1455b1723],
13	assay	NN	O	assay	prep_in	8	SENT_18	[p1l1468t1701r1578b1731],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1468t1701r1578b1731],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1593t1694r1655b1723],
16	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1670t1694r1709b1731],
17	monitoring	VBG	O	monitor	agent	8	SENT_18	[p1l1722t1694r1902b1731],
18	intracellular	JJ	O	intracellular	amod	20	SENT_18	[p1l256t1745r456b1775],
19	ATP	NN	O	atp	nn	20	SENT_18	[p1l472t1745r547b1774],
20	levels	NNS	O	level	dobj	17	SENT_18	[p1l566t1745r664b1775],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l683t1745r709b1774],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_18	[p1l727t1745r781b1775],
23	presence	NN	O	presence	prep_in	17	SENT_18	[p1l799t1752r959b1782],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l977t1744r1008b1775],
25	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	prep_of	23	SENT_18	[p1l1024t1744r1130b1775],
26	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	25	SENT_18	[p1l1151t1745r1243b1775],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1151t1745r1243b1775],

1	Indicating	VBG	O	indicate	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1265t1745r1429b1783],
2	slow	JJ	O	slow	amod	3	SENT_19	[p1l1448t1745r1525b1775],
3	distribution	NN	O	distribution	dobj	1	SENT_19	[p1l1543t1745r1730b1775],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1749t1744r1781b1775],
5	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	prep_of	3	SENT_19	[p1l1797t1744r1903b1775],
6	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	5	SENT_19	[p1l258t1797r340b1826],
7	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l353t1796r412b1826],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_19	[p1l423t1796r475b1826],
9	membrane	NN	O	membrane	prep_into	5	SENT_19	[p1l488t1796r681b1831],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l488t1796r681b1831],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l694t1796r756b1826],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l770t1796r796b1825],
13	agreement	NN	O	agreement	prep_in	5	SENT_19	[p1l809t1798r994b1834],
14	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1004t1796r1070b1825],
15	an	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_19	[p1l1083t1804r1124b1826],
16	intramembranal	JJ	O	intramembranal	amod	19	SENT_19	[p1l1137t1796r1404b1826],
17	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1416t1803r1450b1826],
18	intracellular	JJ	O	intracellular	conj_or	16	SENT_19	[p1l1462t1796r1658b1826],
19	side	NN	O	side	prep_with	1	SENT_19	[p1l1668t1796r1738b1826],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1749t1796r1781b1826],
21	action	NN	O	action	nn	26	SENT_19	[p1l1791t1796r1902b1831],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1791t1796r1902b1831],
23	Caco-2	NN	O	caco-2	dep	26	SENT_19	[p1l255t1847r380b1877],
24	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	26	SENT_19	[p1l394t1847r450b1877],
25	monolayer	NN	O	monolayer	nn	26	SENT_19	[p1l467t1847r649b1885],
26	experiments	NNS	O	experiment	prep_of	19	SENT_19	[p1l662t1847r875b1885],
27	preincubated	VBN	O	preincubate	partmod	26	SENT_19	[p1l890t1847r1115b1885],
28	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1129t1847r1197b1877],
29	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	prep_with	27	SENT_19	[p1l1211t1847r1317b1877],
30	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	29	SENT_19	[p1l1334t1848r1417b1877],
31	produce	VBP	O	produce	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l1432t1847r1572b1885],
32	stronger	JJR	O	stronger	amod	33	SENT_19	[p1l1586t1849r1730b1885],
33	substrate	NN	O	substrate	dobj	31	SENT_19	[p1l1743t1847r1903b1877],
34	inhibitory	JJ	O	inhibitory	amod	35	SENT_19	[p1l256t1898r412b1936],
35	activity	NN	O	activity	nsubj	1	SENT_19	[p1l427t1898r546b1936],
36	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l560t1898r634b1928],
37	those	DT	O	those	prep_than	35	SENT_19	[p1l650t1898r745b1928],
38	conducted	VBN	O	conduct	partmod	37	SENT_19	[p1l761t1898r940b1928],
39	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l958t1898r997b1936],
40	direct	JJ	O	direct	amod	41	SENT_19	[p1l1012t1898r1107b1928],
41	substrate	NN	O	substrate	agent	38	SENT_19	[p1l1122t1898r1282b1928],
42	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1298t1898r1360b1928],
43	surfactant	JJ	O	surfactant	amod	44	SENT_19	[p1l1377t1898r1549b1928],
44	coapplication	NN	O	coapplication	conj_and	41	SENT_19	[p1l1564t1898r1802b1936],
45	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1564t1898r1802b1936],

1	Keywords	NNPS	O	Keywords	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l257t1954r453b1992],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l257t1954r453b1992],
3	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	dep	1	SENT_20	[p1l484t1954r741b1992],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l484t1954r741b1992],
5	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	7	SENT_20	[p1l759t1954r881b1984],
6	E	NN	O	e	nn	7	SENT_20	[p1l900t1954r922b1983],
7	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	dep	3	SENT_20	[p1l937t1953r1053b1989],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l937t1953r1053b1989],
9	efflux	NN	O	efflux	nn	10	SENT_20	[p1l1071t1953r1164b1984],
10	transporter	NN	O	transporter	dep	3	SENT_20	[p1l1178t1956r1377b1991],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1178t1956r1377b1991],
12	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	dep	10	SENT_20	[p1l1396t1954r1557b1989],
13	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1396t1954r1557b1989],
14	ATP	NN	O	atp	dep	3	SENT_20	[p1l1575t1954r1659b1989],
15	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1575t1954r1659b1989],
16	conformation	NN	O	conformation	dep	14	SENT_20	[p1l1677t1953r1902b1984],

1	1	LS	NUMBER	1	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l12t2171r82b2241],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l12t2171r82b2241],

1	Introduction	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l149t2169r710b2242],

1	Drug	NN	O	drug	nn	3	SENT_23	[p1l92t2288r272b2368],
2	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	3	SENT_23	[p1l310t2286r445b2349],
3	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	nsubjpass	6	SENT_23	[p1l479t2286r994b2368],
4	may	MD	O	may	aux	6	SENT_23	[p1l1030t2306r1180b2368],
5	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_23	[p1l1215t2286r1298b2349],
6	inﬂuenced	VBN	O	inﬂuenced	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1334t2286r1704b2349],
7	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1737t2286r1825b2368],
8	intrinsic	JJ	O	intrinsic	amod	9	SENT_23	[p1l1861t2286r2150b2349],
9	solubility	NN	O	solubility	agent	6	SENT_23	[p1l10t2390r342b2472],
10	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l381t2410r454b2453],
11	instability	NN	O	instability	conj_or	9	SENT_23	[p1l489t2390r864b2472],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l489t2390r864b2472],
13	low	JJ	O	low	amod	15	SENT_23	[p1l904t2390r1035b2453],
14	membrane	NN	O	membrane	nn	15	SENT_23	[p1l1073t2390r1448b2453],
15	permeability	NN	O	permeability	conj_or	9	SENT_23	[p1l1485t2390r1955b2472],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1485t2390r1955b2472],
17	high	JJ	O	high	amod	20	SENT_23	[p1l1995t2390r2152b2472],
18	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	nn	20	SENT_23	[p1l8t2494r144b2557],
19	pass	NN	O	pass	nn	20	SENT_23	[p1l166t2514r315b2576],
20	metabolism	NN	O	metabolism	conj_or	9	SENT_23	[p1l341t2494r771b2569],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l341t2494r771b2569],
22	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l800t2514r872b2557],
23	active	JJ	O	active	amod	24	SENT_23	[p1l896t2494r1103b2557],
24	excretion	NN	O	excretion	conj_or	9	SENT_23	[p1l1128t2494r1455b2557],
25	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	24	SENT_23	[p1l1482t2494r1633b2572],
26	i.e.	FW	O	i.e.	nn	24	SENT_23	[p1l1482t2494r1633b2572],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1482t2494r1633b2572],
28	efﬂux	FW	O	efﬂux	dep	24	SENT_23	[p1l1661t2494r1864b2557],
29	pumps	NNS	O	pump	dep	24	SENT_23	[p1l1888t2495r2150b2575],
30	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	29	SENT_23	[p1l1888t2495r2150b2575],
31	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l7t2598r180b2661],
32	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_23	[p1l225t2598r332b2661],
33	enterocytes	NNS	O	enterocyte	prep_from	6	SENT_23	[p1l380t2608r782b2680],
34	back	RB	O	back	advmod	6	SENT_23	[p1l830t2598r999b2661],
35	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1044t2598r1180b2661],
36	the	DT	O	the	det	38	SENT_23	[p1l1228t2598r1334b2661],
37	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	38	SENT_23	[p1l1382t2598r1707b2661],
38	lumen	NN	O	luman	prep_into	6	SENT_23	[p1l1755t2598r1993b2661],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1755t2598r1993b2661],

1	An	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_24	[p1l2045t2599r2152b2660],
2	extensively	RB	O	extensively	nsubj	3	SENT_24	[p1l8t2702r402b2784],
3	studied	VBN	O	study	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l429t2702r677b2765],
4	ATP	NN	O	atp	nn	6	SENT_24	[p1l699t2702r1159b2784],
5	—	NN	O	—	nn	6	SENT_24	[p1l699t2702r1159b2784],
6	binding	NN	O	binding	dobj	3	SENT_24	[p1l699t2702r1159b2784],
7	cassette	NN	O	cassette	nn	9	SENT_24	[p1l1184t2711r1452b2765],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	9	SENT_24	[p1l1479t2703r1711b2780],
9	ABC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	ABC	dep	6	SENT_24	[p1l1479t2703r1711b2780],
10	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	12	SENT_24	[p1l1479t2703r1711b2780],
11	superfamily	NN	O	superfamily	nn	12	SENT_24	[p1l1740t2702r2152b2784],
12	member	NN	O	member	dep	6	SENT_24	[p1l7t2806r316b2880],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l7t2806r316b2880],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l354t2806r479b2869],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_24	[p1l509t2806r616b2869],
16	product	NN	O	product	conj_and	6	SENT_24	[p1l647t2806r920b2887],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l952t2806r1028b2869],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_24	[p1l1054t2806r1160b2869],
19	multi	NNS	O	multus	nn	22	SENT_24	[p1l1192t2806r1378b2869],
20	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	22	SENT_24	[p1l1411t2806r1571b2888],
21	resistance	NN	O	resistance	nn	22	SENT_24	[p1l1602t2806r1953b2869],
22	gene	NN	O	gene	prep_of	16	SENT_24	[p1l1986t2826r2151b2888],

1	*	NN	O	*	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l56t3011r86b3044],
2	Corresponding	VBG	O	correspond	partmod	1	SENT_25	[p1l113t3010r587b3083],
3	author	NN	O	author	dobj	2	SENT_25	[p1l616t3010r834b3066],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l616t3010r834b3066],

1	Mailing	VBG	O	mail	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l865t3010r1117b3083],
2	address	NN	O	address	dobj	1	SENT_26	[p1l1146t3010r1400b3066],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1146t3010r1400b3066],
4	Biopharmaceutics	NNS	ORGANIZATION	biopharmaceutic	dep	2	SENT_26	[p1l1432t3010r2009b3083],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l2039t3010r2153b3066],
6	Pharmaceutical	NNP	O	Pharmaceutical	nn	7	SENT_26	[p1l172t3114r666b3170],
7	Technology	NNP	O	Technology	dep	2	SENT_26	[p1l712t3114r1112b3187],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l712t3114r1112b3187],
9	Saarland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Saarland	nn	10	SENT_26	[p1l1163t3114r1441b3170],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	2	SENT_26	[p1l1486t3114r1841b3187],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1486t3114r1841b3187],
12	Campus	NNP	O	Campus	nn	13	SENT_26	[p1l1891t3114r2150b3187],
13	A4	NN	O	a4	appos	10	SENT_26	[p1l172t3217r337b3283],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l172t3217r337b3283],

1	l	NN	O	l	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l172t3217r337b3283],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l172t3217r337b3283],
3	66123	CD	NUMBER	66123	dep	1	SENT_27	[p1l362t3216r547b3273],
4	Saarbruecken	NNP	LOCATION	Saarbruecken	dep	3	SENT_27	[p1l574t3216r999b3283],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l574t3216r999b3283],
6	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	dep	1	SENT_27	[p1l1023t3217r1320b3289],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1023t3217r1320b3289],

1	Phone	NN	O	phone	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1345t3216r1550b3273],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1345t3216r1550b3273],
3	+49 681 3022939	CD	NUMBER	+49 681 3022939	dep	1	SENT_28	[p1l1870t3217r2149b3273],[p1l1579t3217r1711b3273],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1870t3217r2149b3273],

1	Fax	NN	O	fax	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l172t3321r305b3375],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l172t3321r305b3375],
3	+49 681 3024677	CD	NUMBER	+49 681 3024677	dep	1	SENT_29	[p1l629t3319r915b3376],[p1l333t3319r468b3376],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l629t3319r915b3376],

1	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l939t3319r1167b3375],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l939t3319r1167b3375],
3	e.co1lnot@mX.uni-saarland.de	NN	O	e.co1lnot@mx.uni-saarland.de	dep	1	SENT_30	[p1l1193t3319r2149b3376],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1193t3319r2149b3376],

1	T	NN	O	t	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l54t3411r78b3452],
2	Saarland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Saarland	nn	3	SENT_31	[p1l105t3423r383b3479],
3	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	1	SENT_31	[p1l411t3423r765b3496],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l411t3423r765b3496],

1	*	NN	O	*	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l54t3514r78b3555],
2	Eastman	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Eastman	nn	4	SENT_32	[p1l103t3527r378b3582],
3	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	4	SENT_32	[p1l408t3525r713b3582],
4	Company	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Company	dep	1	SENT_32	[p1l743t3526r1069b3599],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l743t3526r1069b3599],

1	§	NNP	O	§	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l54t3617r77b3658],
2	Virginia	NNP	O	Virginia	nn	3	SENT_33	[p1l103t3629r370b3702],
3	Tech	NNP	O	Tech	dep	1	SENT_33	[p1l398t3629r573b3685],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l398t3629r573b3685],
5	"	''	O	"	punct	3	SENT_33	[p1l52t3719r433b3805],

1	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l52t3719r433b3805],
2	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l464t3732r533b3788],
3	Colorado	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Colorado	nn	4	SENT_34	[p1l558t3732r853b3788],
4	Denver	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Denver	prep_of	1	SENT_34	[p1l883t3733r1134b3788],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l883t3733r1134b3788],

1	642	CD	NUMBER	642	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l8t29r122b81],
2	MOLECULAR	NNP	O	MOLECULAR	nn	4	SENT_35	[p2l229t26r679b81],
3	PHARMACEUTICS	NNP	O	PHARMACEUTICS	nn	4	SENT_35	[p2l708t26r1328b81],
4	VOL	NNP	O	VOL	dep	1	SENT_35	[p2l1371t26r1527b81],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1371t26r1527b81],

1	7	CD	NUMBER	7	nsubj	21	SENT_36	[p2l1557t30r1608b90],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1557t30r1608b90],
3	NO.	NNP	O	NO.	appos	1	SENT_36	[p2l1640t26r1756b81],
4	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	3	SENT_36	[p2l1785t29r1837b90],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1785t29r1837b90],
6	642-651	CD	NUMBER	642-651	num	3	SENT_36	[p2l1866t29r2128b81],
7	MDR1	NN	O	mdr1	nn	14	SENT_36	[p2l7t125r272b199],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l7t125r272b199],
9	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	dep	14	SENT_36	[p2l333t125r863b206],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	14	SENT_36	[p2l923t126r1144b206],
11	P	NN	O	p	nn	14	SENT_36	[p2l923t126r1144b206],
12	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	14	SENT_36	[p2l923t126r1144b206],
13	gp	NN	O	gp	nn	14	SENT_36	[p2l923t126r1144b206],
14	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	16	SENT_36	[p2l923t126r1144b206],
15	predominantly	RB	O	predominantly	advmod	16	SENT_36	[p2l1203t125r1723b206],
16	locates	VBZ	O	locate	rcmod	3	SENT_36	[p2l1781t125r2025b188],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l2085t125r2152b187],
18	epithelia	NN	O	epithelium	nn	20	SENT_36	[p2l8t232r314b313],
19	apical	JJ	O	apical	amod	20	SENT_36	[p2l350t232r559b313],
20	membranes	NNS	O	membrane	prep_in	16	SENT_36	[p2l595t232r1003b295],
21	(	VBP	O	(	dep	47	SENT_36	[p2l1043t233r1216b313],
22	e.g.	FW	O	e.g.	dep	40	SENT_36	[p2l1043t233r1216b313],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1043t233r1216b313],
24	luminal	JJ	O	luminal	amod	25	SENT_36	[p2l1255t232r1525b295],
25	surface	NN	O	surface	dep	22	SENT_36	[p2l1565t232r1817b295],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1854t232r1931b295],
27	small	JJ	O	small	amod	28	SENT_36	[p2l1963t232r2151b295],
28	intestine	NN	O	intestine	prep_of	25	SENT_36	[p2l7t339r327b413],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l7t339r327b413],
30	colon	NN	O	colon	nn	35	SENT_36	[p2l358t339r572b413],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l358t339r572b413],
32	brain	NN	O	brain	nn	35	SENT_36	[p2l601t339r783b402],
33	capillary	JJ	O	capillary	amod	35	SENT_36	[p2l811t339r1120b420],
34	endothelial	JJ	O	endothelial	amod	35	SENT_36	[p2l1148t339r1542b402],
35	cells	NNS	O	cell	conj_and	28	SENT_36	[p2l1570t339r1728b402],
36	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1759t339r1885b402],
37	kidney	NN	O	kidney	nn	39	SENT_36	[p2l1910t339r2151b420],
38	proximal	JJ	O	proximal	amod	39	SENT_36	[p2l6t445r327b526],
39	tubules	NNS	O	tubule	conj_and	28	SENT_36	[p2l358t429r784b523],
40	)	VBP	O	)	dep	21	SENT_36	[p2l358t429r784b523],
41	.1	CD	NUMBER	.1	num	42	SENT_36	[p2l358t429r784b523],
42	_	CD	NUMBER	_	dobj	40	SENT_36	[p2l358t429r784b523],
43	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	46	SENT_36	[p2l358t429r784b523],
44	P	NN	O	p	nn	46	SENT_36	[p2l817t446r983b526],
45	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	46	SENT_36	[p2l817t446r983b526],
46	gp	NN	O	gp	nsubj	40	SENT_36	[p2l817t446r983b526],
47	protects	VBZ	O	protect	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1014t454r1294b526],
48	cells	NNS	O	cell	dobj	47	SENT_36	[p2l1328t445r1487b508],
49	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1519t445r1606b526],
50	actively	RB	O	actively	advmod	51	SENT_36	[p2l1640t445r1918b526],
51	trans	JJ	O	trans	amod	52	SENT_36	[p2l1950t454r2149b508, p2l47t673r129b737],
52	(	NN	O	(	prep_by	48	SENT_36	[p2l1950t454r2149b508, p2l47t673r129b737],
53	l	NN	O	l	tmod	47	SENT_36	[p2l1950t454r2149b508, p2l47t673r129b737],
54	)	CD	NUMBER	)	nsubj	47	SENT_36	[p2l1950t454r2149b508, p2l47t673r129b737],

1	Ueda	NNP	PERSON	Ueda	nn	3	SENT_37	[p2l171t672r346b735],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l171t672r346b735],
3	K.	NNP	O	K.	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l395t674r484b735],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l395t674r484b735],
5	Cornwell	NNP	PERSON	Cornwell	dep	3	SENT_37	[p2l533t672r829b735],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l533t672r829b735],
7	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	8	SENT_37	[p2l876t674r957b725],
8	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	5	SENT_37	[p2l1005t674r1109b735],
9	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1005t674r1109b735],
10	Gottesman	NNP	PERSON	Gottesman	dep	3	SENT_37	[p2l1158t673r1500b735],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1158t673r1500b735],
12	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	13	SENT_37	[p2l1548t674r1628b725],
13	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	10	SENT_37	[p2l1677t674r1780b735],
14	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1677t674r1780b735],
15	Pastan	NNP	PERSON	Pastan	dep	3	SENT_37	[p2l1828t674r2041b735],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1828t674r2041b735],
17	1.	CD	NUMBER	1.	appos	15	SENT_37	[p2l2088t674r2149b735],
18	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l2088t674r2149b735],
19	Roninson	NNP	PERSON	Roninson	dep	3	SENT_37	[p2l171t766r477b829],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l171t766r477b829],
21	I.	NNP	PERSON	I.	nn	22	SENT_37	[p2l528t767r566b819],
22	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	appos	19	SENT_37	[p2l618t767r703b829],
23	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l618t767r703b829],
24	Ling	NNP	PERSON	Ling	dep	3	SENT_37	[p2l753t766r911b835],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l753t766r911b835],
26	V.	NNP	O	V.	appos	24	SENT_37	[p2l962t767r1052b829],
27	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l962t767r1052b829],
28	Riordan	NNP	PERSON	Riordan	dep	3	SENT_37	[p2l1102t766r1362b829],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1102t766r1362b829],
30	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	34	SENT_37	[p2l1411t767r1454b819],
31	R.	NNP	O	R.	nn	34	SENT_37	[p2l1506t767r1570b819],
32	The	NNP	O	The	nn	34	SENT_37	[p2l1621t766r1737b819],
33	mdrl	NN	O	mdrl	nn	34	SENT_37	[p2l1785t766r1937b819],
34	gene	NN	O	gene	appos	28	SENT_37	[p2l1992t782r2149b835],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1992t782r2149b835],
36	responsible	JJ	O	responsible	amod	28	SENT_37	[p2l170t859r517b928],
37	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l552t859r640b913],
38	multidrug	JJ	O	multidrug	amod	40	SENT_37	[p2l673t859r1315b928],
39	—	NN	O	—	nn	40	SENT_37	[p2l673t859r1315b928],
40	resistance	NN	O	resistance	prep_for	36	SENT_37	[p2l673t859r1315b928],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l673t859r1315b928],
42	codes	NNS	O	code	appos	40	SENT_37	[p2l1353t859r1522b913],
43	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1558t859r1646b913],
44	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	prep_for	42	SENT_37	[p2l1679t859r2146b928],
45	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1679t859r2146b928],

1	Biochem	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biochem	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l169t954r447b1007],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l169t954r447b1007],

1	Bioghys	NNS	O	bioghy	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l480t954r736b1024],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l480t954r736b1024],

1	Res	NNP	O	Res	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l769t956r891b1007],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l769t956r891b1007],

1	Commun	NNP	O	Commun	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l929t955r1210b1008],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l929t955r1210b1008],

1	1986	CD	DATE	1986	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1248t953r1410b1017],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1248t953r1410b1017],
3	I41	NN	O	i41	dep	1	SENT_42	[p2l1443t954r1547b1006],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	3	SENT_42	[p2l1582t954r1683b1020],
5	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	6	SENT_42	[p2l1582t954r1683b1020],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	3	SENT_42	[p2l1582t954r1683b1020],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1582t954r1683b1020],
8	956-962	CD	NUMBER	956-962	dep	1	SENT_42	[p2l1714t954r1994b1008],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1714t954r1994b1008],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l47t1049r129b1114],
2	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	9	SENT_43	[p2l47t1049r129b1114],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	9	SENT_43	[p2l47t1049r129b1114],
4	Higgins	NNP	PERSON	Higgins	nn	9	SENT_43	[p2l171t1048r426b1117],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l171t1048r426b1117],
6	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	appos	9	SENT_43	[p2l458t1049r521b1102],
7	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	9	SENT_43	[p2l552t1050r608b1102],
8	ABC	NNP	PERSON	ABC	nn	9	SENT_43	[p2l640t1049r793b1102],
9	transporters	NNS	O	transporter	dep	1	SENT_43	[p2l823t1056r1196b1117],
10	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l823t1056r1196b1117],
11	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1229t1048r1376b1102],
12	microorganisms	NNS	O	microorganism	prep_from	9	SENT_43	[p2l1403t1048r1889b1117],
13	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1919t1057r1975b1102],
14	man	NN	O	man	prep_to	12	SENT_43	[p2l2004t1065r2148b1102],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l2004t1065r2148b1102],

1	Annu	NNP	PERSON	Annu	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l166t1144r341b1196],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l166t1144r341b1196],

1	Rev.	NNP	O	Rev.	nn	3	SENT_45	[p2l374t1145r503b1196],
2	Cell	NNP	PERSON	Cell	nn	3	SENT_45	[p2l541t1143r664b1197],
3	Biol	NNP	PERSON	Biol	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l688t1143r826b1196],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l688t1143r826b1196],

1	1992	CD	DATE	1992	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l865t1142r1027b1206],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l865t1142r1027b1206],
3	8	CD	NUMBER	8	appos	1	SENT_46	[p2l1058t1143r1110b1206],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1058t1143r1110b1206],
5	67-113	CD	NUMBER	67-113	appos	3	SENT_46	[p2l1141t1143r1383b1196],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1141t1143r1383b1196],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l47t1238r129b1302],
2	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	4	SENT_47	[p2l47t1238r129b1302],
3	)	NN	O	)	nn	4	SENT_47	[p2l47t1238r129b1302],
4	Thiebaut	NNP	O	Thiebaut	dep	1	SENT_47	[p2l171t1237r454b1300],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l171t1237r454b1300],
6	F.	NNP	O	F.	appos	4	SENT_47	[p2l477t1239r555b1300],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l477t1239r555b1300],
8	Tsuruo	NNP	PERSON	Tsuruo	dep	4	SENT_47	[p2l579t1239r808b1300],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l579t1239r808b1300],
10	T.	NNP	O	T.	appos	8	SENT_47	[p2l831t1239r912b1300],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l831t1239r912b1300],
12	Hamada	NNP	PERSON	Hamada	dep	4	SENT_47	[p2l936t1237r1203b1300],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l936t1237r1203b1300],
14	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	12	SENT_47	[p2l1226t1239r1316b1300],
15	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1226t1239r1316b1300],
16	Gottesman	NNP	PERSON	Gottesman	dep	4	SENT_47	[p2l1341t1238r1683b1300],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1341t1238r1683b1300],
18	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	19	SENT_47	[p2l1706t1239r1787b1290],
19	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	16	SENT_47	[p2l1811t1239r1914b1300],
20	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1811t1239r1914b1300],
21	Pastan	NNP	PERSON	Pastan	dep	4	SENT_47	[p2l1937t1239r2150b1300],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1937t1239r2150b1300],
23	I.	NN	O	i.	appos	21	SENT_47	[p2l171t1332r232b1394],
24	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l171t1332r232b1394],
25	Willingham	NNP	PERSON	Willingham	dep	4	SENT_47	[p2l268t1331r648b1400],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l268t1331r648b1400],
27	M.	NNP	O	M.	nn	29	SENT_47	[p2l684t1332r766b1384],
28	C.	NNP	O	C.	nn	29	SENT_47	[p2l804t1331r867b1384],
29	Cellular	NNP	O	Cellular	appos	25	SENT_47	[p2l906t1331r1151b1384],
30	Localization	NN	O	localization	dep	1	SENT_47	[p2l1183t1331r1564b1384],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1598t1331r1664b1384],
32	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_47	[p2l1692t1331r1784b1384],
33	MultidrugResistance	NNP	O	MultidrugResistance	nn	36	SENT_47	[p2l1817t1331r2149b1400, p2l171t1424r494b1478],
34	Gene	NNP	O	Gene	nn	36	SENT_47	[p2l547t1425r703b1478],
35	Product	NNP	O	Product	nn	36	SENT_47	[p2l755t1424r990b1478],
36	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	prep_of	30	SENT_47	[p2l1040t1424r1490b1493],
37	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1541t1424r1598b1477],
38	Normal	JJ	O	normal	amod	40	SENT_47	[p2l1648t1424r1879b1478],
39	Human	JJ	O	human	amod	40	SENT_47	[p2l1930t1426r2152b1478],
40	Tissues	NNS	O	tissue	prep_in	36	SENT_47	[p2l171t1519r412b1572],
41	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l171t1519r412b1572],

1	Proc	NNP	O	Proc	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l437t1521r596b1572],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l437t1521r596b1572],

1	Natl.	NNP	O	Natl.	nn	2	SENT_49	[p2l622t1519r765b1572],
2	Acad	NNP	O	Acad	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l789t1519r961b1572],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l789t1519r961b1572],

1	Sci	NNP	O	Sci	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l989t1520r1092b1573],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l989t1520r1092b1573],

1	U.S.A.	NNP	O	U.S.A.	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1128t1520r1308b1573],
2	1987	CD	DATE	1987	num	1	SENT_51	[p2l1341t1518r1504b1582],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1341t1518r1504b1582],
4	84	CD	NUMBER	84	num	1	SENT_51	[p2l1529t1519r1602b1572],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	6	SENT_51	[p2l1626t1519r1765b1585],
6	21	CD	NUMBER	21	num	7	SENT_51	[p2l1626t1519r1765b1585],
7	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_51	[p2l1626t1519r1765b1585],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1626t1519r1765b1585],
9	7735-7738	CD	DURATION	7735-7738	appos	7	SENT_51	[p2l1790t1519r2147b1572],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1790t1519r2147b1572],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l47t1614r129b1679],
2	4	CD	NUMBER	4	number	3	SENT_52	[p2l47t1614r129b1679],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_52	[p2l47t1614r129b1679],
4	From	IN	O	from	prep	3	SENT_52	[p2l171t1615r410b1676],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l171t1615r410b1676],
6	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	8	SENT_52	[p2l457t1615r538b1667],
7	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	8	SENT_52	[p2l587t1615r643b1667],
8	Importance	NNP	PERSON	Importance	appos	3	SENT_52	[p2l692t1615r1036b1682],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1083t1613r1148b1667],
10	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	prep_of	8	SENT_52	[p2l1188t1613r1639b1682],
11	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1685t1622r1738b1667],
12	blood-tissue	JJ	O	blood-tissue	amod	13	SENT_52	[p2l1781t1613r2151b1667],
13	barriers	NNS	O	barrier	prep_at	10	SENT_52	[p2l170t1708r416b1761],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l170t1708r416b1761],

1	Trends	NNS	O	trend	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l451t1708r657b1761],
2	Pharmacol	NNP	O	Pharmacol	dep	1	SENT_53	[p2l683t1708r1032b1761],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l683t1708r1032b1761],

1	Sci	NNP	O	Sci	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1067t1709r1170b1762],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1067t1709r1170b1762],

1	2004	CD	DATE	2004	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1204t1707r1370b1771],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1204t1707r1370b1771],
3	25	CD	NUMBER	25	number	4	SENT_55	[p2l1400t1708r1475b1761],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	appos	1	SENT_55	[p2l1504t1708r1605b1774],
5	8	CD	NUMBER	8	num	6	SENT_55	[p2l1504t1708r1605b1774],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	4	SENT_55	[p2l1504t1708r1605b1774],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1504t1708r1605b1774],
8	423-429	CD	NUMBER	423-429	appos	1	SENT_55	[p2l1634t1708r1916b1762],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1634t1708r1916b1762],

1	10.1021	CD	NUMBER	10.1021	num	2	SENT_56	[p2l497t1861r1073b1920],
2	lmp900191s	NNS	O	lmp900191	nsubj	3	SENT_56	[p2l497t1861r1073b1920],
3	©	VBP	O	©	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l1099t1864r1142b1908],
4	2010	CD	DATE	2010	dobj	3	SENT_56	[p2l1167t1862r1304b1908],
5	American	JJ	ORGANIZATION	american	prep	3	SENT_56	[p2l1327t1861r1608b1908],
6	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	7	SENT_56	[p2l1634t1861r1906b1908],
7	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	dep	5	SENT_56	[p2l1934t1861r2153b1920],
8	Published	VBN	O	publish	partmod	7	SENT_56	[p2l1189t1935r1493b1988],
9	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l1523t1948r1596b1988],
10	Web	NN	O	web	nn	11	SENT_56	[p2l1625t1935r1769b1988],
11	O3/O5/2010	NN	O	o3/o5/2010	prep_on	8	SENT_56	[p2l1797t1933r2151b1988],

1	P	NN	O	p	nn	4	SENT_57	[p2l30t2075r110b2113],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	4	SENT_57	[p2l30t2075r110b2113],
3	gp	NN	O	gp	nn	4	SENT_57	[p2l30t2075r110b2113],
4	Inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	nsubj	47	SENT_57	[p2l128t2074r292b2103],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l312t2074r350b2113],
6	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	prep_by	4	SENT_57	[p2l371t2074r479b2103],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l371t2074r479b2103],
8	ATP	NN	O	atp	nn	9	SENT_57	[p2l498t2074r574b2102],
9	Levels	NNS	O	level	dep	4	SENT_57	[p2l592t2074r700b2103],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l719t2074r782b2103],
11	P-gg	JJ	O	p-gg	amod	13	SENT_57	[p2l799t2075r879b2113],
12	Conformation	NN	O	conformation	nn	13	SENT_57	[p2l901t2074r1131b2113],
13	articles	NNS	O	article	dep	4	SENT_57	[p2l1942t2063r2128b2103],
14	porting	VBG	O	port	dep	4	SENT_57	[p2l6t2274r261b2355],
15	substrates	NNS	O	substrate	dobj	14	SENT_57	[p2l323t2274r668b2336],
16	against	IN	O	against	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l730t2274r980b2355],
17	a	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_57	[p2l1039t2294r1076b2336],
18	concentration	NN	O	concentration	nn	19	SENT_57	[p2l1133t2274r1616b2336],
19	gradient	NN	O	gradient	prep_against	15	SENT_57	[p2l1675t2274r1965b2355],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l2024t2274r2149b2336],
21	thereby	RB	O	thereby	advmod	22	SENT_57	[p2l7t2368r272b2449],
22	reducing	VBG	O	reduce	conj_and	14	SENT_57	[p2l301t2368r611b2449],
23	intracellular	JJ	O	intracellular	amod	24	SENT_57	[p2l642t2368r1073b2430],
24	levels	NNS	O	level	dobj	22	SENT_57	[p2l1101t2368r1305b2431],
25	below	IN	O	below	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l1336t2368r1552b2431],
26	effective	JJ	O	effective	amod	29	SENT_57	[p2l1583t2368r1893b2430],
27	and/or	JJ	O	and/or	amod	29	SENT_57	[p2l1924t2368r2150b2431],
28	toxic	JJ	O	toxic	amod	29	SENT_57	[p2l7t2475r181b2538],
29	concentration	NN	O	concentration	prep_below	22	SENT_57	[p2l211t2459r746b2538],
30	.8	CD	NUMBER	.8	dobj	14	SENT_57	[p2l211t2459r746b2538],
31	Located	VBN	O	locate	partmod	30	SENT_57	[p2l775t2475r1061b2538],
32	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l1089t2485r1151b2538],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_57	[p2l1176t2475r1283b2538],
34	enterocyte	NN	O	enterocyte	nn	36	SENT_57	[p2l1311t2485r1678b2557],
35	apical	JJ	O	apical	amod	36	SENT_57	[p2l1708t2475r1916b2557],
36	membrane	NN	O	membrane	prep_at	31	SENT_57	[p2l1944t2495r2147b2538, p2l6t2570r199b2632],
37	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l224t2570r378b2633],
38	broad	JJ	O	broad	amod	44	SENT_57	[p2l399t2570r599b2632],
39	substrate	NN	O	substrate	nn	44	SENT_57	[p2l625t2570r931b2632],
40	speciﬁcity	NN	O	speciﬁcity	nn	44	SENT_57	[p2l958t2570r1331b2651],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l958t2570r1331b2651],
42	P	NN	O	p	dep	44	SENT_57	[p2l1357t2572r1521b2651],
43	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	44	SENT_57	[p2l1357t2572r1521b2651],
44	gp	NN	O	gp	prep_with	36	SENT_57	[p2l1357t2572r1521b2651],
45	may	MD	O	may	aux	47	SENT_57	[p2l1545t2590r1694b2651],
46	signiﬁcantly	RB	O	signiﬁcantly	advmod	47	SENT_57	[p2l1721t2570r2149b2651],
47	limit	VB	O	limit	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l7t2667r174b2730],
48	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	50	SENT_57	[p2l233t2668r392b2749],
49	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	50	SENT_57	[p2l452t2668r587b2730],
50	absorption	NN	O	absorption	nsubj	53	SENT_57	[p2l648t2651r1075b2749],
51	.9	CD	NUMBER	.9	dep	50	SENT_57	[p2l648t2651r1075b2749],
52	To	TO	O	to	aux	53	SENT_57	[p2l1135t2669r1230b2730],
53	enhance	VB	O	enhance	xcomp	47	SENT_57	[p2l1291t2668r1580b2730],
54	substrate	NN	O	substrate	dobj	53	SENT_57	[p2l1641t2668r1953b2730],
55	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	60	SENT_57	[p2l2013t2667r2148b2730],
56	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	nn	60	SENT_57	[p2l6t2762r540b2843],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l6t2762r540b2843],
58	P	NN	O	p	dep	60	SENT_57	[p2l577t2764r742b2843],
59	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	60	SENT_57	[p2l577t2764r742b2843],
60	gp	NN	O	gp	nsubjpass	63	SENT_57	[p2l577t2764r742b2843],
61	may	MD	O	may	aux	63	SENT_57	[p2l778t2782r929b2843],
62	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	63	SENT_57	[p2l962t2762r1045b2824],
63	inhibited	VBN	O	inhibit	rcmod	54	SENT_57	[p2l1080t2762r1395b2824],
64	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l1428t2762r1515b2843],
65	coadministration	NN	O	coadministration	agent	63	SENT_57	[p2l1551t2762r2149b2824],
66	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l7t2859r164b2923],
67	compounds	NNS	O	compound	prep_with	63	SENT_57	[p2l204t2859r611b2941],
68	such	JJ	O	such	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l656t2859r814b2922],
69	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l856t2879r924b2922],
70	GFl209l8	NN	O	gfl209l8	prep_such_as	67	SENT_57	[p2l968t2860r1343b2923],
71	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l1387t2879r1460b2922],
72	PSC	NN	O	psc	prep_such_as	67	SENT_57	[p2l1498t2843r1986b2934],
73	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	74	SENT_57	[p2l1498t2843r1986b2934],
74	833,1	CD	NUMBER	833,1	num	75	SENT_57	[p2l1498t2843r1986b2934],
75	O	NN	O	o	dep	70	SENT_57	[p2l1498t2843r1986b2934],
76	’“	CD	NUMBER	’“	num	77	SENT_57	[p2l1498t2843r1986b2934],
77	ﬂavonoids	NNS	O	ﬂavonoids	dep	70	SENT_57	[p2l2033t2859r2146b2922, p2l7t2951r376b3041],
78	,12	CD	NUMBER	,12	num	80	SENT_57	[p2l2033t2859r2146b2922, p2l7t2951r376b3041],
79	bile	NN	O	bile	nn	80	SENT_57	[p2l408t2967r540b3030],
80	salts	NNS	O	salt	dep	77	SENT_57	[p2l575t2951r815b3041],
81	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l575t2951r815b3041],
82	”	CD	NUMBER	”	appos	70	SENT_57	[p2l575t2951r815b3041],
83	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l852t2987r924b3030],
84	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	conj_or	82	SENT_57	[p2l958t2951r1548b3030],
85	.14	CD	NUMBER	.14	num	84	SENT_57	[p2l958t2951r1548b3030],
86	"	``	O	"	punct	53	SENT_57	[p2l958t2951r1548b3030],
87	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	88	SENT_57	[p2l958t2951r1548b3030],
88	°	CD	NUMBER	°	dobj	53	SENT_57	[p2l958t2951r1548b3030],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_58	[p2l92t3062r154b3123],
2	Water	NN	O	water	nn	3	SENT_58	[p2l197t3061r680b3124],
3	—	NN	O	—	dep	19	SENT_58	[p2l197t3061r680b3124],
4	soluble	JJ	O	soluble	amod	5	SENT_58	[p2l197t3061r680b3124],
5	form	NN	O	form	dep	3	SENT_58	[p2l723t3061r895b3123],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l937t3061r1014b3123],
7	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	8	SENT_58	[p2l1051t3061r1321b3124],
8	E	NN	O	e	prep_of	5	SENT_58	[p2l1363t3063r1434b3135],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1363t3063r1434b3135],
10	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	nn	13	SENT_58	[p2l1480t3062r1692b3124],
11	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	13	SENT_58	[p2l1747t3062r1914b3124],
12	(	NN	O	(	nn	13	SENT_58	[p2l1960t3062r2146b3138],
13	D	NN	O	d	appos	8	SENT_58	[p2l1960t3062r2146b3138],
14	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	15	SENT_58	[p2l1960t3062r2146b3138],
15	oL	NN	O	ol	dep	19	SENT_58	[p2l1960t3062r2146b3138],
16	—	NN	O	—	nn	19	SENT_58	[p2l1960t3062r2146b3138],
17	tocopheryl	NN	O	tocopheryl	nn	19	SENT_58	[p2l7t3155r386b3236],
18	polyethylene	NN	O	polyethylene	nn	19	SENT_58	[p2l421t3155r881b3236],
19	glycol	NN	O	glycol	dep	23	SENT_58	[p2l918t3155r1137b3236],
20	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	22	SENT_58	[p2l1182t3156r1349b3218],
21	succinate	JJ	O	succinate	amod	22	SENT_58	[p2l1388t3155r1742b3232],
22	)	NN	O	)	dep	19	SENT_58	[p2l1388t3155r1742b3232],
23	contains	VBZ	O	contain	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1781t3155r2074b3217],
24	a	DT	O	a	det	32	SENT_58	[p2l2113t3175r2150b3217],
25	hydrophilic	JJ	O	hydrophilic	amod	32	SENT_58	[p2l6t3249r410b3330],
26	polar	JJ	O	polar	amod	32	SENT_58	[p2l435t3249r617b3330],
27	(	NN	O	(	nn	32	SENT_58	[p2l642t3249r1174b3326],
28	water	NN	O	water	nn	32	SENT_58	[p2l642t3249r1174b3326],
29	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	32	SENT_58	[p2l642t3249r1174b3326],
30	soluble	JJ	O	soluble	amod	32	SENT_58	[p2l642t3249r1174b3326],
31	)	NN	O	)	nn	32	SENT_58	[p2l642t3249r1174b3326],
32	PEG	NN	O	peg	nsubj	36	SENT_58	[p2l1200t3250r1366b3312],
33	chain	NN	O	chain	xcomp	23	SENT_58	[p2l1391t3249r1579b3311],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1605t3249r1729b3311],
35	a	DT	O	a	det	36	SENT_58	[p2l1754t3269r1791b3311],
36	lipophilic	JJ	O	lipophilic	xcomp	23	SENT_58	[p2l1814t3249r2148b3330],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l47t3431r129b3497],
2	5	CD	NUMBER	5	number	3	SENT_59	[p2l47t3431r129b3497],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_59	[p2l47t3431r129b3497],
4	Mizuno	NNP	PERSON	Mizuno	nn	6	SENT_59	[p2l171t3431r422b3494],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l171t3431r422b3494],
6	N.	NNP	O	N.	dep	3	SENT_59	[p2l452t3433r542b3494],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l452t3433r542b3494],
8	Niwa	NNP	PERSON	Niwa	dep	3	SENT_59	[p2l574t3431r752b3494],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l574t3431r752b3494],
10	T.	NNP	O	T.	appos	8	SENT_59	[p2l784t3433r865b3495],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l784t3433r865b3495],
12	Yotsumoto	NNP	PERSON	Yotsumoto	dep	3	SENT_59	[p2l897t3433r1248b3494],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l897t3433r1248b3494],
14	Y.	NNP	O	Y.	appos	12	SENT_59	[p2l1280t3433r1369b3494],
15	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l1280t3433r1369b3494],
16	Sugiyama	NNP	PERSON	Sugiyama	nn	19	SENT_59	[p2l1403t3431r1719b3500],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l1403t3431r1719b3500],
18	Y.	NNP	O	Y.	appos	19	SENT_59	[p2l1750t3433r1818b3485],
19	Impact	NNP	O	Impact	dep	3	SENT_59	[p2l1850t3433r2060b3500],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l2088t3431r2153b3485],
21	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	23	SENT_59	[p2l172t3526r308b3595],
22	transporter	NN	O	transporter	nn	23	SENT_59	[p2l348t3534r678b3595],
23	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	19	SENT_59	[p2l719t3526r925b3579],
24	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l966t3542r1040b3579],
25	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	26	SENT_59	[p2l1080t3526r1216b3595],
26	discovery	NN	O	discovery	prep_on	23	SENT_59	[p2l1257t3526r1550b3595],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l1591t3526r1698b3579],
28	development	NN	O	development	prep_on	23	SENT_59	[p2l1738t3526r2145b3595],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l1738t3526r2145b3595],

1	Pharmacol	NNP	O	Pharmacol	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l170t3620r518b3674],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l170t3620r518b3674],

1	Rev.	NNP	O	Rev.	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l551t3622r679b3674],
2	2003	CD	DATE	2003	num	1	SENT_61	[p2l714t3620r880b3684],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l714t3620r880b3684],
4	55	CD	NUMBER	55	num	1	SENT_61	[p2l910t3621r985b3673],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	6	SENT_61	[p2l1014t3621r1114b3686],
6	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	7	SENT_61	[p2l1014t3621r1114b3686],
7	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_61	[p2l1014t3621r1114b3686],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1014t3621r1114b3686],
9	425-461	CD	NUMBER	425-461	appos	7	SENT_61	[p2l1144t3620r1425b3674],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1144t3620r1425b3674],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	3	SENT_62	[p2l47t3715r129b3781],
2	6	CD	NUMBER	6	num	3	SENT_62	[p2l47t3715r129b3781],
3	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l47t3715r129b3781],
4	Lankas	NNP	O	Lankas	nn	7	SENT_62	[p2l171t3715r405b3778],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l171t3715r405b3778],
6	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	appos	7	SENT_62	[p2l450t3715r516b3768],
7	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	dep	3	SENT_62	[p2l562t3716r648b3778],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l562t3716r648b3778],
9	Wise	NNP	O	Wise	dep	3	SENT_62	[p2l692t3715r863b3778],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l692t3715r863b3778],
11	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	nn	12	SENT_62	[p2l907t3716r967b3768],
12	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	appos	9	SENT_62	[p2l1012t3716r1102b3778],
13	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1012t3716r1102b3778],
14	Cartwright	NNP	PERSON	Cartwright	dep	3	SENT_62	[p2l1147t3715r1490b3784],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1147t3715r1490b3784],
16	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	17	SENT_62	[p2l1534t3716r1615b3768],
17	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	appos	14	SENT_62	[p2l1660t3716r1742b3778],
18	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1660t3716r1742b3778],
19	Pippert	NNP	PERSON	Pippert	dep	3	SENT_62	[p2l1786t3715r2020b3784],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1786t3715r2020b3784],
21	T.	NNP	O	T.	appos	19	SENT_62	[p2l2064t3716r2146b3778],
22	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l2064t3716r2146b3778],

1	Umbenhauer	NNP	O	Umbenhauer	nsubj	8	SENT_63	[p3l171t19r576b82],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l171t19r576b82],
3	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	4	SENT_63	[p3l600t21r667b73],
4	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	appos	1	SENT_63	[p3l692t21r755b73],
5	Placental	JJ	PERSON	placental	amod	7	SENT_63	[p3l780t19r1055b73],
6	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	nn	7	SENT_63	[p3l1076t19r1524b88],
7	deﬁciency	NN	O	deﬁciency	dep	4	SENT_63	[p3l1545t19r1853b88],
8	enhances	VBZ	O	enhance	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1875t19r2148b73],
9	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	dobj	8	SENT_63	[p3l174t114r567b183],
10	to	TO	O	to	aux	12	SENT_63	[p3l587t122r643b167],
11	chemically	RB	O	chemically	advmod	12	SENT_63	[p3l664t114r989b183],
12	induced	VBN	O	induce	xcomp	8	SENT_63	[p3l1010t114r1245b167],
13	birth	NN	O	birth	nn	14	SENT_63	[p3l1264t114r1405b167],
14	defects	NNS	O	defect	dobj	12	SENT_63	[p3l1425t114r1632b167],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1654t114r1710b166],
16	mice	NNS	O	mouse	prep_in	14	SENT_63	[p3l1730t114r1888b167],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1730t114r1888b167],

1	Regrod	NN	O	regrod	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1910t114r2142b184],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1910t114r2142b184],

1	T	NN	O	t	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l174t210r218b261],
2	oxicol	NN	O	oxicol	dep	1	SENT_65	[p3l214t208r408b262],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l214t208r408b262],

1	1998	CD	DATE	1998	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l447t208r609b271],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l447t208r609b271],
3	I2	NN	O	i2	dep	1	SENT_66	[p3l642t209r711b261],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	3	SENT_66	[p3l743t209r843b274],
5	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	6	SENT_66	[p3l743t209r843b274],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	3	SENT_66	[p3l743t209r843b274],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l743t209r843b274],
8	457-463	CD	NUMBER	457-463	dep	1	SENT_66	[p3l873t208r1152b262],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l873t208r1152b262],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	6	SENT_67	[p3l47t303r129b368],
2	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	6	SENT_67	[p3l47t303r129b368],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	6	SENT_67	[p3l47t303r129b368],
4	Van	NNP	PERSON	Van	nn	6	SENT_67	[p3l171t319r279b355],
5	der	NNP	PERSON	der	nn	6	SENT_67	[p3l305t303r400b355],
6	Valk	NNP	PERSON	Valk	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l424t303r585b365],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l424t303r585b365],
8	P.	NNP	O	P.	appos	6	SENT_67	[p3l613t304r690b365],
9	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l613t304r690b365],
10	Van	NNP	PERSON	Van	nn	11	SENT_67	[p3l719t319r826b355],
11	Kalken	NNP	PERSON	Kalken	dep	6	SENT_67	[p3l852t303r1084b365],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l852t303r1084b365],
13	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	14	SENT_67	[p3l1113t303r1176b356],
14	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	appos	11	SENT_67	[p3l1206t304r1294b365],
15	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1206t304r1294b365],
16	Ketelaars	NNP	PERSON	Ketelaars	dep	11	SENT_67	[p3l1324t303r1623b365],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1324t303r1623b365],
18	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	16	SENT_67	[p3l1651t304r1741b365],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1651t304r1741b365],
20	Broxterman	NNP	PERSON	Broxterman	dep	11	SENT_67	[p3l1769t304r2146b365],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1769t304r2146b365],
22	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	23	SENT_67	[p3l171t397r239b449],
23	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	appos	20	SENT_67	[p3l279t397r344b459],
24	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l279t397r344b459],
25	Scheffer	NNP	PERSON	Scheffer	dep	11	SENT_67	[p3l385t395r655b459],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l385t395r655b459],
27	G.	NNP	O	G.	appos	25	SENT_67	[p3l695t396r784b458],
28	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l695t396r784b458],
29	Kuiper	NNP	O	Kuiper	dep	11	SENT_67	[p3l825t395r1049b464],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l825t395r1049b464],
31	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	32	SENT_67	[p3l1089t396r1152b449],
32	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	29	SENT_67	[p3l1192t397r1295b459],
33	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1192t397r1295b459],
34	Tsuruo	NNP	PERSON	Tsuruo	dep	11	SENT_67	[p3l1334t397r1564b459],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1334t397r1564b459],
36	T.	NNP	O	T.	appos	34	SENT_67	[p3l1603t397r1684b459],
37	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1603t397r1684b459],
38	Lankelma	NNP	LOCATION	Lankelma	dep	11	SENT_67	[p3l1723t395r2042b459],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1723t395r2042b459],
40	J.	NNP	O	J.	appos	38	SENT_67	[p3l2080t397r2145b458],
41	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l2080t397r2145b458],
42	Meijer	NNP	PERSON	Meijer	dep	11	SENT_67	[p3l171t490r386b559],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l171t490r386b559],
44	C.	NNP	O	C.	nn	45	SENT_67	[p3l410t490r472b543],
45	J	NNP	O	J	appos	42	SENT_67	[p3l497t491r524b543],
46	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l530t507r560b553],

1	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l530t507r560b553],
2	Pinedo	NNP	PERSON	Pinedo	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l584t490r807b553],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l584t490r807b553],
4	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	6	SENT_68	[p3l831t491r898b543],
5	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	6	SENT_68	[p3l922t491r1002b543],
6	Distribution	NN	PERSON	distribution	appos	2	SENT_68	[p3l1027t490r1389b543],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l1410t490r1475b543],
8	multi-drug	JJ	O	multi-drug	amod	10	SENT_68	[p3l1490t490r1809b559],
9	resistanceassociated	JJ	O	resistanceassociated	amod	10	SENT_68	[p3l1830t490r2148b543, p3l173t583r477b637],
10	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	prep_of	2	SENT_68	[p3l496t583r938b652],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l958t583r1015b636],
12	normal	JJ	O	normal	amod	16	SENT_68	[p3l1034t583r1244b637],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l1266t583r1372b637],
14	neoplastic	JJ	O	neoplastic	amod	16	SENT_68	[p3l1391t583r1690b652],
15	human	JJ	O	human	amod	16	SENT_68	[p3l1711t583r1914b637],
16	tissues	NNS	O	tissue	prep_in	10	SENT_68	[p3l1934t583r2146b637],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l1934t583r2146b637],

1	Analysis	NN	O	analysis	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l171t678r433b747],
2	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l479t678r612b731],
3	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	5	SENT_69	[p3l657t678r687b731],
4	monoclonal	JJ	O	monoclonal	amod	5	SENT_69	[p3l735t678r1091b731],
5	antibodies	NNS	O	antibody	prep_with	1	SENT_69	[p3l1137t678r1444b731],
6	recognizing	VBG	O	recognize	partmod	1	SENT_69	[p3l1488t678r1845b747],
7	different	JJ	O	different	amod	8	SENT_69	[p3l1890t678r2150b731],
8	epitopes	NNS	O	epitope	dobj	6	SENT_69	[p3l172t771r419b840],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l443t771r508b825],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_69	[p3l524t771r614b825],
11	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	nn	12	SENT_69	[p3l635t771r1082b840],
12	molecule	NN	O	molecule	prep_of	8	SENT_69	[p3l1103t771r1393b825],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1103t771r1393b825],

1	Ann	NNP	PERSON	Ann	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1412t772r1549b825],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1412t772r1549b825],

1	Oncol	NN	O	oncol	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l1580t771r1771b825],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l1580t771r1771b825],

1	1990	CD	DATE	1990	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1803t771r1964b834],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1803t771r1964b834],
3	I	PRP	O	I	nsubj	4	SENT_72	[p3l1991t772r2019b824],
4	(	VBP	O	(	dep	1	SENT_72	[p3l2047t772r2147b837],
5	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	6	SENT_72	[p3l2047t772r2147b837],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dobj	4	SENT_72	[p3l2047t772r2147b837],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l2047t772r2147b837],
8	56-64	CD	NUMBER	56-64	appos	1	SENT_72	[p3l172t865r374b919],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l172t865r374b919],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l47t960r129b1025],
2	8	CD	NUMBER	8	number	3	SENT_73	[p3l47t960r129b1025],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_73	[p3l47t960r129b1025],
4	Roninson	NNP	O	Roninson	nn	7	SENT_73	[p3l171t959r477b1023],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l171t959r477b1023],
6	I.	NNP	PERSON	I.	appos	7	SENT_73	[p3l503t961r541b1013],
7	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	dep	3	SENT_73	[p3l570t961r633b1013],
8	Molecular	JJ	PERSON	molecular	amod	9	SENT_73	[p3l661t959r973b1013],
9	mechanism	NN	O	mechanism	dep	1	SENT_73	[p3l995t959r1340b1013],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1364t959r1430b1013],
11	multidrug	JJ	O	multidrug	amod	12	SENT_73	[p3l1449t959r1745b1028],
12	resistance	NN	O	resistance	prep_of	9	SENT_73	[p3l1769t959r2067b1013],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l2092t959r2149b1012],
14	tumor	NN	O	tumor	nn	15	SENT_73	[p3l171t1062r352b1107],
15	cells	NNS	O	cell	prep_in	12	SENT_73	[p3l379t1054r530b1107],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l379t1054r530b1107],

1	Clin	NNP	O	Clin	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l565t1054r702b1108],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l565t1054r702b1108],

1	Physiol	NNP	O	Physiol	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l735t1054r974b1124],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l735t1054r974b1124],

1	Biochem	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biochem	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l1006t1054r1284b1107],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l1006t1054r1284b1107],

1	1987	CD	DATE	1987	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l1322t1053r1484b1117],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l1322t1053r1484b1117],
3	5	CD	NUMBER	5	number	4	SENT_77	[p3l1514t1055r1551b1107],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	appos	1	SENT_77	[p3l1580t1054r1777b1119],
5	3-4	CD	NUMBER	3-4	num	6	SENT_77	[p3l1580t1054r1777b1119],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	4	SENT_77	[p3l1580t1054r1777b1119],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l1580t1054r1777b1119],
8	140-151	CD	NUMBER	140-151	appos	1	SENT_77	[p3l1815t1054r2089b1107],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l1815t1054r2089b1107],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	3	SENT_78	[p3l47t1149r129b1214],
2	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	3	SENT_78	[p3l47t1149r129b1214],
3	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l47t1149r129b1214],
4	Suzuki	NNP	PERSON	Suzuki	nn	6	SENT_78	[p3l173t1148r396b1211],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l173t1148r396b1211],
6	H.	NNP	O	H.	dep	3	SENT_78	[p3l423t1150r513b1211],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l423t1150r513b1211],
8	Sugiyama	NNP	PERSON	Sugiyama	dep	3	SENT_78	[p3l542t1148r858b1217],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l542t1148r858b1217],
10	Y.	NNP	O	Y.	nn	11	SENT_78	[p3l886t1150r953b1202],
11	Role	NN	O	role	appos	8	SENT_78	[p3l981t1148r1122b1202],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l1148t1148r1213b1202],
13	metabolic	JJ	O	metabolic	amod	14	SENT_78	[p3l1232t1148r1528b1202],
14	enzymes	NNS	O	enzyme	prep_of	11	SENT_78	[p3l1554t1165r1816b1217],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l1843t1148r1950b1202],
16	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	nn	17	SENT_78	[p3l1974t1148r2148b1202],
17	transporters	NNS	O	transporter	prep_of	11	SENT_78	[p3l171t1250r526b1312],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l556t1243r613b1295],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_78	[p3l641t1243r732b1296],
20	absorption	NN	O	absorption	prep_in	14	SENT_78	[p3l761t1243r1079b1312],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l1108t1243r1173b1296],
22	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_of	20	SENT_78	[p3l1197t1243r1361b1312],
23	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l1391t1243r1538b1296],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_78	[p3l1564t1243r1655b1296],
25	small	JJ	O	small	amod	26	SENT_78	[p3l1686t1243r1846b1296],
26	intestine	NN	O	intestine	prep_from	22	SENT_78	[p3l1874t1243r2145b1296],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l1874t1243r2145b1296],

1	Eur	NNP	O	Eur	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l170t1339r295b1391],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l170t1339r295b1391],

1	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	2	SENT_80	[p3l327t1339r373b1391],
2	Pharm	NNP	PERSON	Pharm	_	0	SENT_80	[p3l406t1337r624b1391],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_80	[p3l406t1337r624b1391],

1	Sci	NNP	O	Sci	_	0	SENT_81	[p3l659t1338r761b1391],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_81	[p3l659t1338r761b1391],

1	2000	CD	DATE	2000	_	0	SENT_82	[p3l795t1337r961b1400],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p3l795t1337r961b1400],
3	I2	NN	O	i2	nn	4	SENT_82	[p3l994t1338r1063b1390],
4	(	NN	O	(	dep	1	SENT_82	[p3l1095t1338r1195b1403],
5	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	6	SENT_82	[p3l1095t1338r1195b1403],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	4	SENT_82	[p3l1095t1338r1195b1403],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p3l1095t1338r1195b1403],
8	3-12	CD	NUMBER	3-12	dep	1	SENT_82	[p3l1227t1338r1393b1391],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_82	[p3l1227t1338r1393b1391],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	4	SENT_83	[p3l9t1432r129b1497],
2	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	4	SENT_83	[p3l9t1432r129b1497],
3	)	NN	O	)	nn	4	SENT_83	[p3l9t1432r129b1497],
4	Malingre	NN	O	malingre	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l171t1432r464b1501],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l171t1432r464b1501],
6	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	7	SENT_83	[p3l499t1433r580b1485],
7	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	4	SENT_83	[p3l617t1433r720b1495],
8	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l617t1433r720b1495],
9	Beijnen	NNP	PERSON	Beijnen	dep	4	SENT_83	[p3l756t1432r1006b1501],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l756t1432r1006b1501],
11	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	12	SENT_83	[p3l1042t1433r1085b1485],
12	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	appos	9	SENT_83	[p3l1122t1433r1212b1495],
13	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1122t1433r1212b1495],
14	Rosing	NNP	PERSON	Rosing	dep	9	SENT_83	[p3l1248t1432r1477b1501],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1248t1432r1477b1501],
16	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	14	SENT_83	[p3l1513t1433r1603b1495],
17	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1513t1433r1603b1495],
18	Koopman	NNP	PERSON	Koopman	dep	9	SENT_83	[p3l1640t1433r1953b1501],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1640t1433r1953b1501],
20	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	21	SENT_83	[p3l1988t1433r2044b1485],
21	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	appos	18	SENT_83	[p3l2081t1433r2145b1495],
22	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l2081t1433r2145b1495],
23	Jewell	NNP	PERSON	Jewell	dep	9	SENT_83	[p3l171t1525r375b1588],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l171t1525r375b1588],
25	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	26	SENT_83	[p3l397t1527r460b1578],
26	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	appos	23	SENT_83	[p3l485t1526r568b1588],
27	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l485t1526r568b1588],
28	Paul	NNP	PERSON	Paul	dep	9	SENT_83	[p3l591t1525r737b1588],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l591t1525r737b1588],
30	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	nn	31	SENT_83	[p3l759t1527r818b1578],
31	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	28	SENT_83	[p3l841t1527r943b1588],
32	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l841t1527r943b1588],
33	Ten	CD	PERSON	ten	num	35	SENT_83	[p3l965t1527r1080b1578],
34	Bokkel	NNP	PERSON	Bokkel	nn	35	SENT_83	[p3l1099t1525r1313b1578],
35	Huinink	NNP	PERSON	Huinink	dep	9	SENT_83	[p3l1333t1525r1591b1588],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1333t1525r1591b1588],
37	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	38	SENT_83	[p3l1612t1527r1697b1578],
38	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	appos	35	SENT_83	[p3l1720t1527r1826b1588],
39	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1720t1527r1826b1588],
40	Schellens	NNP	O	Schellens	dep	9	SENT_83	[p3l1851t1525r2148b1588],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1851t1525r2148b1588],
42	J	NNP	O	J	appos	40	SENT_83	[p3l171t1620r199b1672],
43	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l205t1663r214b1672],

1	H.	NNP	O	H.	nn	2	SENT_84	[p3l244t1620r312b1672],
2	Co-administration	NN	O	co-administration	nsubj	6	SENT_84	[p3l343t1619r893b1672],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l920t1619r985b1672],
4	GF1209l8	NN	O	gf1209l8	nn	5	SENT_84	[p3l1008t1619r1327b1673],
5	signiﬁcantly	NN	O	signiﬁcantly	prep_of	2	SENT_84	[p3l1358t1619r1728b1688],
6	increases	VBZ	O	increase	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1755t1619r2030b1672],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_84	[p3l2058t1619r2149b1672],
8	systemic	JJ	O	systemic	amod	9	SENT_84	[p3l174t1712r435b1781],
9	exposure	NN	O	exposure	dobj	6	SENT_84	[p3l472t1729r744b1781],
10	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l780t1721r836b1766],
11	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	12	SENT_84	[p3l873t1712r988b1766],
12	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	prep_to	6	SENT_84	[p3l1023t1712r1318b1781],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1354t1712r1411b1765],
14	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	15	SENT_84	[p3l1447t1729r1644b1766],
15	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	12	SENT_84	[p3l1677t1712r1929b1781],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1677t1712r1929b1781],

1	1	CD	PERCENT	1	num	2	SENT_85	[p3l1966t1714r2149b1783],
2	%	NN	PERCENT	%	_	0	SENT_85	[p3l1966t1714r2149b1783],
3	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	2	SENT_85	[p3l175t1808r396b1861],
4	2001	CD	DATE	2001	num	3	SENT_85	[p3l420t1806r586b1870],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_85	[p3l420t1806r586b1870],
6	84	CD	NUMBER	84	num	7	SENT_85	[p3l617t1807r690b1860],
7	(	NN	O	(	appos	3	SENT_85	[p3l720t1807r820b1873],
8	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	9	SENT_85	[p3l720t1807r820b1873],
9	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_85	[p3l720t1807r820b1873],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_85	[p3l720t1807r820b1873],
11	42-47	CD	NUMBER	42-47	appos	9	SENT_85	[p3l850t1807r1055b1860],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_85	[p3l850t1807r1055b1860],

1	(	RB	O	(	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l9t1902r129b1967],
2	11	CD	NUMBER	11	number	3	SENT_86	[p3l9t1902r129b1967],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l9t1902r129b1967],
4	Cagliero	NNP	O	Cagliero	nn	6	SENT_86	[p3l172t1901r447b1970],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l172t1901r447b1970],
6	E.	NNP	O	E.	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l480t1903r561b1964],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l480t1903r561b1964],
8	Ferracini	NNP	PERSON	Ferracini	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l594t1901r883b1965],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l594t1901r883b1965],
10	R.	NNP	O	R.	appos	8	SENT_86	[p3l916t1903r1002b1964],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l916t1903r1002b1964],
12	Morello	NNP	PERSON	Morello	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l1035t1901r1294b1965],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1035t1901r1294b1965],
14	E.	NNP	O	E.	appos	12	SENT_86	[p3l1327t1903r1408b1964],
15	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1327t1903r1408b1964],
16	Scotlandi	NNP	LOCATION	Scotlandi	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l1444t1901r1743b1965],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1444t1901r1743b1965],
18	K.	NNP	O	K.	appos	16	SENT_86	[p3l1778t1903r1866b1965],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1778t1903r1866b1965],
20	Manara	NNP	LOCATION	Manara	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l1899t1903r2146b1965],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1899t1903r2146b1965],
22	M.	NNP	O	M.	nn	23	SENT_86	[p3l171t1997r252b2049],
23	C.	NNP	O	C.	appos	20	SENT_86	[p3l278t1996r363b2058],
24	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l278t1996r363b2058],
25	Buracco	NNP	LOCATION	Buracco	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l388t1997r656b2058],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l388t1997r656b2058],
27	P.	NNP	O	P.	appos	25	SENT_86	[p3l680t1997r758b2058],
28	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l680t1997r758b2058],
29	Comandone	NNP	O	Comandone	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l784t1996r1164b2058],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l784t1996r1164b2058],
31	A.	NN	O	a.	appos	29	SENT_86	[p3l1189t1996r1278b2058],
32	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1189t1996r1278b2058],
33	Baroetto	NNP	PERSON	Baroetto	nn	34	SENT_86	[p3l1304t1997r1562b2049],
34	Parisi	NNP	PERSON	Parisi	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l1585t1996r1772b2058],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1585t1996r1772b2058],
36	R.	NNP	O	R.	appos	34	SENT_86	[p3l1797t1997r1883b2058],
37	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1797t1997r1883b2058],
38	Baldini	NNP	PERSON	Baldini	dep	34	SENT_86	[p3l1908t1996r2146b2058],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1908t1996r2146b2058],
40	N.	NNP	O	N.	nn	41	SENT_86	[p3l171t2090r239b2142],
41	Reversal	NN	O	reversal	appos	3	SENT_86	[p3l270t2088r533b2142],
42	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l562t2088r627b2142],
43	multidrug	JJ	O	multidrug	amod	45	SENT_86	[p3l649t2088r1271b2157],
44	—	NN	O	—	nn	45	SENT_86	[p3l649t2088r1271b2157],
45	resistance	NN	O	resistance	prep_of	41	SENT_86	[p3l649t2088r1271b2157],
46	using	VBG	O	use	partmod	45	SENT_86	[p3l1298t2088r1461b2157],
47	Valspodar	NNP	O	Valspodar	nn	49	SENT_86	[p3l1488t2088r1800b2157],
48	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	49	SENT_86	[p3l1828t2089r1983b2154],
49	PSC	NN	O	psc	dobj	46	SENT_86	[p3l1828t2089r1983b2154],
50	833	CD	NUMBER	833	num	51	SENT_86	[p3l2014t2089r2146b2154],
51	)	NN	O	)	dep	49	SENT_86	[p3l2014t2089r2146b2154],
52	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l173t2183r278b2236],
53	doxorubicin	NN	O	doxorubicin	dobj	46	SENT_86	[p3l298t2183r656b2236],
54	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l675t2183r731b2235],
55	osteosarcoma	NN	O	osteosarcoma	prep_in	53	SENT_86	[p3l752t2191r1169b2236],
56	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l752t2191r1169b2236],

1	Oncol	NN	O	oncol	_	0	SENT_87	[p3l1196t2183r1384b2237],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_87	[p3l1196t2183r1384b2237],

1	Reg	NNP	PERSON	Reg	_	0	SENT_88	[p3l1409t2185r1537b2253],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_88	[p3l1409t2185r1537b2253],

1	2004	CD	DATE	2004	_	0	SENT_89	[p3l1563t2182r1727b2246],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_89	[p3l1563t2182r1727b2246],
3	I2	NN	O	i2	dep	1	SENT_89	[p3l1752t2183r1820b2235],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	3	SENT_89	[p3l1844t2182r1943b2248],
5	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	6	SENT_89	[p3l1844t2182r1943b2248],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	3	SENT_89	[p3l1844t2182r1943b2248],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_89	[p3l1844t2182r1943b2248],
8	10231031	CD	NUMBER	10231031	dep	1	SENT_89	[p3l1973t2183r2152b2236, p3l178t2277r338b2330],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_89	[p3l1973t2183r2152b2236, p3l178t2277r338b2330],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l9t2371r129b2437],
2	12	CD	NUMBER	12	number	3	SENT_90	[p3l9t2371r129b2437],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_90	[p3l9t2371r129b2437],
4	Kitagawa	NNP	PERSON	Kitagawa	nn	6	SENT_90	[p3l172t2371r476b2440],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l172t2371r476b2440],
6	S.	NNP	O	S.	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l531t2371r606b2434],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l531t2371r606b2434],
8	Nabekura	NNP	PERSON	Nabekura	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l660t2371r970b2434],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l660t2371r970b2434],
10	T.	NNP	O	T.	appos	8	SENT_90	[p3l1023t2372r1104b2434],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1023t2372r1104b2434],
12	Takahashi	NNP	PERSON	Takahashi	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l1158t2371r1484b2434],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1158t2371r1484b2434],
14	T.	NNP	O	T.	appos	12	SENT_90	[p3l1537t2372r1618b2434],
15	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1537t2372r1618b2434],
16	Nakamura	NNP	PERSON	Nakamura	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l1672t2371r2002b2434],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1672t2371r2002b2434],
18	Y.	NNP	O	Y.	appos	16	SENT_90	[p3l2056t2372r2146b2434],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l2056t2372r2146b2434],
20	Sakamoto	NNP	PERSON	Sakamoto	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l173t2464r489b2527],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l173t2464r489b2527],
22	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	20	SENT_90	[p3l531t2466r620b2527],
23	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l531t2466r620b2527],
24	Tano	NNP	PERSON	Tano	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l663t2466r833b2527],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l663t2466r833b2527],
26	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	24	SENT_90	[p3l875t2466r964b2527],
27	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l875t2466r964b2527],
28	Hirai	NNP	PERSON	Hirai	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l1007t2464r1177b2527],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1007t2464r1177b2527],
30	M.	NNP	O	M.	appos	28	SENT_90	[p3l1219t2466r1321b2527],
31	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1219t2466r1321b2527],
32	Tsukahara	NNP	PERSON	Tsukahara	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l1364t2464r1694b2527],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1364t2464r1694b2527],
34	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	36	SENT_90	[p3l1737t2465r1804b2518],
35	Structureactivity	NNP	PERSON	Structureactivity	nn	36	SENT_90	[p3l1849t2465r2147b2518, p3l173t2558r396b2627],
36	relationships	NNS	O	relationship	appos	32	SENT_90	[p3l429t2558r814b2627],
37	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l850t2558r916b2611],
38	the	DT	O	the	det	40	SENT_90	[p3l944t2558r1034b2611],
39	inhibitory	JJ	O	inhibitory	amod	40	SENT_90	[p3l1068t2558r1365b2627],
40	effects	NNS	O	effect	prep_of	36	SENT_90	[p3l1399t2558r1598b2611],
41	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1633t2558r1699b2611],
42	ﬂavonoids	NNS	O	ﬂavonoids	prep_of	40	SENT_90	[p3l1728t2558r2039b2611],
43	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l2076t2574r2149b2611],
44	P-glycoprotein-mediated	JJ	O	p-glycoprotein-mediated	amod	45	SENT_90	[p3l171t2651r925b2720],
45	transport	NN	O	transport	prep_on	42	SENT_90	[p3l950t2659r1220b2720],
46	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1245t2651r1302b2704],
47	KB-C2	NN	O	kb-c2	nn	48	SENT_90	[p3l1330t2652r1545b2705],
48	cells	NNS	O	cell	prep_in	45	SENT_90	[p3l1573t2651r1724b2705],
49	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1573t2651r1724b2705],

1	Biol	NNP	O	Biol	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l1753t2651r1891b2705],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l1753t2651r1891b2705],

1	Pharm	NNP	O	Pharm	_	0	SENT_92	[p3l1924t2651r2141b2705],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_92	[p3l1924t2651r2141b2705],

1	Bull	NN	O	bull	_	0	SENT_93	[p3l169t2746r307b2816],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_93	[p3l169t2746r307b2816],

1	2005	CD	DATE	2005	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l342t2745r508b2809],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l342t2745r508b2809],
3	28	CD	NUMBER	28	number	4	SENT_94	[p3l538t2746r613b2799],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	appos	1	SENT_94	[p3l641t2746r780b2812],
5	12	CD	NUMBER	12	num	6	SENT_94	[p3l641t2746r780b2812],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	4	SENT_94	[p3l641t2746r780b2812],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l641t2746r780b2812],
8	2274-2278	CD	DATE	2274-2278	appos	1	SENT_94	[p3l811t2746r1167b2799],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l811t2746r1167b2799],

1	(	RB	O	(	advmod	4	SENT_95	[p3l9t2840r129b2904],
2	13	CD	NUMBER	13	num	4	SENT_95	[p3l9t2840r129b2904],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	4	SENT_95	[p3l9t2840r129b2904],
4	Schuldes	NNS	O	schulde	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l173t2839r460b2902],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l173t2839r460b2902],
6	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	4	SENT_95	[p3l491t2841r581b2902],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l491t2841r581b2902],
8	Dolderer	NNP	O	Dolderer	dep	4	SENT_95	[p3l613t2839r898b2902],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l613t2839r898b2902],
10	J	NNP	O	J	appos	8	SENT_95	[p3l929t2841r957b2892],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l963t2883r972b2892],

1	H.	NN	O	h.	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1005t2841r1095b2902],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1005t2841r1095b2902],
3	Zimmer	NNP	PERSON	Zimmer	dep	1	SENT_96	[p3l1126t2839r1386b2902],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1126t2839r1386b2902],
5	G.	NNP	O	G.	appos	3	SENT_96	[p3l1419t2840r1508b2902],
6	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1419t2840r1508b2902],
7	Knobloch	NNP	PERSON	Knobloch	dep	1	SENT_96	[p3l1541t2839r1853b2902],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1541t2839r1853b2902],
9	J.	NNP	O	J.	appos	7	SENT_96	[p3l1885t2841r1950b2902],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1885t2841r1950b2902],
11	Bickeboller	NNP	O	Bickeboller	dep	1	SENT_96	[p3l1982t2839r2147b2892, p3l172t2933r396b2996],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1982t2839r2147b2892, p3l172t2933r396b2996],
13	R.	NNP	O	R.	appos	11	SENT_96	[p3l429t2934r515b2996],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l429t2934r515b2996],
15	Jonas	NNP	PERSON	Jonas	dep	1	SENT_96	[p3l548t2934r732b2996],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l548t2934r732b2996],
17	D.	NNP	O	D.	appos	15	SENT_96	[p3l765t2934r855b2996],
18	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l765t2934r855b2996],
19	Woodcock	NNP	PERSON	Woodcock	dep	1	SENT_96	[p3l887t2933r1231b2996],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l887t2933r1231b2996],
21	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	23	SENT_96	[p3l1265t2934r1329b2986],
22	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	23	SENT_96	[p3l1364t2933r1431b2986],
23	Reversal	NN	PERSON	reversal	appos	19	SENT_96	[p3l1465t2933r1729b2986],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1760t2933r1826b2986],
25	multidrug	JJ	O	multidrug	amod	26	SENT_96	[p3l1851t2933r2148b3002],
26	resistance	NN	O	resistance	prep_of	23	SENT_96	[p3l170t3026r465b3080],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l487t3026r593b3080],
28	increase	NN	O	increase	prep_of	23	SENT_96	[p3l613t3026r857b3080],
29	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l878t3026r934b3079],
30	plasma	NN	O	plasma	nn	32	SENT_96	[p3l954t3026r1168b3095],
31	membrane	NN	O	membrane	nn	32	SENT_96	[p3l1187t3026r1502b3080],
32	ﬂuidity	NN	O	ﬂuidity	prep_in	23	SENT_96	[p3l1524t3026r1738b3095],
33	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1759t3026r1816b3079],
34	CHO	NN	O	cho	nn	35	SENT_96	[p3l1837t3027r1992b3080],
35	cells	NNS	O	cell	prep_in	32	SENT_96	[p3l2015t3026r2148b3080],
36	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l172t3121r303b3174],
37	R-Veraparnil	NN	O	r-veraparnil	nn	40	SENT_96	[p3l322t3121r694b3190],
38	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l716t3121r822b3174],
39	bile	NN	O	bile	conj_and	37	SENT_96	[p3l840t3121r951b3174],
40	salts	NNS	O	salt	prep_with	35	SENT_96	[p3l974t3121r1117b3174],
41	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l974t3121r1117b3174],

1	Eur	NNP	O	Eur	_	0	SENT_97	[p3l1139t3123r1262b3174],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_97	[p3l1139t3123r1262b3174],

1	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	2	SENT_98	[p3l1288t3123r1332b3175],
2	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l1363t3122r1582b3175],
3	2001	CD	DATE	2001	num	2	SENT_98	[p3l1598t3120r1762b3184],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l1598t3120r1762b3184],
5	37	CD	NUMBER	37	num	2	SENT_98	[p3l1785t3121r1862b3174],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	7	SENT_98	[p3l1881t3121r1979b3187],
7	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	8	SENT_98	[p3l1881t3121r1979b3187],
8	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_98	[p3l1881t3121r1979b3187],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l1881t3121r1979b3187],
10	660667	CD	NUMBER	660667	appos	8	SENT_98	[p3l2003t3121r2152b3174, p3l172t3214r301b3268],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l2003t3121r2152b3174, p3l172t3214r301b3268],

1	(	RB	O	(	advmod	2	SENT_99	[p3l9t3309r129b3374],
2	14	CD	NUMBER	14	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l9t3309r129b3374],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	2	SENT_99	[p3l9t3309r129b3374],
4	Dintaman	NNP	O	Dintaman	nn	6	SENT_99	[p3l171t3309r485b3372],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l171t3309r485b3372],
6	J	NNP	O	J	dep	3	SENT_99	[p3l519t3310r547b3362],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l553t3353r561b3362],

1	M.	NN	O	m.	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l597t3310r700b3372],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l597t3310r700b3372],
3	Silverman	NNP	PERSON	Silverman	nn	5	SENT_100	[p3l737t3309r1061b3372],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l737t3309r1061b3372],
5	J	NNP	O	J	dep	1	SENT_100	[p3l1095t3310r1123b3362],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l1129t3353r1138b3362],

1	A.	NN	O	a.	nn	2	SENT_101	[p3l1173t3309r1241b3362],
2	Inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l1277t3309r1575b3362],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l1607t3309r1673b3362],
4	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	prep_of	2	SENT_101	[p3l1699t3309r2149b3378],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l170t3402r243b3471],
6	D	NN	O	d	nn	12	SENT_101	[p3l264t3402r832b3471],
7	—	NN	O	—	nn	12	SENT_101	[p3l264t3402r832b3471],
8	alpha	NN	O	alpha	nn	12	SENT_101	[p3l264t3402r832b3471],
9	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	12	SENT_101	[p3l264t3402r832b3471],
10	tocopheryl	NN	O	tocopheryl	nn	12	SENT_101	[p3l264t3402r832b3471],
11	polyethylene	NN	O	polyethylene	nn	12	SENT_101	[p3l852t3402r1227b3471],
12	glycol	NN	O	glycol	prep_by	2	SENT_101	[p3l1249t3402r1428b3471],
13	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	15	SENT_101	[p3l1456t3403r1594b3456],
14	succinate	JJ	O	succinate	amod	15	SENT_101	[p3l1618t3402r1884b3456],
15	(	NN	O	(	dep	12	SENT_101	[p3l1907t3403r2145b3468],
16	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	nn	17	SENT_101	[p3l1907t3403r2145b3468],
17	)	NN	O	)	dep	15	SENT_101	[p3l1907t3403r2145b3468],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l1907t3403r2145b3468],

1	Pharm	NNP	O	Pharm	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l170t3497r388b3550],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l170t3497r388b3550],

1	Res	NNP	O	Res	_	0	SENT_103	[p3l420t3499r541b3550],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_103	[p3l420t3499r541b3550],

1	1999	CD	DATE	1999	_	0	SENT_104	[p3l579t3496r742b3560],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_104	[p3l579t3496r742b3560],
3	16	CD	NUMBER	16	number	4	SENT_104	[p3l774t3496r849b3550],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	appos	1	SENT_104	[p3l876t3497r1014b3563],
5	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	6	SENT_104	[p3l876t3497r1014b3563],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	4	SENT_104	[p3l876t3497r1014b3563],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_104	[p3l876t3497r1014b3563],
8	1550-1556	CD	DATE	1550-1556	appos	1	SENT_104	[p3l1051t3496r1401b3550],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_104	[p3l1051t3496r1401b3550],

1	(	RB	O	(	advmod	3	SENT_105	[p3l9t3591r129b3656],
2	15	CD	NUMBER	15	number	3	SENT_105	[p3l9t3591r129b3656],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l9t3591r129b3656],
4	Shono	NNP	PERSON	Shono	nn	6	SENT_105	[p3l173t3591r379b3654],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l173t3591r379b3654],
6	Y.	NNP	O	Y.	dep	3	SENT_105	[p3l403t3593r493b3654],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l403t3593r493b3654],
8	Nishihara	NNP	PERSON	Nishihara	dep	3	SENT_105	[p3l516t3591r826b3654],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l516t3591r826b3654],
10	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	8	SENT_105	[p3l850t3593r940b3654],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l850t3593r940b3654],
12	Matsuda	NNP	PERSON	Matsuda	dep	3	SENT_105	[p3l963t3591r1240b3654],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l963t3591r1240b3654],
14	Y.	NNP	O	Y.	appos	12	SENT_105	[p3l1264t3593r1353b3654],
15	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l1264t3593r1353b3654],
16	Furukawa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Furukawa	dep	3	SENT_105	[p3l1377t3591r1695b3654],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l1377t3591r1695b3654],
18	S.	NNP	O	S.	appos	16	SENT_105	[p3l1721t3592r1796b3654],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l1721t3592r1796b3654],
20	Okada	NNP	PERSON	Okada	dep	3	SENT_105	[p3l1822t3591r2032b3654],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l1822t3591r2032b3654],
22	N.	NNP	O	N.	appos	20	SENT_105	[p3l2056t3593r2146b3654],
23	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l2056t3593r2146b3654],
24	Fujita	NNP	PERSON	Fujita	dep	3	SENT_105	[p3l171t3685r361b3754],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l171t3685r361b3754],
26	T.	NNP	O	T.	appos	24	SENT_105	[p3l385t3686r466b3748],
27	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l385t3686r466b3748],
28	Yamamoto	NNP	PERSON	Yamamoto	dep	3	SENT_105	[p3l490t3686r839b3748],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l490t3686r839b3748],
30	A.	NNP	O	A.	nn	31	SENT_105	[p3l862t3685r930b3738],
31	Modulation	NN	O	modulation	appos	28	SENT_105	[p3l954t3685r1305b3738],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l1327t3685r1392b3738],
33	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	35	SENT_105	[p3l1407t3685r1682b3738],
34	P-glycoprotein	NN	MISC	p-glycoprotein	nn	35	SENT_105	[p3l1703t3685r2149b3754],
35	function	NN	O	function	prep_of	31	SENT_105	[p4l171t19r422b73],
36	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_105	[p4l452t19r526b88],
37	cremophor	NN	O	cremophor	nn	38	SENT_105	[p4l558t19r885b88],
38	EL	NN	O	el	prep_by	35	SENT_105	[p4l914t21r1005b72],
39	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_105	[p4l1037t19r1143b73],
40	other	JJ	O	other	amod	41	SENT_105	[p4l1174t19r1329b73],
41	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	conj_and	3	SENT_105	[p4l1360t19r1683b73],
42	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_105	[p4l1714t19r1789b88],
43	an	DT	O	a	nn	48	SENT_105	[p4l1821t36r1889b73],
44	in	FW	O	in	nn	45	SENT_105	[p4l1919t19r1977b72],
45	vitro	FW	O	vitro	advmod	47	SENT_105	[p4l2007t19r2147b73],
46	diffusion	NN	O	diffusion	nn	47	SENT_105	[p4l172t114r445b167],
47	chamber	NN	O	chamber	dep	43	SENT_105	[p4l498t114r760b167],
48	method	NN	O	method	prep_by	41	SENT_105	[p4l811t114r1038b167],
49	using	VBG	O	use	partmod	3	SENT_105	[p4l1090t114r1253b183],
50	the	DT	O	the	det	52	SENT_105	[p4l1307t114r1397b167],
51	isolated	VBN	O	isolate	amod	52	SENT_105	[p4l1451t114r1687b167],
52	rat	NN	O	rat	dobj	49	SENT_105	[p4l1738t121r1819b167],
53	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	52	SENT_105	[p4l1870t114r2148b167],
54	membranes	NNS	O	membrane	dep	53	SENT_105	[p4l171t208r534b262],
55	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_105	[p4l171t208r534b262],

1	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	2	SENT_106	[p4l564t210r609b262],
2	Pharm	NNP	PERSON	Pharm	_	0	SENT_106	[p4l642t208r860b262],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_106	[p4l642t208r860b262],

1	Sci	NNP	O	Sci	_	0	SENT_107	[p4l894t209r997b262],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_107	[p4l894t209r997b262],

1	2004	CD	DATE	2004	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1031t208r1197b271],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1031t208r1197b271],
3	93	CD	NUMBER	93	number	4	SENT_108	[p4l1228t209r1300b262],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	appos	1	SENT_108	[p4l1331t209r1431b274],
5	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	6	SENT_108	[p4l1331t209r1431b274],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	4	SENT_108	[p4l1331t209r1431b274],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1331t209r1431b274],
8	877-885	CD	NUMBER	877-885	appos	1	SENT_108	[p4l1465t208r1743b262],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_108	[p4l1465t208r1743b262],

1	(	RB	O	(	advmod	3	SENT_109	[p4l9t303r129b369],
2	16	CD	NUMBER	16	number	3	SENT_109	[p4l9t303r129b369],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l9t303r129b369],
4	Collnot	NNP	O	Collnot	dep	3	SENT_109	[p4l172t303r413b366],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l172t303r413b366],
6	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	nn	7	SENT_109	[p4l447t304r507b356],
7	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	3	SENT_109	[p4l542t304r645b366],
8	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l542t304r645b366],
9	Baldes	NNP	PERSON	Baldes	nn	11	SENT_109	[p4l679t303r900b366],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l679t303r900b366],
11	C.	NNP	O	C.	dep	7	SENT_109	[p4l935t303r1020b366],
12	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l935t303r1020b366],
13	Wempe	NNP	PERSON	Wempe	dep	3	SENT_109	[p4l1053t304r1305b372],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1053t304r1305b372],
15	M.	NNP	O	M.	nn	16	SENT_109	[p4l1339t304r1420b356],
16	F.	NNP	O	F.	appos	13	SENT_109	[p4l1454t304r1532b366],
17	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1454t304r1532b366],
18	Hyatt	NNP	LOCATION	Hyatt	dep	3	SENT_109	[p4l1567t304r1750b372],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1567t304r1750b372],
20	J.	NNP	O	J.	appos	18	SENT_109	[p4l1783t304r1848b366],
21	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1783t304r1848b366],
22	Navarro	NNP	PERSON	Navarro	dep	3	SENT_109	[p4l1883t304r2146b366],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1883t304r2146b366],
24	L.	NNP	O	L.	appos	22	SENT_109	[p4l171t398r252b460],
25	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l171t398r252b460],
26	Edgar	NNP	PERSON	Edgar	dep	3	SENT_109	[p4l275t396r470b465],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l275t396r470b465],
28	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	nn	29	SENT_109	[p4l495t398r561b450],
29	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	appos	26	SENT_109	[p4l585t398r649b459],
30	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l585t398r649b459],
31	Schaefer	NNP	PERSON	Schaefer	dep	3	SENT_109	[p4l675t396r951b460],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l675t396r951b460],
33	U.	NNP	PERSON	U.	nn	34	SENT_109	[p4l974t398r1042b450],
34	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	appos	31	SENT_109	[p4l1066t398r1143b459],
35	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1066t398r1143b459],
36	Lehr	NNP	PERSON	Lehr	nn	40	SENT_109	[p4l1166t396r1323b459],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1166t396r1323b459],
38	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	appos	40	SENT_109	[p4l1348t397r1410b450],
39	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	40	SENT_109	[p4l1434t398r1515b450],
40	Inﬂuence	NNP	PERSON	Inﬂuence	dep	3	SENT_109	[p4l1539t396r1818b450],
41	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1840t396r1905b450],
42	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	48	SENT_109	[p4l1920t396r2149b450],
43	E	NN	O	e	nn	48	SENT_109	[p4l171t492r216b543],
44	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	nn	48	SENT_109	[p4l258t491r438b544],
45	poly	NN	O	poly	nn	48	SENT_109	[p4l484t491r900b560],
46	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	48	SENT_109	[p4l484t491r900b560],
47	ethylene	NN	O	ethylene	nn	48	SENT_109	[p4l484t491r900b560],
48	glycol	NN	O	glycol	prep_of	40	SENT_109	[p4l944t491r1154b560],
49	)	NN	O	)	nn	51	SENT_109	[p4l944t491r1154b560],
50	chain	NN	O	chain	nn	51	SENT_109	[p4l1200t491r1362b544],
51	length	NN	O	length	dep	48	SENT_109	[p4l1404t491r1592b560],
52	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1636t507r1709b544],
53	apical	JJ	O	apical	amod	55	SENT_109	[p4l1753t491r1930b560],
54	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	nn	55	SENT_109	[p4l1974t491r2148b544],
55	transporters	NNS	O	transporter	prep_on	51	SENT_109	[p4l171t593r526b654],
56	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l564t585r621b638],
57	Caco-2	NN	O	caco-2	nn	59	SENT_109	[p4l659t586r874b639],
58	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	59	SENT_109	[p4l912t585r1019b639],
59	monolayers	NNS	O	monolayer	prep_in	55	SENT_109	[p4l1056t585r1423b654],
60	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1056t585r1423b654],

1	J.	NNP	MISC	J.	nn	2	SENT_110	[p4l1462t587r1507b639],
2	Controlled	NNP	MISC	Controlled	_	0	SENT_110	[p4l1555t585r1881b639],
3	Release	NNP	MISC	Release	dep	2	SENT_110	[p4l1912t585r2148b639],
4	2006	CD	DATE	2006	num	3	SENT_110	[p4l171t678r337b741],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_110	[p4l171t678r337b741],
6	11	CD	NUMBER	11	num	3	SENT_110	[p4l370t679r474b731],
7	]	CD	NUMBER	]	number	8	SENT_110	[p4l370t679r474b731],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	3	SENT_110	[p4l509t679r706b744],
9	1-2	CD	NUMBER	1-2	num	10	SENT_110	[p4l509t679r706b744],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_110	[p4l509t679r706b744],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_110	[p4l509t679r706b744],
12	35-40	CD	NUMBER	35-40	appos	10	SENT_110	[p4l738t679r942b732],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_110	[p4l738t679r942b732],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	2	SENT_111	[p4l10t770r617b847],
2	water	NN	O	water	_	0	SENT_111	[p4l10t770r617b847],
3	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	6	SENT_111	[p4l10t770r617b847],
4	insoluble	JJ	O	insoluble	amod	6	SENT_111	[p4l10t770r617b847],
5	)	NN	O	)	nn	6	SENT_111	[p4l10t770r617b847],
6	oL	NN	O	ol	dep	2	SENT_111	[p4l655t770r1118b851],
7	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	9	SENT_111	[p4l655t770r1118b851],
8	tocopherol	NN	O	tocopherol	nn	9	SENT_111	[p4l655t770r1118b851],
9	head	NN	O	head	dep	6	SENT_111	[p4l1151t770r1335b832],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_111	[p4l1151t770r1335b832],

1	TPGS	NNS	O	tpg	nsubjpass	5	SENT_112	[p4l1374t771r1585b833],
2	1000	CD	DATE	1000	dep	1	SENT_112	[p4l1631t771r1798b833],
3	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	5	SENT_112	[p4l1831t770r1947b832],
4	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_112	[p4l1981t770r2149b832],
5	shown	VBN	O	show	_	0	SENT_112	[p4l10t872r238b934],
6	to	TO	O	to	aux	8	SENT_112	[p4l266t882r332b934],
7	be	VB	O	be	cop	8	SENT_112	[p4l361t872r443b934],
8	one	CD	NUMBER	one	xcomp	5	SENT_112	[p4l473t892r598b934],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_112	[p4l628t872r705b934],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_112	[p4l727t872r834b934],
11	most	RBS	O	most	advmod	12	SENT_112	[p4l862t882r1035b934],
12	potent	JJ	O	potent	amod	15	SENT_112	[p4l1061t881r1284b953],
13	commercially	RB	O	commercially	advmod	14	SENT_112	[p4l1312t872r1799b953],
14	available	JJ	O	available	amod	15	SENT_112	[p4l1830t872r2148b935],
15	P	NN	O	p	prep_of	8	SENT_112	[p4l7t976r170b1056],
16	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	19	SENT_112	[p4l7t976r170b1056],
17	gp	NN	O	gp	nn	19	SENT_112	[p4l7t976r170b1056],
18	inhibitor	NN	O	inhibitor	nn	19	SENT_112	[p4l195t974r498b1037],
19	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	dep	15	SENT_112	[p4l523t958r987b1037],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_112	[p4l523t958r987b1037],

1	”	NN	O	”	nsubjpass	12	SENT_113	[p4l523t958r987b1037],
2	Due	JJ	O	due	prep	1	SENT_113	[p4l1010t976r1155b1037],
3	to	TO	O	to	aux	4	SENT_113	[p4l1179t984r1245b1037],
4	surface	VB	O	surface	dep	2	SENT_113	[p4l1273t974r1521b1037],
5	active	JJ	O	active	amod	6	SENT_113	[p4l1547t974r1753b1037],
6	properties	NNS	O	property	dobj	4	SENT_113	[p4l1776t974r2146b1056],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l1776t974r2146b1056],
8	TPGS	NNS	O	tpg	appos	6	SENT_113	[p4l7t1078r218b1140],
9	1000	CD	DATE	1000	dep	8	SENT_113	[p4l285t1078r452b1140],
10	may	MD	DATE	may	aux	12	SENT_113	[p4l506t1097r657b1158],
11	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	12	SENT_113	[p4l709t1077r792b1139],
12	used	VBN	O	use	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l845t1077r1008b1139],
13	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l1062t1097r1130b1139],
14	a	DT	O	a	det	16	SENT_113	[p4l1187t1097r1224b1139],
15	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	16	SENT_113	[p4l1277t1077r1436b1158],
16	solubilizer	NN	O	solubilizer	prep_as	12	SENT_113	[p4l1494t1077r1884b1151],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l1494t1077r1884b1151],
18	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l1943t1097r2011b1139],
19	an	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_113	[p4l2068t1097r2149b1139],
20	emulsiﬁer	NN	O	emulsiﬁer	prep_as	12	SENT_113	[p4l8t1179r380b1253],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l8t1179r380b1253],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l429t1179r555b1241],
23	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l600t1199r668b1241],
24	a	DT	O	a	det	25	SENT_113	[p4l715t1199r752b1241],
25	vehicle	NN	O	vehicle	prep_as	12	SENT_113	[p4l795t1179r1049b1242],
26	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l1093t1179r1161b1241],
27	lipid	NN	O	lipid	prep_in	25	SENT_113	[p4l1204t1179r1366b1260],
28	based	VBN	O	base	partmod	27	SENT_113	[p4l1408t1179r1610b1241],
29	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	31	SENT_113	[p4l1654t1179r1813b1260],
30	delivery	NN	O	delivery	nn	31	SENT_113	[p4l1859t1179r2148b1260],
31	formulations	NNS	O	formulation	dobj	28	SENT_113	[p4l7t1281r479b1343],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l7t1281r479b1343],

1	Previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	4	SENT_114	[p4l516t1281r915b1362],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l516t1281r915b1362],
3	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	4	SENT_114	[p4l952t1301r1053b1344],
4	disclosed	VBD	O	disclose	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l1087t1281r1417b1343],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_114	[p4l1451t1301r1488b1343],
6	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	dep	12	SENT_114	[p4l1520t1282r1732b1344],
7	structureactivity	NN	O	structureactivity	nn	8	SENT_114	[p4l1772t1291r2142b1343, p4l9t1383r279b1465],
8	relationship	NN	O	relationship	dep	6	SENT_114	[p4l342t1383r772b1465],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_114	[p4l840t1384r1069b1461],
10	SAR	NN	O	sar	dep	12	SENT_114	[p4l840t1384r1069b1461],
11	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	12	SENT_114	[p4l840t1384r1069b1461],
12	study	NN	O	study	dep	15	SENT_114	[p4l1139t1367r1423b1465],
13	.16	CD	NUMBER	.16	dep	12	SENT_114	[p4l1139t1367r1423b1465],
14	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	15	SENT_114	[p4l1486t1385r1609b1446],
15	showed	VBD	O	show	dep	45	SENT_114	[p4l1677t1383r1950b1446],
16	that	IN	O	that	complm	29	SENT_114	[p4l2013t1383r2149b1446],
17	Rhodamine	NN	O	rhodamine	nsubj	29	SENT_114	[p4l7t1486r406b1548],
18	123	CD	NUMBER	123	number	19	SENT_114	[p4l437t1487r553b1549],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	23	SENT_114	[p4l582t1487r817b1563],
20	RHO	NN	MISC	rho	nn	23	SENT_114	[p4l582t1487r817b1563],
21	)	NN	O	)	nn	23	SENT_114	[p4l582t1487r817b1563],
22	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	nn	23	SENT_114	[p4l843t1486r1042b1548],
23	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	dep	17	SENT_114	[p4l1065t1486r1398b1548],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l1420t1486r1486b1548],
25	Caco-2	NN	O	caco-2	nn	28	SENT_114	[p4l1509t1487r1756b1549],
26	monolayer	NN	O	monolayer	nn	28	SENT_114	[p4l1779t1486r2150b1567],
27	transport	NN	O	transport	nn	28	SENT_114	[p4l7t1598r323b1669],
28	experiments	NNS	O	experiment	prep_in	17	SENT_114	[p4l354t1588r785b1669],
29	varied	VBD	O	vary	ccomp	15	SENT_114	[p4l819t1588r1041b1651],
30	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l1072t1588r1228b1651],
31	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	nn	35	SENT_114	[p4l1260t1589r1471b1651],
32	PEG	NN	O	peg	nn	35	SENT_114	[p4l1507t1589r1674b1651],
33	chain	NN	O	chain	nn	35	SENT_114	[p4l1706t1588r1896b1650],
34	length	NN	O	length	nn	35	SENT_114	[p4l1928t1588r2149b1669],
35	(	NN	O	(	prep_with	29	SENT_114	[p4l10t1690r332b1767],
36	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l10t1690r332b1767],
37	200	CD	NUMBER	200	num	41	SENT_114	[p4l357t1691r487b1753],
38	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l514t1690r640b1752],
39	6000	CD	DATE	6000	conj_and	37	SENT_114	[p4l665t1690r839b1753],
40	Da	NN	O	da	nn	41	SENT_114	[p4l864t1691r1017b1767],
41	)	NN	O	)	prep_between	35	SENT_114	[p4l864t1691r1017b1767],
42	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l864t1691r1017b1767],
43	the	DT	O	the	det	44	SENT_114	[p4l1045t1690r1152b1752],
44	results	NNS	O	result	nsubj	45	SENT_114	[p4l1176t1690r1405b1752],
45	afforded	VBD	O	afford	ccomp	4	SENT_114	[p4l1434t1690r1733b1752],
46	a	DT	O	a	dobj	45	SENT_114	[p4l1758t1710r1795b1752],
47	predicted	VBN	O	predict	partmod	46	SENT_114	[p4l1817t1690r2149b1771],
48	optimal	JJ	O	optimal	acomp	47	SENT_114	[p4l8t1792r273b1873],
49	in	FW	O	in	prep	47	SENT_114	[p4l299t1795r361b1854],
50	vitro	FW	O	vitro	nn	53	SENT_114	[p4l392t1795r552b1855],
51	efﬁux	FW	O	efﬁux	nn	53	SENT_114	[p4l577t1792r779b1854],
52	inhibitory	JJ	O	inhibitory	amod	53	SENT_114	[p4l802t1792r1144b1873],
53	effect	NN	O	effect	pobj	49	SENT_114	[p4l1169t1792r1366b1854],
54	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l1391t1801r1451b1854],
55	a	DT	O	a	det	58	SENT_114	[p4l1475t1812r1512b1854],
56	PEG	NN	O	peg	nn	58	SENT_114	[p4l1533t1793r1699b1855],
57	chain	NN	O	chain	nn	58	SENT_114	[p4l1722t1792r1910b1854],
58	length	NN	O	length	prep_at	53	SENT_114	[p4l1933t1792r2150b1873],
59	residing	VBG	O	reside	partmod	46	SENT_114	[p4l6t1894r291b1975],
60	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l323t1894r619b1956],
61	1581	CD	DATE	1581	prep_between	59	SENT_114	[p4l659t1894r819b1957],
62	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l862t1896r923b1956],
63	|	CD	NUMBER	|	prep_between	59	SENT_114	[p4l862t1896r923b1956],
64	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l862t1896r923b1956],
65	209	CD	NUMBER	209	num	66	SENT_114	[p4l959t1895r1087b1957],
66	Da	NN	O	da	prep_between	59	SENT_114	[p4l1121t1896r1224b1956],
67	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	69	SENT_114	[p4l1257t1894r1680b1975],
68	absorptive	JJ	O	absorptive	amod	69	SENT_114	[p4l1257t1894r1680b1975],
69	)	NN	O	)	dep	66	SENT_114	[p4l1257t1894r1680b1975],
70	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l1717t1894r1842b1956],
71	1182	CD	DATE	1182	num	73	SENT_114	[p4l1882t1895r2049b1957],
72	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l2084t1896r2145b1956],
73	|	CD	NUMBER	|	prep_between	59	SENT_114	[p4l2084t1896r2145b1956],
74	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l2084t1896r2145b1956],
75	476	CD	NUMBER	476	num	76	SENT_114	[p4l7t1996r135b2059],
76	Da	NN	O	da	dep	73	SENT_114	[p4l158t1998r260b2058],
77	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	79	SENT_114	[p4l284t1997r670b2077],
78	secretory	JJ	O	secretory	amod	79	SENT_114	[p4l284t1997r670b2077],
79	)	NN	O	)	dep	76	SENT_114	[p4l284t1997r670b2077],
80	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l284t1997r670b2077],
