1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_1	[p1l383t81r429b102],
2	NEW	NNP	O	NEW	nn	4	SENT_1	[p1l447t83r532b102],
3	ENGLAND	NNP	O	ENGLAND	nn	4	SENT_1	[p1l551t83r740b102],
4	JOURNAL	NNP	O	JOURNAL	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l759t83r938b109],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l958t81r986b108],
6	MEDICINE	NNP	O	MEDICINE	prep_of	4	SENT_1	[p1l998t83r1197b102],

1	l	NN	O	l	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l90t184r93b303],
2	ORIGINAL	NNP	O	ORIGINAL	nn	3	SENT_2	[p1l579t234r803b260],
3	ARTICLE	NN	O	article	dep	1	SENT_2	[p1l815t234r1001b260],
4	I	PRP	O	I	dep	1	SENT_2	[p1l1488t184r1491b303],

1	Crizotinib	NNP	O	Crizotinib	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l93t378r396b433],
2	versus	CC	O	versus	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l423t396r612b433],
3	Chemotherapy	NNP	O	Chemotherapy	conj_versus	1	SENT_3	[p1l642t378r1088b448],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1113t378r1170b432],
5	Advanced	NNP	O	Advanced	prep_in	1	SENT_3	[p1l1196t378r1488b433],

1	ALK-Positive	JJ	O	alk-positive	amod	3	SENT_4	[p1l392t462r766b516],
2	Lung	NN	O	lung	nn	3	SENT_4	[p1l794t466r949b531],
3	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l976t465r1186b516],

1	Alice	NNP	PERSON	Alice	nn	3	SENT_5	[p1l306t584r387b615],
2	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	nn	3	SENT_5	[p1l398t587r428b615],
3	Shaw	NNP	PERSON	Shaw	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l443t584r540b621],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l443t584r540b621],
5	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	nn	14	SENT_5	[p1l557t587r647b621],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l557t587r647b621],
7	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	14	SENT_5	[p1l665t584r764b621],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l665t584r764b621],
9	Dong-Wan	NNP	PERSON	Dong-Wan	appos	14	SENT_5	[p1l781t587r959b625],
10	Kim	NNP	PERSON	Kim	nn	14	SENT_5	[p1l976t587r1049b621],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l976t587r1049b621],
12	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	14	SENT_5	[p1l1066t587r1156b621],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1066t587r1156b621],
14	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	3	SENT_5	[p1l1173t584r1272b621],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1173t584r1272b621],

1	Kazuhiko	NNP	PERSON	Kazuhiko	nn	2	SENT_6	[p1l168t633r321b664],
2	Nakagawa	NNP	PERSON	Nakagawa	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l336t633r518b674],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l336t633r518b674],
4	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	2	SENT_6	[p1l535t636r626b670],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l535t636r626b670],
6	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l643t633r742b670],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l643t633r742b670],
8	Takashi	NNP	PERSON	Takashi	nn	9	SENT_6	[p1l755t633r884b664],
9	Seto	NNP	PERSON	Seto	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l899t635r981b670],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l899t635r981b670],
11	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l998t636r1088b670],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l998t636r1088b670],
13	Lucio	NNP	PERSON	Lucio	nn	14	SENT_6	[p1l1105t636r1193b664],
14	Criné	NNP	PERSON	Criné	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l1207t635r1307b670],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1207t635r1307b670],
16	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l1324t636r1414b670],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1324t636r1414b670],
18	Myung-Ju	NNP	O	Myung-Ju	nn	19	SENT_6	[p1l136t685r295b723],
19	Ahn	NNP	PERSON	Ahn	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l308t682r385b719],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l308t682r385b719],
21	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l402t685r492b719],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l402t685r492b719],
23	Tommaso	NNP	PERSON	Tommaso	nn	25	SENT_6	[p1l505t685r679b713],
24	De	NNP	PERSON	De	nn	25	SENT_6	[p1l695t685r738b713],
25	Pas	NNP	PERSON	Pas	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l754t685r819b719],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l754t685r819b719],
27	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l836t685r926b719],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l836t685r926b719],
29	Benjamin	NNP	PERSON	Benjamin	nn	30	SENT_6	[p1l943t685r1101b723],
30	Besse	NNP	PERSON	Besse	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l1118t685r1222b719],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1118t685r1222b719],
32	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l1239t685r1329b719],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1239t685r1329b719],
34	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l1346t682r1445b719],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1346t682r1445b719],
36	Benjamin	NNP	PERSON	Benjamin	nn	37	SENT_6	[p1l101t734r277b772],
37	]	NNP	O	]	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l101t734r277b772],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l101t734r277b772],

1	Solomon	NNP	PERSON	Solomon	nn	23	SENT_7	[p1l289t731r441b768],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l289t731r441b768],
3	M.B.	NNP	LOCATION	M.B.	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l455t734r534b768],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l455t734r534b768],
5	B.S.	NNP	O	B.S.	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l548t733r613b768],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l548t733r613b768],
7	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l628t731r719b768],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l628t731r719b768],
9	Fiona	NNP	PERSON	Fiona	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l734t734r818b762],
10	Blackhall	NNP	PERSON	Blackhall	nn	23	SENT_7	[p1l831t731r975b768],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l831t731r975b768],
12	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l989t734r1074b768],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l989t734r1074b768],
14	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l1088t731r1180b768],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1088t731r1180b768],
16	Yi-LongWu	NNP	O	Yi-LongWu	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l1190t734r1382b772],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1190t734r1382b772],
18	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l1396t734r1480b768],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1396t734r1480b768],
20	Michael	NNP	PERSON	Michael	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l138t780r268b811],
21	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	Thomas	nn	23	SENT_7	[p1l281t780r429b817],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l281t780r429b817],
23	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l446t783r536b817],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l446t783r536b817],
25	Kenneth	NNP	PERSON	Kenneth	nn	26	SENT_7	[p1l553t780r722b820],
26	]	NNP	O	]	appos	23	SENT_7	[p1l553t780r722b820],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l553t780r722b820],

1	O’Byrne	NNP	O	O’Byrne	nn	6	SENT_8	[p1l737t782r882b821],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l737t782r882b821],
3	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	6	SENT_8	[p1l899t783r989b817],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l899t783r989b817],
5	Denis	NNP	PERSON	Denis	appos	6	SENT_8	[p1l1006t783r1100b811],
6	Moro-Sibilot	NNP	PERSON	Moro-Sibilot	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1117t780r1336b817],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1117t780r1336b817],
8	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	dep	6	SENT_8	[p1l1353t783r1444b817],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1353t783r1444b817],

1	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	3	SENT_9	[p1l223t832r256b860],
2	Ross	NNP	PERSON	Ross	nn	3	SENT_9	[p1l273t832r350b860],
3	Camidge	NNP	PERSON	Camidge	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l364t829r523b870],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l364t829r523b870],
5	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	dep	3	SENT_9	[p1l541t832r631b866],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l541t832r631b866],
7	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	5	SENT_9	[p1l648t829r747b866],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l648t829r747b866],
9	Tony	NNP	PERSON	Tony	nn	10	SENT_9	[p1l760t832r843b870],
10	Mok	NNP	PERSON	Mok	appos	5	SENT_9	[p1l858t829r939b866],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l858t829r939b866],
12	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	5	SENT_9	[p1l956t832r1046b866],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l956t832r1046b866],
14	Vera	NNP	PERSON	Vera	nn	15	SENT_9	[p1l1059t832r1134b860],
15	Hirsh	NNP	PERSON	Hirsh	appos	5	SENT_9	[p1l1151t829r1251b866],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1151t829r1251b866],
17	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	5	SENT_9	[p1l1268t832r1358b866],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1268t832r1358b866],

1	Gregory	NNP	PERSON	Gregory	nn	2	SENT_10	[p1l172t880r337b919],
2	]	NNP	O	]	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l172t880r337b919],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l172t880r337b919],

1	Riely	NNP	PERSON	Riely	nn	8	SENT_11	[p1l354t878r438b919],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l354t878r438b919],
3	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	8	SENT_11	[p1l455t881r545b915],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l455t881r545b915],
5	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	8	SENT_11	[p1l562t878r661b915],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l562t878r661b915],
7	Shrividya	NNP	PERSON	Shrividya	appos	8	SENT_11	[p1l676t878r829b919],
8	Iyer	NNP	PERSON	Iyer	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l845t881r911b919],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l845t881r911b919],
10	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	8	SENT_11	[p1l928t878r1027b915],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l928t878r1027b915],
12	Vanessa	NNP	PERSON	Vanessa	nn	13	SENT_11	[p1l1040t881r1181b909],
13	Tassell	NNP	PERSON	Tassell	conj_and	10	SENT_11	[p1l1193t878r1320b915],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1193t878r1320b915],
15	B.S.	NNP	O	B.S.	conj_and	10	SENT_11	[p1l1337t880r1408b915],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1337t880r1408b915],
17	Anna	NNP	PERSON	Anna	nn	18	SENT_11	[p1l189t929r277b958],
18	Polli	NNP	PERSON	Polli	conj_and	10	SENT_11	[p1l293t927r372b964],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l293t927r372b964],
20	B.S.	NNP	O	B.S.	conj_and	10	SENT_11	[p1l389t929r460b964],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l389t929r460b964],
22	Keith	NNP	PERSON	Keith	nn	24	SENT_11	[p1l477t927r558b958],
23	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	24	SENT_11	[p1l575t930r608b958],
24	Wilner	NNP	PERSON	Wilner	conj_and	10	SENT_11	[p1l621t927r740b964],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l621t927r740b964],
26	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	8	SENT_11	[p1l758t927r857b964],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l758t927r857b964],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l872t927r931b958],
29	Pasi	NNP	PERSON	Pasi	nn	31	SENT_11	[p1l949t930r1013b958],
30	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	31	SENT_11	[p1l1026t929r1175b967],
31	janne	NNP	PERSON	janne	appos	8	SENT_11	[p1l1026t929r1175b967],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1026t929r1175b967],
33	M.D.	NNP	O	M.D.	appos	8	SENT_11	[p1l1192t930r1283b964],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1192t930r1283b964],
35	Ph.D.	NNP	O	Ph.D.	appos	8	SENT_11	[p1l1300t927r1389b958],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1300t927r1389b958],

1	ABSTRACT	NN	O	abstract	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l679t1035r901b1058],

1	BAC	NN	O	bac	nn	2	SENT_13	[p1l93t1151r148b1170],
2	KG	NN	O	kg	tmod	24	SENT_13	[p1l154t1151r190b1170],
3	no	DT	O	no	det	6	SENT_13	[p1l197t1151r236b1170],
4	u	NN	O	u	nn	6	SENT_13	[p1l242t1151r258b1170],
5	N	NN	O	n	nn	6	SENT_13	[p1l266t1151r283b1170],
6	D	NN	O	d	dep	2	SENT_13	[p1l290t1151r308b1170],
7	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l91t1197r126b1224],
8	single-group	JJ	O	single-group	amod	9	SENT_13	[p1l138t1194r349b1234],
9	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_in	24	SENT_13	[p1l362t1194r488b1232],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l362t1194r488b1232],
11	chromosomal	JJ	O	chromosomal	amod	12	SENT_13	[p1l502t1194r734b1225],
12	rearrangements	NNS	O	rearrangement	nsubjpass	24	SENT_13	[p1l746t1201r1010b1234],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1023t1194r1062b1225],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_13	[p1l1067t1194r1119b1225],
15	anaplastic	JJ	O	anaplastic	amod	20	SENT_13	[p1l1131t1194r1300b1233],
16	lymphoma	NN	O	lymphoma	nn	20	SENT_13	[p1l1311t1194r1490b1233],
17	kinase	NN	O	kinase	nn	20	SENT_13	[p1l91t1245r197b1275],
18	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	20	SENT_13	[p1l209t1254r285b1284],
19	(	NN	O	(	nn	20	SENT_13	[p1l299t1247r384b1280],
20	ALK	NN	O	alk	prep_of	12	SENT_13	[p1l299t1247r384b1280],
21	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	20	SENT_13	[p1l299t1247r384b1280],
22	have	VBP	O	have	aux	24	SENT_13	[p1l398t1244r470b1275],
23	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	24	SENT_13	[p1l482t1244r559b1275],
24	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l570t1244r739b1275],
25	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l749t1244r824b1275],
26	marked	JJ	O	marked	amod	28	SENT_13	[p1l835t1244r960b1275],
27	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	28	SENT_13	[p1l972t1244r1091b1275],
28	responses	NNS	O	response	prep_with	24	SENT_13	[p1l1102t1254r1263b1283],
29	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1276t1251r1307b1275],
30	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	prep_to	24	SENT_13	[p1l1319t1245r1487b1282],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1319t1245r1487b1282],
32	an	DT	O	a	det	36	SENT_13	[p1l91t1304r130b1325],
33	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	36	SENT_13	[p1l142t1294r204b1325],
34	tyrosine	NN	O	tyrosine	nn	36	SENT_13	[p1l215t1295r343b1333],
35	kinase	NN	O	kinase	nn	36	SENT_13	[p1l355t1294r459b1325],
36	inhibitor	NN	O	inhibitor	appos	30	SENT_13	[p1l470t1294r611b1325],
37	targeting	VBG	O	target	partmod	36	SENT_13	[p1l622t1295r770b1334],
38	ALK	NNP	O	ALK	dobj	37	SENT_13	[p1l778t1297r858b1326],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l778t1297r858b1326],

1	Whether	IN	O	whether	complm	4	SENT_14	[p1l870t1294r1011b1325],
2	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	nsubj	4	SENT_14	[p1l1021t1294r1176b1325],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	4	SENT_14	[p1l1188t1295r1213b1325],
4	superior	JJ	O	superior	csubj	13	SENT_14	[p1l1225t1295r1357b1333],
5	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1367t1301r1398b1325],
6	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	7	SENT_14	[p1l1410t1301r1489b1325, p1l92t1344r165b1375],
7	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_to	4	SENT_14	[p1l177t1344r413b1383],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l423t1344r499b1375],
9	respect	NN	O	respect	prep_with	7	SENT_14	[p1l512t1351r632b1383],
10	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l644t1351r675b1375],
11	efficacy	NN	O	efficacy	prep_to	4	SENT_14	[p1l689t1344r820b1383],
12	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	13	SENT_14	[p1l831t1345r857b1375],
13	unknown	JJ	O	unknown	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l871t1344r1040b1375],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l871t1344r1040b1375],

1	METHODS	NNS	O	method	nsubj	3	SENT_15	[p1l94t1441r246b1461],
2	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	3	SENT_15	[p1l90t1487r142b1515],
3	conducted	VBD	O	conduct	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l156t1485r327b1515],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_15	[p1l340t1495r358b1515],
5	phase	NN	O	phase	nn	9	SENT_15	[p1l370t1485r467b1523],
6	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	9	SENT_15	[p1l481t1487r508b1522],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l481t1487r508b1522],
8	open-label	JJ	O	open-label	amod	9	SENT_15	[p1l524t1485r698b1523],
9	trial	NN	O	trial	dobj	3	SENT_15	[p1l712t1485r781b1515],
10	comparing	VBG	O	compare	xcomp	3	SENT_15	[p1l794t1485r976b1524],
11	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	dobj	10	SENT_15	[p1l989t1485r1152b1515],
12	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1165t1485r1240b1515],
13	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_with	10	SENT_15	[p1l1255t1485r1491b1523],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l91t1534r124b1564],
15	347	CD	NUMBER	347	num	16	SENT_15	[p1l140t1536r198b1565],
16	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	13	SENT_15	[p1l214t1534r347b1573],
17	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l362t1534r438b1565],
18	locally	RB	O	locally	advmod	19	SENT_15	[p1l454t1534r564b1573],
19	advanced	VBN	O	advance	prep_with	10	SENT_15	[p1l578t1534r732b1565],
20	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l748t1544r783b1565],
21	metastatic	JJ	O	metastatic	amod	26	SENT_15	[p1l798t1534r971b1564],
22	ALK	NN	O	alk	nn	26	SENT_15	[p1l985t1534r1189b1573],
23	—	NN	O	—	nn	26	SENT_15	[p1l985t1534r1189b1573],
24	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	26	SENT_15	[p1l985t1534r1189b1573],
25	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	26	SENT_15	[p1l1205t1534r1280b1573],
26	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_with	10	SENT_15	[p1l1295t1544r1404b1564],
27	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	29	SENT_15	[p1l1418t1534r1489b1565],
28	had	VBD	O	have	aux	29	SENT_15	[p1l91t1584r151b1615],
29	received	VBN	O	receive	rcmod	26	SENT_15	[p1l165t1584r296b1615],
30	one	CD	NUMBER	one	dobj	29	SENT_15	[p1l309t1594r367b1615],
31	prior	RB	O	prior	prep	29	SENT_15	[p1l380t1584r461b1623],
32	platinum-based	JJ	O	platinum-based	amod	33	SENT_15	[p1l472t1584r729b1623],
33	regimen	NN	O	regimen	pobj	31	SENT_15	[p1l742t1584r886b1623],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l742t1584r886b1623],

1	Patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubjpass	4	SENT_16	[p1l901t1584r1030b1614],
2	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_16	[p1l1042t1594r1119b1615],
3	randomly	RB	O	randomly	advmod	4	SENT_16	[p1l1133t1584r1291b1623],
4	assigned	VBN	O	assign	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1302t1584r1444b1623],
5	to	TO	O	to	aux	6	SENT_16	[p1l1458t1590r1489b1615],
6	receive	VB	O	receive	xcomp	4	SENT_16	[p1l91t1634r203b1665],
7	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	8	SENT_16	[p1l218t1634r283b1665],
8	treatment	NN	O	treatment	dobj	6	SENT_16	[p1l297t1640r462b1664],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l473t1634r549b1665],
10	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	nn	11	SENT_16	[p1l564t1634r727b1665],
11	(	NN	O	(	prep_with	6	SENT_16	[p1l744t1636r814b1669],
12	250	CD	NUMBER	250	num	14	SENT_16	[p1l744t1636r814b1669],
13	mg	NN	O	mg	nn	14	SENT_16	[p1l829t1637r893b1673],
14	)	NN	O	)	tmod	11	SENT_16	[p1l829t1637r893b1673],
15	twice	RB	O	twice	advmod	16	SENT_16	[p1l910t1634r998b1665],
16	daily	RB	SET	daily	advmod	14	SENT_16	[p1l1014t1634r1094b1673],
17	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1108t1644r1142b1665],
18	intravenous	JJ	O	intravenous	amod	19	SENT_16	[p1l1155t1634r1349b1665],
19	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_with	6	SENT_16	[p1l1365t1634r1489b1665, p1l92t1753r216b1792],

1	with	IN	O	with	prep	19	SENT_17	[p1l227t1753r303b1784],
2	either	CC	O	either	dep	1	SENT_17	[p1l317t1753r413b1784],
3	pemetrexed	JJ	O	pemetrexed	amod	6	SENT_17	[p1l425t1753r620b1792],
4	(	NN	O	(	nn	6	SENT_17	[p1l636t1755r706b1788],
5	500	CD	NUMBER	500	num	6	SENT_17	[p1l636t1755r706b1788],
6	mg	NN	O	mg	conj	1	SENT_17	[p1l720t1763r774b1792],
7	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l786t1763r841b1792],
8	square	NN	O	square	nn	9	SENT_17	[p1l854t1763r964b1792],
9	meter	NN	O	meter	prep_per	1	SENT_17	[p1l978t1759r1074b1784],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1087t1753r1126b1784],
11	body-surface	JJ	O	body-surface	amod	13	SENT_17	[p1l1133t1753r1346b1792],
12	area	NN	O	area	nn	13	SENT_17	[p1l1360t1756r1440b1788],
13	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	9	SENT_17	[p1l1360t1756r1440b1788],
14	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1456t1763r1491b1784],
15	docetaxel	NN	O	docetaxel	prep_per	1	SENT_17	[p1l92t1803r249b1834],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	17	SENT_17	[p1l267t1806r316b1839],
17	75	CD	NUMBER	75	num	18	SENT_17	[p1l267t1806r316b1839],
18	mg	NN	O	mg	dep	15	SENT_17	[p1l334t1813r388b1843],
19	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l403t1813r457b1842],
20	square	NN	O	square	nn	21	SENT_17	[p1l473t1813r583b1842],
21	meter	NN	O	meter	pobj	19	SENT_17	[p1l600t1806r705b1839],
22	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	19	SENT_17	[p1l600t1806r705b1839],
23	every	DT	SET	every	quantmod	24	SENT_17	[p1l724t1813r810b1842],
24	3	CD	SET	3	num	25	SENT_17	[p1l825t1805r842b1834],
25	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	tmod	22	SENT_17	[p1l858t1803r969b1834],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l858t1803r969b1834],

1	Patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubjpass	11	SENT_18	[p1l987t1804r1119b1834],
2	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1136t1804r1169b1833],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_18	[p1l1186t1803r1237b1834],
4	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nn	5	SENT_18	[p1l1254t1803r1491b1842],
5	group	NN	O	group	prep_in	1	SENT_18	[p1l91t1863r188b1893],
6	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	7	SENT_18	[p1l198t1853r268b1884],
7	had	VBD	O	have	rcmod	5	SENT_18	[p1l280t1853r340b1884],
8	disease	NN	O	disease	nn	9	SENT_18	[p1l352t1853r470b1884],
9	progression	NN	O	progression	dobj	7	SENT_18	[p1l481t1854r675b1893],
10	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_18	[p1l684t1864r761b1884],
11	permitted	VBN	O	permit	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l773t1853r935b1892],
12	to	TO	O	to	aux	13	SENT_18	[p1l946t1860r978b1884],
13	cross	VB	O	cross	xcomp	11	SENT_18	[p1l990t1863r1073b1884],
14	over	IN	O	over	prep	13	SENT_18	[p1l1085t1863r1153b1884],
15	to	TO	O	to	pcomp	14	SENT_18	[p1l1164t1860r1195b1884],
16	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	pobj	15	SENT_18	[p1l1207t1853r1366b1884],
17	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1378t1864r1411b1884],
18	part	NN	O	part	prep_as	13	SENT_18	[p1l1423t1860r1491b1892],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l92t1903r131b1934],
20	a	DT	O	a	det	22	SENT_18	[p1l137t1913r154b1934],
21	separate	JJ	O	separate	amod	22	SENT_18	[p1l167t1910r305b1942],
22	study	NN	O	study	prep_of	18	SENT_18	[p1l319t1903r413b1942],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l319t1903r413b1942],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_19	[p1l427t1903r489b1934],
2	primary	JJ	O	primary	amod	4	SENT_19	[p1l502t1903r638b1942],
3	end	NN	O	end	nn	4	SENT_19	[p1l650t1903r709b1934],
4	point	NN	O	point	nsubj	7	SENT_19	[p1l722t1903r811b1942],
5	was	VBD	O	be	cop	7	SENT_19	[p1l821t1913r884b1934],
6	progression-free	JJ	O	progression-free	amod	7	SENT_19	[p1l898t1903r1172b1942],
7	survival	NN	O	survival	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1186t1903r1324b1934],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1186t1903r1324b1934],

1	RESULTS	NNS	O	result	nsubj	8	SENT_20	[p1l93t1993r221b2013],
2	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_20	[p1l90t2037r152b2067],
3	median	JJ	O	median	amod	5	SENT_20	[p1l168t2037r293b2067],
4	progression-free	JJ	O	progression-free	amod	5	SENT_20	[p1l308t2036r582b2076],
5	survival	NN	O	survival	dep	1	SENT_20	[p1l598t2037r727b2067],
6	was	VBD	O	be	cop	8	SENT_20	[p1l740t2047r803b2067],
7	7.7	CD	DURATION	7.7	num	8	SENT_20	[p1l820t2039r864b2067],
8	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l879t2037r1006b2067],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1022t2037r1054b2067],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_20	[p1l1069t2037r1121b2067],
11	crizotinib	JJ	O	crizotinib	amod	12	SENT_20	[p1l1136t2037r1299b2067],
12	group	NN	O	group	prep_in	8	SENT_20	[p1l1315t2046r1413b2076],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1428t2037r1489b2067],
14	3.0	CD	DURATION	3.0	num	15	SENT_20	[p1l92t2089r140b2117],
15	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	conj_and	8	SENT_20	[p1l153t2087r280b2117],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l294t2087r326b2117],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_20	[p1l339t2087r391b2117],
18	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nn	22	SENT_20	[p1l404t2087r641b2125],
19	group	NN	O	group	nn	22	SENT_20	[p1l651t2096r750b2126],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	22	SENT_20	[p1l765t2087r891b2122],
21	hazard	NN	O	hazard	nn	22	SENT_20	[p1l765t2087r891b2122],
22	ratio	NN	O	ratio	prep_in	15	SENT_20	[p1l904t2087r980b2117],
23	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l993t2086r1041b2117],
24	progression	NN	O	progression	prep_for	22	SENT_20	[p1l1052t2087r1251b2126],
25	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1264t2096r1298b2117],
26	death	NN	O	death	prep_for	22	SENT_20	[p1l1310t2087r1402b2117],
27	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1414t2087r1489b2117],
28	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	prep_with	15	SENT_20	[p1l92t2137r263b2173],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l92t2137r263b2173],
30	0.49	CD	NUMBER	0.49	appos	28	SENT_20	[p1l279t2139r356b2173],
31	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l279t2139r356b2173],
32	95	CD	NUMBER	95	number	33	SENT_20	[p1l371t2139r443b2167],
33	°	CD	NUMBER	°	dep	15	SENT_20	[p1l371t2139r443b2167],
34	/	:	O	/	punct	40	SENT_20	[p1l371t2139r443b2167],
35	o	NN	O	o	nn	40	SENT_20	[p1l371t2139r443b2167],
36	confidence	NN	O	confidence	nn	40	SENT_20	[p1l456t2136r639b2167],
37	interval	NN	O	interval	nn	40	SENT_20	[p1l652t2137r779b2167],
38	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	40	SENT_20	[p1l795t2139r864b2173],
39	CI	NN	O	ci	nn	40	SENT_20	[p1l795t2139r864b2173],
40	]	NN	O	]	dep	33	SENT_20	[p1l795t2139r864b2173],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l795t2139r864b2173],
42	0.37	CD	NUMBER	0.37	appos	40	SENT_20	[p1l879t2139r947b2167],
43	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l961t2143r993b2167],
44	0.64	CD	NUMBER	0.64	prep_to	33	SENT_20	[p1l1007t2139r1086b2173],
45	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1007t2139r1086b2173],
46	P	NN	O	p	dep	47	SENT_20	[p1l1101t2139r1251b2172],
47	<	JJR	O	<	dep	15	SENT_20	[p1l1101t2139r1251b2172],
48	0.001	CD	NUMBER	0.001	num	49	SENT_20	[p1l1101t2139r1251b2172],
49	)	NN	O	)	dep	47	SENT_20	[p1l1101t2139r1251b2172],
50	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1101t2139r1251b2172],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_21	[p1l1266t2137r1328b2167],
2	response	NN	O	response	nn	3	SENT_21	[p1l1341t2146r1489b2175],
3	rates	NNS	O	rate	nsubj	6	SENT_21	[p1l91t2193r170b2217],
4	were	VBD	O	be	cop	6	SENT_21	[p1l182t2197r260b2217],
5	65	CD	NUMBER	65	number	6	SENT_21	[p1l274t2189r345b2217],
6	°	CD	NUMBER	°	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l274t2189r345b2217],
7	/	:	O	/	punct	8	SENT_21	[p1l274t2189r345b2217],
8	o	NN	O	o	dep	6	SENT_21	[p1l274t2189r345b2217],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_21	[p1l359t2189r441b2222],
10	95	CD	NUMBER	95	num	11	SENT_21	[p1l359t2189r441b2222],
11	°	NN	O	°	dep	8	SENT_21	[p1l359t2189r441b2222],
12	/	:	O	/	punct	8	SENT_21	[p1l359t2189r441b2222],
13	o	NN	O	o	nn	14	SENT_21	[p1l359t2189r441b2222],
14	CI	NN	O	ci	dep	8	SENT_21	[p1l454t2189r498b2223],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l454t2189r498b2223],
16	58	CD	NUMBER	58	number	19	SENT_21	[p1l514t2189r552b2217],
17	to	TO	O	to	dep	19	SENT_21	[p1l566t2193r597b2217],
18	72	CD	NUMBER	72	number	19	SENT_21	[p1l611t2189r659b2222],
19	)	CD	NUMBER	)	appos	14	SENT_21	[p1l611t2189r659b2222],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l673t2187r749b2217],
21	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	prep_with	14	SENT_21	[p1l762t2187r933b2224],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l762t2187r933b2224],
23	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l948t2197r981b2217],
24	compared	VBN	O	compare	prepc_as	6	SENT_21	[p1l996t2187r1161b2225],
25	with	IN	O	with	pcomp	24	SENT_21	[p1l1172t2187r1248b2217],
26	20	CD	NUMBER	20	number	27	SENT_21	[p1l1261t2189r1333b2217],
27	°	CD	NUMBER	°	amod	35	SENT_21	[p1l1261t2189r1333b2217],
28	/	:	O	/	punct	29	SENT_21	[p1l1261t2189r1333b2217],
29	o	NN	O	o	dep	27	SENT_21	[p1l1261t2189r1333b2217],
30	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	31	SENT_21	[p1l1348t2189r1430b2222],
31	95	CD	NUMBER	95	dep	29	SENT_21	[p1l1348t2189r1430b2222],
32	°	NN	O	°	dep	31	SENT_21	[p1l1348t2189r1430b2222],
33	/	:	O	/	punct	29	SENT_21	[p1l1348t2189r1430b2222],
34	o	NN	O	o	nn	35	SENT_21	[p1l1348t2189r1430b2222],
35	CI	NN	O	ci	pobj	25	SENT_21	[p1l1443t2189r1487b2224],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1443t2189r1487b2224],

1	14	CD	NUMBER	14	number	4	SENT_22	[p1l93t2308r128b2336],
2	to	TO	O	to	dep	4	SENT_22	[p1l139t2312r170b2336],
3	26	CD	NUMBER	26	number	4	SENT_22	[p1l181t2308r230b2341],
4	)	CD	NUMBER	)	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l181t2308r230b2341],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l241t2306r315b2336],
6	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nn	8	SENT_22	[p1l326t2306r558b2344],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_22	[p1l569t2308r727b2341],
8	P	NN	O	p	prep_with	4	SENT_22	[p1l569t2308r727b2341],
9	<	JJR	O	<	dep	4	SENT_22	[p1l569t2308r727b2341],
10	0.001	CD	NUMBER	0.001	num	11	SENT_22	[p1l569t2308r727b2341],
11	)	NN	O	)	dep	9	SENT_22	[p1l569t2308r727b2341],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l569t2308r727b2341],

1	An	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_23	[p1l739t2308r786b2336],
2	interim	JJ	O	interim	amod	3	SENT_23	[p1l797t2306r918b2336],
3	analysis	NN	O	analysis	nsubj	7	SENT_23	[p1l928t2306r1057b2344],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1068t2305r1107b2336],
5	overall	JJ	O	overall	amod	6	SENT_23	[p1l1110t2306r1219b2336],
6	survival	NN	O	survival	prep_of	3	SENT_23	[p1l1229t2306r1355b2336],
7	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1366t2306r1489b2336],
8	no	DT	O	no	det	10	SENT_23	[p1l91t2365r132b2386],
9	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	amod	10	SENT_23	[p1l145t2355r322b2395],
10	improvement	NN	O	improvement	dobj	7	SENT_23	[p1l332t2356r550b2394],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l558t2356r633b2386],
12	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	prep_with	7	SENT_23	[p1l645t2356r804b2386],
13	as	IN	O	as	prep	7	SENT_23	[p1l816t2366r849b2386],
14	compared	VBN	O	compare	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l862t2356r1025b2394],
15	with	IN	O	with	prepc_compared_with	7	SENT_23	[p1l1035t2356r1109b2386],
16	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nn	19	SENT_23	[p1l1121t2356r1354b2394],
17	(	NN	O	(	nn	19	SENT_23	[p1l1366t2356r1489b2391],
18	hazard	NN	O	hazard	nn	19	SENT_23	[p1l1366t2356r1489b2391],
19	ratio	NN	O	ratio	pobj	7	SENT_23	[p1l91t2406r166b2436],
20	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l179t2405r226b2436],
21	death	NN	O	death	prep_for	19	SENT_23	[p1l237t2406r327b2436],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l339t2406r371b2436],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_23	[p1l384t2406r434b2436],
24	crizotinib	JJ	O	crizotinib	amod	25	SENT_23	[p1l447t2406r606b2436],
25	group	NN	O	group	prep_in	21	SENT_23	[p1l618t2415r723b2445],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l618t2415r723b2445],
27	1.02	CD	NUMBER	1.02	num	29	SENT_23	[p1l738t2408r813b2442],
28	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l738t2408r813b2442],
29	95	CD	NUMBER	95	dep	7	SENT_23	[p1l827t2408r897b2436],
30	°	CD	NUMBER	°	dep	29	SENT_23	[p1l827t2408r897b2436],
31	/	:	O	/	punct	29	SENT_23	[p1l827t2408r897b2436],
32	o	NN	O	o	nn	33	SENT_23	[p1l827t2408r897b2436],
33	CI	NN	O	ci	dep	29	SENT_23	[p1l909t2408r953b2443],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l909t2408r953b2443],
35	0.68	CD	NUMBER	0.68	number	37	SENT_23	[p1l967t2408r1035b2436],
36	to	TO	O	to	dep	37	SENT_23	[p1l1048t2412r1079b2436],
37	1.54	CD	NUMBER	1.54	appos	33	SENT_23	[p1l1093t2408r1169b2442],
38	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1093t2408r1169b2442],
39	P	NN	O	p	dep	33	SENT_23	[p1l1182t2408r1321b2441],
40	=	JJ	O	=	amod	42	SENT_23	[p1l1182t2408r1321b2441],
41	0.54	CD	NUMBER	0.54	tmod	40	SENT_23	[p1l1182t2408r1321b2441],
42	)	NN	O	)	dep	39	SENT_23	[p1l1182t2408r1321b2441],
43	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1182t2408r1321b2441],

1	Common	JJ	O	common	amod	3	SENT_24	[p1l1336t2408r1489b2436],
2	adverse	JJ	O	adverse	amod	3	SENT_24	[p1l91t2525r211b2555],
3	events	NNS	O	event	nsubj	9	SENT_24	[p1l227t2531r327b2555],
4	associated	VBN	O	associate	partmod	3	SENT_24	[p1l343t2525r512b2555],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l526t2525r600b2555],
6	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	prep_with	4	SENT_24	[p1l616t2525r775b2555],
7	were	VBD	O	be	cop	9	SENT_24	[p1l790t2535r867b2555],
8	visual	JJ	O	visual	amod	9	SENT_24	[p1l881t2525r976b2555],
9	disorder	NN	O	disorder	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l992t2525r1135b2562],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l992t2525r1135b2562],
11	gastrointestinal	JJ	O	gastrointestinal	amod	13	SENT_24	[p1l1152t2525r1410b2564],
12	side	JJ	O	side	amod	13	SENT_24	[p1l1427t2525r1489b2555],
13	effects	NNS	O	effect	conj_and	9	SENT_24	[p1l92t2574r210b2612],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l92t2574r210b2612],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l224t2575r285b2605],
16	elevated	JJ	O	elevated	amod	19	SENT_24	[p1l298t2575r431b2606],
17	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	19	SENT_24	[p1l442t2575r514b2606],
18	aminotransferase	NN	O	aminotransferase	nn	19	SENT_24	[p1l524t2574r818b2605],
19	levels	NNS	O	level	conj_and	9	SENT_24	[p1l830t2575r929b2612],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l830t2575r929b2612],
21	whereas	IN	O	whereas	mark	28	SENT_24	[p1l942t2575r1078b2606],
22	common	JJ	O	common	amod	24	SENT_24	[p1l1091t2585r1239b2605],
23	adverse	JJ	O	adverse	amod	24	SENT_24	[p1l1251t2575r1373b2606],
24	events	NNS	O	event	nsubj	28	SENT_24	[p1l1386t2581r1488b2606],
25	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l90t2625r166b2656],
26	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_with	24	SENT_24	[p1l181t2625r418b2664],
27	were	VBD	O	be	cop	28	SENT_24	[p1l430t2635r509b2656],
28	fatigue	NN	O	fatigue	advcl	9	SENT_24	[p1l524t2625r648b2664],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l524t2625r648b2664],
30	alopecia	NN	O	alopecia	advcl	9	SENT_24	[p1l666t2625r812b2664],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l666t2625r812b2664],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l830t2625r891b2656],
33	dyspnea	NN	O	dyspnea	conj_and	28	SENT_24	[p1l907t2625r1049b2664],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l907t2625r1049b2664],

1	Patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	2	SENT_25	[p1l1066t2625r1198b2655],
2	reported	VBD	O	report	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1215t2625r1357b2664],
3	greater	JJR	O	greater	amod	4	SENT_25	[p1l1372t2631r1490b2664],
4	reductions	NNS	O	reduction	dobj	2	SENT_25	[p1l91t2675r266b2706],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l281t2675r313b2705],
6	symptoms	NNS	O	symptom	prep_in	2	SENT_25	[p1l328t2681r500b2714],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l515t2675r554b2706],
8	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	9	SENT_25	[p1l561t2675r636b2714],
9	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	6	SENT_25	[p1l649t2685r758b2706],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l770t2675r832b2706],
11	greater	JJR	O	greater	amod	12	SENT_25	[p1l846t2681r964b2714],
12	improvement	NN	O	improvement	prep_in	2	SENT_25	[p1l977t2675r1199b2714],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1211t2675r1244b2705],
14	global	JJ	O	global	amod	15	SENT_25	[p1l1258t2675r1361b2714],
15	quality	NN	O	quality	prep_in	12	SENT_25	[p1l1376t2675r1491b2714],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l92t2725r131b2756],
17	life	NN	O	life	prep_of	15	SENT_25	[p1l136t2725r189b2756],
18	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l201t2725r277b2756],
19	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	prep_with	17	SENT_25	[p1l290t2725r453b2756],
20	than	IN	O	than	prep	2	SENT_25	[p1l467t2725r543b2756],
21	with	IN	O	with	pcomp	20	SENT_25	[p1l555t2725r631b2756],
22	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	pobj	21	SENT_25	[p1l644t2725r886b2764],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l644t2725r886b2764],

1	CONCLUSIONS	NNS	O	conclusion	nsubj	14	SENT_26	[p1l92t2822r318b2841],
2	Crizotinib	NNP	O	Crizotinib	nsubj	4	SENT_26	[p1l92t2865r262b2895],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	4	SENT_26	[p1l273t2865r299b2895],
4	superior	JJ	O	superior	parataxis	14	SENT_26	[p1l312t2865r449b2904],
5	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l460t2871r492b2895],
6	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	7	SENT_26	[p1l504t2865r651b2895],
7	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_to	4	SENT_26	[p1l663t2865r900b2904],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l909t2865r942b2895],
9	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	7	SENT_26	[p1l952t2865r1085b2904],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1096t2865r1171b2895],
11	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	12	SENT_26	[p1l1182t2865r1353b2904],
12	treated	VBN	O	treat	prepc_with	4	SENT_26	[p1l1363t2865r1487b2902],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1363t2865r1487b2902],
14	advanced	VBD	O	advance	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l91t2915r245b2945],
15	non	JJ	O	non	amod	21	SENT_26	[p1l260t2915r509b2945],
16	—	JJ	O	—	amod	17	SENT_26	[p1l260t2915r509b2945],
17	small	JJ	O	small	amod	21	SENT_26	[p1l260t2915r509b2945],
18	—	NN	O	—	nn	21	SENT_26	[p1l260t2915r509b2945],
19	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	21	SENT_26	[p1l260t2915r509b2945],
20	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	21	SENT_26	[p1l524t2915r599b2954],
21	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dobj	14	SENT_26	[p1l613t2925r722b2945],
22	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l734t2915r810b2945],
23	ALK	NN	O	alk	nn	24	SENT_26	[p1l822t2917r890b2945],
24	rearrangement	NN	O	rearrangement	prep_with	21	SENT_26	[p1l902t2921r1159b2954],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l902t2921r1159b2954],

1	(	NN	O	(	nsubj	2	SENT_27	[p1l1178t2915r1313b2950],
2	Funded	VBN	O	fund	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1178t2915r1313b2950],
3	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1328t2915r1366b2953],
4	Pfizer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pfizer	prep_by	2	SENT_27	[p1l1379t2914r1488b2951],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1379t2914r1488b2951],
6	ClinicalTrials	NNP	O	ClinicalTrials	dep	4	SENT_27	[p1l91t2965r387b3004],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l91t2965r387b3004],

1	gov	NN	O	gov	nn	2	SENT_28	[p1l91t2965r387b3004],
2	number	NN	O	number	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l399t2965r537b3002],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l399t2965r537b3002],
4	NCT00932893	NN	O	nct00932893	appos	2	SENT_28	[p1l551t2967r809b3000],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l551t2967r809b3000],
6	)	SYM	O	)	dep	2	SENT_28	[p1l551t2967r809b3000],

1	NENGi_JMED368	NN	O	nengi_jmed368	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l476t3068r738b3096],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l476t3068r738b3096],
3	25	CD	NUMBER	25	num	5	SENT_29	[p1l476t3068r738b3096],
4	NEJM.ORG	NN	O	nejm.org	nn	5	SENT_29	[p1l773t3074r897b3096],
5	jUNE20	NN	O	june20	dep	1	SENT_29	[p1l928t3074r1106b3096],
6	,2013	CD	NUMBER	,2013	dep	5	SENT_29	[p1l928t3074r1106b3096],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_30	[p1l750t3131r801b3155],
2	New	NNP	O	New	nn	5	SENT_30	[p1l810t3132r872b3155],
3	England	NNP	O	England	nn	5	SENT_30	[p1l881t3131r992b3162],
4	J	NNP	O	J	nn	5	SENT_30	[p1l1000t3132r1013b3155],
5	oumal	NN	O	oumal	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1014t3131r1098b3155],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1107t3131r1136b3155],
7	Medicine	NN	O	medicine	prep_of	5	SENT_30	[p1l1143t3131r1268b3155],

1	From	IN	O	from	dep	22	SENT_31	[p1l1531t1010r1592b1031],
2	Massachusetts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Massachusetts	nn	4	SENT_31	[p1l1624t1008r1807b1032],
3	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	General	nn	4	SENT_31	[p1l1836t1008r1930b1032],
4	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	pobj	1	SENT_31	[p1l1961t1008r2063b1039],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_31	[p1l1532t1047r1615b1076],
6	A.T.S.	NNP	O	A.T.S.	nn	7	SENT_31	[p1l1532t1047r1615b1076],
7	)	NN	O	)	dep	4	SENT_31	[p1l1532t1047r1615b1076],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1630t1045r1673b1069],
9	Lowe	NNP	PERSON	Lowe	nn	10	SENT_31	[p1l1689t1048r1751b1069],
10	Center	NNP	PERSON	Center	conj_and	4	SENT_31	[p1l1763t1047r1844b1069],
11	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1855t1045r1889b1069],
12	Thoracic	NNP	O	Thoracic	nn	13	SENT_31	[p1l1899t1045r2006b1069],
13	Oncology	NNP	O	Oncology	prep_for	10	SENT_31	[p1l2018t1047r2064b1069, p1l1529t1082r1609b1114],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1618t1082r1661b1106],
15	Belfer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Belfer	nn	16	SENT_31	[p1l1674t1082r1743b1106],
16	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	conj_and	4	SENT_31	[p1l1754t1085r1853b1106],
17	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1862t1082r1896b1106],
18	Applied	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Applied	nn	20	SENT_31	[p1l1904t1082r1998b1114],
19	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	20	SENT_31	[p1l2009t1084r2064b1106, p1l1529t1130r1566b1146],
20	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	prep_for	16	SENT_31	[p1l1578t1124r1677b1150],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1578t1124r1677b1150],
22	Dana	NNP	PERSON	Dana	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1693t1122r1853b1146],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1693t1122r1853b1146],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1693t1122r1853b1146],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1693t1122r1853b1146],

1	Farber	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Farber	nn	8	SENT_33	[p1l1693t1122r1853b1146],
2	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	8	SENT_33	[p1l1865t1124r1951b1146],
3	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	nn	8	SENT_33	[p1l1965t1124r2064b1146],
4	(	NNP	O	(	nn	8	SENT_33	[p1l1532t1161r1617b1191],
5	P.A.j.	NNP	O	P.A.j.	nn	8	SENT_33	[p1l1532t1161r1617b1191],
6	)	NNP	O	)	nn	8	SENT_33	[p1l1532t1161r1617b1191],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1532t1161r1617b1191],
8	Boston	NNP	LOCATION	Boston	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1634t1162r1726b1188],
9	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1634t1162r1726b1188],
10	Seoul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Seoul	nn	13	SENT_33	[p1l1741t1160r1807b1184],
11	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	13	SENT_33	[p1l1824t1160r1926b1184],
12	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	13	SENT_33	[p1l1943t1162r2065b1191],
13	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	conj_and	8	SENT_33	[p1l1531t1197r1632b1228],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_33	[p1l1645t1199r1752b1228],
15	D.-W.K.	NNP	O	D.-W.K.	nn	16	SENT_33	[p1l1645t1199r1752b1228],
16	)	NN	O	)	dep	8	SENT_33	[p1l1645t1199r1752b1228],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1763t1197r1807b1221],
18	Sungkyunkwan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sungkyunkwan	nn	20	SENT_33	[p1l1817t1197r2003b1229],
19	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	20	SENT_33	[p1l2014t1200r2064b1221, p1l1528t1237r1608b1266],
20	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	conj_and	8	SENT_33	[p1l1616t1235r1698b1259],
21	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1708t1235r1735b1259],
22	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	prep_of	20	SENT_33	[p1l1741t1235r1859b1263],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1741t1235r1859b1263],
24	Samsung	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Samsung	nn	28	SENT_33	[p1l1870t1237r1985b1266],
25	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	28	SENT_33	[p1l1995t1235r2064b1258, p1l1529t1272r1561b1296],
26	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	nn	28	SENT_33	[p1l1580t1274r1661b1296],
27	(	NNP	O	(	nn	28	SENT_33	[p1l1680t1274r1786b1303],
28	M.	NNP	O	M.	conj_and	8	SENT_33	[p1l1680t1274r1786b1303],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1680t1274r1786b1303],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l1680t1274r1786b1303],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l1680t1274r1786b1303],

1	J.A.	NNP	PERSON	J.A.	nn	7	SENT_35	[p1l1680t1274r1786b1303],
2	)	NNP	O	)	nn	7	SENT_35	[p1l1680t1274r1786b1303],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1680t1274r1786b1303],
4	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	appos	7	SENT_35	[p1l1805t1272r1879b1300],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1805t1272r1879b1300],
6	South	NNP	LOCATION	South	appos	7	SENT_35	[p1l1898t1272r1969b1296],
7	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1990t1275r2063b1300],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1990t1275r2063b1300],
9	Kinki	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kinki	nn	12	SENT_35	[p1l1531t1310r1588b1333],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	12	SENT_35	[p1l1598t1312r1720b1341],
11	Faculty	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Faculty	nn	12	SENT_35	[p1l1729t1310r1813b1341],
12	ofMedicine	NNP	O	ofMedicine	dep	7	SENT_35	[p1l1820t1310r1970b1338],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1820t1310r1970b1338],
14	Osakasayama	NNP	LOCATION	Osakasayama	nn	15	SENT_35	[p1l1979t1310r2064b1334, p1l1530t1356r1620b1378],
15	City	NNP	LOCATION	City	dep	7	SENT_35	[p1l1629t1349r1680b1378],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1629t1349r1680b1378],
17	Osaka	NNP	LOCATION	Osaka	nn	20	SENT_35	[p1l1689t1347r1766b1371],
18	(	NNP	O	(	nn	20	SENT_35	[p1l1777t1349r1853b1378],
19	K.N.	NNP	LOCATION	K.N.	nn	20	SENT_35	[p1l1777t1349r1853b1378],
20	)	NNP	O	)	dep	7	SENT_35	[p1l1777t1349r1853b1378],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1777t1349r1853b1378],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1863t1347r1907b1371],
23	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	26	SENT_35	[p1l1918t1347r2020b1371],
24	Kyushu	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kyushu	nn	26	SENT_35	[p1l2031t1350r2064b1378, p1l1530t1385r1588b1409],
25	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	26	SENT_35	[p1l1597t1387r1683b1409],
26	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	7	SENT_35	[p1l1691t1387r1776b1413],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1691t1387r1776b1413],
28	Fukuoka	NNP	LOCATION	Fukuoka	dep	7	SENT_35	[p1l1787t1385r1888b1409],
29	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	28	SENT_35	[p1l1900t1387r1960b1416],
30	T.S.	NNP	O	T.S.	dep	28	SENT_35	[p1l1900t1387r1960b1416],
31	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	32	SENT_35	[p1l1900t1387r1960b1416],
32	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	30	SENT_35	[p1l1969t1400r2001b1402],
33	both	DT	O	both	dep	32	SENT_35	[p1l2009t1385r2063b1409],
34	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1530t1425r1549b1446],
35	japan	NN	LOCATION	japan	prep_in	32	SENT_35	[p1l1558t1425r1636b1454],
36	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1558t1425r1636b1454],
37	Azienda	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Azienda	nn	39	SENT_35	[p1l1648t1423r1747b1446],
38	Ospedale	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ospedale	nn	39	SENT_35	[p1l1760t1423r1877b1454],
39	Perugia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Perugia	dep	7	SENT_35	[p1l1891t1425r1987b1454],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1891t1425r1987b1454],
41	Perugia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Perugia	appos	39	SENT_35	[p1l2002t1425r2064b1447, p1l1529t1463r1563b1491],
42	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	41	SENT_35	[p1l1576t1462r1645b1491],
43	L.C.	NNP	O	L.C.	dep	41	SENT_35	[p1l1576t1462r1645b1491],
44	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	43	SENT_35	[p1l1576t1462r1645b1491],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1576t1462r1645b1491],
46	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1657t1460r1700b1484],
47	European	NNP	ORGANIZATION	European	nn	48	SENT_35	[p1l1713t1463r1827b1491],
48	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	12	SENT_35	[p1l1840t1463r1940b1484],
49	ofOncology	NN	O	ofoncology	nn	52	SENT_35	[p1l1949t1460r2064b1484, p1l1529t1506r1573b1529],
50	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	52	SENT_35	[p1l1583t1500r1668b1529],
51	T.D.P.	NN	O	t.d.p.	nn	52	SENT_35	[p1l1583t1500r1668b1529],
52	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	12	SENT_35	[p1l1583t1500r1668b1529],
53	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1679t1498r1723b1521],
54	Pfizer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pfizer	nn	55	SENT_35	[p1l1734t1498r1804b1521],
55	Italia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Italia	conj_and	52	SENT_35	[p1l1813t1498r1869b1521],
56	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	57	SENT_35	[p1l1880t1499r1949b1529],
57	A.P.	NNP	O	A.P.	dep	55	SENT_35	[p1l1880t1499r1949b1529],
58	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	57	SENT_35	[p1l1880t1499r1949b1529],
59	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1880t1499r1949b1529],
60	Milan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Milan	conj_and	52	SENT_35	[p1l1960t1498r2026b1521],
61	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	60	SENT_35	[p1l2034t1512r2065b1515],
62	all	DT	O	all	advmod	60	SENT_35	[p1l1529t1535r1554b1558],
63	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1566t1537r1586b1558],
64	Italy	NNP	LOCATION	Italy	prep_in	60	SENT_35	[p1l1599t1535r1653b1566],
65	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1599t1535r1653b1566],
66	Institut	NNP	PERSON	Institut	nn	68	SENT_35	[p1l1666t1537r1752b1559],
67	Gustave	NNP	PERSON	Gustave	nn	68	SENT_35	[p1l1762t1537r1862b1559],
68	Roussy	NNP	PERSON	Roussy	conj_and	12	SENT_35	[p1l1874t1537r1964b1566],
69	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1874t1537r1964b1566],
70	Villejuif	NNP	LOCATION	Villejuif	nn	73	SENT_35	[p1l1974t1535r2069b1566],
71	(	NNP	O	(	nn	73	SENT_35	[p1l1532t1574r1603b1603],
72	B.B.	NNP	PERSON	B.B.	nn	73	SENT_35	[p1l1532t1574r1603b1603],
73	)	NNP	O	)	appos	68	SENT_35	[p1l1532t1574r1603b1603],
74	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1532t1574r1603b1603],
75	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1615t1572r1659b1596],
76	Thoracic	NNP	O	Thoracic	nn	78	SENT_35	[p1l1669t1572r1776b1596],
77	Oncology	NNP	O	Oncology	nn	78	SENT_35	[p1l1785t1572r1905b1603],
78	Unit	NNP	O	Unit	conj_and	12	SENT_35	[p1l1916t1575r1973b1600],
79	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1916t1575r1973b1600],
80	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	nn	83	SENT_35	[p1l1984t1574r2064b1596],
81	Hospitalier	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospitalier	nn	83	SENT_35	[p1l1531t1610r1666b1641],
82	Universitaire	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universitaire	nn	83	SENT_35	[p1l1679t1612r1832b1634],
83	Grenoble	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Grenoble	appos	78	SENT_35	[p1l1845t1610r1965b1638],
84	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1845t1610r1965b1638],
85	Grenoble	NNP	LOCATION	Grenoble	nn	87	SENT_35	[p1l1979t1612r2064b1634, p1l1530t1647r1565b1671],
86	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	87	SENT_35	[p1l1577t1649r1684b1678],
87	D.M.-S	NN	O	d.m.-s	appos	78	SENT_35	[p1l1577t1649r1684b1678],
88	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1577t1649r1684b1678],
89	)	SYM	O	)	dep	7	SENT_35	[p1l1577t1649r1684b1678],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1695t1662r1727b1664],
2	both	CC	O	both	dep	3	SENT_36	[p1l1737t1647r1790b1671],
3	in	IN	O	in	dep	1	SENT_36	[p1l1803t1650r1822b1671],
4	France	NNP	LOCATION	France	pobj	3	SENT_36	[p1l1835t1650r1921b1675],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1835t1650r1921b1675],
6	Peter	NNP	PERSON	Peter	nn	7	SENT_36	[p1l1934t1650r1995b1671],
7	MacCallum	NNP	PERSON	MacCallum	dep	1	SENT_36	[p1l2007t1650r2064b1671, p1l1529t1754r1614b1778],

1	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1636t1756r1722b1778],
2	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	nn	10	SENT_37	[p1l1742t1756r1828b1782],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1742t1756r1828b1782],
4	Melbourne	NNP	LOCATION	Melbourne	appos	10	SENT_37	[p1l1852t1754r1991b1782],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1852t1754r1991b1782],
6	VIC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	VIC	appos	10	SENT_37	[p1l2012t1756r2063b1782],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l2012t1756r2063b1782],
8	Australia	NNP	LOCATION	Australia	appos	10	SENT_37	[p1l1528t1791r1636b1815],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_37	[p1l1653t1793r1740b1823],
10	B.J.S.	NNP	O	B.J.S.	dep	1	SENT_37	[p1l1653t1793r1740b1823],
11	)	NN	O	)	dep	10	SENT_37	[p1l1653t1793r1740b1823],
12	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1653t1793r1740b1823],
13	Christie	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Christie	nn	23	SENT_37	[p1l1755t1791r1848b1815],
14	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	23	SENT_37	[p1l1864t1791r1966b1815],
15	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	23	SENT_37	[p1l1984t1791r2063b1815],
16	Service	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Service	nn	23	SENT_37	[p1l1529t1831r1617b1853],
17	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Foundation	nn	23	SENT_37	[p1l1647t1829r1785b1853],
18	Trust	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Trust	nn	23	SENT_37	[p1l1813t1831r1882b1857],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1813t1831r1882b1857],
20	Manchester	NNP	LOCATION	Manchester	appos	23	SENT_37	[p1l1914t1829r2063b1857],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1914t1829r2063b1857],
22	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	appos	23	SENT_37	[p1l1530t1867r1610b1891],
23	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	dep	10	SENT_37	[p1l1629t1867r1738b1898],
24	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	23	SENT_37	[p1l1758t1869r1825b1898],
25	F.B.	NNP	LOCATION	F.B.	dep	23	SENT_37	[p1l1758t1869r1825b1898],
26	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	25	SENT_37	[p1l1758t1869r1825b1898],
27	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1758t1869r1825b1898],
28	Guangdong	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Guangdong	nn	31	SENT_37	[p1l1842t1867r1988b1898],
29	Lung	NN	ORGANIZATION	lung	nn	31	SENT_37	[p1l2005t1869r2065b1898],
30	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	31	SENT_37	[p1l1529t1906r1615b1928],
31	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	10	SENT_37	[p1l1626t1906r1731b1932],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1626t1906r1731b1932],
33	Guangdong	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Guangdong	nn	41	SENT_37	[p1l1743t1904r1889b1935],
34	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	General	nn	41	SENT_37	[p1l1899t1904r1994b1928],
35	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	nn	41	SENT_37	[p1l2007t1906r2064b1928, p1l1530t1942r1587b1973],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l2007t1906r2064b1928, p1l1530t1942r1587b1973],
37	Guangzhou	NNP	LOCATION	Guangzhou	appos	41	SENT_37	[p1l1611t1942r1761b1973],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1611t1942r1761b1973],
39	China	NNP	LOCATION	China	appos	41	SENT_37	[p1l1784t1942r1854b1965],
40	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	41	SENT_37	[p1l1879t1944r1985b1973],
41	Y.-L.W.	NNP	O	Y.-L.W.	appos	31	SENT_37	[p1l1879t1944r1985b1973],
42	)	NN	O	)	dep	41	SENT_37	[p1l1879t1944r1985b1973],
43	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1879t1944r1985b1973],
44	Thoraxklinik	NNP	O	Thoraxklinik	nn	47	SENT_37	[p1l2007t1942r2064b1965, p1l1530t1973r1629b1996],
45	im	NNP	O	im	nn	47	SENT_37	[p1l1650t1975r1679b1996],
46	Universitatsklinikum	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universitatsklinikum	nn	47	SENT_37	[p1l1702t1973r1953b1997],
47	Heidelberg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heidelberg	dep	10	SENT_37	[p1l1977t1973r2064b1997, p1l1530t2010r1589b2041],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1977t1973r2064b1997, p1l1530t2010r1589b2041],
49	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1615t2010r1659b2034],
50	Translational	JJ	ORGANIZATION	translational	amod	56	SENT_37	[p1l1684t2010r1841b2034],
51	Lung	NN	ORGANIZATION	lung	nn	56	SENT_37	[p1l1869t2013r1929b2042],
52	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	56	SENT_37	[p1l1955t2010r2063b2034],
53	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	nn	56	SENT_37	[p1l1529t2050r1610b2072],
54	Heidelberg	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heidelberg	nn	56	SENT_37	[p1l1631t2048r1766b2079],
55	(	NNP	O	(	nn	56	SENT_37	[p1l1788t2048r1903b2079],
56	Member	NNP	O	Member	dep	10	SENT_37	[p1l1788t2048r1903b2079],
57	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1921t2048r1948b2072],
58	German	NNP	O	German	nn	59	SENT_37	[p1l1964t2050r2063b2071],
59	Center	NNP	O	Center	prep_of	56	SENT_37	[p1l1529t2087r1610b2109],
60	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1616t2085r1651b2109],
61	Lung	NN	ORGANIZATION	lung	nn	63	SENT_37	[p1l1660t2088r1720b2116],
62	Research	NN	ORGANIZATION	research	nn	63	SENT_37	[p1l1729t2085r1852b2116],
63	)	NN	O	)	prep_for	59	SENT_37	[p1l1729t2085r1852b2116],
64	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1729t2085r1852b2116],
65	Heidelberg	NNP	LOCATION	Heidelberg	nn	70	SENT_37	[p1l1863t2085r2004b2116],
66	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1863t2085r2004b2116],
67	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	appos	70	SENT_37	[p1l2013t2087r2064b2109, p1l1530t2131r1596b2154],
68	(	NNP	O	(	nn	70	SENT_37	[p1l1610t2125r1685b2154],
69	M.T.	NNP	LOCATION	M.T.	nn	70	SENT_37	[p1l1610t2125r1685b2154],
70	)	NNP	O	)	appos	63	SENT_37	[p1l1610t2125r1685b2154],
71	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1610t2125r1685b2154],
72	ICORG	NNP	LOCATION	ICORG	dep	10	SENT_37	[p1l1699t2125r1790b2151],
73	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1699t2125r1790b2151],
74	the	DT	O	the	det	80	SENT_37	[p1l1802t2123r1841b2147],
75	All	NNP	ORGANIZATION	All	nn	80	SENT_37	[p1l1851t2123r1881b2146],
76	Ireland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ireland	nn	80	SENT_37	[p1l1896t2123r1977b2146],
77	Cooperative	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cooperative	nn	80	SENT_37	[p1l1990t2125r2064b2154, p1l1529t2163r1609b2184],
78	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	nn	80	SENT_37	[p1l1624t2160r1743b2192],
79	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	80	SENT_37	[p1l1759t2160r1867b2184],
80	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	appos	72	SENT_37	[p1l1883t2162r1966b2191],
81	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1883t2162r1966b2191],
82	Dublin	NNP	LOCATION	Dublin	appos	72	SENT_37	[p1l1984t2160r2063b2184],
83	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	85	SENT_37	[p1l1532t2200r1631b2229],
84	K.J.O.	NNP	O	K.J.O.	nn	85	SENT_37	[p1l1532t2200r1631b2229],
85	)	NN	O	)	dep	82	SENT_37	[p1l1532t2200r1631b2229],
86	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1532t2200r1631b2229],
87	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	10	SENT_37	[p1l1649t2200r1779b2229],
88	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1795t2198r1823b2221],
89	Colorado	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Colorado	nn	91	SENT_37	[p1l1834t2198r1960b2226],
90	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1834t2198r1960b2226],
91	Aurora	NNP	LOCATION	Aurora	prep_of	87	SENT_37	[p1l1976t2199r2064b2222],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	3	SENT_38	[p1l1532t2306r1632b2335],
2	D.R.C.	NN	O	d.r.c.	nn	3	SENT_38	[p1l1532t2306r1632b2335],
3	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1532t2306r1632b2335],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1532t2306r1632b2335],
5	Chinese	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chinese	nn	6	SENT_38	[p1l1643t2304r1740b2328],
6	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	3	SENT_38	[p1l1752t2307r1874b2335],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1883t2304r1910b2328],
8	Hong	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hong	nn	9	SENT_38	[p1l1917t2307r1985b2336],
9	Kong	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kong	prep_of	6	SENT_38	[p1l1996t2306r2063b2335],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1996t2306r2063b2335],
11	Shatin	NNP	LOCATION	Shatin	nn	16	SENT_38	[p1l1529t2342r1612b2370],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1529t2342r1612b2370],
13	China	NNP	LOCATION	China	appos	16	SENT_38	[p1l1637t2342r1707b2365],
14	(	NNP	O	(	nn	16	SENT_38	[p1l1734t2344r1812b2373],
15	T.M.	NNP	LOCATION	T.M.	nn	16	SENT_38	[p1l1734t2344r1812b2373],
16	)	NNP	O	)	appos	9	SENT_38	[p1l1734t2344r1812b2373],
17	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1734t2344r1812b2373],
18	McGill	NNP	ORGANIZATION	McGill	nn	21	SENT_38	[p1l1839t2342r1916b2366],
19	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	21	SENT_38	[p1l1943t2344r2065b2373],
20	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	21	SENT_38	[p1l1531t2379r1610b2403],
21	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	dep	6	SENT_38	[p1l1625t2381r1711b2407],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1625t2381r1711b2407],
23	Montreal	NNP	LOCATION	Montreal	nn	26	SENT_38	[p1l1728t2379r1836b2403],
24	(	NNP	O	(	nn	26	SENT_38	[p1l1854t2381r1930b2410],
25	V.H.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	V.H.	nn	26	SENT_38	[p1l1854t2381r1930b2410],
26	)	NNP	O	)	appos	21	SENT_38	[p1l1854t2381r1930b2410],
27	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1854t2381r1930b2410],
28	Memorial	NNP	O	Memorial	nn	31	SENT_38	[p1l1946t2379r2063b2403],
29	Sloan-Kettering	NNP	O	Sloan-Kettering	nn	31	SENT_38	[p1l1529t2417r1720b2448],
30	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	nn	31	SENT_38	[p1l1731t2419r1816b2441],
31	Center	NNP	O	Center	dep	6	SENT_38	[p1l1827t2419r1908b2441],
32	(	NNP	O	(	nn	36	SENT_38	[p1l1921t2419r2005b2448],
33	G.	NNP	O	G.	nn	36	SENT_38	[p1l1921t2419r2005b2448],
34	_	NNP	O	_	nn	36	SENT_38	[p1l1921t2419r2005b2448],
35	l.R.	NNP	O	l.R.	nn	36	SENT_38	[p1l1921t2419r2005b2448],
36	)	NNP	O	)	tmod	31	SENT_38	[p1l1921t2419r2005b2448],
37	and	CC	O	and	advmod	36	SENT_38	[p1l2019t2417r2063b2441],

1	Pfizer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pfizer	nn	5	SENT_39	[p1l1531t2523r1600b2547],
2	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	nn	5	SENT_39	[p1l1608t2523r1727b2555],
3	(	NNP	O	(	nn	5	SENT_39	[p1l1737t2525r1798b2554],
4	S.	NNP	O	S.	nn	5	SENT_39	[p1l1737t2525r1798b2554],
5	|	NNP	O	|	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1737t2525r1798b2554],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1737t2525r1798b2554],
7	)	NN	O	)	dep	5	SENT_39	[p1l1737t2525r1798b2554],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l1737t2525r1798b2554],
2	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	3	SENT_40	[p1l1809t2526r1864b2547],
3	York	NNP	LOCATION	York	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l1871t2523r1931b2551],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l1871t2523r1931b2551],
5	and	CC	O	and	dep	7	SENT_40	[p1l1941t2523r1984b2547],
6	Pfizer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pfizer	nn	7	SENT_40	[p1l1996t2523r2065b2547],
7	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	dep	3	SENT_40	[p1l1529t2561r1653b2592],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l1529t2561r1653b2592],
9	La	NNP	PERSON	La	nn	10	SENT_40	[p1l1671t2563r1696b2585],
10	Jolla	NNP	PERSON	Jolla	appos	7	SENT_40	[p1l1707t2561r1769b2591],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l1707t2561r1769b2591],
12	CA	NNP	LOCATION	CA	nn	14	SENT_40	[p1l1785t2563r1821b2585],
13	(	NNP	O	(	nn	14	SENT_40	[p1l1838t2563r1894b2592],
14	V.T.	NNP	O	V.T.	appos	7	SENT_40	[p1l1838t2563r1894b2592],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l1838t2563r1894b2592],
16	K.D.W.	NNP	O	K.D.W.	appos	7	SENT_40	[p1l1912t2563r2007b2592],
17	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	16	SENT_40	[p1l1912t2563r2007b2592],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l1912t2563r2007b2592],

1	Address	NN	O	address	nsubj	2	SENT_41	[p1l2022t2561r2064b2585, p1l1529t2599r1593b2622],
2	reprint	VB	O	reprint	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1606t2601r1687b2630],
3	requests	NNS	O	request	dobj	2	SENT_41	[p1l1699t2603r1802b2630],
4	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1813t2603r1837b2622],
5	Dr.	NNP	O	Dr.	nn	6	SENT_41	[p1l1850t2601r1883b2622],
6	Shaw	NNP	PERSON	Shaw	prep_to	2	SENT_41	[p1l1895t2599r1961b2622],
7	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1971t2603r1993b2622],
8	Massachusetts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Massachusetts	nn	12	SENT_41	[p1l2005t2601r2064b2622, p1l1530t2636r1660b2660],
9	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	General	nn	12	SENT_41	[p1l1669t2636r1763b2660],
10	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	nn	12	SENT_41	[p1l1775t2636r1876b2667],
11	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	12	SENT_41	[p1l1885t2638r1971b2660],
12	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	prep_at	6	SENT_41	[p1l1978t2638r2063b2664],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1978t2638r2063b2664],
14	Yawkey	NNP	O	Yawkey	nn	15	SENT_41	[p1l1528t2674r1617b2705],
15	7B	NN	O	7b	prep_at	6	SENT_41	[p1l1628t2676r1664b2702],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1628t2676r1664b2702],
17	32	CD	NUMBER	32	num	19	SENT_41	[p1l1676t2676r1703b2697],
18	Fruit	NNP	O	Fruit	nn	19	SENT_41	[p1l1715t2676r1770b2698],
19	St.	NNP	O	St.	prep_at	6	SENT_41	[p1l1780t2676r1816b2702],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1780t2676r1816b2702],
21	Boston	NNP	LOCATION	Boston	prep_at	6	SENT_41	[p1l1830t2676r1921b2702],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1830t2676r1921b2702],
23	MA	NNP	LOCATION	MA	prep_at	6	SENT_41	[p1l1935t2675r1977b2697],
24	02114	CD	DATE	02114	num	23	SENT_41	[p1l1986t2675r2063b2702],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1986t2675r2063b2702],
26	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1529t2720r1554b2735],
27	at	IN	O	at	advmod	12	SENT_41	[p1l1561t2716r1583b2735],
28	ashaw1@partners.org	NN	O	ashaw1@partners.org	prep_at	6	SENT_41	[p1l1590t2711r1868b2743],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1590t2711r1868b2743],

1	Drs.	NNP	O	Drs.	nn	2	SENT_42	[p1l1531t2764r1582b2785],
2	Shaw	NNP	PERSON	Shaw	nsubj	5	SENT_42	[p1l1592t2762r1660b2786],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l1667t2762r1713b2785],
4	Kim	NNP	PERSON	Kim	nsubj	5	SENT_42	[p1l1725t2764r1772b2785],
5	contributed	VBD	O	contribute	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l1781t2762r1932b2786],
6	equally	RB	O	equally	advmod	5	SENT_42	[p1l1941t2762r2032b2793],
7	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l2039t2766r2064b2785],
8	this	DT	O	this	det	9	SENT_42	[p1l1528t2799r1575b2823],
9	article	NN	O	article	prep_to	5	SENT_42	[p1l1585t2799r1672b2823],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l1585t2799r1672b2823],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_43	[p1l1528t2849r1582b2873],
2	article	NN	O	article	nsubjpass	4	SENT_43	[p1l1602t2849r1682b2873],
3	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_43	[p1l1700t2857r1749b2873],
4	published	VBN	O	publish	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1770t2849r1896b2880],
5	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1916t2857r1947b2873],
6	June	NNP	DATE	June	prep_on	4	SENT_43	[p1l1963t2851r2024b2879],
7	1	CD	DATE	1	num	6	SENT_43	[p1l2045t2851r2063b2877],
8	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l2045t2851r2063b2877],
9	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	6	SENT_43	[p1l1529t2888r1596b2914],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1529t2888r1596b2914],
11	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1607t2891r1629b2910],
12	NEJM.org	NN	O	nejm.org	prep_at	4	SENT_43	[p1l1640t2889r1772b2917],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1640t2889r1772b2917],

1	N	NN	MISC	n	nn	3	SENT_44	[p1l1530t2940r1547b2960],
2	Englj	NNP	MISC	Englj	nn	3	SENT_44	[p1l1558t2938r1620b2967],
3	Med	NNP	O	Med	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l1631t2938r1681b2960],
4	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	3	SENT_44	[p1l1689t2939r1902b2964],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l1689t2939r1902b2964],
6	368:2385	CD	NUMBER	368:2385	number	7	SENT_44	[p1l1689t2939r1902b2964],
7	-94	CD	NUMBER	-94	dep	3	SENT_44	[p1l1689t2939r1902b2964],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l1689t2939r1902b2964],

1	DOI	NNP	O	DOI	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1530t2977r1585b2997],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1530t2977r1585b2997],
3	10.1056	CD	NUMBER	10.1056	dep	1	SENT_45	[p1l1594t2977r1713b3004],
4	/	:	O	/	punct	6	SENT_45	[p1l1594t2977r1713b3004],
5	N	NN	O	n	nn	6	SENT_45	[p1l1594t2977r1713b3004],
6	E	NN	O	e	dep	3	SENT_45	[p1l1718t2977r1891b3004],
7	]	CD	NUMBER	]	num	8	SENT_45	[p1l1718t2977r1891b3004],
8	Moa1214886	NN	O	moa1214886	dep	6	SENT_45	[p1l1718t2977r1891b3004],
9	Copyright	NN	O	copyright	nn	14	SENT_45	[p1l1529t3016r1623b3041],
10	©	CD	NUMBER	©	num	14	SENT_45	[p1l1632t3018r1653b3039],
11	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	14	SENT_45	[p1l1663t3017r1711b3035],
12	Massachusetts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Massachusetts	nn	14	SENT_45	[p1l1721t3016r1861b3035],
13	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	14	SENT_45	[p1l1870t3016r1947b3035],
14	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	dep	3	SENT_45	[p1l1955t3017r2027b3041],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1955t3017r2027b3041],

1	2385	CD	DATE	2385	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l1987t3064r2063b3087],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_47	[p1l673t3319r719b3340],
2	NEW	NNP	O	NEW	nn	4	SENT_47	[p1l737t3321r822b3340],
3	ENGLAND	NNP	O	ENGLAND	nn	4	SENT_47	[p1l841t3321r1030b3340],
4	JOURNAL	NNP	O	JOURNAL	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l1049t3321r1228b3347],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l1248t3319r1276b3346],
6	MEDICINE	NNP	O	MEDICINE	prep_of	4	SENT_47	[p1l1288t3321r1487b3340],

1	NAPLASTIC	NNP	O	NAPLASTIC	nn	3	SENT_48	[p2l336t119r837b176],
2	LYMPHOMA	NNP	O	LYMPHOMA	nn	3	SENT_48	[p2l866t119r1391b176],
3	KINASE	NNP	O	KINASE	nsubj	11	SENT_48	[p2l1417t120r1756b178],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_48	[p2l1787t104r2021b189],
5	ALK	NNP	O	ALK	dep	3	SENT_48	[p2l1787t104r2021b189],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	5	SENT_48	[p2l1787t104r2021b189],
7	IS	VBZ	O	be	cop	11	SENT_48	[p2l2055t120r2132b176],
8	avalidated	JJ	O	avalidated	amod	11	SENT_48	[p2l332t226r771b305],
9	tyrosine	NN	O	tyrosine	nn	11	SENT_48	[p2l799t228r1137b327],
10	kinase	NN	O	kinase	nn	11	SENT_48	[p2l1164t227r1438b306],
11	target	NN	O	target	dep	40	SENT_48	[p2l1466t243r1716b327],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1738t228r1821b304],
13	several	JJ	O	several	amod	14	SENT_48	[p2l1850t227r2134b305],
14	cancers	NNS	O	cancer	prep_in	11	SENT_48	[p2l333t381r678b451],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l333t381r678b451],
16	including	VBG	O	include	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l754t355r1164b456],
17	non	JJ	O	non	amod	23	SENT_48	[p2l1232t355r1875b434],
18	—	JJ	O	—	amod	23	SENT_48	[p2l1232t355r1875b434],
19	small	JJ	O	small	amod	23	SENT_48	[p2l1232t355r1875b434],
20	—	NN	O	—	nn	23	SENT_48	[p2l1232t355r1875b434],
21	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	23	SENT_48	[p2l1232t355r1875b434],
22	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	23	SENT_48	[p2l1944t355r2138b456],
23	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_including	11	SENT_48	[p2l12t510r311b580],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l12t510r311b580],
25	anaplastic	JJ	O	anaplastic	amod	23	SENT_48	[p2l358t484r794b585],
26	large	JJ	O	large	amod	29	SENT_48	[p2l833t484r1234b585],
27	—	NN	O	—	nn	29	SENT_48	[p2l833t484r1234b585],
28	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	29	SENT_48	[p2l833t484r1234b585],
29	lymphoma	NN	O	lymphoma	tmod	25	SENT_48	[p2l1274t484r1756b585],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1274t484r1756b585],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1802t484r1960b563],
32	pediatric	JJ	O	pediatric	amod	34	SENT_48	[p2l2000t510r2133b585, p2l12t612r289b691],
33	neuroblastoma	NN	O	neuroblastoma	nn	34	SENT_48	[p2l367t612r1133b691],
34	.1	NN	NUMBER	.1	tmod	25	SENT_48	[p2l367t612r1133b691],
35	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l367t612r1133b691],
36	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	38	SENT_48	[p2l367t612r1133b691],
37	ALK	NN	O	alk	nn	38	SENT_48	[p2l1207t618r1381b690],
38	rearrangements	NNS	O	rearrangement	nsubj	54	SENT_48	[p2l1451t629r2132b713],
39	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	40	SENT_48	[p2l11t767r140b819],
40	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l179t740r431b819],
41	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l469t741r553b818],
42	approximately	RB	O	approximately	quantmod	43	SENT_48	[p2l591t740r1207b841],
43	5	CD	PERCENT	5	num	44	SENT_48	[p2l1243t745r1374b819],
44	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_in	40	SENT_48	[p2l1243t745r1374b819],
45	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1413t740r1513b819],
46	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	44	SENT_48	[p2l1534t767r1756b819],
47	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1798t740r1898b819],
48	nonsmall	JJ	O	nonsmall	amod	52	SENT_48	[p2l1918t766r2137b819, p2l13t868r432b947],
49	—	NN	O	—	nn	52	SENT_48	[p2l1918t766r2137b819, p2l13t868r432b947],
50	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	52	SENT_48	[p2l1918t766r2137b819, p2l13t868r432b947],
51	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	52	SENT_48	[p2l469t868r662b969],
52	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	46	SENT_48	[p2l698t894r978b947],
53	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1013t868r1171b947],
54	define	VB	O	define	conj_and	40	SENT_48	[p2l1210t868r1480b947],
55	a	DT	O	a	det	58	SENT_48	[p2l1518t895r1563b947],
56	distinct	JJ	O	distinct	amod	58	SENT_48	[p2l1600t868r1929b947],
57	molecular	JJ	O	molecular	amod	58	SENT_48	[p2l1962t894r2133b947, p2l11t996r305b1075],
58	subtype	NN	O	subtype	dobj	54	SENT_48	[p2l350t996r683b1097],
59	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l732t996r831b1075],
60	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	61	SENT_48	[p2l860t996r1053b1097],
61	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	58	SENT_48	[p2l1098t1002r1498b1075],
62	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1098t1002r1498b1075],

1	“	NN	O	“	npadvmod	22	SENT_49	[p2l1098t1002r1498b1075],
2	With	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1542t996r1755b1075],
3	an	DT	O	a	det	16	SENT_49	[p2l1802t1022r1905b1075],
4	estimated	VBN	O	estimate	amod	16	SENT_49	[p2l1953t997r2133b1075, p2l12t1124r278b1203],
5	1.3	CD	NUMBER	1.3	number	6	SENT_49	[p2l330t1130r450b1203],
6	million	CD	NUMBER	million	num	8	SENT_49	[p2l502t1124r817b1203],
7	new	JJ	O	new	amod	8	SENT_49	[p2l865t1150r1043b1204],
8	cases	NNS	O	case	dep	4	SENT_49	[p2l1088t1151r1310b1203],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1362t1124r1462b1203],
10	non	JJ	O	non	amod	13	SENT_49	[p2l1492t1124r2134b1203],
11	—	JJ	O	—	amod	13	SENT_49	[p2l1492t1124r2134b1203],
12	small	JJ	O	small	amod	13	SENT_49	[p2l1492t1124r2134b1203],
13	—	NN	O	—	prep_of	8	SENT_49	[p2l1492t1124r2134b1203],
14	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	16	SENT_49	[p2l1492t1124r2134b1203],
15	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	16	SENT_49	[p2l11t1252r204b1353],
16	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_with	22	SENT_49	[p2l235t1278r515b1331],
17	worldwide	JJ	O	worldwide	amod	16	SENT_49	[p2l541t1252r991b1332],
18	each	DT	SET	each	det	19	SENT_49	[p2l1025t1252r1217b1331],
19	year	NN	SET	year	tmod	17	SENT_49	[p2l1245t1258r1485b1353],
20	,8	CD	NUMBER	,8	nsubj	22	SENT_49	[p2l1245t1258r1485b1353],
21	this	DT	O	this	dep	20	SENT_49	[p2l1519t1252r1679b1331],
22	translates	VBZ	O	translate	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1715t1252r2132b1331],
23	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l11t1381r180b1459],
24	more	JJR	O	more	mwe	25	SENT_49	[p2l214t1406r433b1459],
25	than	IN	O	than	quantmod	26	SENT_49	[p2l466t1380r663b1459],
26	60,000	CD	NUMBER	60,000	num	27	SENT_49	[p2l696t1386r982b1476],
27	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_into	22	SENT_49	[p2l1014t1381r1355b1481],
28	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1386t1380r1581b1459],
29	ALK	NN	O	alk	npadvmod	31	SENT_49	[p2l1607t1381r2134b1481],
30	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	29	SENT_49	[p2l1607t1381r2134b1481],
31	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	33	SENT_49	[p2l1607t1381r2134b1481],
32	non	JJ	O	non	amod	33	SENT_49	[p2l12t1508r654b1587],
33	—	NN	O	—	prep_with	22	SENT_49	[p2l12t1508r654b1587],
34	small	JJ	O	small	amod	38	SENT_49	[p2l12t1508r654b1587],
35	—	NN	O	—	nn	38	SENT_49	[p2l12t1508r654b1587],
36	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	38	SENT_49	[p2l12t1508r654b1587],
37	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	38	SENT_49	[p2l687t1508r880b1609],
38	cancer	NN	O	cancer	tmod	33	SENT_49	[p2l912t1534r1193b1587],
39	annually	RB	SET	annually	advmod	38	SENT_49	[p2l1224t1508r1611b1609],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1224t1508r1611b1609],

1	Crizotinib	NNP	O	Crizotinib	nsubj	10	SENT_50	[p2l141t1636r580b1715],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	10	SENT_50	[p2l623t1637r688b1715],
3	an	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_50	[p2l733t1662r836b1715],
4	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	10	SENT_50	[p2l880t1636r1045b1715],
5	small	JJ	O	small	amod	10	SENT_50	[p2l1089t1636r1744b1715],
6	—	NN	O	—	nn	10	SENT_50	[p2l1089t1636r1744b1715],
7	molecule	NN	O	molecule	nn	10	SENT_50	[p2l1089t1636r1744b1715],
8	tyrosine	NN	O	tyrosine	nn	10	SENT_50	[p2l1788t1637r2134b1737],
9	kinase	NN	O	kinase	nn	10	SENT_50	[p2l12t1764r290b1844],
10	inhibitor	NN	O	inhibitor	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l330t1764r712b1843],
11	targeting	VBG	O	target	partmod	10	SENT_50	[p2l750t1765r1149b1865],
12	ALK	NNP	O	ALK	dobj	11	SENT_50	[p2l1182t1772r1393b1860],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1182t1772r1393b1860],
14	MET	NN	O	met	conj_and	12	SENT_50	[p2l1436t1770r1658b1860],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1436t1770r1658b1860],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1703t1764r1861b1843],
17	R081	NN	O	r081	conj_and	12	SENT_50	[p2l1900t1770r2133b1848],
18	tyrosine	NN	O	tyrosine	nn	19	SENT_50	[p2l12t1893r350b1993],
19	l	NN	O	l	tmod	11	SENT_50	[p2l383t1892r903b1972],
20	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	21	SENT_50	[p2l383t1892r903b1972],
21	’	NN	O	’	nsubj	32	SENT_50	[p2l383t1892r903b1972],
22	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	23	SENT_50	[p2l383t1892r903b1972],
23	°	CD	NUMBER	°	num	21	SENT_50	[p2l383t1892r903b1972],
24	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l934t1900r1022b1970],
25	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	29	SENT_50	[p2l1055t1909r1210b1972],
26	single	JJ	O	single	amod	29	SENT_50	[p2l1245t1892r1777b1993],
27	—	NN	O	—	nn	29	SENT_50	[p2l1245t1892r1777b1993],
28	group	NN	O	group	nn	29	SENT_50	[p2l1245t1892r1777b1993],
29	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_in	21	SENT_50	[p2l1812t1892r2129b1988],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1812t1892r2129b1988],
31	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	appos	29	SENT_50	[p2l12t2020r432b2099],
32	showed	VBD	O	show	dep	11	SENT_50	[p2l480t2020r803b2099],
33	marked	JJ	O	marked	amod	35	SENT_50	[p2l849t2020r1176b2100],
34	antitumor	NN	O	antitumor	nn	35	SENT_50	[p2l1221t2021r1658b2099],
35	activity	NN	O	activity	dobj	32	SENT_50	[p2l1700t2021r2010b2121],
36	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l2051t2021r2134b2098],
37	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	32	SENT_50	[p2l11t2149r352b2249],
38	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l395t2148r590b2227],
39	advanced	JJ	O	advanced	amod	52	SENT_50	[p2l636t2148r1032b2228],
40	ALK	NNP	O	ALK	nn	52	SENT_50	[p2l1071t2149r1598b2249],
41	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	52	SENT_50	[p2l1071t2149r1598b2249],
42	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	52	SENT_50	[p2l1071t2149r1598b2249],
43	non	JJ	O	non	amod	47	SENT_50	[p2l1644t2148r2133b2227, p2l12t2276r158b2355],
44	—	NN	O	—	nn	47	SENT_50	[p2l1644t2148r2133b2227, p2l12t2276r158b2355],
45	smallcell	NN	O	smallcell	nn	47	SENT_50	[p2l1644t2148r2133b2227, p2l12t2276r158b2355],
46	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	47	SENT_50	[p2l193t2276r385b2377],
47	cancer	NN	O	cancer	tmod	42	SENT_50	[p2l419t2302r718b2372],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l419t2302r718b2372],
49	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l754t2276r949b2355],
50	objective	JJ	O	objective	amod	51	SENT_50	[p2l986t2276r1359b2377],
51	response	NN	O	response	prep_with	47	SENT_50	[p2l1395t2302r1775b2377],
52	rates	NNS	O	rate	prep_with	32	SENT_50	[p2l1811t2293r2014b2355],
53	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l2052t2276r2152b2355],
54	approximately	RB	O	approximately	quantmod	55	SENT_50	[p2l11t2404r602b2505],
55	60	CD	PERCENT	60	num	56	SENT_50	[p2l632t2409r816b2483],
56	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_of	52	SENT_50	[p2l632t2409r816b2483],
57	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l849t2404r1002b2483],
58	a	DT	O	a	det	63	SENT_50	[p2l1035t2431r1080b2483],
59	median	JJ	O	median	amod	63	SENT_50	[p2l1112t2404r1425b2483],
60	progression	NN	O	progression	nn	63	SENT_50	[p2l1458t2404r2134b2505],
61	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	63	SENT_50	[p2l1458t2404r2134b2505],
62	free	JJ	O	free	amod	63	SENT_50	[p2l1458t2404r2134b2505],
63	survival	NN	O	survival	conj_and	56	SENT_50	[p2l13t2532r345b2611],
64	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l383t2532r483b2611],
65	8.1	CD	DURATION	8.1	num	66	SENT_50	[p2l503t2538r628b2611],
66	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	prep_of	63	SENT_50	[p2l667t2532r994b2611],
67	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1033t2533r1116b2610],
68	one	CD	NUMBER	one	prep_in	66	SENT_50	[p2l1155t2558r1306b2611],
69	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1346t2532r1445b2611],
70	the	DT	O	the	det	71	SENT_50	[p2l1465t2532r1598b2611],
71	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	52	SENT_50	[p2l1637t2532r1937b2611],
72	and	CC	O	and	cc	71	SENT_50	[p2l1976t2532r2134b2611],

1	9.7	CD	DURATION	9.7	num	2	SENT_51	[p2l12t2665r131b2737],
2	months	NNS	DURATION	month	nsubjpass	33	SENT_51	[p2l164t2659r486b2737],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l520t2660r602b2736],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_51	[p2l635t2659r765b2737],
5	other	JJ	O	other	amod	30	SENT_51	[p2l799t2659r1207b2737],
6	.11	CD	NUMBER	.11	number	7	SENT_51	[p2l799t2659r1207b2737],
7	»	CD	NUMBER	»	amod	30	SENT_51	[p2l799t2659r1207b2737],
8	12	CD	NUMBER	12	dep	7	SENT_51	[p2l799t2659r1207b2737],
9	In	IN	O	in	dep	8	SENT_51	[p2l1239t2667r1326b2736],
10	contrast	NN	O	contrast	pobj	9	SENT_51	[p2l1359t2676r1724b2754],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1359t2676r1724b2754],
12	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	16	SENT_51	[p2l1763t2659r2134b2737],
13	single	JJ	O	single	amod	16	SENT_51	[p2l13t2787r540b2888],
14	—	JJ	O	—	amod	16	SENT_51	[p2l13t2787r540b2888],
15	agent	NN	O	agent	nn	16	SENT_51	[p2l13t2787r540b2888],
16	chemotherapies	NNS	O	chemotherapy	appos	10	SENT_51	[p2l574t2787r1252b2888],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1291t2788r1374b2865],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_51	[p2l1413t2787r1546b2866],
19	general	JJ	O	general	amod	20	SENT_51	[p2l1583t2787r1900b2888],
20	population	NN	O	population	prep_in	16	SENT_51	[p2l1936t2813r2133b2888, p2l12t2915r309b2994],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l348t2915r447b2994],
22	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_of	20	SENT_51	[p2l465t2916r799b3016],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l835t2915r1027b2995],
24	non	JJ	O	non	amod	29	SENT_51	[p2l1065t2915r1693b2994],
25	—	JJ	O	—	amod	29	SENT_51	[p2l1065t2915r1693b2994],
26	small	JJ	O	small	amod	29	SENT_51	[p2l1065t2915r1693b2994],
27	—	NN	O	—	nn	29	SENT_51	[p2l1065t2915r1693b2994],
28	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	29	SENT_51	[p2l1065t2915r1693b2994],
29	lung	NN	O	lung	prep_with	22	SENT_51	[p2l1730t2915r1920b3016],
30	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_in	2	SENT_51	[p2l1956t2941r2133b2994, p2l12t3069r139b3122],
31	have	VBP	O	have	aux	33	SENT_51	[p2l180t3043r370b3122],
32	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	33	SENT_51	[p2l413t3043r615b3122],
33	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l658t3043r1102b3122],
34	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1141t3043r1337b3122],
35	response	NN	O	response	nn	36	SENT_51	[p2l1380t3069r1760b3144],
36	rates	NNS	O	rate	prep_with	33	SENT_51	[p2l1804t3060r2006b3122],
37	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l2053t3043r2152b3122],
38	10	CD	PERCENT	10	num	39	SENT_51	[p2l15t3176r192b3250],
39	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_of	36	SENT_51	[p2l15t3176r192b3250],
40	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l221t3197r308b3250],
41	lower	JJR	O	lower	conj_or	39	SENT_51	[p2l333t3171r562b3251],
42	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l588t3171r741b3250],
43	median	JJ	O	median	amod	44	SENT_51	[p2l771t3171r1083b3250],
44	progression	NN	O	progression	conj_and	36	SENT_51	[p2l1111t3171r1787b3272],
45	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	47	SENT_51	[p2l1111t3171r1787b3272],
46	free	JJ	O	free	amod	47	SENT_51	[p2l1111t3171r1787b3272],
47	survival	NN	O	survival	dep	44	SENT_51	[p2l1818t3171r2134b3250],
48	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l12t3300r110b3379],
49	2	CD	DURATION	2	number	51	SENT_51	[p2l132t3306r179b3378],
50	to	TO	DURATION	to	dep	51	SENT_51	[p2l220t3317r301b3379],
51	3	CD	DURATION	3	num	52	SENT_51	[p2l342t3306r386b3379],
52	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	prep_of	47	SENT_51	[p2l430t3300r955b3379],
53	.13	CD	NUMBER	.13	number	54	SENT_51	[p2l430t3300r955b3379],
54	'15	CD	NUMBER	'15	num	52	SENT_51	[p2l430t3300r955b3379],

1	To	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l137t3434r242b3507],
2	date	NN	O	date	prep_to	12	SENT_52	[p2l279t3428r475b3524],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l279t3428r475b3524],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_52	[p2l516t3428r647b3507],
5	activity	NN	O	activity	nsubjpass	12	SENT_52	[p2l682t3429r985b3529],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1016t3428r1115b3507],
7	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	8	SENT_52	[p2l1133t3428r1504b3507],
8	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	prep_of	5	SENT_52	[p2l1540t3428r2139b3529],
9	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	12	SENT_52	[p2l12t3556r156b3635],
10	not	RB	O	not	neg	12	SENT_52	[p2l214t3573r357b3635],
11	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	12	SENT_52	[p2l408t3556r609b3635],
12	established	VBN	O	establish	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l666t3556r1148b3635],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1203t3557r1286b3634],
14	ALK	NNP	O	ALK	nn	21	SENT_52	[p2l1335t3557r1862b3657],
15	—	CD	NUMBER	—	npadvmod	16	SENT_52	[p2l1335t3557r1862b3657],
16	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	21	SENT_52	[p2l1335t3557r1862b3657],
17	nonsmall	JJ	O	nonsmall	amod	21	SENT_52	[p2l1918t3582r2137b3635, p2l13t3684r421b3763],
18	—	NN	O	—	nn	21	SENT_52	[p2l1918t3582r2137b3635, p2l13t3684r421b3763],
19	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	21	SENT_52	[p2l1918t3582r2137b3635, p2l13t3684r421b3763],
20	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	21	SENT_52	[p2l458t3684r648b3785],
21	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_in	12	SENT_52	[p2l683t3710r975b3763],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l683t3710r975b3763],

1	Retrospective	JJ	O	retrospective	amod	2	SENT_53	[p2l1017t3685r1585b3785],
2	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	3	SENT_53	[p2l1624t3684r1917b3763],
3	suggest	VBP	O	suggest	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1959t3711r2133b3785, p3l12t37r185b121],

1	that	IN	O	that	dep	6	SENT_54	[p3l216t20r389b99],
2	ALK	NN	O	alk	nn	3	SENT_54	[p3l415t26r590b98],
3	rearrangements	NNS	O	rearrangement	nsubjpass	6	SENT_54	[p3l620t37r1301b121],
4	may	MD	O	may	aux	6	SENT_54	[p3l1342t46r1520b121],
5	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_54	[p3l1555t20r1652b99],
6	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1689t20r2134b99],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l7t148r202b227],
8	enhanced	VBN	O	enhance	amod	9	SENT_54	[p3l259t148r673b227],
9	sensitivity	NN	O	sensitivity	prep_with	6	SENT_54	[p3l730t149r1163b249],
10	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1214t165r1296b227],
11	pemetreXed	JJ	O	pemetrexed	amod	12	SENT_54	[p3l1351t148r2134b249],
12	—	NN	O	—	prep_to	9	SENT_54	[p3l1351t148r2134b249],
13	based	VBN	O	base	partmod	12	SENT_54	[p3l1351t148r2134b249],
14	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	dobj	13	SENT_54	[p3l12t276r636b377],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l12t276r636b377],
16	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l679t276r874b355],
17	durations	NNS	O	duration	prep_with	13	SENT_54	[p3l917t276r1325b355],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1370t276r1470b355],
19	response	NN	O	response	prep_of	17	SENT_54	[p3l1493t302r1874b377],
20	similar	JJ	O	similar	amod	19	SENT_54	[p3l1918t277r2133b355, p3l11t404r127b483],
21	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l163t421r245b483],
22	those	DT	O	those	prep_to	20	SENT_54	[p3l287t404r518b483],
23	observed	VBN	O	observe	partmod	22	SENT_54	[p3l558t404r939b483],
24	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l974t404r1169b483],
25	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	prep_with	23	SENT_54	[p3l1209t404r1821b483],
26	.15	CD	NUMBER	.15	number	27	SENT_54	[p3l1209t404r1821b483],
27	’17	CD	NUMBER	’17	num	25	SENT_54	[p3l1209t404r1821b483],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_55	[p3l137t540r269b611],
2	conducted	VBD	O	conduct	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l301t532r734b611],
3	a	DT	O	a	dobj	2	SENT_55	[p3l765t559r809b611],
4	randomized	VBN	O	randomize	dep	3	SENT_55	[p3l839t532r1372b628],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l839t532r1372b628],
6	controlled	VBN	O	control	dep	4	SENT_55	[p3l1410t532r1859b628],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1410t532r1859b628],
8	openlabel	NN	O	openlabel	nn	12	SENT_55	[p3l1897t558r2133b633, p3l11t660r227b756],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1897t558r2133b633, p3l11t660r227b756],
10	phase	NN	O	phase	dep	12	SENT_55	[p3l264t660r504b761],
11	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	12	SENT_55	[p3l537t666r581b739],
12	trial	NN	O	trial	npadvmod	6	SENT_55	[p3l617t660r786b739],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l818t660r916b739],
14	crizotinib	NN	O	crizotinib	prep_of	6	SENT_55	[p3l930t660r1351b756],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l930t660r1351b756],
16	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1389t687r1472b739],
17	compared	VBN	O	compare	prepc_as	6	SENT_55	[p3l1507t660r1918b761],
18	with	IN	O	with	pcomp	17	SENT_55	[p3l1946t660r2134b739],
19	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	20	SENT_55	[p3l13t788r385b867],
20	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	pobj	18	SENT_55	[p3l412t788r1011b889],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1033t789r1115b866],
22	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	20	SENT_55	[p3l1141t789r1475b889],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1500t788r1692b867],
24	advanced	JJ	O	advanced	prep_with	22	SENT_55	[p3l1718t788r2129b884],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1718t788r2129b884],
26	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	27	SENT_55	[p3l11t916r430b1017],
27	treated	VBN	O	treat	dep	4	SENT_55	[p3l459t916r744b995],
28	ALK	NNP	O	ALK	dep	30	SENT_55	[p3l769t917r1273b1017],
29	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	28	SENT_55	[p3l769t917r1273b1017],
30	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	32	SENT_55	[p3l769t917r1273b1017],
31	non	JJ	O	non	amod	32	SENT_55	[p3l1306t916r1920b995],
32	—	NN	O	—	dobj	27	SENT_55	[p3l1306t916r1920b995],
33	small	JJ	O	small	amod	37	SENT_55	[p3l1306t916r1920b995],
34	—	NN	O	—	nn	37	SENT_55	[p3l1306t916r1920b995],
35	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	37	SENT_55	[p3l1306t916r1920b995],
36	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	37	SENT_55	[p3l1951t916r2138b1017],
37	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dobj	4	SENT_55	[p3l12t1042r311b1095],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l12t1042r311b1095],

1	METHODS	NNS	O	method	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l801t1313r1343b1372],

1	PATIENTS	NNS	O	patient	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l17t1547r384b1596],

1	Patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	3	SENT_58	[p3l11t1646r350b1724],
2	were	VBD	O	be	cop	3	SENT_58	[p3l381t1671r582b1724],
3	eligible	JJ	O	eligible	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l616t1645r925b1746],
4	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l959t1645r1082b1724],
5	inclusion	NN	O	inclusion	prep_for	3	SENT_58	[p3l1111t1645r1503b1724],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1535t1646r1618b1723],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_58	[p3l1651t1645r1784b1724],
8	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	3	SENT_58	[p3l1818t1645r2048b1746],
9	if	IN	O	if	mark	13	SENT_58	[p3l2076t1645r2152b1723],
10	they	PRP	O	they	nsubj	13	SENT_58	[p3l12t1773r189b1874],
11	had	VBD	O	have	aux	13	SENT_58	[p3l212t1773r365b1852],
12	locally	RB	O	locally	advmod	13	SENT_58	[p3l392t1773r662b1874],
13	advanced	VBN	O	advance	dep	8	SENT_58	[p3l685t1773r1066b1853],
14	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1095t1799r1182b1852],
15	metastatic	JJ	O	metastatic	amod	20	SENT_58	[p3l1208t1774r1635b1852],
16	non	JJ	O	non	amod	20	SENT_58	[p3l1663t1773r2133b1852, p3l12t1901r158b1980],
17	—	NN	O	—	nn	20	SENT_58	[p3l1663t1773r2133b1852, p3l12t1901r158b1980],
18	smallcell	NN	O	smallcell	nn	20	SENT_58	[p3l1663t1773r2133b1852, p3l12t1901r158b1980],
19	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	20	SENT_58	[p3l203t1901r396b2002],
20	cancer	NN	O	cancer	conj_or	8	SENT_58	[p3l440t1927r721b1980],
21	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	23	SENT_58	[p3l764t1901r937b1980],
22	was	VBD	O	be	cop	23	SENT_58	[p3l974t1928r1136b1980],
23	positive	JJ	O	positive	rcmod	20	SENT_58	[p3l1183t1902r1514b2002],
24	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1560t1901r1684b1980],
25	ALK	NN	O	alk	nn	26	SENT_58	[p3l1721t1907r1895b1979],
26	rearrangements	NNS	O	rearrangement	prep_for	23	SENT_58	[p3l1933t1927r2133b1980, p3l12t2046r542b2130],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1933t1927r2133b1980, p3l12t2046r542b2130],

1	ALK	NN	O	alk	nn	2	SENT_59	[p3l571t2035r745b2107],
2	testing	NN	O	testing	nsubjpass	4	SENT_59	[p3l767t2030r1065b2130],
3	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_59	[p3l1086t2056r1248b2108],
4	performed	VBN	O	perform	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1279t2029r1735b2130],
5	centrally	RB	O	centrally	amod	12	SENT_59	[p3l1765t2029r2138b2130],
6	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l7t2157r202b2236],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_59	[p3l235t2157r368b2236],
8	use	NN	O	use	prep_with	5	SENT_59	[p3l402t2184r541b2236],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l576t2157r675b2236],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_59	[p3l689t2184r733b2236],
11	breal	NN	O	breal	prep_of	8	SENT_59	[p3l765t2157r1261b2258],
12	<	JJR	O	<	dobj	4	SENT_59	[p3l765t2157r1261b2258],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l765t2157r1261b2258],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l765t2157r1261b2258],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l765t2157r1261b2258],

1	apart	RB	O	apart	dep	2	SENT_61	[p3l765t2157r1261b2258],
2	fluorescence	NN	O	fluorescence	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1288t2157r1830b2236],
3	in	FW	O	in	nn	4	SENT_61	[p3l1863t2158r1946b2235],
4	situ	FW	O	situ	advmod	6	SENT_61	[p3l1980t2158r2134b2236],
5	hybridization	NN	O	hybridization	nn	6	SENT_61	[p3l12t2285r589b2386],
6	assay	NN	O	assay	rcmod	2	SENT_61	[p3l623t2312r863b2386],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l623t2312r863b2386],
8	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	9	SENT_61	[p3l899t2285r1162b2365],
9	has	VBZ	O	have	dep	43	SENT_61	[p3l1196t2285r1341b2364],
10	an	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_61	[p3l1377t2311r1480b2364],
11	analytic	JJ	O	analytic	amod	14	SENT_61	[p3l1515t2285r1853b2386],
12	sensi	NN	O	sensus	nn	14	SENT_61	[p3l1889t2286r2133b2364],
13	—	NN	O	—	nn	14	SENT_61	[p3l1889t2286r2133b2364],
14	tivity	NN	O	tivity	dobj	9	SENT_61	[p3l12t2414r229b2514],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l266t2413r366b2492],
16	100	CD	PERCENT	100	number	17	SENT_61	[p3l391t2419r627b2492],
17	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	21	SENT_61	[p3l391t2419r627b2492],
18	(	CD	PERCENT	(	number	19	SENT_61	[p3l672t2418r883b2504],
19	95	CD	PERCENT	95	dep	20	SENT_61	[p3l672t2418r883b2504],
20	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	21	SENT_61	[p3l672t2418r883b2504],
21	confidence	NN	O	confidence	prep_of	14	SENT_61	[p3l924t2413r1395b2492],
22	interval	NN	O	interval	nn	25	SENT_61	[p3l1436t2413r1762b2492],
23	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	25	SENT_61	[p3l1811t2419r1987b2509],
24	CI	NN	O	ci	nn	25	SENT_61	[p3l1811t2419r1987b2509],
25	]	NN	O	]	dep	21	SENT_61	[p3l1811t2419r1987b2509],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1811t2419r1987b2509],
27	98	CD	NUMBER	98	number	29	SENT_61	[p3l2033t2419r2132b2492],
28	to	TO	O	to	dep	29	SENT_61	[p3l12t2558r94b2620],
29	100	CD	NUMBER	100	prep_of	14	SENT_61	[p3l145t2547r320b2633],
30	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	29	SENT_61	[p3l145t2547r320b2633],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l372t2541r529b2620],
32	specificity	NN	O	specificity	prep_of	14	SENT_61	[p3l577t2541r1018b2642],
33	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1062t2541r1161b2620],
34	100	CD	PERCENT	100	number	35	SENT_61	[p3l1193t2546r1429b2620],
35	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	39	SENT_61	[p3l1193t2546r1429b2620],
36	(	CD	PERCENT	(	number	37	SENT_61	[p3l1480t2546r1691b2633],
37	95	CD	PERCENT	95	dep	38	SENT_61	[p3l1480t2546r1691b2633],
38	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	39	SENT_61	[p3l1480t2546r1691b2633],
39	CI	NN	O	ci	prep_of	32	SENT_61	[p3l1738t2547r1853b2637],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1738t2547r1853b2637],
41	97	CD	NUMBER	97	number	43	SENT_61	[p3l1905t2547r2003b2620],
42	to	TO	O	to	dep	43	SENT_61	[p3l2051t2558r2132b2620],
43	100	CD	NUMBER	100	appos	2	SENT_61	[p3l15t2674r255b2761],
44	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	45	SENT_61	[p3l15t2674r255b2761],
45	}	CD	NUMBER	}	num	48	SENT_61	[p3l15t2674r255b2761],
46	Other	JJ	O	other	amod	48	SENT_61	[p3l288t2669r536b2748],
47	eligibility	NN	O	eligibility	nn	48	SENT_61	[p3l568t2669r976b2770],
48	criteria	NNS	O	criterion	nsubj	49	SENT_61	[p3l1006t2670r1310b2748],
49	included	VBD	O	include	rcmod	43	SENT_61	[p3l1341t2669r1707b2748],
50	an	DT	O	a	det	51	SENT_61	[p3l1740t2695r1843b2748],
51	age	NN	O	age	dobj	49	SENT_61	[p3l1876t2696r2019b2770],
52	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l2053t2669r2152b2748],
53	at	IN	DURATION	at	quantmod	55	SENT_61	[p3l11t2814r90b2876],
54	least	JJS	DURATION	least	mwe	53	SENT_61	[p3l136t2797r335b2876],
55	18	CD	DURATION	18	num	56	SENT_61	[p3l385t2803r479b2876],
56	years	NNS	NUMBER	year	prep_of	51	SENT_61	[p3l528t2824r772b2898],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l528t2824r772b2898],
58	progressive	JJ	O	progressive	amod	59	SENT_61	[p3l828t2798r1317b2898],
59	disease	NN	O	disease	appos	56	SENT_61	[p3l1370t2797r1680b2876],
60	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1731t2797r1934b2876],
61	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	64	SENT_61	[p3l1983t2823r2134b2876],
62	prior	JJ	O	prior	amod	64	SENT_61	[p3l11t2926r224b3026],
63	platinum	NN	O	platinum	nn	64	SENT_61	[p3l302t2925r977b3026],
64	—	NN	O	—	prep_after	49	SENT_61	[p3l302t2925r977b3026],
65	based	VBN	O	base	partmod	64	SENT_61	[p3l302t2925r977b3026],
66	chemotherapy	NN	O	chemotherapy	nn	67	SENT_61	[p3l1061t2925r1671b3026],
67	regimen	NN	O	regimen	dobj	65	SENT_61	[p3l1749t2926r2129b3026],
68	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1749t2926r2129b3026],
69	measurable	JJ	O	measurable	amod	70	SENT_61	[p3l12t3053r504b3132],
70	disease	NN	O	disease	appos	67	SENT_61	[p3l550t3053r860b3132],
71	as	IN	O	as	amod	70	SENT_61	[p3l906t3079r990b3131],
72	assessed	VBN	O	assess	partmod	70	SENT_61	[p3l1037t3053r1406b3132],
73	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1447t3053r1642b3132],
74	the	DT	O	the	det	75	SENT_61	[p3l1688t3053r1821b3131],
75	use	NN	O	use	prep_with	72	SENT_61	[p3l1866t3079r2006b3132],
76	of	IN	O	of	prep	75	SENT_61	[p3l2053t3052r2152b3132],

1	Response	NN	O	response	nn	3	SENT_62	[p3l11t3187r421b3280],
2	Evaluation	NN	O	evaluation	nn	3	SENT_62	[p3l483t3181r934b3260],
3	Criteria	NNS	O	criterion	nsubj	7	SENT_62	[p3l998t3182r1320b3259],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l1382t3182r1465b3258],
5	Solid	JJ	O	solid	amod	6	SENT_62	[p3l1531t3181r1743b3259],
6	Tumors	NNS	O	tumor	prep_in	3	SENT_62	[p3l1803t3187r2132b3260],
7	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l17t3315r432b3404],
8	RECIST	NN	O	recist	dobj	7	SENT_62	[p3l17t3315r432b3404],
9	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	8	SENT_62	[p3l17t3315r432b3404],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l17t3315r432b3404],
11	version	NN	O	version	dobj	7	SENT_62	[p3l466t3310r773b3388],
12	1.1,18	CD	NUMBER	1.1,18	num	11	SENT_62	[p3l810t3314r1031b3404],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l1064t3309r1222b3387],
14	an	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_62	[p3l1254t3335r1356b3387],
15	Eastern	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Eastern	nn	20	SENT_62	[p3l1388t3316r1711b3387],
16	Cooperative	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cooperative	nn	20	SENT_62	[p3l1743t3315r2133b3408, p3l12t3438r159b3516],
17	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	nn	20	SENT_62	[p3l190t3437r604b3538],
18	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	nn	20	SENT_62	[p3l631t3443r900b3537],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_62	[p3l937t3443r1258b3528],
20	ECOG	NNP	O	ECOG	conj_and	11	SENT_62	[p3l937t3443r1258b3528],
21	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	23	SENT_62	[p3l937t3443r1258b3528],
22	performance	NN	O	performance	nn	23	SENT_62	[p3l1294t3436r1848b3537],
23	status	NN	O	status	dep	11	SENT_62	[p3l1881t3454r2132b3516],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l12t3564r113b3644],
25	o	NN	O	o	prep_of	23	SENT_62	[p3l129t3571r198b3661],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l129t3571r198b3661],
27	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dobj	7	SENT_62	[p3l242t3571r309b3661],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l242t3571r309b3661],
29	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l350t3591r439b3644],
30	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	31	SENT_62	[p3l471t3571r518b3643],
31	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dobj	7	SENT_62	[p3l559t3565r776b3656],
32	With	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l559t3565r776b3656],
33	o	NN	O	o	prep_with	31	SENT_62	[p3l812t3571r858b3644],
34	indicating	VBG	O	indicate	partmod	31	SENT_62	[p3l893t3565r1335b3666],
35	that	IN	O	that	complm	40	SENT_62	[p3l1366t3565r1539b3643],
36	the	DT	O	the	det	37	SENT_62	[p3l1569t3565r1702b3643],
37	patient	NN	O	patient	nsubj	40	SENT_62	[p3l1735t3566r2037b3665],
38	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	40	SENT_62	[p3l2067t3566r2133b3643],
39	fully	RB	O	fully	advmod	40	SENT_62	[p3l12t3691r208b3792],
40	active	JJ	O	active	ccomp	34	SENT_62	[p3l243t3693r506b3788],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l243t3693r506b3788],
42	1	CD	NUMBER	1	conj_or	8	SENT_62	[p3l555t3698r599b3770],
43	that	IN	O	that	complm	47	SENT_62	[p3l641t3692r813b3770],
44	the	DT	O	the	det	45	SENT_62	[p3l849t3692r982b3770],
45	patient	NN	O	patient	nsubj	49	SENT_62	[p3l1021t3693r1323b3792],
46	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	47	SENT_62	[p3l1357t3693r1423b3770],
47	ambulatory	JJ	O	ambulatory	dep	42	SENT_62	[p3l1464t3692r1964b3792],
48	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l2000t3692r2139b3772],
49	restricted	JJ	O	restricted	dep	42	SENT_62	[p4l12t21r419b99],
50	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l471t22r555b98],
51	strenuous	JJ	O	strenuous	amod	52	SENT_62	[p4l611t37r1028b100],
52	activity	NN	O	activity	prep_in	47	SENT_62	[p4l1084t22r1406b120],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l1084t22r1406b120],
54	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l1465t21r1623b99],
55	2	CD	NUMBER	2	conj_or	8	SENT_62	[p4l1677t27r1724b98],
56	that	IN	O	that	complm	60	SENT_62	[p4l1779t21r1952b99],
57	the	DT	O	the	det	58	SENT_62	[p4l2001t21r2134b99],
58	patient	NN	O	patient	nsubj	62	SENT_62	[p4l11t149r313b248],
59	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	60	SENT_62	[p4l337t149r403b226],
60	ambulatory	JJ	O	ambulatory	dep	55	SENT_62	[p4l434t148r933b248],
61	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l958t148r1115b227],
62	capable	JJ	O	capable	dep	55	SENT_62	[p4l1146t148r1466b248],
63	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l1497t147r1596b227],
64	self	NN	O	self	nn	66	SENT_62	[p4l1610t147r1969b226],
65	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	66	SENT_62	[p4l1610t147r1969b226],
66	care	NN	O	care	prep_of	60	SENT_62	[p4l1610t147r1969b226],
67	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l2000t148r2139b228],
68	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	69	SENT_62	[p4l11t278r77b355],
69	unable	JJ	O	unable	dep	55	SENT_62	[p4l127t277r414b356],
70	to	TO	O	to	aux	71	SENT_62	[p4l463t293r544b355],
71	Work	VB	O	work	xcomp	69	SENT_62	[p4l590t277r929b367],
72	”	CD	NUMBER	”	num	73	SENT_62	[p4l590t277r929b367],
73	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dobj	71	SENT_62	[p4l590t277r929b367],
74	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p4l590t277r929b367],

1	Patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	17	SENT_63	[p4l982t278r1321b355],
2	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l1367t277r1563b356],
3	stable	JJ	O	stable	amod	5	SENT_63	[p4l1613t277r1859b355],
4	brain	NN	O	brain	nn	5	SENT_63	[p4l1909t277r2134b355],
5	metastases	NNS	O	metastase	prep_with	1	SENT_63	[p4l12t422r483b483],
6	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	13	SENT_63	[p4l537t405r709b483],
7	had	VBD	O	have	aux	9	SENT_63	[p4l755t405r911b483],
8	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_63	[p4l963t405r1163b483],
9	treated	VBN	O	treat	rcmod	5	SENT_63	[p4l1215t405r1513b483],
10	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	9	SENT_63	[p4l1562t405r2001b504],
11	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l2049t431r2137b483],
12	were	VBD	O	be	cop	13	SENT_63	[p4l7t559r209b612],
13	untreated	JJ	O	untreated	rcmod	5	SENT_63	[p4l252t533r664b612],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l706t533r863b612],
15	asymptomatic	JJ	O	asymptomatic	conj_and	13	SENT_63	[p4l905t534r1513b633],
16	were	VBD	O	be	cop	17	SENT_63	[p4l1551t559r1752b612],
17	eligible	JJ	O	eligible	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l1796t533r2129b634],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p4l1796t533r2129b634],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	2	SENT_64	[p4l8t660r133b738],
2	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	3	SENT_64	[p4l166t661r508b760],
3	provided	VBD	O	provide	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l543t660r918b760],
4	written	VBN	O	write	amod	6	SENT_64	[p4l947t661r1261b740],
5	informed	VBN	O	inform	amod	6	SENT_64	[p4l1295t659r1697b739],
6	consent	NN	O	consent	dobj	3	SENT_64	[p4l1733t677r2088b739],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p4l1733t677r2088b739],

1	STU	NNP	O	STU	nn	5	SENT_65	[p4l12t935r154b985],
2	DY	NNP	O	DY	nn	5	SENT_65	[p4l173t936r268b984],
3	OVERSIGHT	NNP	O	OVERSIGHT	nn	5	SENT_65	[p4l300t935r761b985],
4	The	NNP	O	The	nn	5	SENT_65	[p4l8t1034r169b1112],
5	protocol	NN	O	protocol	nsubjpass	7	SENT_65	[p4l217t1034r578b1133],
6	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_65	[p4l623t1060r785b1113],
7	approved	VBN	O	approve	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l836t1034r1226b1133],
8	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1276t1034r1373b1133],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_65	[p4l1419t1034r1552b1112],
10	institutional	JJ	O	institutional	amod	12	SENT_65	[p4l1601t1034r2134b1113],
11	review	NN	O	review	nn	12	SENT_65	[p4l12t1163r292b1241],
12	board	NN	O	board	agent	7	SENT_65	[p4l320t1162r568b1240],
13	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l601t1188r689b1240],
14	independent	JJ	O	independent	amod	16	SENT_65	[p4l717t1162r1256b1261],
15	ethics	NNS	O	ethic	nn	16	SENT_65	[p4l1283t1162r1534b1240],
16	committee	NN	O	committee	conj_or	12	SENT_65	[p4l1569t1163r2030b1240],
17	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l2060t1178r2139b1240],
18	each	DT	O	each	det	20	SENT_65	[p4l12t1290r205b1368],
19	participating	VBG	O	participate	amod	20	SENT_65	[p4l236t1291r798b1391],
20	site	NN	O	site	prep_at	7	SENT_65	[p4l828t1291r971b1368],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1004t1290r1162b1369],
22	complied	VBN	O	comply	conj_and	7	SENT_65	[p4l1195t1290r1591b1390],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1619t1290r1814b1369],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_65	[p4l1848t1290r1981b1368],
25	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	International	nn	27	SENT_65	[p4l2013t1298r2133b1368, p4l12t1418r487b1497],
26	Ethical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ethical	nn	27	SENT_65	[p4l514t1418r816b1496],
27	Guidelines	NNS	ORGANIZATION	guideline	prep_with	22	SENT_65	[p4l843t1418r1304b1497],
28	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1335t1417r1458b1497],
29	Biomedical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biomedical	nn	31	SENT_65	[p4l1482t1418r1964b1497],
30	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	31	SENT_65	[p4l1991t1425r2133b1501, p4l13t1546r289b1624],
31	Involving	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Involving	prep_for	27	SENT_65	[p4l323t1546r724b1647],
32	Human	JJ	ORGANIZATION	human	amod	33	SENT_65	[p4l756t1554r1080b1625],
33	Subjects	NNS	ORGANIZATION	subject	dobj	7	SENT_65	[p4l1117t1546r1489b1646],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1117t1546r1489b1646],
35	Good	JJ	O	good	amod	38	SENT_65	[p4l1529t1546r1767b1625],
36	Clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	38	SENT_65	[p4l1802t1546r2134b1625],
37	Practice	NN	O	practice	nn	38	SENT_65	[p4l11t1675r348b1753],
38	guidelines	NNS	O	guideline	appos	33	SENT_65	[p4l389t1674r858b1775],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l389t1674r858b1775],
40	the	DT	O	the	det	41	SENT_65	[p4l905t1674r1038b1752],
41	Declaration	NN	O	declaration	conj_and	33	SENT_65	[p4l1077t1674r1579b1753],
42	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1620t1673r1720b1753],
43	Helsinki	NNP	LOCATION	Helsinki	prep_of	41	SENT_65	[p4l1742t1674r2129b1770],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1742t1674r2129b1770],
45	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l11t1802r165b1881],
46	local	JJ	O	local	amod	47	SENT_65	[p4l188t1802r384b1881],
47	laws	NNS	O	law	conj_and	33	SENT_65	[p4l407t1802r612b1881],
48	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l407t1802r612b1881],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_66	[p4l639t1802r795b1880],
2	study	NN	O	study	nsubjpass	4	SENT_66	[p4l821t1802r1042b1902],
3	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_66	[p4l1058t1828r1216b1881],
4	designed	VBN	O	design	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l1243t1802r1610b1903],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l1635t1802r1730b1902],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_66	[p4l1751t1802r1879b1880],
7	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	agent	4	SENT_66	[p4l1905t1828r2133b1902, p4l13t1956r147b2009],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_66	[p4l198t1929r516b2021],
9	Pfizer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pfizer	dobj	4	SENT_66	[p4l198t1929r516b2021],
10	)	VBN	O	)	partmod	9	SENT_66	[p4l198t1929r516b2021],
11	together	RB	O	together	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l571t1930r941b2031],
12	With	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l982t1930r1180b2009],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_66	[p4l1229t1930r1364b2008],
14	members	NNS	O	member	prep_together_with	19	SENT_66	[p4l1413t1930r1817b2009],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l1868t1929r1969b2009],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_66	[p4l2000t1930r2134b2008],
17	PROFILE	NNP	O	PROFILE	prep_of	14	SENT_66	[p4l11t2064r394b2141],
18	1007	CD	DATE	1007	num	17	SENT_66	[p4l440t2064r638b2137],
19	steering	VBG	O	steer	xcomp	10	SENT_66	[p4l681t2059r1027b2159],
20	committee	NN	O	committee	nsubj	22	SENT_66	[p4l1066t2059r1526b2137],
21	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_66	[p4l1571t2065r1728b2149],
22	see	VBP	O	see	ccomp	19	SENT_66	[p4l1571t2065r1728b2149],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_66	[p4l1769t2058r1902b2136],
24	Supplementary	NNP	O	Supplementary	nn	25	SENT_66	[p4l1945t2064r2133b2158, p4l11t2185r501b2285],
25	Appendix	NNP	O	Appendix	dobj	22	SENT_66	[p4l526t2185r964b2285],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l526t2185r964b2285],
27	available	JJ	O	available	amod	25	SENT_66	[p4l1002t2185r1373b2265],
28	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l1402t2185r1598b2265],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_66	[p4l1631t2185r1764b2263],
30	full	JJ	O	full	amod	31	SENT_66	[p4l1797t2184r1946b2265],
31	text	NN	O	text	prep_with	27	SENT_66	[p4l1979t2202r2139b2263],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l12t2313r113b2393],
33	this	DT	O	this	det	34	SENT_66	[p4l131t2314r290b2392],
34	article	NN	O	article	prep_of	31	SENT_66	[p4l328t2314r595b2392],
35	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l631t2331r710b2392],
36	NEJM.org	NN	O	nejm.org	nn	37	SENT_66	[p4l738t2321r1215b2415],
37	)	NN	O	)	prep_at	34	SENT_66	[p4l738t2321r1215b2415],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l738t2321r1215b2415],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_67	[p4l1253t2314r1414b2392],
2	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	nsubj	3	SENT_67	[p4l1451t2340r1795b2414],
3	collected	VBN	O	collect	_	0	SENT_67	[p4l1828t2314r2133b2393, p4l12t2442r107b2520],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_67	[p4l137t2442r265b2520],
5	data	NNS	O	datum	dobj	3	SENT_67	[p4l296t2442r473b2520],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_67	[p4l501t2442r654b2520],
7	analyzed	VBD	O	analyze	conj_and	3	SENT_67	[p4l683t2442r1047b2541],
8	them	PRP	O	they	dobj	7	SENT_67	[p4l1077t2442r1291b2520],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_67	[p4l1320t2443r1401b2519],
10	conjunction	NN	O	conjunction	prep_in	7	SENT_67	[p4l1432t2443r1920b2541],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_67	[p4l1945t2442r2134b2521],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_67	[p4l12t2570r145b2648],
13	authors	NNS	O	author	prep_with	7	SENT_67	[p4l182t2570r530b2649],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p4l182t2570r530b2649],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_68	[p4l569t2570r730b2649],
2	corresponding	JJ	O	corresponding	amod	3	SENT_68	[p4l769t2570r1399b2671],
3	author	NN	O	author	nsubj	4	SENT_68	[p4l1433t2570r1716b2649],
4	Wrote	VBD	O	write	_	0	SENT_68	[p4l1746t2587r1993b2649],
5	all	PDT	O	all	predet	7	SENT_68	[p4l2031t2570r2135b2648],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_68	[p4l12t2697r143b2775],
7	drafts	NNS	O	draft	dobj	4	SENT_68	[p4l172t2696r419b2776],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_68	[p4l450t2696r549b2776],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_68	[p4l559t2697r689b2775],
10	manuscript	NN	O	manuscript	prep_of	7	SENT_68	[p4l718t2698r1220b2797],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p4l718t2698r1220b2797],

1	All	PDT	O	all	predet	3	SENT_69	[p4l1250t2697r1373b2775],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_69	[p4l1401t2697r1532b2775],
3	authors	NNS	O	author	nsubj	4	SENT_69	[p4l1560t2697r1875b2777],
4	made	VBD	O	make	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l1906t2697r2134b2776],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_69	[p4l12t2825r145b2903],
6	decision	NN	O	decision	dobj	4	SENT_69	[p4l184t2825r536b2904],
7	to	TO	O	to	aux	8	SENT_69	[p4l574t2842r656b2904],
8	submit	VB	O	submit	infmod	6	SENT_69	[p4l697t2825r995b2905],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_69	[p4l1029t2825r1162b2903],
10	manuscript	NN	O	manuscript	dobj	8	SENT_69	[p4l1200t2826r1693b2925],
11	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l1725t2824r1849b2904],
12	publication	NN	O	publication	prep_for	10	SENT_69	[p4l1882t2825r2133b2925, p4l12t2954r276b3032],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l311t2953r469b3032],
14	vouch	NN	O	vouch	conj_and	12	SENT_69	[p4l501t2953r753b3033],
15	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l789t2952r912b3032],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_69	[p4l946t2953r1078b3031],
17	accuracy	NN	O	accuracy	prep_for	8	SENT_69	[p4l1114t2979r1485b3053],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l1516t2953r1674b3032],
19	completeness	NN	O	completeness	prep_for	8	SENT_69	[p4l1711t2953r2133b3053, p4l12t3107r196b3159],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l231t3080r331b3160],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_69	[p4l345t3081r478b3159],
22	data	NNS	O	datum	prep_of	17	SENT_69	[p4l510t3081r693b3160],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l723t3081r881b3160],
24	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l912t3080r1036b3160],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_69	[p4l1066t3081r1198b3159],
26	fidelity	NN	O	fidelity	prep_for	8	SENT_69	[p4l1230t3080r1537b3181],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l1565t3080r1665b3160],
28	this	DT	O	this	det	29	SENT_69	[p4l1679t3081r1839b3159],
29	report	NN	O	report	prep_of	26	SENT_69	[p4l1872t3098r2139b3181],
30	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l12t3226r94b3288],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_69	[p4l132t3210r264b3288],
32	study	NN	O	study	nn	33	SENT_69	[p4l302t3210r532b3309],
33	protocol	NN	O	protocol	prep_to	8	SENT_69	[p4l561t3210r945b3309],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l561t3210r945b3309],
