1	hiiiﬁﬁn	NN	O	hiiiﬁﬁn	nn	2	SENT_1	[p1l109t21r402b108],
2	genetics	NNS	O	genetics	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l426t50r754b128],
3	doi	FW	O	doi	dep	2	SENT_1	[p1l1571t207r1626b233],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1571t207r1626b233],
5	10.1111	CD	NUMBER	10.1111	dep	3	SENT_1	[p1l1641t208r2154b240],
6	/	:	O	/	punct	2	SENT_1	[p1l1641t208r2154b240],
7	j.1469-1809	CD	DURATION	j.1469-1809	num	8	SENT_1	[p1l1641t208r2154b240],
8	.2010.00584	NN	O	.2010.00584	dep	2	SENT_1	[p1l1641t208r2154b240],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1641t208r2154b240],

1	x	CC	O	x	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1641t208r2154b240],

1	Association	NNP	O	Association	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l96t305r493b361],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l521t303r593b361],
3	SLC6A	NNP	O	SLC6A	prep_of	1	SENT_3	[p1l615t307r830b361],
4	12	CD	NUMBER	12	num	5	SENT_3	[p1l844t307r916b361],
5	variants	NNS	O	variant	dep	1	SENT_3	[p1l939t305r1218b361],
6	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1242t304r1398b361],
7	aspirin-intolerant	JJ	O	aspirin-intolerant	amod	8	SENT_3	[p1l1427t304r2034b376],
8	asthma	NN	O	asthma	prep_with	5	SENT_3	[p1l98t395r349b452],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l379t396r435b451],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_3	[p1l463t412r499b452],
11	Korean	JJ	MISC	korean	amod	12	SENT_3	[p1l529t399r770b452],
12	population	NN	O	population	prep_in	8	SENT_3	[p1l801t395r1177b467],

1	Charisse	NNP	PERSON	Charisse	nn	5	SENT_4	[p1l98t535r258b569],
2	Flerida	NNP	PERSON	Flerida	nn	5	SENT_4	[p1l276t535r407b569],
3	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	nn	5	SENT_4	[p1l423t537r463b568],
4	Pasaje	NNP	PERSON	Pasaje	nn	5	SENT_4	[p1l482t531r631b578],
5	‘	NNP	O	‘	dep	24	SENT_4	[p1l482t531r631b578],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l482t531r631b578],
7	Jeong-Hyun	NNP	PERSON	Jeong-Hyun	nn	9	SENT_4	[p1l647t537r886b578],
8	Kim	NNP	PERSON	Kim	nn	9	SENT_4	[p1l905t531r1008b574],
9	‘	NNP	O	‘	appos	5	SENT_4	[p1l905t531r1008b574],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l905t531r1008b574],
11	Byung-Lae	NNP	PERSON	Byung-Lae	nn	12	SENT_4	[p1l1027t537r1235b578],
12	Parkz	NNP	PERSON	Parkz	appos	5	SENT_4	[p1l1252t531r1365b574],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1252t531r1365b574],
14	Hyun	NNP	PERSON	Hyun	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l1385t537r1484b578],
15	Sub	NN	PERSON	sub	nn	16	SENT_4	[p1l1501t535r1573b569],
16	Cheongz	NNP	PERSON	Cheongz	appos	5	SENT_4	[p1l1589t531r1771b578],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1589t531r1771b578],
18	Ji-Yong	NNP	PERSON	Ji-Yong	nn	20	SENT_4	[p1l1787t535r1931b578],
19	Chun	NNP	PERSON	Chun	nn	20	SENT_4	[p1l1949t531r2080b574],
20	‘	NNP	O	‘	appos	5	SENT_4	[p1l1949t531r2080b574],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1949t531r2080b574],
22	Tae-Joon	NNP	O	Tae-Joon	nn	23	SENT_4	[p1l96t595r273b627],
23	Park	NNP	O	Park	appos	5	SENT_4	[p1l292t589r405b632],
24	‘	NN	O	‘	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l292t589r405b632],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l292t589r405b632],
26	Jin-Sol	NNP	PERSON	Jin-Sol	nn	28	SENT_4	[p1l421t593r548b627],
27	Lee	NNP	PERSON	Lee	nn	28	SENT_4	[p1l567t589r661b632],
28	‘	NNP	O	‘	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l567t589r661b632],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l567t589r661b632],
30	Yongha	NNP	PERSON	Yongha	nn	32	SENT_4	[p1l677t593r829b636],
31	Kim	NNP	PERSON	Kim	nn	32	SENT_4	[p1l848t589r951b632],
32	‘	NNP	O	‘	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l848t589r951b632],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l848t589r951b632],
34	Joon	NNP	PERSON	Joon	nn	37	SENT_4	[p1l967t595r1060b627],
35	Seol	NNP	PERSON	Seol	nn	37	SENT_4	[p1l1077t593r1156b627],
36	Bae	NNP	O	Bae	nn	37	SENT_4	[p1l1176t589r1274b632],
37	‘	NNP	O	‘	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l1176t589r1274b632],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1176t589r1274b632],
39	Jong	NNP	PERSON	Jong	nn	41	SENT_4	[p1l1290t595r1383b636],
40	Sook	NNP	PERSON	Sook	nn	41	SENT_4	[p1l1401t593r1497b627],
41	Park3	NNP	O	Park3	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l1513t589r1627b632],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1513t589r1627b632],
43	Sang-Hyuk	NNP	O	Sang-Hyuk	nn	44	SENT_4	[p1l1644t593r1859b636],
44	Yoon3	NNP	O	Yoon3	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l1873t589r2004b632],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1873t589r2004b632],
46	Soo-Taek	NNP	O	Soo-Taek	nn	47	SENT_4	[p1l97t657r278b691],
47	Uh4	NNP	O	Uh4	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l295t653r376b696],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l295t653r376b696],
49	Jae-Sung	NNP	PERSON	Jae-Sung	nn	50	SENT_4	[p1l392t659r570b700],
50	Choi5	NNP	O	Choi5	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l587t653r704b696],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l587t653r704b696],
52	Yong-Hoon	NNP	O	Yong-Hoon	nn	53	SENT_4	[p1l720t659r947b700],
53	Kim5	NNP	O	Kim5	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l966t653r1069b696],
54	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l966t653r1069b696],
55	Mi-Kyeong	NNP	O	Mi-Kyeong	nn	56	SENT_4	[p1l1088t658r1304b700],
56	Kim6	NNP	O	Kim6	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l1324t653r1426b696],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1324t653r1426b696],
58	Inseon	NNP	O	Inseon	nn	60	SENT_4	[p1l1446t659r1572b691],
59	S.	NNP	O	S.	nn	60	SENT_4	[p1l1589t659r1618b691],
60	Choi7	NNP	O	Choi7	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l1636t653r1752b696],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1636t653r1752b696],
62	Sang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sang	nn	64	SENT_4	[p1l1770t659r1864b700],
63	Heon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heon	nn	64	SENT_4	[p1l1883t659r1985b691],
64	Chos	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Chos	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l2003t653r2107b696],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l2003t653r2107b696],
66	Byoung	NNP	PERSON	Byoung	nn	68	SENT_4	[p1l99t723r247b763],
67	Whui	NNP	PERSON	Whui	nn	68	SENT_4	[p1l263t720r368b754],
68	Choi9	NNP	O	Choi9	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l386t717r502b759],
69	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l386t717r502b759],
70	Choon	NNP	PERSON	Choon	appos	24	SENT_4	[p1l520t720r723b754],
71	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l520t720r723b754],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l520t720r723b754],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l520t720r723b754],

1	Sik	NNP	PERSON	Sik	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l520t720r723b754],
2	Park3	NNP	O	Park3	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l739t717r858b754],
3	*	NN	O	*	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l739t717r858b754],
4	and	CC	O	and	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l875t720r948b754],
5	Hyoung	NNP	O	Hyoung	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l967t723r1119b763],
6	Doo	NNP	O	Doo	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1138t723r1218b754],
7	Shin	NNP	O	Shin	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1234t717r1377b754],
8	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1234t717r1377b754],
9	v2	NN	O	v2	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1234t717r1377b754],
10	*	NN	O	*	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1234t717r1377b754],
11	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l100t777r108b796],
12	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l114t785r290b821],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l302t783r334b821],
14	Life	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Life	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l339t783r396b821],
15	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l410t785r517b819],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l410t785r517b819],
17	Sogang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sogang	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l535t785r639b821],
18	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l654t785r806b821],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l654t785r806b821],
20	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l824t783r911b818],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l824t783r911b818],
22	121-742	CD	NUMBER	121-742	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l933t784r1075b819],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l933t784r1075b819],
24	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1092t783r1220b821],
25	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1232t783r1264b821],
26	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1269t785r1355b812],
27	2Department	NN	O	2department	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l97t827r290b871],
28	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l302t833r334b871],
29	Genetic	JJ	O	genetic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l343t834r452b862],
30	Epidemiology	NN	O	epidemiology	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l463t833r665b871],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l463t833r665b871],
32	SNP	NN	ORGANIZATION	snp	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l683t834r760b862],
33	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l774t834r900b868],
34	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l774t834r900b868],
35	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l916t835r978b868],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l916t835r978b868],
37	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l996t833r1084b868],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l996t833r1084b868],
39	153-803	CD	NUMBER	153-803	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1106t834r1248b868],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1106t834r1248b868],
41	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1264t833r1393b871],
42	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1405t833r1437b871],
43	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1442t835r1528b862],
44	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l97t877r110b896],
45	Genome	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genome	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l117t884r238b912],
46	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l249t883r377b912],
47	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l392t884r491b912],
48	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l491t882r539b921],
49	Allergy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Allergy	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l547t882r654b921],
50	and	CC	O	and	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l666t882r720b912],
51	Respiratory	JJ	O	respiratory	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l731t884r898b921],
52	Diseases	NNS	O	disease	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l910t884r1039b918],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l910t884r1039b918],
54	Division	NN	O	division	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1054t884r1180b912],
55	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1193t882r1225b921],
56	Allergy	NNP	O	Allergy	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1227t882r1334b921],
57	and	CC	O	and	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1346t882r1400b912],
58	Respiratory	JJ	ORGANIZATION	respiratory	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1411t884r1578b921],
59	Medicine	NN	ORGANIZATION	medicine	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1590t882r1728b918],
60	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1590t882r1728b918],
61	Soonchunhyang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Soonchunhyang	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1746t883r1975b921],
62	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1990t884r2138b921],
63	Bucheon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bucheon	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l97t933r221b962],
64	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l234t933r367b971],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l234t933r367b971],
66	Bucheon	NNP	LOCATION	Bucheon	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l385t933r517b969],
67	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l385t933r517b969],
68	420	CD	NUMBER	420	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l537t934r609b962],
69	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l537t934r609b962],
70	767	CD	NUMBER	767	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l616t934r682b968],
71	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l616t934r682b968],
72	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l698t933r827b971],
73	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l838t933r871b971],
74	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l875t935r962b962],
75	4Division	NN	O	4division	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l98t977r239b1012],
76	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l253t982r285b1021],
77	Allergy	NNP	O	Allergy	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l288t982r395b1021],
78	and	CC	O	and	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l408t983r462b1012],
79	Respiratory	JJ	ORGANIZATION	respiratory	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l473t985r641b1021],
80	Medicine	NN	ORGANIZATION	medicine	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l653t983r792b1018],
81	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l653t983r792b1018],
82	Soonchunhyang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Soonchunhyang	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l810t983r1039b1021],
83	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1055t985r1203b1021],
84	Seoul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Seoul	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1217t983r1297b1012],
85	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1308t982r1442b1021],
86	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1308t982r1442b1021],
87	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1460t983r1547b1018],
88	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1460t983r1547b1018],
89	140-743	CD	NUMBER	140-743	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1569t984r1712b1018],
90	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1569t984r1712b1018],
91	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1728t982r1856b1021],
92	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1868t983r1900b1021],
93	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1905t985r1992b1012],
94	5	CD	NUMBER	5	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l98t1027r111b1047],
95	Division	NNP	O	Division	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l114t1035r239b1062],
96	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l270t1033r302b1071],
97	Allergy	NNP	O	Allergy	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l321t1033r428b1071],
98	and	CC	O	and	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l458t1033r511b1062],
99	Respiratory	JJ	O	respiratory	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l539t1035r707b1071],
100	Disease	NN	O	disease	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l736t1035r853b1068],
101	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l736t1035r853b1068],
102	Soonchunhyang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Soonchunhyang	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l887t1033r1117b1071],
103	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1148t1035r1297b1071],
104	Cheonan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cheonan	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1329t1033r1460b1062],
105	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1489t1033r1622b1071],
106	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1489t1033r1622b1071],
107	Cheonan	NNP	LOCATION	Cheonan	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1658t1033r1798b1069],
108	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1658t1033r1798b1069],
109	330-100	CD	NUMBER	330-100	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1832t1034r1979b1069],
110	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1832t1034r1979b1069],
111	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l2011t1033r2140b1071],
112	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l97t1083r130b1121],
113	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l134t1085r221b1112],
114	5Division	NN	O	5division	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l99t1127r240b1162],
115	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l254t1133r286b1171],
116	Internal	JJ	ORGANIZATION	internal	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l291t1133r407b1162],
117	Medicine	NN	ORGANIZATION	medicine	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l418t1133r557b1168],
118	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l418t1133r557b1168],
119	Chungbule	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chungbule	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l576t1132r730b1171],
120	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l744t1133r875b1162],
121	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l890t1135r1042b1171],
122	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l890t1135r1042b1171],
123	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1061t1132r1168b1171],
124	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1181t1132r1213b1171],
125	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1217t1133r1356b1168],
126	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1217t1133r1356b1168],
127	Cheongju	NNP	LOCATION	Cheongju	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1375t1133r1524b1171],
128	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1375t1133r1524b1171],
129	361-711	CD	NUMBER	361-711	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1542t1134r1688b1168],
130	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1542t1134r1688b1168],
131	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1704t1132r1833b1171],
132	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1845t1132r1877b1171],
133	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1881t1135r1968b1162],
134	7Department	NNP	O	7Department	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l99t1177r291b1220],
135	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l304t1182r336b1220],
136	Allergy	NNP	O	Allergy	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l340t1182r450b1220],
137	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l340t1182r450b1220],
138	Chonnam	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chonnam	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l471t1182r616b1211],
139	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l631t1182r762b1211],
140	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l779t1184r927b1220],
141	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l940t1182r1056b1211],
142	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1070t1182r1164b1211],
143	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1177t1182r1231b1211],
144	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1244t1182r1372b1211],
145	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1386t1184r1506b1211],
146	Qf	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Qf	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1521t1182r1553b1220],
147	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1558t1182r1674b1211],
148	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1688t1184r1806b1218],
149	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1688t1184r1806b1218],
150	Gu/angju	NNP	O	Gu/angju	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1827t1184r1969b1220],
151	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1827t1184r1969b1220],
152	501-757	CD	NUMBER	501-757	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1988t1184r2134b1218],
153	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1988t1184r2134b1218],
154	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l96t1231r225b1269],
155	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l237t1231r269b1269],
156	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l274t1233r360b1260],
157	8Department	NN	O	8department	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l98t1275r290b1319],
158	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l301t1280r333b1319],
159	Internal	JJ	ORGANIZATION	internal	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l336t1280r451b1310],
160	Medicine	NN	ORGANIZATION	medicine	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l461t1281r593b1310],
161	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l604t1280r658b1310],
162	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l668t1282r789b1310],
163	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l800t1280r832b1319],
164	Allergy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Allergy	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l833t1280r940b1319],
165	and	CC	O	and	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l951t1280r1005b1310],
166	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1018t1280r1132b1310],
167	Immunology	NN	ORGANIZATION	immunology	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1142t1280r1327b1319],
168	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1142t1280r1327b1319],
169	Seoul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Seoul	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1343t1281r1423b1310],
170	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1433t1280r1565b1310],
171	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1578t1282r1726b1319],
172	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1740t1280r1846b1319],
173	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1857t1280r1889b1319],
174	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1891t1280r2030b1316],
175	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1891t1280r2030b1316],
176	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l2046t1280r2134b1316],
177	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l2046t1280r2134b1316],
178	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l102t1332r114b1359],
179	10-744	CD	NUMBER	10-744	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l123t1332r245b1366],
180	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l123t1332r245b1366],
181	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l261t1331r389b1369],
182	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l401t1331r433b1369],
183	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l438t1333r525b1360],
184	9	CD	NUMBER	9	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l98t1375r111b1394],
185	Division	NN	O	division	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l114t1383r239b1410],
186	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l256t1381r289b1419],
187	Pulmonology	NNP	O	Pulmonology	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l297t1381r487b1419],
188	and	CC	O	and	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l504t1381r558b1410],
189	Allergy	NNP	O	Allergy	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l571t1381r681b1419],
190	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l571t1381r681b1419],
191	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l701t1383r878b1419],
192	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l893t1381r926b1419],
193	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l934t1381r1050b1410],
194	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1064t1381r1203b1416],
195	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1064t1381r1203b1416],
196	Chung-Ang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chung-Ang	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1226t1381r1404b1419],
197	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1423t1383r1571b1419],
198	Yongsan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Yongsan	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1591t1383r1708b1419],
199	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1724t1381r1857b1419],
200	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1724t1381r1857b1419],
201	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1879t1381r1966b1416],
202	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1879t1381r1966b1416],
203	140-757	CD	NUMBER	140-757	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l1991t1382r2134b1416],
204	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1991t1382r2134b1416],
205	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l96t1431r225b1469],
206	of	IN	O	of	dep	207	SENT_6	[p1l237t1431r269b1469],
207	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l273t1433r360b1460],

1	Summary	NN	O	summary	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l98t1621r307b1666],

1	Aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nn	2	SENT_8	[p1l86t1709r396b1749],
2	—	NN	O	—	nsubj	8	SENT_8	[p1l86t1709r396b1749],
3	intolerant	JJ	O	intolerant	amod	7	SENT_8	[p1l86t1709r396b1749],
4	asthma	NN	O	asthma	nn	7	SENT_8	[p1l414t1709r530b1739],
5	(	NN	O	(	nn	7	SENT_8	[p1l550t1710r643b1748],
6	AIA	NN	ORGANIZATION	aium	nn	7	SENT_8	[p1l550t1710r643b1748],
7	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_8	[p1l550t1710r643b1748],
8	occurs	VBZ	O	occur	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l664t1720r773b1739],
9	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l791t1709r873b1739],
10	asthma	NN	O	asthma	nn	11	SENT_8	[p1l890t1709r1006b1739],
11	exacerbation	NN	O	exacerbation	prep_from	8	SENT_8	[p1l1025t1709r1241b1739],
12	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1259t1709r1334b1739],
13	exposure	NN	O	exposure	prep_after	8	SENT_8	[p1l1352t1720r1502b1749],
14	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1521t1717r1553b1739],
15	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	prep_to	13	SENT_8	[p1l1573t1710r1694b1749],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1573t1710r1694b1749],

1	However	RB	O	however	advmod	11	SENT_9	[p1l1715t1711r1877b1745],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1715t1711r1877b1745],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_9	[p1l1897t1709r1950b1739],
4	underlying	JJ	O	underlying	amod	5	SENT_9	[p1l1968t1709r2154b1749],
5	mechanisms	NNS	O	mechanism	nsubj	11	SENT_9	[p1l87t1759r292b1789],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l303t1759r342b1789],
7	AIA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	AIA	nn	8	SENT_9	[p1l344t1760r417b1789],
8	occurrence	NN	O	occurrence	prep_of	5	SENT_9	[p1l427t1770r616b1789],
9	are	VBP	O	be	cop	11	SENT_9	[p1l627t1770r674b1789],
10	still	RB	O	still	advmod	11	SENT_9	[p1l685t1759r741b1789],
11	unclear	JJ	O	unclear	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l750t1759r881b1789],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l750t1759r881b1789],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_10	[p1l894t1759r962b1789],
2	critical	JJ	O	critical	amod	3	SENT_10	[p1l974t1759r1088b1789],
3	role	NN	O	role	nsubj	37	SENT_10	[p1l1098t1759r1161b1789],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1172t1759r1211b1789],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_10	[p1l1214t1759r1266b1789],
6	solute	JJ	O	solute	amod	12	SENT_10	[p1l1276t1759r1375b1789],
7	carrier	NN	O	carrier	nn	12	SENT_10	[p1l1386t1760r1498b1789],
8	family	NN	O	family	nn	12	SENT_10	[p1l1506t1759r1613b1799],
9	6	CD	NUMBER	6	num	12	SENT_10	[p1l1622t1761r1640b1790],
10	(	NN	O	(	nn	12	SENT_10	[p1l1653t1760r1949b1798],
11	neurotransmitter	NN	O	neurotransmitter	nn	12	SENT_10	[p1l1653t1760r1949b1798],
12	transporter	NN	O	transporter	prep_of	3	SENT_10	[p1l1958t1767r2150b1799],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1958t1767r2150b1799],
14	betaine/GABA	NN	O	betaine/gaba	nn	16	SENT_10	[p1l86t1809r358b1848],
15	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	16	SENT_10	[p1l86t1809r358b1848],
16	member	NN	O	member	appos	12	SENT_10	[p1l373t1809r516b1839],
17	12	CD	NUMBER	12	number	18	SENT_10	[p1l530t1810r567b1839],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	23	SENT_10	[p1l583t1810r675b1848],
19	SLC	NN	O	slc	nn	23	SENT_10	[p1l583t1810r675b1848],
20	6A	NN	O	6a	nn	23	SENT_10	[p1l678t1810r724b1840],
21	12	CD	NUMBER	12	num	23	SENT_10	[p1l733t1809r781b1849],
22	)	NN	O	)	nn	23	SENT_10	[p1l733t1809r781b1849],
23	gene	NN	O	gene	dep	16	SENT_10	[p1l795t1820r873b1849],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l886t1810r919b1839],
25	GABAergic	JJ	MISC	gabaergic	amod	26	SENT_10	[p1l932t1810r1132b1849],
26	transmission	NN	O	transmission	prep_in	23	SENT_10	[p1l1145t1810r1362b1845],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1145t1810r1362b1845],
28	which	WDT	O	which	nsubjpass	30	SENT_10	[p1l1376t1809r1483b1839],
29	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	30	SENT_10	[p1l1494t1810r1517b1839],
30	associated	VBN	O	associate	rcmod	3	SENT_10	[p1l1530t1809r1696b1839],
31	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1707t1809r1785b1839],
32	mucus	NN	O	mucus	nn	33	SENT_10	[p1l1797t1820r1906b1839],
33	production	NN	O	production	prep_with	30	SENT_10	[p1l1918t1809r2108b1849],
34	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l2120t1810r2153b1839],
35	asthma	NN	O	asthma	prep_in	33	SENT_10	[p1l87t1859r212b1895],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l87t1859r212b1895],
37	makes	VBZ	O	make	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l227t1859r329b1889],
38	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	41	SENT_10	[p1l342t1860r365b1889],
39	a	DT	O	a	det	41	SENT_10	[p1l378t1870r394b1889],
40	candidate	NN	O	candidate	nn	41	SENT_10	[p1l407t1859r567b1889],
41	gene	NN	O	gene	xcomp	37	SENT_10	[p1l580t1870r659b1899],
42	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l672t1859r721b1889],
43	AIA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	AIA	nn	45	SENT_10	[p1l731t1860r805b1889],
44	association	NN	O	association	nn	45	SENT_10	[p1l817t1860r999b1889],
45	study	NN	O	study	prep_for	41	SENT_10	[p1l1011t1859r1104b1899],
46	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1011t1859r1104b1899],

1	Eight	CD	NUMBER	eight	num	4	SENT_11	[p1l1118t1859r1211b1899],
2	single	JJ	O	single	amod	4	SENT_11	[p1l1224t1859r1318b1899],
3	nucleotide	NN	O	nucleotide	nn	4	SENT_11	[p1l1331t1859r1510b1889],
4	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubj	5	SENT_11	[p1l1522t1859r1787b1899],
5	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1802t1859r1916b1898],
6	SNPS	NN	O	snp	nn	7	SENT_11	[p1l1802t1859r1916b1898],
7	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	13	SENT_11	[p1l1802t1859r1916b1898],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1931t1860r1964b1889],
9	SLC	NNP	O	SLC	nn	10	SENT_11	[p1l1979t1860r2058b1890],
10	6A	NNP	O	6A	prep_in	7	SENT_11	[p1l2061t1860r2107b1889],
11	12	CD	NUMBER	12	num	10	SENT_11	[p1l2116t1860r2153b1889],
12	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_11	[p1l86t1920r167b1939],
13	genotyped	VBN	O	genotype	ccomp	5	SENT_11	[p1l178t1909r358b1949],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l367t1910r400b1939],
15	163	CD	NUMBER	163	num	17	SENT_11	[p1l413t1910r471b1939],
16	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nn	17	SENT_11	[p1l483t1909r779b1949],
17	—	NN	O	—	prep_in	13	SENT_11	[p1l483t1909r779b1949],
18	intolerant	JJ	O	intolerant	amod	22	SENT_11	[p1l483t1909r779b1949],
19	asthma	NN	O	asthma	nn	22	SENT_11	[p1l789t1909r905b1939],
20	(	NN	O	(	nn	22	SENT_11	[p1l917t1910r1010b1948],
21	AIA	NN	ORGANIZATION	aium	nn	22	SENT_11	[p1l917t1910r1010b1948],
22	)	NN	O	)	dep	17	SENT_11	[p1l917t1910r1010b1948],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1023t1909r1084b1939],
24	429	CD	NUMBER	429	num	32	SENT_11	[p1l1094t1910r1155b1939],
25	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nn	32	SENT_11	[p1l1166t1909r1428b1949],
26	—	NN	O	—	nn	32	SENT_11	[p1l1166t1909r1428b1949],
27	tolerant	JJ	O	tolerant	amod	32	SENT_11	[p1l1166t1909r1428b1949],
28	asthma	NN	O	asthma	nn	32	SENT_11	[p1l1438t1909r1554b1939],
29	(	NN	O	(	nn	32	SENT_11	[p1l1567t1909r1668b1948],
30	ATA	NN	ORGANIZATION	ata	nn	32	SENT_11	[p1l1567t1909r1668b1948],
31	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	32	SENT_11	[p1l1567t1909r1668b1948],
32	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	13	SENT_11	[p1l1680t1910r1810b1949],
33	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1821t1909r1860b1939],
34	Korean	JJ	MISC	korean	amod	35	SENT_11	[p1l1863t1911r1987b1939],
35	ethnicity	NN	O	ethnicity	prep_of	32	SENT_11	[p1l1997t1909r2150b1949],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1997t1909r2150b1949],

1	Associations	NNS	O	association	nsubjpass	9	SENT_12	[p1l86t1960r293b1989],
2	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l310t1959r454b1989],
3	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	prep_between	1	SENT_12	[p1l470t1959r734b1999],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l752t1959r791b1989],
5	SLC6/112	NN	O	slc6/112	prep_of	3	SENT_12	[p1l803t1960r978b1990],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l994t1959r1055b1989],
7	AIA	NN	ORGANIZATION	aium	prep_of	3	SENT_12	[p1l1070t1960r1143b1989],
8	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_12	[p1l1159t1970r1240b1989],
9	analysed	VBN	O	analyse	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1258t1959r1399b1999],
10	using	VBG	O	use	xcomp	9	SENT_12	[p1l1415t1960r1504b1999],
11	multivariate	JJ	O	multivariate	amod	13	SENT_12	[p1l1520t1959r1722b1989],
12	logistic	JJ	O	logistic	amod	13	SENT_12	[p1l1738t1959r1858b1999],
13	analysis	NN	O	analysis	dobj	10	SENT_12	[p1l1876t1959r2009b1999],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1876t1959r2009b1999],

1	Results	NNS	O	result	nsubj	2	SENT_13	[p1l2028t1959r2152b1989],
2	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l87t2009r214b2039],
3	that	IN	O	that	complm	57	SENT_13	[p1l231t2009r295b2039],
4	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	5	SENT_13	[p1l313t2017r376b2039],
5	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubjpass	57	SENT_13	[p1l394t2009r658b2049],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l677t2009r738b2039],
7	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_13	[p1l755t2021r771b2039],
8	haplotype	NN	O	haplotype	conj_and	5	SENT_13	[p1l788t2009r954b2049],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l972t2011r1006b2039],
10	SLC6/112	NN	O	slc6/112	prep_in	8	SENT_13	[p1l1025t2011r1208b2045],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1025t2011r1208b2045],
12	rs499368	NN	O	rs499368	nn	14	SENT_13	[p1l1229t2011r1386b2039],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	14	SENT_13	[p1l1405t2010r1442b2048],
14	P	NN	O	p	conj_and	5	SENT_13	[p1l1405t2010r1442b2048],
15	=	JJ	O	=	amod	14	SENT_13	[p1l1460t2023r1489b2034],
16	0.005	CD	NUMBER	0.005	tmod	15	SENT_13	[p1l1509t2011r1613b2045],
17	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1509t2011r1613b2045],
18	Pm	NNP	O	Pm	conj_and	5	SENT_13	[p1l1634t2011r1696b2039],
19	"	``	O	"	punct	25	SENT_13	[p1l1634t2011r1696b2039],
20	=	JJ	O	=	amod	25	SENT_13	[p1l1716t2023r1746b2034],
21	0.03	CD	NUMBER	0.03	num	22	SENT_13	[p1l1766t2010r1861b2048],
22	)	NN	O	)	tmod	20	SENT_13	[p1l1766t2010r1861b2048],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1766t2010r1861b2048],
24	rs557881	NN	O	rs557881	appos	22	SENT_13	[p1l1882t2011r2036b2039],
25	(	NN	O	(	dep	18	SENT_13	[p1l2058t2010r2152b2048, p1l87t2070r299b2098],
26	nonsynonymous	JJ	O	nonsynonymous	amod	27	SENT_13	[p1l2058t2010r2152b2048, p1l87t2070r299b2098],
27	C10R	NN	O	c10r	dep	25	SENT_13	[p1l320t2060r436b2094],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l320t2060r436b2094],
29	P	NN	O	p	appos	25	SENT_13	[p1l458t2060r483b2088],
30	=	JJ	O	=	amod	29	SENT_13	[p1l502t2072r532b2083],
31	0.007	CD	NUMBER	0.007	tmod	30	SENT_13	[p1l553t2060r657b2094],
32	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l553t2060r657b2094],
33	Pm	NNP	O	Pm	conj_and	5	SENT_13	[p1l679t2060r741b2088],
34	"	``	O	"	punct	37	SENT_13	[p1l679t2060r741b2088],
35	=	JJ	O	=	amod	37	SENT_13	[p1l763t2072r792b2083],
36	0.04	CD	NUMBER	0.04	num	37	SENT_13	[p1l813t2059r909b2097],
37	)	NN	O	)	rcmod	33	SENT_13	[p1l813t2059r909b2097],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l813t2059r909b2097],
39	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l931t2058r991b2088],
40	SLC6/l12	NN	O	slc6/l12	dep	8	SENT_13	[p1l1011t2058r1354b2093],
41	_	CD	NUMBER	_	num	40	SENT_13	[p1l1011t2058r1354b2093],
42	BL1_ht1	NN	O	bl1_ht1	nn	44	SENT_13	[p1l1011t2058r1354b2093],
43	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	44	SENT_13	[p1l1378t2059r1415b2097],
44	P	NN	O	p	conj_and	5	SENT_13	[p1l1378t2059r1415b2097],
45	=	JJ	O	=	amod	44	SENT_13	[p1l1434t2072r1464b2083],
46	0.009	CD	NUMBER	0.009	tmod	45	SENT_13	[p1l1485t2060r1589b2094],
47	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1485t2060r1589b2094],
48	PM	NNP	O	PM	nn	49	SENT_13	[p1l1611t2060r1673b2088],
49	’	NN	O	’	conj_and	5	SENT_13	[p1l1611t2060r1673b2088],
50	=	JJ	O	=	rcmod	49	SENT_13	[p1l1695t2072r1724b2083],
51	0.05	CD	NUMBER	0.05	num	52	SENT_13	[p1l1745t2059r1829b2097],
52	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	50	SENT_13	[p1l1745t2059r1829b2097],
53	respectively	RB	O	respectively	dep	50	SENT_13	[p1l1851t2058r2051b2098],
54	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1851t2058r2051b2098],
55	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	57	SENT_13	[p1l2071t2070r2152b2088],
56	significantly	RB	O	significantly	advmod	57	SENT_13	[p1l87t2107r291b2147],
57	associated	VBN	O	associate	ccomp	2	SENT_13	[p1l309t2107r475b2137],
58	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l491t2107r569b2137],
59	AIA	NN	ORGANIZATION	aium	prep_with	57	SENT_13	[p1l586t2109r659b2137],
60	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l677t2107r751b2137],
61	multiple	JJ	O	multiple	amod	63	SENT_13	[p1l768t2107r908b2147],
62	testing	NN	O	testing	nn	63	SENT_13	[p1l927t2109r1038b2147],
63	corrections	NNS	O	correction	prep_after	57	SENT_13	[p1l1056t2109r1253b2137],
64	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1056t2109r1253b2137],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1274t2109r1310b2137],
2	addition	NN	O	addition	prep_in	9	SENT_14	[p1l1327t2107r1476b2143],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1327t2107r1476b2143],
4	SNPS	NN	O	snp	nsubjpass	9	SENT_14	[p1l1497t2109r1588b2137],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1607t2107r1646b2137],
6	SLC6/112	NN	O	slc6/112	prep_of	4	SENT_14	[p1l1659t2109r1834b2138],
7	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_14	[p1l1850t2119r1931b2137],
8	significantly	RB	O	significantly	advmod	9	SENT_14	[p1l1949t2107r2153b2147],
9	associated	VBN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l87t2156r253b2186],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l268t2156r346b2186],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_14	[p1l362t2156r415b2186],
12	fall	NN	DATE	fall	nn	13	SENT_14	[p1l431t2156r481b2186],
13	rate	NN	O	rate	prep_with	9	SENT_14	[p1l497t2164r558b2186],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l576t2156r615b2186],
15	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	prep_of	13	SENT_14	[p1l625t2158r714b2192],
16	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l733t2156r775b2196],
17	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nn	18	SENT_14	[p1l790t2158r903b2196],
18	provocation	NN	O	provocation	agent	9	SENT_14	[p1l918t2158r1121b2196],
19	suggesting	VBG	O	suggest	xcomp	9	SENT_14	[p1l1137t2158r1312b2196],
20	that	IN	O	that	complm	23	SENT_14	[p1l1327t2156r1392b2186],
21	SLC6/112	NN	O	slc6/112	nsubj	23	SENT_14	[p1l1409t2157r1584b2186],
22	could	MD	O	could	aux	23	SENT_14	[p1l1600t2156r1695b2186],
23	affect	VB	O	affect	ccomp	19	SENT_14	[p1l1711t2156r1800b2186],
24	reversibility	NN	O	reversibility	dobj	23	SENT_14	[p1l1816t2156r2013b2196],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l2030t2156r2069b2186],
26	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	28	SENT_14	[p1l2077t2156r2154b2196],
27	function	NN	O	function	nn	28	SENT_14	[p1l87t2205r231b2235],
28	abnormalities	NNS	O	abnormality	prep_of	24	SENT_14	[p1l251t2205r479b2235],
29	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l499t2207r532b2235],
30	AIA	NN	ORGANIZATION	aium	nn	31	SENT_14	[p1l550t2206r623b2235],
31	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	23	SENT_14	[p1l642t2207r780b2245],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l642t2207r780b2245],

1	Although	IN	O	although	mark	8	SENT_15	[p1l802t2205r965b2245],
2	these	DT	O	these	det	3	SENT_15	[p1l985t2205r1069b2235],
3	results	NNS	O	result	nsubj	8	SENT_15	[p1l1089t2205r1192b2235],
4	are	VBP	O	be	cop	8	SENT_15	[p1l1212t2217r1260b2235],
5	preliminary	JJ	O	preliminary	amod	8	SENT_15	[p1l1279t2205r1477b2245],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1497t2205r1557b2235],
7	future	JJ	DATE	future	amod	8	SENT_15	[p1l1575t2205r1676b2235],
8	replications	NNS	O	replication	advcl	18	SENT_15	[p1l1697t2205r1889b2245],
9	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_15	[p1l1910t2217r1957b2235],
10	needed	VBN	O	need	rcmod	8	SENT_15	[p1l1977t2205r2100b2235],
11	to	TO	O	to	aux	12	SENT_15	[p1l2119t2213r2152b2235],
12	confirm	VB	O	confirm	xcomp	10	SENT_15	[p1l88t2254r225b2284],
13	these	DT	O	these	det	14	SENT_15	[p1l242t2254r326b2284],
14	ﬁndings	NNS	O	ﬁndings	dobj	12	SENT_15	[p1l343t2254r487b2294],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l343t2254r487b2294],
16	this	DT	O	this	det	17	SENT_15	[p1l507t2254r564b2284],
17	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	18	SENT_15	[p1l582t2254r672b2294],
18	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l688t2254r816b2284],
19	evidence	NN	O	evidence	dobj	18	SENT_15	[p1l833t2254r981b2284],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1000t2254r1039b2284],
21	association	NN	O	association	prep_of	19	SENT_15	[p1l1049t2256r1230b2284],
22	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1246t2254r1391b2284],
23	variants	NNS	O	variant	prep_between	21	SENT_15	[p1l1407t2256r1536b2284],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1553t2256r1586b2284],
25	SLC6/112	NN	O	slc6/112	nn	28	SENT_15	[p1l1605t2255r1780b2284],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1796t2254r1857b2284],
27	AIA	NN	ORGANIZATION	aium	nn	28	SENT_15	[p1l1872t2255r1946b2284],
28	occurrence	NN	O	occurrence	prep_in	23	SENT_15	[p1l1963t2266r2152b2284],
29	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l87t2320r204b2348],
30	asthmatics	NNS	O	asthmatic	prep_among	18	SENT_15	[p1l217t2308r388b2339],
31	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l402t2309r435b2338],
32	a	DT	O	a	det	34	SENT_15	[p1l449t2320r465b2339],
33	Korean	JJ	LOCATION	korean	amod	34	SENT_15	[p1l478t2310r601b2339],
34	population	NN	O	population	prep_in	30	SENT_15	[p1l614t2308r808b2348],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l614t2308r808b2348],

1	Keywords	NNS	O	keyword	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l162t2432r330b2470],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l162t2432r330b2470],
3	Aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nn	4	SENT_16	[p1l354t2432r649b2470],
4	—	NN	O	—	dep	1	SENT_16	[p1l354t2432r649b2470],
5	intolerant	JJ	O	intolerant	amod	12	SENT_16	[p1l354t2432r649b2470],
6	asthma	NN	O	asthma	nn	12	SENT_16	[p1l662t2432r781b2466],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l662t2432r781b2466],
8	SLC6/112	NN	O	slc6/112	dep	12	SENT_16	[p1l798t2433r973b2466],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l798t2433r973b2466],
10	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	dep	12	SENT_16	[p1l987t2432r1235b2470],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l987t2432r1235b2470],
12	haplotype	NN	O	haplotype	dep	4	SENT_16	[p1l1250t2432r1409b2470],

1	*	NN	O	*	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l83t2545r320b2579],
2	Corresponding	VBG	O	correspond	partmod	1	SENT_17	[p1l83t2545r320b2579],
3	authors	NNS	O	author	dobj	2	SENT_17	[p1l336t2545r451b2571],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l336t2545r451b2571],
5	Hyoung	NNP	PERSON	Hyoung	nn	7	SENT_17	[p1l470t2547r591b2579],
6	Doo	NNP	PERSON	Doo	nn	7	SENT_17	[p1l606t2546r672b2571],
7	Shin	NNP	PERSON	Shin	dep	1	SENT_17	[p1l691t2545r763b2576],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l691t2545r763b2576],
9	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	appos	7	SENT_17	[p1l782t2546r960b2579],
10	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l977t2545r1011b2571],
11	Life	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Life	nn	12	SENT_17	[p1l1022t2545r1077b2571],
12	Division	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Division	prep_of	9	SENT_17	[p1l1153t2546r1277b2571],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1311t2545r1344b2571],
14	Allergy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Allergy	prep_of	12	SENT_17	[p1l1371t2545r1478b2579],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1511t2545r1563b2571],
16	Respiratory	NNP	O	Respiratory	conj_and	14	SENT_17	[p1l1596t2546r1770b2579],
17	Medicine	NNP	O	Medicine	dep	29	SENT_17	[p1l1802t2545r1948b2576],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1802t2545r1948b2576],
19	Soonchun	NNP	O	Soonchun	nn	21	SENT_17	[p1l1984t2545r2148b2571],
20	—	NNP	O	—	nn	21	SENT_17	[p1l1984t2545r2148b2571],
21	Science	NNP	O	Science	appos	17	SENT_17	[p1l83t2587r200b2617],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l83t2587r200b2617],
23	Sogang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sogang	nn	24	SENT_17	[p1l229t2587r335b2620],
24	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	17	SENT_17	[p1l360t2587r516b2620],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l360t2587r516b2620],
26	1	CD	NUMBER	1	appos	17	SENT_17	[p1l548t2587r559b2611],
27	Shinsu	NN	O	shinsu	dep	29	SENT_17	[p1l590t2586r783b2620],
28	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	27	SENT_17	[p1l590t2586r783b2620],
29	dong	NN	O	dong	dep	9	SENT_17	[p1l590t2586r783b2620],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l590t2586r783b2620],
31	Mapo	NNP	LOCATION	Mapo	nn	33	SENT_17	[p1l811t2588r957b2620],
32	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	33	SENT_17	[p1l811t2588r957b2620],
33	gu	NN	O	gu	appos	29	SENT_17	[p1l811t2588r957b2620],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l811t2588r957b2620],
35	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	appos	29	SENT_17	[p1l987t2586r1075b2617],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l987t2586r1075b2617],
37	hyang	NNP	O	hyang	nn	40	SENT_17	[p1l1153t2586r1239b2620],
38	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	40	SENT_17	[p1l1260t2587r1413b2620],
39	Seoul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Seoul	nn	40	SENT_17	[p1l1436t2586r1517b2612],
40	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	appos	29	SENT_17	[p1l1539t2586r1669b2620],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1539t2586r1669b2620],
42	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	appos	29	SENT_17	[p1l1694t2586r1782b2617],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1694t2586r1782b2617],
44	140-743	CD	NUMBER	140-743	appos	29	SENT_17	[p1l1809t2587r1937b2617],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1809t2587r1937b2617],
46	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	appos	29	SENT_17	[p1l1961t2586r2097b2620],
47	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l2121t2586r2154b2612],
48	121-742	CD	NUMBER	121-742	prep_of	46	SENT_17	[p1l85t2628r213b2658],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l85t2628r213b2658],
50	Republic	NNP	O	Republic	appos	29	SENT_17	[p1l239t2627r374b2661],
51	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l400t2627r433b2653],
52	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	prep_of	9	SENT_17	[p1l451t2629r545b2653],
53	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l451t2629r545b2653],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l572t2627r622b2653],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l572t2627r622b2653],
3	82	CD	NUMBER	82	num	4	SENT_18	[p1l650t2628r883b2658],
4	—	NN	O	—	dep	1	SENT_18	[p1l650t2628r883b2658],
5	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	6	SENT_18	[p1l650t2628r883b2658],
6	—	NN	O	—	dep	4	SENT_18	[p1l650t2628r883b2658],
7	705	CD	NUMBER	705	dep	4	SENT_18	[p1l650t2628r883b2658],
8	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	9	SENT_18	[p1l650t2628r883b2658],
9	8615	CD	DATE	8615	dep	7	SENT_18	[p1l650t2628r883b2658],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l650t2628r883b2658],
11	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	1	SENT_18	[p1l909t2629r968b2653],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l909t2629r968b2653],
13	82	CD	NUMBER	82	num	14	SENT_18	[p1l995t2628r1077b2653],
14	—	NN	O	—	dep	1	SENT_18	[p1l995t2628r1077b2653],
15	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	16	SENT_18	[p1l995t2628r1077b2653],
16	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	17	SENT_18	[p1l995t2628r1077b2653],
17	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	dep	14	SENT_18	[p1l1153t2629r1247b2653],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1153t2629r1247b2653],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1261t2627r1312b2653],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1261t2627r1312b2653],
3	82	CD	NUMBER	82	number	4	SENT_19	[p1l1327t2628r1578b2658],
4	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l1327t2628r1578b2658],
5	32	CD	NUMBER	32	num	6	SENT_19	[p1l1327t2628r1578b2658],
6	—	NN	O	—	dep	4	SENT_19	[p1l1327t2628r1578b2658],
7	621	CD	NUMBER	621	number	8	SENT_19	[p1l1327t2628r1578b2658],
8	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	4	SENT_19	[p1l1327t2628r1578b2658],
9	5105	CD	NUMBER	5105	dep	8	SENT_19	[p1l1327t2628r1578b2658],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1327t2628r1578b2658],
11	Fax	NNP	O	Fax	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l1592t2629r1651b2653],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1592t2629r1651b2653],
13	82	CD	NUMBER	82	number	14	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
14	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	11	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
15	32	CD	NUMBER	32	num	16	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
16	—	NN	O	—	dep	14	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
17	621	CD	NUMBER	621	num	18	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
18	—	NN	O	—	dep	14	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
19	502	CD	NUMBER	502	dep	18	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
20	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
21	E	NN	O	e	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
22	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	23	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
23	mail	NN	O	mail	dep	21	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
24	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1666t2627r2018b2658],
25	schalr	NN	O	schalr	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l2033t2626r2148b2660],
26	@	IN	O	@	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l2033t2626r2148b2660],
27	2026-4299	CD	DURATION	2026-4299	prep_@	25	SENT_19	[p1l82t2669r250b2699],
28	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l82t2669r250b2699],
29	E	NN	O	e	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l272t2668r379b2694],
30	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	31	SENT_19	[p1l272t2668r379b2694],
31	mail	NN	O	mail	dep	29	SENT_19	[p1l272t2668r379b2694],
32	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l272t2668r379b2694],
33	hdshin@sogang.ac.kr;	NN	O	hdshin@sogang.ac.kr;	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l403t2667r721b2702],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l744t2668r796b2694],
35	Choon	NNP	PERSON	Choon	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l818t2668r982b2694],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l818t2668r982b2694],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l818t2668r982b2694],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l818t2668r982b2694],

1	Sik	NNP	PERSON	Sik	nn	2	SENT_21	[p1l818t2668r982b2694],
2	Park	NNP	PERSON	Park	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1003t2668r1075b2699],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1003t2668r1075b2699],
4	schbc	NN	O	schbc	appos	2	SENT_21	[p1l1154t2668r1313b2694],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1154t2668r1313b2694],

1	ac	NN	O	ac	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1154t2668r1313b2694],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1154t2668r1313b2694],

1	kr	NN	O	kr	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1154t2668r1313b2694],

1	326	CD	NUMBER	326	num	2	SENT_24	[p1l6t2777r65b2804],
2	Annals	NNS	O	annals	dep	10	SENT_24	[p1l124t2782r211b2805],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l223t2782r253b2805],
4	Human	JJ	ORGANIZATION	human	amod	5	SENT_24	[p1l258t2783r357b2805],
5	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	prep_of	2	SENT_24	[p1l368t2783r479b2805],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_24	[p1l492t2782r572b2811],
7	2010	CD	DATE	2010	dep	10	SENT_24	[p1l492t2782r572b2811],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	10	SENT_24	[p1l492t2782r572b2811],
9	74,326	CD	NUMBER	74,326	num	10	SENT_24	[p1l585t2783r739b2809],
10	—	NN	O	—	dep	17	SENT_24	[p1l585t2783r739b2809],
11	334	CD	NUMBER	334	number	12	SENT_24	[p1l585t2783r739b2809],
12	©	CD	NUMBER	©	dep	10	SENT_24	[p1l1915t2782r1937b2804],
13	2010	CD	DATE	2010	dep	12	SENT_24	[p1l1948t2783r2012b2805],
14	The	DT	ORGANIZATION	the	det	17	SENT_24	[p1l2023t2782r2075b2805],
15	Authors	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Authors	nn	17	SENT_24	[p1l6t2815r111b2838],
16	Journal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Journal	nn	17	SENT_24	[p1l6t2842r199b2901],
17	compilation	NN	O	compilation	dep	26	SENT_24	[p1l221t2842r528b2901],
18	©	CD	NUMBER	©	num	22	SENT_24	[p1l550t2842r594b2886],
19	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	22	SENT_24	[p1l617t2844r741b2887],
20	Blackwell	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Blackwell	nn	22	SENT_24	[p1l762t2842r1012b2887],
21	Publishing	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Publishing	nn	22	SENT_24	[p1l1032t2842r1303b2901],
22	Ltd	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ltd	dep	17	SENT_24	[p1l1323t2842r1437b2887],
23	/	:	ORGANIZATION	/	punct	26	SENT_24	[p1l1323t2842r1437b2887],
24	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	26	SENT_24	[p1l1441t2844r1710b2901],
25	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	nn	26	SENT_24	[p1l1731t2842r1928b2901],
26	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1949t2842r2154b2887],

1	Introduction	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l14t3062r595b3140],

1	Often	RB	O	often	advmod	2	SENT_27	[p1l1154t3450r1357b3511],
2	referred	VBN	O	refer	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1386t3450r1659b3511],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1687t3466r1753b3511],
4	as	IN	O	as	amod	6	SENT_27	[p1l1786t3473r1843b3511],
5	aspirinintolerant	JJ	O	aspirinintolerant	amod	6	SENT_27	[p1l1875t3453r2137b3531, p1l9t3551r346b3612],
6	asthma	NN	O	asthma	prep_to	2	SENT_27	[p1l382t3551r637b3624],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l382t3551r637b3624],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_27	[p1l678t3551r785b3612],
9	asthma	NN	O	asthma	appos	6	SENT_27	[p1l823t3551r1060b3612],
10	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	12	SENT_27	[p1l1096t3551r1226b3612],
11	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	12	SENT_27	[p1l1262t3554r1308b3612],
12	exacerbated	VBN	O	exacerbate	rcmod	9	SENT_27	[p1l1347t3551r1756b3612],
13	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1790t3551r1873b3631],
14	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	agent	12	SENT_27	[p1l1910t3554r2139b3631],
15	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	19	SENT_27	[p2l9t20r55b78],
16	a	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_27	[p2l85t40r117b78],
17	distinct	JJ	O	distinct	amod	19	SENT_27	[p2l146t17r395b78],
18	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	19	SENT_27	[p2l424t17r666b78],
19	diagnosis	NN	O	diagnosis	auxpass	2	SENT_27	[p2l695t17r1002b98],
20	characterised	VBN	O	characterise	partmod	19	SENT_27	[p2l1034t17r1484b78],
21	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1508t17r1592b98],
22	chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	24	SENT_27	[p2l1620t17r1878b78],
23	hyperplastic	JJ	O	hyperplastic	amod	24	SENT_27	[p2l1908t17r2137b98, p2l8t118r219b198],
24	rhinosinusitis	NN	O	rhinosinusitis	agent	20	SENT_27	[p2l249t118r722b191],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l249t118r722b191],
26	nasal	JJ	O	nasal	amod	27	SENT_27	[p2l754t118r916b179],
27	polyps	NNS	O	polyp	agent	20	SENT_27	[p2l941t118r1163b198],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1192t118r1315b179],
29	asthma	NN	O	asthma	nn	30	SENT_27	[p2l1342t118r1578b179],
30	attacks	NNS	O	attack	agent	20	SENT_27	[p2l1605t118r1831b179],
31	after	IN	O	after	mark	44	SENT_27	[p2l1861t118r2012b179],
32	ingestion	NN	O	ingestion	nsubj	44	SENT_27	[p2l2036t121r2137b178, p2l11t221r256b299],
33	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l288t218r368b279],
34	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	prep_of	32	SENT_27	[p2l386t221r614b299],
35	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l645t219r769b280],
36	other	JJ	O	other	amod	43	SENT_27	[p2l800t218r984b280],
37	non	JJ	O	non	amod	43	SENT_27	[p2l1013t218r1473b280],
38	—	NN	O	—	nn	43	SENT_27	[p2l1013t218r1473b280],
39	steroidal	JJ	O	steroidal	amod	43	SENT_27	[p2l1013t218r1473b280],
40	anti	JJ	O	anti	amod	43	SENT_27	[p2l1504t218r2139b299],
41	—	NN	O	—	nn	43	SENT_27	[p2l1504t218r2139b299],
42	inflammatory	JJ	O	inflammatory	amod	43	SENT_27	[p2l1504t218r2139b299],
43	drugs	NNS	O	drug	conj_and	34	SENT_27	[p2l11t320r196b401],
44	(	VBP	O	(	advcl	20	SENT_27	[p2l237t321r576b399],
45	NSAIDS	NNS	MISC	nsaid	dobj	44	SENT_27	[p2l237t321r576b399],
46	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	47	SENT_27	[p2l237t321r576b399],
47	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	48	SENT_27	[p2l622t320r775b399],
48	Bel	NNP	O	Bel	nsubjpass	2	SENT_27	[p2l622t320r775b399],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l622t320r775b399],
50	2004	CD	DATE	2004	num	51	SENT_27	[p2l815t321r1030b399],
51	)	NN	O	)	appos	48	SENT_27	[p2l815t321r1030b399],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l815t321r1030b399],

1	Although	IN	O	although	mark	7	SENT_28	[p2l1068t320r1401b401],
2	a	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_28	[p2l1436t343r1468b381],
3	number	NN	O	number	nsubj	7	SENT_28	[p2l1502t320r1775b381],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1809t320r1889b381],
5	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	3	SENT_28	[p2l1910t320r2137b381],
6	have	VBP	O	have	aux	7	SENT_28	[p2l10t421r162b482],
7	provided	VBN	O	provide	advcl	57	SENT_28	[p2l198t421r506b501],
8	estimates	NNS	O	estimate	dobj	7	SENT_28	[p2l543t424r848b482],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l888t421r968b482],
10	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	11	SENT_28	[p2l996t422r1182b483],
11	—	NN	O	—	prep_of	8	SENT_28	[p2l996t422r1182b483],
12	2	CD	PERCENT	2	number	13	SENT_28	[p2l996t422r1182b483],
13	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	11	SENT_28	[p2l996t422r1182b483],
14	up	IN	O	up	advmod	11	SENT_28	[p2l1220t442r1305b501],
15	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1344t436r1411b482],
16	20	CD	PERCENT	20	num	17	SENT_28	[p2l1450t422r1597b483],
17	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_to	14	SENT_28	[p2l1450t422r1597b483],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1636t421r1716b482],
19	AIA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	AIA	prep_of	17	SENT_28	[p2l1737t424r1886b481],
20	prevalence	NN	O	prevalence	nn	22	SENT_28	[p2l1920t442r2137b501, p2l8t521r189b583],
21	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	22	SENT_28	[p2l225t521r625b600],
22	McDonald	NNP	O	McDonald	dep	11	SENT_28	[p2l225t521r625b600],
23	et	FW	O	et	nn	24	SENT_28	[p2l655t537r716b583],
24	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	11	SENT_28	[p2l746t521r840b594],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l746t521r840b594],
26	1972	CD	DATE	1972	appos	24	SENT_28	[p2l880t524r1063b594],
27	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l880t524r1063b594],
28	Spector	NNP	PERSON	Spector	dep	24	SENT_28	[p2l1100t524r1364b602],
29	et	FW	O	et	nn	30	SENT_28	[p2l1393t537r1454b583],
30	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	28	SENT_28	[p2l1484t521r1578b594],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1484t521r1578b594],
32	1979	CD	DATE	1979	appos	30	SENT_28	[p2l1618t524r1801b594],
33	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1618t524r1801b594],
34	Hedman	NNP	PERSON	Hedman	dep	24	SENT_28	[p2l1836t522r2139b583],
35	et	FW	O	et	nn	36	SENT_28	[p2l12t639r72b684],
36	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	34	SENT_28	[p2l114t623r208b696],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l114t623r208b696],
38	1999	CD	DATE	1999	num	39	SENT_28	[p2l260t624r471b702],
39	)	NN	O	)	appos	11	SENT_28	[p2l260t624r471b702],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l260t624r471b702],
41	the	DT	O	the	det	43	SENT_28	[p2l518t623r624b684],
42	pathophysiologic	JJ	O	pathophysiologic	amod	43	SENT_28	[p2l666t623r1258b704],
43	mechanisms	NNS	O	mechanism	nsubjpass	57	SENT_28	[p2l1301t623r1719b684],
44	underlying	VBG	O	underlie	partmod	43	SENT_28	[p2l1762t623r2140b704],
45	the	DT	O	the	det	46	SENT_28	[p2l10t724r116b785],
46	development	NN	O	development	dobj	44	SENT_28	[p2l151t724r600b804],
47	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l633t724r712b785],
48	this	DT	O	this	det	51	SENT_28	[p2l730t724r848b785],
49	speciﬁc	NN	O	speciﬁc	nn	51	SENT_28	[p2l882t724r1134b804],
50	asthma	NN	O	asthma	nn	51	SENT_28	[p2l1169t724r1405b785],
51	phenotype	NN	O	phenotype	prep_of	46	SENT_28	[p2l1434t724r1805b804],
52	have	VBP	O	have	aux	57	SENT_28	[p2l1838t724r1990b785],
53	not	RB	O	not	neg	57	SENT_28	[p2l2023t739r2139b785],
54	yet	RB	O	yet	advmod	57	SENT_28	[p2l7t841r110b906],
55	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	57	SENT_28	[p2l135t825r303b886],
56	fully	RB	O	fully	advmod	57	SENT_28	[p2l330t825r483b906],
57	understood	VBN	O	understand	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l510t825r905b886],
58	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dobj	57	SENT_28	[p2l937t827r1247b906],
59	Namazy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Namazy	tmod	57	SENT_28	[p2l937t827r1247b906],
60	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	&	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1275t833r1336b886],
61	Simon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Simon	tmod	57	SENT_28	[p2l1365t828r1608b898],
62	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1365t828r1608b898],
63	2002	CD	DATE	2002	num	64	SENT_28	[p2l1641t826r1856b904],
64	)	NN	O	)	appos	59	SENT_28	[p2l1641t826r1856b904],
65	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1641t826r1856b904],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_29	[p2l99t926r239b987],
2	solute	JJ	O	solute	amod	7	SENT_29	[p2l276t926r477b987],
3	carrier	NN	O	carrier	nn	7	SENT_29	[p2l515t929r743b987],
4	family	NN	O	family	nn	7	SENT_29	[p2l775t926r992b1006],
5	6	CD	NUMBER	6	num	7	SENT_29	[p2l1027t929r1063b987],
6	(	NN	O	(	nn	7	SENT_29	[p2l1106t927r1708b1004],
7	neurotransmitter	NN	O	neurotransmitter	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1106t927r1708b1004],
8	transporter	NN	O	transporter	nn	17	SENT_29	[p2l1741t941r2134b1006],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1741t941r2134b1006],
10	betaine/GABA	NN	O	betaine/gaba	dep	17	SENT_29	[p2l8t1026r561b1105],
11	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	17	SENT_29	[p2l8t1026r561b1105],
12	member	NN	O	member	nn	17	SENT_29	[p2l630t1026r922b1087],
13	12	CD	NUMBER	12	num	17	SENT_29	[p2l988t1029r1064b1087],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_29	[p2l1134t1028r1536b1105],
15	SLC6/112	NN	O	slc6/112	nn	17	SENT_29	[p2l1134t1028r1536b1105],
16	)	NN	O	)	nn	17	SENT_29	[p2l1134t1028r1536b1105],
17	gene	NN	O	gene	nsubjpass	38	SENT_29	[p2l1605t1050r1783b1107],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1605t1050r1783b1107],
19	also	RB	O	also	advmod	20	SENT_29	[p2l1851t1026r1974b1088],
20	referred	VBN	O	refer	dep	38	SENT_29	[p2l2039t1050r2137b1087, p2l9t1128r215b1189],
21	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l247t1144r313b1189],
22	as	IN	O	as	dep	34	SENT_29	[p2l349t1151r406b1189],
23	sodium	NN	O	sodium	pobj	22	SENT_29	[p2l441t1128r695b1189],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l728t1128r851b1189],
25	chloride	NN	O	chloride	nn	26	SENT_29	[p2l884t1128r1575b1209],
26	—	NN	O	—	dep	34	SENT_29	[p2l884t1128r1575b1209],
27	dependent	JJ	O	dependent	amod	30	SENT_29	[p2l884t1128r1575b1209],
28	betaine/GABA	NN	O	betaine/gaba	nn	30	SENT_29	[p2l1606t1128r2139b1189],
29	transporter	NN	O	transporter	nn	30	SENT_29	[p2l10t1232r458b1309],
30	—	NN	O	—	dep	26	SENT_29	[p2l10t1232r458b1309],
31	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	32	SENT_29	[p2l10t1232r458b1309],
32	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	30	SENT_29	[p2l510t1230r820b1308],
33	BGT-1	NN	O	bgt-1	nn	34	SENT_29	[p2l510t1230r820b1308],
34	)	NN	O	)	prep_to	20	SENT_29	[p2l510t1230r820b1308],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l510t1230r820b1308],
36	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	38	SENT_29	[p2l863t1232r909b1290],
37	widely	RB	O	widely	advmod	38	SENT_29	[p2l946t1229r1181b1309],
38	expressed	VBN	O	express	rcmod	7	SENT_29	[p2l1220t1229r1547b1309],
39	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1583t1232r1650b1289],
40	the	DT	O	the	det	42	SENT_29	[p2l1688t1229r1795b1290],
41	proximal	JJ	O	proximal	amod	42	SENT_29	[p2l1832t1229r2139b1309],
42	tubules	NNS	O	tubule	prep_in	38	SENT_29	[p2l10t1329r254b1391],
43	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l297t1329r376b1390],
44	the	DT	O	the	det	45	SENT_29	[p2l403t1329r509b1390],
45	kidney	NN	O	kidney	prep_of	42	SENT_29	[p2l550t1329r786b1410],
46	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l826t1330r949b1391],
47	cells	NNS	O	cell	prep_in	38	SENT_29	[p2l990t1329r1129b1391],
48	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1173t1329r1252b1390],
49	the	DT	O	the	det	52	SENT_29	[p2l1279t1329r1385b1391],
50	central	JJ	O	central	amod	52	SENT_29	[p2l1428t1329r1659b1391],
51	nervous	JJ	O	nervous	amod	52	SENT_29	[p2l1699t1353r1969b1390],
52	system	NN	O	system	prep_of	47	SENT_29	[p2l2012t1353r2137b1410, p2l10t1447r143b1492],
53	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	54	SENT_29	[p2l187t1431r442b1510],
54	Rasola	NNP	O	Rasola	dep	7	SENT_29	[p2l187t1431r442b1510],
55	et	FW	O	et	nn	56	SENT_29	[p2l483t1447r543b1492],
56	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	54	SENT_29	[p2l583t1431r677b1504],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l583t1431r677b1504],
58	1995	CD	DATE	1995	appos	56	SENT_29	[p2l728t1434r911b1504],
59	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l728t1434r911b1504],
60	Matskevitch	NNP	O	Matskevitch	dep	7	SENT_29	[p2l955t1431r1377b1492],
61	et	FW	O	et	nn	62	SENT_29	[p2l1418t1447r1478b1492],
62	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	60	SENT_29	[p2l1519t1431r1613b1504],
63	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1519t1431r1613b1504],
64	1999	CD	DATE	1999	num	65	SENT_29	[p2l1663t1432r1872b1510],
65	)	NN	O	)	appos	62	SENT_29	[p2l1663t1432r1872b1510],
66	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1663t1432r1872b1510],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1920t1435r1991b1491],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_30	[p2l2031t1431r2137b1492],
3	renal	JJ	O	renal	amod	4	SENT_30	[p2l10t1532r177b1593],
4	medulla	NN	O	medullum	prep_in	10	SENT_30	[p2l207t1532r500b1604],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l207t1532r500b1604],
6	elevated	JJ	O	elevated	amod	7	SENT_30	[p2l537t1532r815b1593],
7	transcription	NN	O	transcription	nsubj	10	SENT_30	[p2l845t1535r1287b1612],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1319t1532r1398b1593],
9	SLC6A12	NN	O	slc6a12	prep_of	7	SENT_30	[p2l1417t1535r1758b1593],
10	causes	VBZ	O	cause	dep	20	SENT_30	[p2l1792t1555r1998b1593],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_30	[p2l2031t1532r2137b1593],
12	cells	NNS	O	cell	nsubj	14	SENT_30	[p2l12t1633r152b1694],
13	to	TO	O	to	aux	14	SENT_30	[p2l195t1649r261b1694],
14	accumulate	VB	O	accumulate	xcomp	10	SENT_30	[p2l306t1633r695b1694],
15	compatible	JJ	O	compatible	amod	16	SENT_30	[p2l740t1633r1120b1714],
16	osmolytes	NNS	O	osmolyte	dobj	14	SENT_30	[p2l1165t1633r1503b1714],
17	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1546t1649r1613b1694],
18	high	JJ	O	high	amod	19	SENT_30	[p2l1657t1633r1811b1714],
19	concentrations	NNS	O	concentration	prep_to	14	SENT_30	[p2l1854t1656r2137b1694, p2l10t1737r264b1795],
20	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l308t1734r673b1813],
21	Yamauchi	NNP	PERSON	Yamauchi	dobj	20	SENT_30	[p2l308t1734r673b1813],
22	et	FW	O	et	nn	23	SENT_30	[p2l712t1749r772b1795],
23	al.	FW	O	al.	nsubj	20	SENT_30	[p2l810t1734r904b1807],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l810t1734r904b1807],
25	1992	CD	DATE	1992	num	26	SENT_30	[p2l951t1735r1138b1813],
26	)	NN	O	)	appos	23	SENT_30	[p2l951t1735r1138b1813],
27	resulting	VBG	O	result	partmod	26	SENT_30	[p2l1181t1734r1478b1814],
28	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1513t1737r1580b1794],
29	a	DT	O	a	det	34	SENT_30	[p2l1618t1757r1649b1795],
30	balanced	JJ	O	balanced	amod	34	SENT_30	[p2l1684t1734r1988b1795],
31	extracellular	JJ	O	extracellular	amod	34	SENT_30	[p2l2026t1757r2137b1795, p2l10t1835r351b1896],
32	hypertonicity	NN	O	hypertonicity	nn	34	SENT_30	[p2l379t1835r848b1915],
33	(	NN	O	(	nn	34	SENT_30	[p2l882t1835r1137b1913],
34	Rasola	NN	O	rasolum	prep_in	27	SENT_30	[p2l882t1835r1137b1913],
35	et	FW	O	et	nn	36	SENT_30	[p2l1169t1850r1229b1896],
36	al.	FW	O	al.	dobj	27	SENT_30	[p2l1260t1835r1354b1908],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1260t1835r1354b1908],
38	1995	CD	DATE	1995	num	39	SENT_30	[p2l1394t1836r1605b1913],
39	)	NN	O	)	appos	36	SENT_30	[p2l1394t1836r1605b1913],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1394t1836r1605b1913],
41	thus	RB	O	thus	advmod	39	SENT_30	[p2l1640t1835r1800b1907],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1640t1835r1800b1907],
43	reducing	VBG	O	reduce	xcomp	27	SENT_30	[p2l1835t1835r2140b1915],
44	hypertonicity	NN	O	hypertonicity	nn	45	SENT_30	[p2l10t1936r478b2017],
45	stress	NN	O	stress	dobj	43	SENT_30	[p2l503t1952r690b1997],
46	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l503t1952r690b1997],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_31	[p2l721t1936r862b1997],
2	basolateral	JJ	O	basolateral	amod	3	SENT_31	[p2l886t1936r1246b1997],
3	distribution	NN	O	distribution	nsubj	7	SENT_31	[p2l1272t1936r1676b1997],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1702t1936r1782b1997],
5	SLC6A12	NN	O	slc6a12	prep_of	3	SENT_31	[p2l1795t1939r2136b1998],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	7	SENT_31	[p2l9t2046r55b2104],
7	suggestive	JJ	O	suggestive	dep	33	SENT_31	[p2l90t2046r433b2123],
8	of	IN	O	of	prep	7	SENT_31	[p2l470t2043r549b2104],
9	either	CC	O	either	dep	8	SENT_31	[p2l571t2043r770b2104],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_31	[p2l803t2066r835b2104],
11	post	NN	O	post	nn	14	SENT_31	[p2l866t2046r1322b2123],
12	—	NN	O	—	nn	14	SENT_31	[p2l866t2046r1322b2123],
13	synaptic	JJ	O	synaptic	amod	14	SENT_31	[p2l866t2046r1322b2123],
14	site	NN	O	site	dep	9	SENT_31	[p2l1359t2046r1468b2104],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1505t2043r1584b2104],
16	action	NN	O	action	prep_of	14	SENT_31	[p2l1605t2046r1816b2104],
17	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1851t2066r1924b2104],
18	alternatively	RB	O	alternatively	conj_or	9	SENT_31	[p2l1956t2043r2137b2104, p2l10t2143r284b2224],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1956t2043r2137b2104, p2l10t2143r284b2224],
20	that	IN	O	that	complm	23	SENT_31	[p2l320t2143r451b2204],
21	this	DT	O	this	det	22	SENT_31	[p2l483t2143r600b2205],
22	transporter	NN	O	transporter	nsubj	23	SENT_31	[p2l633t2159r1013b2224],
23	serves	VBZ	O	serve	ccomp	7	SENT_31	[p2l1042t2167r1240b2204],
24	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1273t2159r1339b2204],
25	clear	JJ	O	clear	amod	26	SENT_31	[p2l1375t2143r1536b2205],
26	GABA	NN	O	gaba	prep_to	23	SENT_31	[p2l1568t2146r1803b2205],
27	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1833t2143r2000b2205],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_31	[p2l2031t2143r2137b2205],
29	cerebrospinal	JJ	O	cerebrospinal	amod	30	SENT_31	[p2l12t2245r466b2326],
30	ﬂuid	NN	O	ﬂuid	prep_from	23	SENT_31	[p2l489t2245r684b2306],
31	/	:	O	/	punct	33	SENT_31	[p2l489t2245r684b2306],
32	extracellular	JJ	O	extracellular	amod	33	SENT_31	[p2l693t2245r1115b2306],
33	ﬂuid	NN	O	ﬂuid	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1137t2245r1296b2306],
34	in	IN	O	in	dep	33	SENT_31	[p2l1319t2248r1386b2305],
35	non	JJ	O	non	amod	36	SENT_31	[p2l1411t2248r1861b2326],
36	—	NN	O	—	pobj	34	SENT_31	[p2l1411t2248r1861b2326],
37	synaptic	JJ	O	synaptic	amod	38	SENT_31	[p2l1411t2248r1861b2326],
38	regions	NNS	O	region	nsubj	39	SENT_31	[p2l1888t2248r2137b2326],
39	(	VBP	O	(	rcmod	36	SENT_31	[p2l15t2346r312b2424],
40	Borden	NNP	PERSON	Borden	dobj	39	SENT_31	[p2l15t2346r312b2424],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l15t2346r312b2424],
42	1996	CD	DATE	1996	num	43	SENT_31	[p2l352t2347r561b2424],
43	)	NN	O	)	appos	40	SENT_31	[p2l352t2347r561b2424],
44	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l352t2347r561b2424],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_32	[p2l597t2346r737b2407],
2	lack	NN	O	lack	nsubj	19	SENT_32	[p2l766t2346r905b2407],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l935t2346r1014b2407],
4	agreement	NN	O	agreement	prep_of	2	SENT_32	[p2l1031t2361r1394b2426],
5	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1421t2346r1716b2407],
6	in	FW	O	in	dep	11	SENT_32	[p2l1744t2349r1811b2406],
7	vivo	FW	O	vivo	pobj	6	SENT_32	[p2l1838t2349r1983b2407],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l2016t2346r2139b2407],
9	in	FW	O	in	nn	10	SENT_32	[p2l9t2455r77b2512],
10	vitro	FW	O	vitro	conj_and	6	SENT_32	[p2l99t2455r260b2513],
11	experiments	NNS	O	experiment	prep_between	4	SENT_32	[p2l289t2455r713b2533],
12	regarding	VBG	O	regard	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l740t2452r1065b2533],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_32	[p2l1088t2452r1195b2513],
14	expression	NN	O	expression	prep_regarding	4	SENT_32	[p2l1223t2455r1581b2533],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1607t2452r1730b2513],
16	function	NN	O	function	prep_regarding	4	SENT_32	[p2l1753t2452r2046b2513],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l2073t2452r2152b2513],
18	SLC6A12	NN	O	slc6a12	prep_of	14	SENT_32	[p2l11t2556r353b2614],
19	explains	VBZ	O	explain	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l394t2553r667b2633],
20	why	WRB	O	why	advmod	31	SENT_32	[p2l704t2553r854b2633],
21	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	24	SENT_32	[p2l890t2556r962b2614],
22	precise	JJ	O	precise	amod	24	SENT_32	[p2l998t2556r1234b2633],
23	physiological	JJ	O	physiological	amod	24	SENT_32	[p2l1270t2553r1723b2633],
24	role	NN	O	role	nsubjpass	31	SENT_32	[p2l1760t2553r1889b2614],
25	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1926t2556r1994b2613],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_32	[p2l2031t2553r2137b2614],
27	nervous	JJ	O	nervous	amod	28	SENT_32	[p2l10t2677r281b2715],
28	system	NN	O	system	prep_in	24	SENT_32	[p2l311t2669r539b2734],
29	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	31	SENT_32	[p2l565t2654r669b2715],
30	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	31	SENT_32	[p2l696t2654r864b2715],
31	difﬁcult	VBN	O	difﬁcult	advcl	19	SENT_32	[p2l893t2654r1161b2715],
32	to	TO	O	to	aux	33	SENT_32	[p2l1188t2669r1254b2715],
33	determine	VB	O	determine	xcomp	31	SENT_32	[p2l1286t2654r1657b2715],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1286t2654r1657b2715],

1	An	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_33	[p2l97t2758r202b2815],
2	excitatory	JJ	O	excitatory	amod	4	SENT_33	[p2l241t2758r587b2836],
3	GABAergic	JJ	O	gabaergic	amod	4	SENT_33	[p2l627t2758r1033b2836],
4	system	NN	O	system	nsubjpass	6	SENT_33	[p2l1073t2771r1301b2836],
5	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_33	[p2l1336t2778r1458b2816],
6	described	VBN	O	describe	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1497t2755r1827b2816],
7	recently	RB	DATE	recently	advmod	6	SENT_33	[p2l1863t2755r2139b2836],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l9t2859r77b2916],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_33	[p2l116t2856r223b2917],
10	airway	NN	O	airway	nn	11	SENT_33	[p2l266t2859r487b2936],
11	epithelium	NN	O	epithelium	prep_in	6	SENT_33	[p2l529t2856r920b2936],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l529t2856r920b2936],

1	It	PRP	O	it	nsubjpass	4	SENT_34	[p2l967t2860r1018b2917],
2	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	4	SENT_34	[p2l1058t2856r1162b2917],
3	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_34	[p2l1202t2856r1369b2917],
4	revealed	VBN	O	reveal	dep	18	SENT_34	[p2l1409t2856r1690b2917],
5	that	IN	O	that	complm	12	SENT_34	[p2l1729t2856r1860b2917],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_34	[p2l1900t2856r2006b2917],
7	yaminobutyric	JJ	O	yaminobutyric	amod	11	SENT_34	[p2l2051t2875r2137b2934, p2l11t2956r477b3037],
8	acid	NN	O	acid	nn	11	SENT_34	[p2l515t2957r653b3018],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_34	[p2l692t2958r972b3035],
10	GABA	NN	O	gaba	nn	11	SENT_34	[p2l692t2958r972b3035],
11	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	12	SENT_34	[p2l692t2958r972b3035],
12	signaling	NN	O	signaling	ccomp	4	SENT_34	[p2l1014t2956r1318b3037],
13	pathway	NN	O	pathway	dobj	12	SENT_34	[p2l1349t2956r1638b3037],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1671t2959r1738b3017],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_34	[p2l1773t2956r1880b3018],
16	airway	NN	O	airway	nn	17	SENT_34	[p2l1918t2959r2139b3037],
17	epithelium	NN	O	epithelium	prep_in	13	SENT_34	[p2l12t3058r387b3139],
18	plays	VBZ	O	play	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l404t3058r568b3139],
19	a	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_34	[p2l591t3081r622b3119],
20	critical	JJ	O	critical	amod	21	SENT_34	[p2l644t3058r878b3119],
21	role	NN	O	role	dobj	18	SENT_34	[p2l897t3058r1027b3119],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1047t3061r1114b3118],
23	asthma	NN	O	asthma	nn	24	SENT_34	[p2l1136t3058r1372b3119],
24	development	NN	O	development	prep_in	18	SENT_34	[p2l1393t3058r1842b3139],
25	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1862t3058r2139b3139],
26	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	27	SENT_34	[p2l9t3162r81b3220],
27	ability	NN	O	ability	prep_through	18	SENT_34	[p2l113t3159r324b3239],
28	to	TO	O	to	aux	29	SENT_34	[p2l353t3174r419b3220],
29	enhance	VB	O	enhance	infmod	27	SENT_34	[p2l453t3159r736b3220],
30	mucus	NN	O	mucus	nn	31	SENT_34	[p2l766t3182r988b3220],
31	production	NN	O	production	dobj	29	SENT_34	[p2l1017t3159r1403b3239],
32	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	31	SENT_34	[p2l1437t3160r1671b3239],
33	Xiang	NNP	PERSON	Xiang	nsubj	18	SENT_34	[p2l1437t3160r1671b3239],
34	et	FW	O	et	nn	35	SENT_34	[p2l1700t3174r1760b3220],
35	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	33	SENT_34	[p2l1790t3159r1884b3232],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1790t3159r1884b3232],
37	2007	CD	DATE	2007	num	38	SENT_34	[p2l1918t3160r2133b3237],
38	)	NN	O	)	appos	35	SENT_34	[p2l1918t3160r2133b3237],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1918t3160r2133b3237],

1	Previous	JJ	O	previous	amod	2	SENT_35	[p2l9t3262r305b3321],
2	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	4	SENT_35	[p2l337t3260r565b3321],
3	have	VBP	O	have	aux	4	SENT_35	[p2l596t3259r749b3320],
4	indicated	VBN	O	indicate	ccomp	29	SENT_35	[p2l780t3260r1098b3321],
5	that	IN	O	that	complm	19	SENT_35	[p2l1127t3259r1258b3320],
6	during	IN	O	during	dep	12	SENT_35	[p2l1290t3260r1522b3340],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_35	[p2l1551t3259r1657b3320],
8	development	NN	O	development	nsubj	12	SENT_35	[p2l1691t3259r2139b3340],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l11t3361r91b3422],
10	allergen	NN	O	allergen	nn	11	SENT_35	[p2l104t3361r691b3442],
11	—	NN	O	—	prep_of	8	SENT_35	[p2l104t3361r691b3442],
12	induced	VBD	O	induce	dep	19	SENT_35	[p2l104t3361r691b3442],
13	airway	NN	O	airway	nn	14	SENT_35	[p2l716t3364r938b3441],
14	responses	NNS	O	response	dobj	12	SENT_35	[p2l963t3382r1302b3442],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l963t3382r1302b3442],
16	activation	NN	O	activation	nsubj	19	SENT_35	[p2l1333t3364r1666b3422],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1694t3361r1773b3422],
18	PI3K/Akt	NN	O	pi3k/akt	prep_of	16	SENT_35	[p2l1785t3361r2138b3422],
19	leads	VBZ	O	lead	ccomp	4	SENT_35	[p2l8t3463r172b3524],
20	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l210t3478r277b3524],
21	an	DT	O	a	det	22	SENT_35	[p2l316t3486r394b3524],
22	increase	NN	O	increase	prep_to	19	SENT_35	[p2l430t3466r701b3524],
23	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l738t3466r805b3523],
24	IL-13	NN	MISC	il-13	prep_in	22	SENT_35	[p2l843t3466r1036b3524],
25	that	IN	O	that	dep	26	SENT_35	[p2l1076t3463r1206b3524],
26	in	IN	O	in	dep	22	SENT_35	[p2l1242t3466r1309b3523],
27	turn	NN	O	turn	pobj	26	SENT_35	[p2l1345t3478r1512b3536],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1345t3478r1512b3536],
29	activates	VBZ	O	activate	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1554t3466r1836b3524],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_35	[p2l1874t3463r1981b3524],
31	airway	NN	O	airway	dobj	29	SENT_35	[p2l2019t3466r2137b3524, p2l8t3587r145b3645],
32	epithelial	JJ	O	epithelial	amod	35	SENT_35	[p2l182t3564r496b3645],
33	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	35	SENT_35	[p2l534t3564r649b3625],
34	(	NN	O	(	nn	35	SENT_35	[p2l690t3566r907b3643],
35	AEC	NNS	ORGANIZATION	aec	nsubj	36	SENT_35	[p2l690t3566r907b3643],
36	)	VBP	O	)	rcmod	31	SENT_35	[p2l690t3566r907b3643],
37	GABAergic	JJ	O	gabaergic	amod	38	SENT_35	[p2l952t3567r1358b3645],
38	system	NN	O	system	dobj	36	SENT_35	[p2l1397t3580r1626b3645],
39	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	40	SENT_35	[p2l1659t3564r1877b3625],
40	acts	VBZ	O	act	rcmod	38	SENT_35	[p2l1914t3580r2034b3625],
41	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l2072t3567r2139b3624],
42	autocrine	NN	O	autocrine	nn	45	SENT_35	[p3l11t23r339b81],
43	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l380t20r503b81],
44	paracrine	NN	O	paracrine	conj_and	42	SENT_35	[p3l538t23r860b100],
45	fashions	NNS	O	fashion	prep_in	40	SENT_35	[p3l899t20r1173b81],
46	to	TO	O	to	aux	47	SENT_35	[p3l1213t36r1279b81],
47	enhance	VB	O	enhance	xcomp	40	SENT_35	[p3l1323t20r1606b81],
48	mucus	NN	O	mucus	nn	49	SENT_35	[p3l1646t43r1868b81],
49	hypersecretion	NN	O	hypersecretion	dobj	47	SENT_35	[p3l1908t20r2137b100, p3l10t123r319b182],
50	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l353t120r433b181],
51	AECs	NNS	O	aec	prep_of	49	SENT_35	[p3l450t123r652b182],
52	resulting	VBG	O	result	partmod	51	SENT_35	[p3l686t120r983b201],
53	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1015t136r1080b182],
54	airway	NN	O	airway	nn	55	SENT_35	[p3l1117t123r1339b201],
55	obstruction	NN	O	obstruction	prep_to	52	SENT_35	[p3l1373t120r1769b182],
56	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	55	SENT_35	[p3l1807t122r2045b201],
57	Corry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Corry	nsubj	29	SENT_35	[p3l1807t122r2045b201],
58	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	&	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l2078t128r2138b182],
59	Kheradmand	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kheradmand	nsubj	29	SENT_35	[p3l9t222r478b295],
60	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l9t222r478b295],
61	2007	CD	DATE	2007	appos	57	SENT_35	[p3l512t225r700b295],
62	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l512t225r700b295],
63	Lu	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Lu	dep	61	SENT_35	[p3l734t226r826b283],
64	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	&	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l857t230r918b283],
65	Inman	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inman	conj_and	63	SENT_35	[p3l948t226r1189b295],
66	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l948t226r1189b295],
67	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	68	SENT_35	[p3l1223t223r1438b301],
68	)	NN	O	)	appos	63	SENT_35	[p3l1223t223r1438b301],
69	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1223t223r1438b301],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1475t226r1546b282],
2	another	DT	O	another	det	3	SENT_36	[p3l1576t222r1842b283],
3	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	8	SENT_36	[p3l1869t222r2058b302],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1869t222r2058b302],
5	it	PRP	O	it	nsubjpass	8	SENT_36	[p3l2092t225r2139b283],
6	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	8	SENT_36	[p3l10t323r113b384],
7	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_36	[p3l137t323r304b384],
8	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l327t323r533b384],
9	that	IN	O	that	complm	12	SENT_36	[p3l555t323r686b384],
10	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nsubjpass	12	SENT_36	[p3l710t326r939b403],
11	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	12	SENT_36	[p3l961t326r1007b384],
12	involved	VBN	O	involve	ccomp	8	SENT_36	[p3l1032t323r1325b384],
13	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1346t326r1414b383],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_36	[p3l1437t323r1543b384],
15	detoxiﬁcation	NN	O	detoxiﬁcation	prep_in	12	SENT_36	[p3l1570t323r2048b384],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l2073t323r2152b384],
17	GABA	NN	O	gaba	nn	18	SENT_36	[p3l13t423r430b504],
18	—	NN	O	—	prep_of	15	SENT_36	[p3l13t423r430b504],
19	lytic	JJ	O	lytic	amod	20	SENT_36	[p3l13t423r430b504],
20	picrotoxin	NN	O	picrotoxin	dep	34	SENT_36	[p3l466t426r825b504],
21	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	23	SENT_36	[p3l866t425r1040b502],
22	PT	NN	O	pt	nn	23	SENT_36	[p3l866t425r1040b502],
23	)	NN	O	)	dep	20	SENT_36	[p3l866t425r1040b502],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l866t425r1040b502],
25	an	DT	O	a	det	26	SENT_36	[p3l1081t447r1158b485],
26	antagonist	NN	O	antagonist	appos	23	SENT_36	[p3l1194t426r1544b504],
27	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1578t423r1677b484],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_36	[p3l1711t423r1817b484],
29	GABAA	NN	O	gabaa	nn	32	SENT_36	[p3l1857t426r2135b497],
30	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nn	32	SENT_36	[p3l10t541r298b606],
31	chloride	NN	O	chloride	nn	32	SENT_36	[p3l327t525r613b586],
32	channels	NNS	O	channel	prep_for	26	SENT_36	[p3l645t525r938b586],
33	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	34	SENT_36	[p3l973t525r1296b604],
34	Golovko	NNP	PERSON	Golovko	dep	15	SENT_36	[p3l973t525r1296b604],
35	et	FW	O	et	nn	36	SENT_36	[p3l1329t541r1390b586],
36	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	34	SENT_36	[p3l1419t525r1513b598],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1419t525r1513b598],
38	1995	CD	DATE	1995	num	39	SENT_36	[p3l1552t526r1762b604],
39	)	NN	O	)	appos	15	SENT_36	[p3l1552t526r1762b604],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1552t526r1762b604],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_37	[p3l1797t525r1937b586],
2	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	nsubj	7	SENT_37	[p3l1967t525r2137b585, p3l8t626r216b687],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l249t626r328b687],
4	picrotoxin	NN	O	picrotoxin	prep_of	2	SENT_37	[p3l344t629r704b706],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l733t626r816b706],
6	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	prep_by	4	SENT_37	[p3l848t629r1077b706],
7	restores	VBZ	O	restore	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l1108t641r1362b687],
8	GABA	NN	O	gaba	nn	9	SENT_37	[p3l1398t629r1633b687],
9	activity	NN	O	activity	dobj	7	SENT_37	[p3l1665t629r1922b706],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l1665t629r1922b706],

1	With	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1956t626r2138b687],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_38	[p3l10t727r116b788],
3	critical	JJ	O	critical	amod	4	SENT_38	[p3l147t727r381b788],
4	role	NN	O	role	prep_with	16	SENT_38	[p3l408t727r537b788],
5	played	VBN	O	play	partmod	4	SENT_38	[p3l563t727r783b808],
6	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l807t727r891b808],
7	SLC6A12	NN	O	slc6a12	agent	5	SENT_38	[p3l919t730r1260b789],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1289t730r1356b787],
9	GABAergic	JJ	MISC	gabaergic	amod	10	SENT_38	[p3l1386t730r1793b808],
10	transmission	NN	O	transmission	prep_in	5	SENT_38	[p3l1822t730r2137b788, p3l10t831r149b889],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l177t831r245b888],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_38	[p3l273t828r379b889],
13	brain	NN	O	brain	prep_in	10	SENT_38	[p3l408t828r603b901],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l408t828r603b901],
15	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	16	SENT_38	[p3l635t851r733b889],
16	considered	VBD	O	consider	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l765t828r1136b889],
17	it	PRP	O	it	dobj	16	SENT_38	[p3l1163t831r1210b889],
18	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1239t851r1296b889],
19	a	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_38	[p3l1327t851r1359b889],
20	candidate	NN	O	candidate	nn	21	SENT_38	[p3l1389t828r1714b889],
21	gene	NN	O	gene	prep_as	16	SENT_38	[p3l1745t851r1905b908],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1935t831r2002b888],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_38	[p3l2031t828r2137b889],
24	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	16	SENT_38	[p3l10t929r193b1009],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l221t928r301b989],
26	AIA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	AIA	prep_of	24	SENT_38	[p3l313t931r479b989],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l313t931r479b989],

1	©	RB	O	©	dep	2	SENT_39	[p3l11t1171r58b1219],
2	2010	CD	DATE	2010	dep	4	SENT_39	[p3l83t1172r218b1219],
3	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_39	[p3l242t1170r354b1219],
4	Authors	NNPS	O	Authors	_	0	SENT_39	[p3l376t1170r600b1219],

1	SLC6A12	NN	O	slc6a12	nn	2	SENT_40	[p3l1010t1264r1279b1314],
2	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l1305t1261r1777b1328],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l1801t1261r1914b1314],
4	AIA	NN	ORGANIZATION	aium	conj_and	2	SENT_40	[p3l1939t1265r2054b1313],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l104t1464r173b1518],
2	an	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_41	[p3l205t1482r279b1519],
3	attempt	NN	O	attempt	prep_in	14	SENT_41	[p3l312t1475r564b1538],
4	to	TO	O	to	aux	5	SENT_41	[p3l595t1475r658b1519],
5	examine	VB	O	examine	infmod	3	SENT_41	[p3l694t1463r972b1519],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_41	[p3l1005t1460r1107b1519],
7	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	8	SENT_41	[p3l1141t1463r1377b1538],
8	role	NN	O	role	dobj	5	SENT_41	[p3l1410t1460r1534b1519],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1566t1463r1630b1518],
10	AIA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	AIA	nn	11	SENT_41	[p3l1660t1463r1803b1518],
11	occurrence	NN	O	occurrence	prep_in	5	SENT_41	[p3l1836t1482r2053b1519, p3l18t1578r212b1626],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1836t1482r2053b1519, p3l18t1578r212b1626],
13	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	14	SENT_41	[p3l254t1578r348b1615],
14	focused	VBD	O	focus	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l388t1556r640b1615],
15	our	PRP$	O	we	poss	16	SENT_41	[p3l680t1578r794b1615],
16	analysis	NN	O	analysis	dobj	14	SENT_41	[p3l833t1556r1072b1633],
17	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1115t1578r1199b1615],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_41	[p3l1238t1556r1340b1615],
19	association	NN	O	association	prep_on	14	SENT_41	[p3l1382t1559r1735b1615],
20	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1773t1556r2054b1615],
21	SLC6/I12	NN	O	slc6/i12	prep_between	19	SENT_41	[p3l21t1654r362b1710],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l392t1651r510b1710],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_41	[p3l540t1651r642b1710],
24	occurrence	NN	O	occurrence	conj_and	19	SENT_41	[p3l675t1674r1044b1710],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1077t1651r1153b1710],
26	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nn	28	SENT_41	[p3l1172t1651r1796b1729],
27	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	28	SENT_41	[p3l1172t1651r1796b1729],
28	intolerance	NN	O	intolerance	prep_of	24	SENT_41	[p3l1172t1651r1796b1729],
29	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1829t1674r2056b1729],
30	asthmatics	NNS	O	asthmatic	prep_among	14	SENT_41	[p3l19t1746r369b1804],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l19t1746r369b1804],

1	Material	NN	O	material	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l23t1958r395b2033],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l432t1958r596b2033],
3	Methods	NNS	O	method	conj_and	1	SENT_42	[p3l637t1958r1034b2033],

1	Study	NNP	O	Study	nn	2	SENT_43	[p3l21t2175r245b2256],
2	Subjects	NNPS	O	Subjects	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l280t2175r600b2256],

1	To	TO	O	to	aux	2	SENT_44	[p3l18t2336r97b2389],
2	serve	VB	O	serve	purpcl	13	SENT_44	[p3l118t2354r273b2389],
3	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l294t2354r345b2389],
4	primary	JJ	O	primary	amod	5	SENT_44	[p3l363t2336r618b2407],
5	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_as	2	SENT_44	[p3l636t2333r876b2407],
6	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l895t2333r986b2389],
7	this	DT	O	this	det	8	SENT_44	[p3l1003t2333r1109b2389],
8	study	NN	O	study	prep_for	5	SENT_44	[p3l1130t2333r1302b2407],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1130t2333r1302b2407],
10	592	CD	NUMBER	592	num	11	SENT_44	[p3l1326t2336r1438b2389],
11	asthmatics	NNS	O	asthmatic	nsubjpass	13	SENT_44	[p3l1460t2333r1776b2389],
12	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_44	[p3l1795t2355r1944b2389],
13	recruited	VBN	O	recruit	dep	18	SENT_44	[p3l1964t2354r2053b2389, p3l19t2427r242b2483],
14	from	IN	O	from	prep	13	SENT_44	[p3l261t2427r412b2483],
15	among	IN	O	among	pcomp	14	SENT_44	[p3l434t2448r649b2500],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_44	[p3l669t2427r766b2483],
17	patients	NNS	O	patient	pobj	15	SENT_44	[p3l787t2429r1026b2500],
18	enrolled	VBD	O	enrol	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1051t2427r1306b2483],
19	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1327t2441r1379b2483],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_44	[p3l1400t2427r1497b2483],
21	Asthma	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Asthma	nn	22	SENT_44	[p3l1517t2427r1758b2483],
22	Genome	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genome	prep_at	18	SENT_44	[p3l1781t2429r2053b2483],
23	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	24	SENT_44	[p3l17t2520r309b2576],
24	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	nsubj	18	SENT_44	[p3l335t2523r566b2586],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l335t2523r566b2586],
26	a	DT	O	a	det	27	SENT_44	[p3l595t2541r624b2576],
27	part	NN	O	part	appos	24	SENT_44	[p3l646t2534r771b2594],
28	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l796t2520r868b2576],
29	Soonchunhyang	NNP	LOCATION	Soonchunhyang	nn	36	SENT_44	[p3l882t2520r1407b2594],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l882t2520r1407b2594],
31	Chunnam	NNP	LOCATION	Chunnam	prep_of	27	SENT_44	[p3l1438t2520r1773b2586],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1438t2520r1773b2586],
33	Chungbuk	NNP	LOCATION	Chungbuk	prep_of	27	SENT_44	[p3l1804t2520r2052b2594, p3l16t2612r153b2679],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1804t2520r2052b2594, p3l16t2612r153b2679],
35	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	prep_of	27	SENT_44	[p3l201t2612r376b2669],
36	National	NNP	O	National	prep_of	27	SENT_44	[p3l417t2612r692b2668],
37	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l734t2612r846b2668],
38	Chung	NNP	PERSON	Chung	prep_of	27	SENT_44	[p3l889t2612r1275b2686],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l889t2612r1275b2686],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l889t2612r1275b2686],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l889t2612r1275b2686],

1	Ang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ang	nn	3	SENT_46	[p3l889t2612r1275b2686],
2	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	3	SENT_46	[p3l1315t2615r1645b2686],
3	hospitals	NNS	O	hospital	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1685t2612r1951b2686],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1993t2615r2054b2667],
5	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	prep_in	3	SENT_46	[p3l17t2710r204b2762],
6	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l237t2706r389b2762],
7	2003-2008	CD	DATE	2003-2008	prep_from	3	SENT_46	[p3l423t2708r792b2762],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l423t2708r792b2762],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_47	[p3l833t2706r1020b2762],
2	subjects	NNS	O	subject	nsubj	3	SENT_47	[p3l1057t2706r1297b2779],
3	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1333t2706r1569b2762],
4	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	5	SENT_47	[p3l1604t2706r1824b2762],
5	symptoms	NNS	O	symptom	nsubj	36	SENT_47	[p3l1859t2725r2053b2779, p3l18t2813r168b2855],
6	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	7	SENT_47	[p3l202t2799r321b2855],
7	met	VBD	O	meet	rcmod	5	SENT_47	[p3l353t2813r474b2855],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_47	[p3l507t2799r604b2855],
9	criteria	NNS	O	criterion	dobj	7	SENT_47	[p3l640t2802r865b2855],
10	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l896t2799r987b2855],
11	asthma	NN	O	asthma	prep_for	7	SENT_47	[p3l1019t2799r1250b2865],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1019t2799r1250b2865],
13	such	JJ	O	such	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1288t2799r1428b2855],
14	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1462t2820r1513b2855],
15	cough	NN	O	cough	prep_such_as	7	SENT_47	[p3l1549t2799r1760b2873],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1549t2799r1760b2873],
17	wheeze	NN	O	wheeze	conj_or	15	SENT_47	[p3l1796t2799r2050b2865],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1796t2799r2050b2865],
19	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l19t2912r86b2946],
20	shortness	NN	O	shortness	conj_or	15	SENT_47	[p3l114t2890r397b2946],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l429t2890r501b2946],
22	breath	NN	O	breath	prep_of	15	SENT_47	[p3l517t2890r731b2957],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l517t2890r731b2957],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l765t2893r826b2946],
25	accordance	NN	O	accordance	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l856t2890r1204b2946],
26	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1234t2890r1379b2946],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_47	[p3l1409t2890r1505b2946],
28	Global	JJ	O	global	amod	29	SENT_47	[p3l1539t2890r1747b2947],
29	Initiative	NNP	O	Initiative	prep_in_accordance_with	7	SENT_47	[p3l1778t2893r2053b2946],
30	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l17t2985r108b3041],
31	Asthma	NNP	O	Asthma	prep_for	29	SENT_47	[p3l140t2985r380b3041],
32	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	31	SENT_47	[p3l420t2986r663b3057],
33	GINA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	GINA	nn	36	SENT_47	[p3l420t2986r663b3057],
34	)	NN	O	)	nn	36	SENT_47	[p3l420t2986r663b3057],
35	Global	JJ	O	global	amod	36	SENT_47	[p3l707t2985r915b3041],
36	Strategy	NN	O	strategy	xcomp	3	SENT_47	[p3l952t2987r1205b3058],
37	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1240t2985r1330b3041],
38	Asthma	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Asthma	nn	39	SENT_47	[p3l1363t2985r1603b3041],
39	Management	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Management	prep_for	36	SENT_47	[p3l1638t2989r2055b3058],
40	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l19t3078r130b3134],
41	Prevention	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Prevention	nn	42	SENT_47	[p3l153t3081r497b3134],
42	study	NN	O	study	conj_and	39	SENT_47	[p3l522t3078r693b3152],
43	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l522t3078r693b3152],

1	Evaluation	NN	O	evaluation	nsubj	5	SENT_48	[p3l720t3078r1058b3134],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1083t3078r1155b3134],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_48	[p3l1167t3078r1264b3134],
4	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_of	1	SENT_48	[p3l1290t3078r1530b3152],
5	included	VBD	O	include	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1555t3078r1829b3134],
6	airway	NN	O	airway	nn	7	SENT_48	[p3l1853t3081r2055b3152],
7	reversibility	NN	O	reversibility	nsubj	14	SENT_48	[p3l18t3170r383b3244],
8	measured	VBN	O	measure	partmod	7	SENT_48	[p3l400t3170r697b3226],
9	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l712t3170r788b3244],
10	an	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_48	[p3l806t3192r877b3226],
11	inhalant	NN	O	inhalant	nn	12	SENT_48	[p3l894t3170r1146b3226],
12	bronchodilator	NN	O	bronchodilator	agent	8	SENT_48	[p3l1162t3170r1923b3226],
13	—	RB	O	—	advmod	14	SENT_48	[p3l1162t3170r1923b3226],
14	induced	VBD	O	induce	ccomp	5	SENT_48	[p3l1162t3170r1923b3226],
15	improvement	NN	O	improvement	dobj	14	SENT_48	[p3l1939t3173r2052b3225, p3l16t3278r355b3337],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l382t3263r454b3319],
17	more	JJR	O	more	mwe	18	SENT_48	[p3l468t3285r630b3319],
18	than	IN	O	than	quantmod	19	SENT_48	[p3l659t3263r795b3319],
19	15	CD	PERCENT	15	num	20	SENT_48	[p3l827t3265r955b3321],
20	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_of	15	SENT_48	[p3l827t3265r955b3321],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l984t3263r1056b3319],
22	forced	JJ	O	forced	amod	24	SENT_48	[p3l1069t3263r1268b3319],
23	expiratory	JJ	O	expiratory	amod	24	SENT_48	[p3l1295t3266r1619b3337],
24	volume	NN	O	volume	prep_of	20	SENT_48	[p3l1643t3263r1879b3319],
25	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1905t3266r1967b3319],
26	1s	NNS	O	1	nn	27	SENT_48	[p3l1998t3266r2053b3319],
27	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	prep_in	14	SENT_48	[p3l19t3361r184b3424],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l228t3357r374b3413],
29	/	:	O	/	punct	41	SENT_48	[p3l228t3357r374b3413],
30	or	CC	O	or	dep	41	SENT_48	[p3l380t3378r447b3413],
31	hyper	JJ	O	hyper	amod	33	SENT_48	[p3l480t3357r981b3431],
32	—	NN	O	—	nn	33	SENT_48	[p3l480t3357r981b3431],
33	reactivity	NN	O	reactivity	npadvmod	35	SENT_48	[p3l480t3357r981b3431],
34	of	IN	O	of	prep	33	SENT_48	[p3l1016t3357r1088b3413],
35	less	JJR	O	less	dep	41	SENT_48	[p3l1108t3357r1210b3413],
36	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1245t3357r1382b3413],
37	10mg/mL	NN	O	10mg/ml	prep_than	35	SENT_48	[p3l1422t3360r1740b3431],
38	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1776t3357r1848b3413],
39	metacholine	NN	O	metacholine	prep_of	37	SENT_48	[p3l1870t3371r2053b3413, p3l19t3449r250b3505],
40	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	39	SENT_48	[p3l284t3450r499b3523],
41	Crapo	NNP	PERSON	Crapo	dep	27	SENT_48	[p3l284t3450r499b3523],
42	et	FW	O	et	nn	43	SENT_48	[p3l532t3463r586b3505],
43	al.	FW	O	al.	conj_and	27	SENT_48	[p3l615t3449r700b3516],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l615t3449r700b3516],
45	2000	CD	DATE	2000	num	46	SENT_48	[p3l733t3450r929b3521],
46	)	NN	O	)	appos	43	SENT_48	[p3l733t3450r929b3521],
47	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l733t3450r929b3521],

1	In	IN	O	in	mark	4	SENT_49	[p3l964t3453r1029b3504],
2	order	NN	O	order	dep	4	SENT_49	[p3l1059t3449r1226b3505],
3	to	TO	O	to	aux	4	SENT_49	[p3l1253t3463r1313b3505],
4	categorise	VB	O	categorise	dep	24	SENT_49	[p3l1345t3452r1656b3523],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_49	[p3l1686t3449r1783b3505],
6	subjects	NNS	O	subject	dobj	4	SENT_49	[p3l1813t3449r2053b3523],
7	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l19t3565r70b3599],
8	having	VBG	O	have	prepc_as	4	SENT_49	[p3l97t3543r307b3617],
9	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nn	10	SENT_49	[p3l333t3543r881b3617],
10	—	NN	O	—	dobj	8	SENT_49	[p3l333t3543r881b3617],
11	intolerant	JJ	O	intolerant	amod	14	SENT_49	[p3l333t3543r881b3617],
12	asthma	NN	O	asthma	nn	14	SENT_49	[p3l907t3543r1122b3599],
13	(	NN	O	(	nn	14	SENT_49	[p3l1153t3545r1212b3615],
14	n	NN	O	n	dep	10	SENT_49	[p3l1153t3545r1212b3615],
15	=	JJ	O	=	advmod	8	SENT_49	[p3l1240t3568r1295b3590],
16	163	CD	NUMBER	163	num	17	SENT_49	[p3l1329t3545r1481b3616],
17	)	NN	O	)	dep	15	SENT_49	[p3l1329t3545r1481b3616],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1329t3545r1481b3616],
19	an	DT	O	a	det	22	SENT_49	[p3l1512t3565r1583b3599],
20	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nn	22	SENT_49	[p3l1610t3546r1817b3617],
21	provocation	NN	O	provocation	nn	22	SENT_49	[p3l1842t3563r2053b3617, p3l19t3668r210b3721],
22	test	NN	O	test	nsubjpass	24	SENT_49	[p3l241t3679r346b3721],
23	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	24	SENT_49	[p3l375t3686r486b3721],
24	performed	VBN	O	perform	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l517t3665r854b3739],
25	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l885t3686r965b3721],
26	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_on	24	SENT_49	[p3l997t3665r1237b3739],
27	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1268t3665r1413b3721],
28	a	DT	O	a	det	29	SENT_49	[p3l1445t3686r1474b3721],
29	history	NN	O	history	prep_with	26	SENT_49	[p3l1504t3665r1723b3739],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1755t3665r1827b3721],
31	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	nn	32	SENT_49	[p3l1846t3668r2054b3739],
32	hypersensitivity	NN	O	hypersensitivity	prep_of	29	SENT_49	[p4l18t30r515b104],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l18t30r515b104],
34	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l558t52r624b86],
35	those	DT	O	those	nsubj	36	SENT_49	[p4l661t30r824b86],
36	detected	VBN	O	detect	conj_or	24	SENT_49	[p4l864t30r1129b86],
37	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l1164t30r1309b86],
38	urticaria	NN	O	urticarium	prep_with	36	SENT_49	[p4l1347t33r1626b97],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l1347t33r1626b97],
40	nasal	JJ	O	nasal	amod	41	SENT_49	[p4l1668t30r1815b86],
41	polyps	NNS	O	polyp	conj_and	38	SENT_49	[p4l1851t30r2053b104],
42	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l19t124r130b179],
43	sinusitis	NN	O	sinusitis	prep_with	36	SENT_49	[p4l158t126r396b179],
44	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l428t145r508b180],
45	water	NN	O	water	poss	47	SENT_49	[p4l534t124r744b180],
46	’s	POS	O	’s	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l534t124r744b180],
47	view	NN	O	view	prep_on	36	SENT_49	[p4l772t126r930b179],
48	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l772t126r930b179],

1	ATA	NN	ORGANIZATION	ata	nn	2	SENT_50	[p4l962t126r1114b179],
2	controls	NNS	O	control	nsubj	3	SENT_50	[p4l1143t123r1390b180],
3	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1424t125r1484b196],
4	n	NN	O	n	dobj	3	SENT_50	[p4l1424t125r1484b196],
5	=	JJ	O	=	amod	7	SENT_50	[p4l1514t148r1569b170],
6	429	CD	NUMBER	429	num	7	SENT_50	[p4l1601t125r1735b196],
7	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	8	SENT_50	[p4l1601t125r1735b196],
8	consisted	VBD	O	consist	rcmod	4	SENT_50	[p4l1771t124r2055b180],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l19t217r91b273],
10	asthmatics	NNS	O	asthmatic	prep_of	8	SENT_50	[p4l108t217r425b273],
11	exhibiting	VBG	O	exhibit	xcomp	8	SENT_50	[p4l456t217r777b291],
12	15	CD	PERCENT	15	number	13	SENT_50	[p4l809t218r937b274],
13	%	NN	PERCENT	%	num	16	SENT_50	[p4l809t218r937b274],
14	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l968t238r1035b273],
15	more	JJR	O	more	num	16	SENT_50	[p4l1061t238r1224b273],
16	reduction	NN	O	reduction	dobj	11	SENT_50	[p4l1253t217r1557b273],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1587t217r1659b273],
18	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	prep_of	16	SENT_50	[p4l1676t221r1841b284],
19	without	IN	O	without	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1877t217r2053b273, p4l19t324r123b366],
20	extrabronchial	JJ	O	extrabronchial	amod	21	SENT_50	[p4l148t310r599b366],
21	nasal	NN	O	nasal	prep_without	11	SENT_50	[p4l622t310r769b366],
22	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l794t331r860b366],
23	skin	NN	O	skin	nn	24	SENT_50	[p4l882t310r1007b366],
24	symptoms	NNS	O	symptom	conj_or	21	SENT_50	[p4l1030t324r1346b384],
25	whereas	IN	O	whereas	mark	42	SENT_50	[p4l1369t310r1621b366],
26	subjects	NNS	O	subject	nsubjpass	42	SENT_50	[p4l1646t310r1886b384],
27	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1909t310r2054b366],
28	hypertension	NN	O	hypertension	prep_with	26	SENT_50	[p4l18t404r428b478],
29	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l448t405r560b460],
30	diabetes	NN	O	diabetes	conj_and	28	SENT_50	[p4l581t404r828b460],
31	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l850t426r917b460],
32	those	DT	O	those	nsubjpass	42	SENT_50	[p4l935t404r1098b460],
33	taking	VBG	O	take	partmod	32	SENT_50	[p4l1120t404r1316b478],
34	angiotensin	NN	O	angiotensin	dobj	33	SENT_50	[p4l1335t407r1698b478],
35	converting	VBG	O	convert	xcomp	33	SENT_50	[p4l1719t407r2056b478],
36	enzyme	NN	O	enzyme	dobj	35	SENT_50	[p4l19t518r261b572],
37	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	40	SENT_50	[p4l291t499r485b570],
38	ACE	NN	O	ace	nn	40	SENT_50	[p4l291t499r485b570],
39	)	NN	O	)	nn	40	SENT_50	[p4l291t499r485b570],
40	inhibitors	NNS	O	inhibitor	dep	36	SENT_50	[p4l514t498r817b554],
41	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	42	SENT_50	[p4l841t519r991b554],
42	excluded	VBN	O	exclude	advcl	11	SENT_50	[p4l1018t498r1301b554],
43	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1323t498r1475b554],
44	this	DT	O	this	det	45	SENT_50	[p4l1498t498r1605b554],
45	study	NN	O	study	prep_from	42	SENT_50	[p4l1631t498r1802b572],
46	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1631t498r1802b572],

1	Finally	RB	O	finally	advmod	7	SENT_51	[p4l1832t498r2050b572],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l1832t498r2050b572],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_51	[p4l19t613r48b648],
4	written	VBN	O	write	amod	5	SENT_51	[p4l78t595r313b648],
5	consent	NN	O	consent	nsubjpass	7	SENT_51	[p4l347t606r587b648],
6	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_51	[p4l618t613r729b648],
7	secured	VBN	O	secure	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l764t592r999b648],
8	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l1030t592r1182b648],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_51	[p4l1214t592r1311b648],
10	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_from	7	SENT_51	[p4l1345t592r1585b666],
11	prior	JJ	O	prior	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l1618t595r1779b666],
12	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l1811t606r1871b648],
13	conducting	VBG	O	conduct	prepc_prior_to	7	SENT_51	[p4l1908t613r2053b648, p4l19t685r258b758],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_51	[p4l292t684r389b740],
15	study	NN	O	study	dobj	13	SENT_51	[p4l427t685r593b758],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l629t685r741b740],
17	ethical	JJ	O	ethical	amod	18	SENT_51	[p4l777t684r981b741],
18	approval	NN	O	approval	nsubjpass	20	SENT_51	[p4l1017t684r1278b758],
19	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_51	[p4l1312t706r1423b741],
20	obtained	VBN	O	obtain	conj_and	7	SENT_51	[p4l1462t684r1735b740],
21	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l1769t684r1921b740],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_51	[p4l1956t684r2053b740],
23	Institutional	JJ	ORGANIZATION	institutional	amod	25	SENT_51	[p4l19t778r399b834],
24	Review	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Review	nn	25	SENT_51	[p4l421t780r672b834],
25	Board	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Board	prep_from	20	SENT_51	[p4l692t778r884b834],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l908t778r980b834],
27	each	DT	O	each	det	28	SENT_51	[p4l993t778r1132b834],
28	hospital	NN	O	hospital	prep_of	25	SENT_51	[p4l1156t778r1413b851],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l1156t778r1413b851],

1	Table	NNP	O	Table	nsubj	3	SENT_52	[p4l1443t778r1610b834],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	1	SENT_52	[p4l1640t780r1664b833],
3	summarises	VBZ	O	summarise	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l1695t780r2053b834],
4	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	5	SENT_52	[p4l19t871r239b927],
5	characteristics	NNS	O	characteristic	dobj	3	SENT_52	[p4l266t871r700b927],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l728t871r800b927],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_52	[p4l813t871r910b927],
8	study	NN	O	study	nn	9	SENT_52	[p4l937t871r1102b945],
9	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_of	5	SENT_52	[p4l1127t871r1385b945],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l1127t871r1385b945],

1	SNP	NN	O	snp	nn	2	SENT_53	[p4l21t1102r194b1161],
2	Selection	NN	O	selection	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l231t1099r587b1161],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l622t1099r762b1161],
4	Genotyping	NN	O	genotyping	conj_and	2	SENT_53	[p4l797t1100r1262b1180],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_54	[p4l16t1261r120b1314],
2	chose	VBD	O	choose	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l150t1257r323b1313],
3	several	JJ	O	several	amod	5	SENT_54	[p4l353t1257r557b1313],
4	candidate	NN	O	candidate	nn	5	SENT_54	[p4l586t1257r881b1313],
5	genes	NNS	O	gene	dobj	2	SENT_54	[p4l912t1278r1082b1331],
6	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1110t1257r1261b1313],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_54	[p4l1288t1257r1385b1313],
8	literature	NN	O	literature	prep_from	2	SENT_54	[p4l1413t1257r1710b1324],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1413t1257r1710b1324],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1743t1257r1855b1313],
11	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	nsubjpass	16	SENT_54	[p4l1884t1260r2053b1314],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l17t1353r78b1406],
13	those	DT	O	those	det	14	SENT_54	[p4l105t1350r268b1407],
14	genes	NNS	O	gene	prep_in	11	SENT_54	[p4l297t1372r467b1424],
15	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_54	[p4l494t1372r643b1407],
16	selected	VBN	O	select	conj_and	2	SENT_54	[p4l672t1350r918b1407],
17	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l943t1350r1094b1407],
18	dbSNP	NN	O	dbsnp	prep_from	16	SENT_54	[p4l1121t1350r1347b1407],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1374t1353r1436b1406],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_54	[p4l1462t1350r1559b1407],
21	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	22	SENT_54	[p4l1587t1350r1862b1407],
22	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	prep_in	18	SENT_54	[p4l1891t1353r2053b1407, p4l18t1458r103b1500],
23	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l130t1444r220b1500],
24	Biotechnology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biotechnology	nn	26	SENT_54	[p4l246t1444r715b1518],
25	Information	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Information	nn	26	SENT_54	[p4l746t1444r1130b1500],
26	(	NNP	O	(	prep_for	22	SENT_54	[p4l1164t1444r1344b1516],
27	build	VB	O	build	ccomp	16	SENT_54	[p4l1164t1444r1344b1516],
28	36	CD	NUMBER	36	number	29	SENT_54	[p4l1374t1445r1468b1516],
29	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dobj	27	SENT_54	[p4l1374t1445r1468b1516],
30	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1504t1444r1616b1500],
31	International	NNP	MISC	International	nn	36	SENT_54	[p4l1646t1444r2055b1500],
32	HapMap	NNP	MISC	HapMap	nn	36	SENT_54	[p4l18t1541r295b1611],
33	Project	NNP	MISC	Project	nn	36	SENT_54	[p4l337t1540r561b1611],
34	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	36	SENT_54	[p4l606t1537r1716b1611],
35	http://hapmap.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/	NN	O	http://hapmap.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/	nn	36	SENT_54	[p4l606t1537r1716b1611],
36	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	29	SENT_54	[p4l606t1537r1716b1611],
37	based	VBN	O	base	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1761t1537r1933b1593],
38	on	IN	O	on	prepc_based_on	27	SENT_54	[p4l1975t1558r2054b1593],
39	the	DT	O	the	det	40	SENT_54	[p4l18t1631r115b1687],
40	frequencies	NNS	O	frequency	pobj	27	SENT_54	[p4l150t1631r504b1705],
41	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l540t1634r601b1686],
42	the	DT	O	the	det	44	SENT_54	[p4l636t1631r733b1687],
43	Asian	JJ	LOCATION	asian	amod	44	SENT_54	[p4l767t1634r940b1687],
44	population	NN	O	population	prep_in	40	SENT_54	[p4l974t1631r1317b1705],
45	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1353t1632r1465b1687],
46	LD	NN	O	ld	nn	47	SENT_54	[p4l1498t1635r1599b1686],
47	status	NN	O	status	conj_and	44	SENT_54	[p4l1637t1645r1803b1687],
48	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1840t1653r2056b1713],
49	the	DT	O	the	det	50	SENT_54	[p4l18t1754r115b1810],
50	SNPs	NNS	O	snp	prep_among	44	SENT_54	[p4l162t1757r349b1810],
51	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l162t1757r349b1810],

1	To	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l399t1757r478b1810],
2	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_to	7	SENT_55	[p4l526t1768r816b1828],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_55	[p4l862t1754r959b1810],
4	data	NNS	O	datum	dep	2	SENT_55	[p4l1006t1754r1146b1821],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l1006t1754r1146b1821],
6	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	7	SENT_55	[p4l1194t1776r1283b1810],
7	adapted	VBD	O	adapt	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l1330t1754r1572b1828],
8	BeadXpress	NNP	O	BeadXpress	dobj	7	SENT_55	[p4l1614t1742r2047b1828],
9	®	CD	NUMBER	®	number	10	SENT_55	[p4l1614t1742r2047b1828],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_55	[p4l22t1847r322b1919],
11	Illumina	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Illumina	dep	8	SENT_55	[p4l22t1847r322b1919],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l22t1847r322b1919],
13	San	NNP	LOCATION	San	nn	18	SENT_55	[p4l358t1850r467b1903],
14	Diego	NNP	LOCATION	Diego	nn	18	SENT_55	[p4l495t1850r703b1921],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l495t1850r703b1921],
16	CA	NNP	LOCATION	CA	appos	18	SENT_55	[p4l739t1850r864b1914],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l739t1850r864b1914],
18	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	appos	8	SENT_55	[p4l896t1848r1071b1919],
19	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	18	SENT_55	[p4l896t1848r1071b1919],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	amod	18	SENT_55	[p4l1111t1847r1415b1921],
21	Oliphant	NNP	PERSON	Oliphant	dep	20	SENT_55	[p4l1111t1847r1415b1921],
22	et	FW	O	et	nn	23	SENT_55	[p4l1445t1861r1500b1903],
23	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	21	SENT_55	[p4l1530t1847r1615b1914],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l1530t1847r1615b1914],
25	2002	CD	DATE	2002	num	26	SENT_55	[p4l1649t1848r1823b1919],
26	)	CD	NUMBER	)	appos	21	SENT_55	[p4l1649t1848r1823b1919],
27	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	28	SENT_55	[p4l1856t1847r2054b1903],
28	allows	VBZ	O	allow	rcmod	26	SENT_55	[p4l19t1939r207b1995],
29	genotyping	NN	O	genotyping	dobj	28	SENT_55	[p4l240t1942r598b2013],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l629t1939r701b1995],
31	96-384	CD	NUMBER	96-384	num	32	SENT_55	[p4l720t1942r953b1996],
32	SNPS	NNS	O	snp	prep_of	29	SENT_55	[p4l986t1942r1156b1996],
33	simultaneously	RB	O	simultaneously	advmod	28	SENT_55	[p4l1188t1939r1659b2013],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l1188t1939r1659b2013],
