1	Biochemical	JJ	O	biochemical	amod	2	SENT_3	[p1l732t286r1050b332],
2	Pharmacology	NN	O	pharmacology	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1074t286r1447b344],

1	’	SYM	O	’	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l36t385r81b396],
2	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l36t385r81b396],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l216t372r252b396],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l216t372r252b396],
5	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l216t372r252b396],

1	ELSEV	NN	O	elsev	nn	4	SENT_5	[p1l14t417r249b453],
2	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	4	SENT_5	[p1l14t417r249b453],
3	ER	NN	O	er	nn	4	SENT_5	[p1l14t417r249b453],
4	journal	NN	O	journal	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l512t418r643b448],
5	homepage	NN	O	homepage	dep	4	SENT_5	[p1l664t418r867b449],
6	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l664t418r867b449],
7	www	NN	O	www	dep	4	SENT_5	[p1l885t418r1663b448],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l885t418r1663b448],

1	e	LS	O	e	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l885t418r1663b448],
2	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	3	SENT_6	[p1l885t418r1663b448],
3	sevier.com/locate/biochempharm	NN	O	sevier.com/locate/biochempharm	nsubj	1	SENT_6	[p1l885t418r1663b448],

1	Intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	2	SENT_7	[p1l6t565r255b610],
2	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nsubj	13	SENT_7	[p1l280t567r485b610],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l509t565r605b610],
4	midazolam	NN	O	midazolam	nn	5	SENT_7	[p1l629t565r925b610],
5	disposition	NN	O	disposition	conj_and	2	SENT_7	[p1l949t565r1242b621],
6	in	FW	O	in	prep	2	SENT_7	[p1l1266t566r1311b610],
7	vivo	FW	O	vivo	pobj	6	SENT_7	[p1l1334t566r1438b610],
8	associate	NN	O	associate	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1462t566r1701b610],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1724t565r1846b610],
10	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	11	SENT_7	[p1l1870t568r1976b610],
11	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	prep_with	8	SENT_7	[p1l6t636r422b692],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l447t636r542b681],
13	show	VBP	O	show	conj_and	8	SENT_7	[p1l567t636r708b681],
14	seasonal	JJ	O	seasonal	amod	15	SENT_7	[p1l730t636r954b681],
15	variation	NN	O	variation	dobj	13	SENT_7	[p1l977t637r1215b681],

1	Ranjit	NNP	PERSON	Ranjit	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l11t742r133b786],
2	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l151t744r187b777],
3	Thirumaran	NNP	PERSON	Thirumaran	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l204t742r453b777],
4	"	``	O	"	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l463t735r564b783],
5	"	``	O	"	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l463t735r564b783],
6	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l463t735r564b783],
7	“	NN	O	“	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l463t735r564b783],
8	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l463t735r564b783],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l463t735r564b783],
10	Jatinder	NNP	PERSON	Jatinder	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l577t742r747b786],
11	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l765t744r801b777],
12	Lamba	NNP	PERSON	Lamba	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l820t734r1070b783],
13	"	``	O	"	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l820t734r1070b783],
14	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l820t734r1070b783],
15	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l820t734r1070b783],
16	'	''	DATE	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l820t734r1070b783],
17	12	CD	DATE	12	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l820t734r1070b783],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l820t734r1070b783],
19	Richard	NNP	PERSON	Richard	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1089t742r1246b777],
20	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1265t744r1299b777],
21	Kim	NNP	PERSON	Kim	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1319t742r1401b777],
22	"	``	O	"	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1411t735r1463b783],
23	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1411t735r1463b783],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1411t735r1463b783],
25	Brad	NNP	PERSON	Brad	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1482t742r1576b777],
26	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1594t744r1624b777],
27	Urquhart	NNP	PERSON	Urquhart	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1643t742r1834b786],
28	‘‘	NN	O	‘‘	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1843t734r1899b783],
29	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1843t734r1899b783],
30	4	CD	NUMBER	4	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1843t734r1899b783],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1843t734r1899b783],
32	Jamie	NNP	PERSON	Jamie	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l6t795r126b839],
33	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l145t797r179b831],
34	Gregore	NNP	PERSON	Gregore	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l198t788r402b839],
35	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l198t788r402b839],
36	5	CD	NUMBER	5	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l198t788r402b839],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l198t788r402b839],
38	Nilesh	NNP	PERSON	Nilesh	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l421t795r552b830],
39	Chande	NNP	PERSON	Chande	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l570t795r724b830],
40	9	CD	NUMBER	9	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l735t788r788b836],
41	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l735t788r788b836],
42	5	CD	NUMBER	5	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l735t788r788b836],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l735t788r788b836],
44	Yiping	NNP	O	Yiping	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l805t795r939b845],
45	Fan	NNP	O	Fan	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l957t797r1029b830],
46	£	NN	MONEY	£	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1039t787r1085b836],
47	7	CD	MONEY	7	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1039t787r1085b836],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1039t787r1085b836],
49	An	DT	O	a	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1103t796r1159b830],
50	Qig	NN	O	qig	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1177t788r1285b837],
51	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1177t788r1285b837],
52	8	CD	NUMBER	8	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1177t788r1285b837],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1177t788r1285b837],
54	Cheng	NNP	PERSON	Cheng	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1304t795r1433b839],
55	Chengg	NNP	PERSON	Chengg	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1450t788r1643b839],
56	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1450t788r1643b839],
57	9	CD	NUMBER	9	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1450t788r1643b839],
58	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1450t788r1643b839],
59	Kenneth	NNP	PERSON	Kenneth	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l11t849r185b884],
60	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l204t851r236b885],
61	Thummelh	NNP	PERSON	Thummelh	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l254t841r541b890],
62	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l254t841r541b890],
63	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l254t841r541b890],
64	°	NN	O	°	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l254t841r541b890],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l254t841r541b890],
66	Stephen	NNP	PERSON	Stephen	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l560t849r728b893],
67	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l747t851r786b885],
68	Hall	NNP	PERSON	Hall	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l806t849r888b884],
69	‘	NN	O	‘	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l899t842r964b890],
70	'	''	DATE	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l899t842r964b890],
71	11	CD	DATE	11	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l899t842r964b890],
72	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l899t842r964b890],
73	Erin	NNP	PERSON	Erin	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l983t849r1066b884],
74	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1084t850r1123b885],
75	Schuetz	NNP	PERSON	Schuetz	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1142t849r1304b884],
76	"	``	O	"	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1314t847r1356b868],
77	"	``	O	"	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1314t847r1356b868],
78	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1314t847r1356b868],
79	*	CD	NUMBER	*	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1314t847r1356b868],
80	“	NNP	O	“	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l6t924r168b952],
81	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l6t924r168b952],
82	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l177t925r203b952],
83	Pharmaceutical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceutical	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l209t925r396b947],
84	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l406t925r510b950],
85	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l406t925r510b950],
86	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l521t926r549b947],
87	Jude	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jude	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l556t925r612b952],
88	Children	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Children	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l623t925r740b947],
89	's	POS	ORGANIZATION	's	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l623t925r740b947],
90	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l750t925r856b947],
91	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l867t925r971b952],
92	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l867t925r971b952],
93	Memphis	NNP	LOCATION	Memphis	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l983t925r1098b952],
94	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l983t925r1098b952],
95	TN	NN	O	tn	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1111t926r1147b950],
96	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1111t926r1147b950],
97	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1161t925r1240b947],
98	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1249t926r1321b947],
99	"	``	O	"	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l7t955r169b987],
100	Department	NNP	O	Department	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l7t955r169b987],
101	of	IN	O	of	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l178t960r205b987],
102	Experimental	JJ	O	experimental	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l210t960r370b987],
103	and	CC	O	and	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l380t960r425b982],
104	Clinical	JJ	O	clinical	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l436t960r523b982],
105	Pharmacology	NN	O	pharmacology	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l533t960r709b987],
106	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l533t960r709b987],
107	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l723t960r844b987],
108	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l855t960r881b987],
109	Minnesota	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Minnesota	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l887t960r1018b985],
110	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l887t960r1018b985],
111	Minneapolis	NNP	LOCATION	Minneapolis	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1030t960r1182b987],
112	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1030t960r1182b987],
113	MN	NN	O	mn	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1193t961r1241b985],
114	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1193t961r1241b985],
115	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1254t960r1333b982],
116	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1342t961r1414b982],
117	“	NNP	O	“	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l6t995r109b1017],
118	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l6t995r109b1017],
119	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l119t995r198b1017],
120	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l209t996r308b1017],
121	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l319t997r401b1021],
122	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l319t997r401b1021],
123	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l414t996r536b1023],
124	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l545t996r650b1023],
125	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l545t996r650b1023],
126	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l662t995r755b1021],
127	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l662t995r755b1021],
128	ON	NNP	O	ON	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l768t997r809b1021],
129	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l768t997r809b1021],
130	Canada	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Canada	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l821t996r910b1017],
131	dSchulich	NNP	ORGANIZATION	dSchulich	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l6t1026r122b1053],
132	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l132t1031r210b1053],
133	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l221t1031r247b1058],
134	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l252t1031r362b1053],
135	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l372t1031r417b1053],
136	Dentistry	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Dentistry	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l426t1031r542b1058],
137	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l426t1031r542b1058],
138	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l556t1031r678b1058],
139	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l688t1031r714b1058],
140	Western	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Western	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l721t1032r820b1053],
141	Ontario	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ontario	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l831t1031r926b1056],
142	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l831t1031r926b1056],
143	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l938t1031r1032b1056],
144	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l938t1031r1032b1056],
145	ON	NNP	O	ON	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1044t1032r1085b1056],
146	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1044t1032r1085b1056],
147	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1098t1031r1186b1053],
148	eLondon	NNP	O	eLondon	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l6t1065r110b1088],
149	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l120t1066r199b1088],
150	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l209t1066r309b1088],
151	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l320t1067r402b1091],
152	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l320t1067r402b1091],
153	Victoria	NNP	LOCATION	Victoria	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l414t1066r507b1088],
154	Hospital	NNP	LOCATION	Hospital	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l517t1066r622b1093],
155	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l517t1066r622b1093],
156	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l633t1066r726b1091],
157	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l633t1066r726b1091],
158	ON	NNP	O	ON	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l739t1067r780b1091],
159	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l739t1067r780b1091],
160	Canada	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Canada	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l792t1066r881b1088],
161	‘	NNP	ORGANIZATION	‘	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l7t1096r161b1128],
162	Information	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Information	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l7t1096r161b1128],
163	Sciences	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l171t1101r270b1123],
164	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l280t1102r430b1128],
165	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l280t1102r430b1128],
166	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l441t1102r469b1123],
167	Jude	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jude	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l476t1101r532b1128],
168	Children	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Children	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l543t1101r661b1123],
169	's	POS	ORGANIZATION	's	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l543t1101r661b1123],
170	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l671t1101r777b1123],
171	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l788t1101r892b1128],
172	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l788t1101r892b1128],
173	Memphis	NNP	LOCATION	Memphis	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l904t1101r1019b1128],
174	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l904t1101r1019b1128],
175	TN	NN	O	tn	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1031t1102r1068b1126],
176	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1031t1102r1068b1126],
177	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1081t1101r1160b1123],
178	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1169t1102r1241b1123],
179	gDepartment	NN	O	gdepartment	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l6t1136r168b1163],
180	of	IN	O	of	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l178t1136r204b1163],
181	Biostatistics	NNS	O	biostatistic	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l209t1137r357b1161],
182	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l209t1137r357b1161],
183	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l368t1138r396b1158],
184	Jude	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jude	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l403t1136r459b1163],
185	Children	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Children	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l470t1136r588b1158],
186	's	POS	ORGANIZATION	's	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l470t1136r588b1158],
187	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l598t1136r704b1158],
188	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l714t1136r819b1163],
189	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l714t1136r819b1163],
190	Memphis	NNP	LOCATION	Memphis	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l830t1136r946b1163],
191	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l830t1136r946b1163],
192	TN	NN	O	tn	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l958t1138r995b1161],
193	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l958t1138r995b1161],
194	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1008t1136r1087b1158],
195	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l1096t1138r1168b1158],
196	“	NNP	O	“	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l7t1166r170b1198],
197	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l7t1166r170b1198],
198	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l179t1171r205b1198],
199	Pharmaceutics	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceutics	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l210t1171r392b1196],
200	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l210t1171r392b1196],
201	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l405t1171r527b1198],
202	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l538t1171r564b1198],
203	Washington	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Washington	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l570t1171r719b1198],
204	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l570t1171r719b1198],
205	Seattle	NNP	LOCATION	Seattle	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l731t1171r817b1196],
206	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l731t1171r817b1196],
207	WA	NNP	LOCATION	WA	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l829t1172r876b1196],
208	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l829t1172r876b1196],
209	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l889t1171r968b1193],
210	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l977t1172r1049b1193],
211	‘	NNP	O	‘	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l7t1202r78b1233],
212	Drug	NNP	O	Drug	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l7t1202r78b1233],
213	Disposition	NNP	O	Disposition	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l86t1207r226b1233],
214	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l86t1207r226b1233],
215	Eli	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Eli	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l237t1206r267b1228],
216	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Lilly	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l276t1206r326b1233],
217	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l337t1206r381b1228],
218	Co.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Co.	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l392t1207r432b1231],
219	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l392t1207r432b1231],
220	Indianapolis	NNP	LOCATION	Indianapolis	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l443t1206r596b1233],
221	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l443t1206r596b1233],
222	IN	IN	O	in	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l608t1208r639b1231],
223	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l608t1208r639b1231],
224	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	dep	225	SENT_8	[p1l652t1206r731b1228],
225	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l740t1207r812b1228],

1	Article	NNP	O	Article	nn	2	SENT_10	[p1l6t1421r82b1443],
2	history	NN	O	history	nsubjpass	16	SENT_10	[p1l96t1421r183b1448],
3	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l96t1421r183b1448],
4	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	num	6	SENT_10	[p1l96t1421r183b1448],
5	Vitamin	NN	PERSON	vitamin	nn	6	SENT_10	[p1l699t1423r813b1447],
6	D	NN	PERSON	d	dep	2	SENT_10	[p1l828t1424r855b1451],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l828t1424r855b1451],
8	whose	WP$	O	whose	dep	10	SENT_10	[p1l870t1423r962b1447],
9	levels	NNS	O	level	nsubj	10	SENT_10	[p1l977t1422r1057b1447],
10	vary	VBP	O	vary	dep	6	SENT_10	[p1l1071t1430r1134b1453],
11	seasonally	RB	O	seasonally	advmod	10	SENT_10	[p1l1149t1422r1296b1453],
12	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1310t1423r1375b1447],
13	sunlight	NN	O	sunlight	prep_with	10	SENT_10	[p1l1391t1422r1513b1453],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1391t1422r1513b1453],
15	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_10	[p1l1529t1423r1549b1447],
16	activated	VBN	O	activate	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1565t1422r1694b1447],
17	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1709t1426r1737b1447],
18	1oL,25-dihydroxyvitamin	NN	O	1ol,25-dihydroxyvitamin	nn	19	SENT_10	[p1l1754t1422r2106b1453],
19	D3	NN	O	d3	prep_to	16	SENT_10	[p1l2121t1424r2154b1452],
20	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	21	SENT_10	[p1l6t1462r63b1486],
21	Received	VBD	O	receive	rcmod	19	SENT_10	[p1l7t1490r118b1512],
22	17	CD	DATE	17	num	23	SENT_10	[p1l131t1491r159b1511],
23	February	NNP	DATE	February	dobj	21	SENT_10	[p1l171t1490r282b1517],
24	2012	CD	DATE	2012	num	23	SENT_10	[p1l293t1491r354b1512],
25	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	amod	26	SENT_10	[p1l6t1526r121b1553],
26	22	CD	DATE	22	dep	23	SENT_10	[p1l133t1527r162b1547],
27	March	NNP	DATE	March	tmod	23	SENT_10	[p1l174t1526r254b1547],
28	2012	CD	DATE	2012	num	27	SENT_10	[p1l265t1527r326b1547],
29	Available	JJ	O	available	amod	23	SENT_10	[p1l6t1562r118b1583],
30	online	NN	O	online	prep	23	SENT_10	[p1l129t1562r204b1583],
31	30	CD	DATE	30	dep	30	SENT_10	[p1l214t1563r244b1583],
32	March	NNP	DATE	March	tmod	21	SENT_10	[p1l254t1562r331b1583],
33	2012	CD	DATE	2012	num	32	SENT_10	[p1l341t1563r400b1583],

1	binds	VBZ	O	bind	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l6t1675r82b1699],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_11	[p1l96t1675r141b1699],
3	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	5	SENT_11	[p1l154t1675r264b1699],
4	D	NN	O	d	nn	5	SENT_11	[p1l277t1677r297b1699],
5	receptor	NN	O	receptor	dobj	1	SENT_11	[p1l311t1679r429b1705],
6	(	NN	O	(	nn	8	SENT_11	[p1l442t1675r525b1705],
7	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	8	SENT_11	[p1l442t1675r525b1705],
8	)	NN	O	)	dep	5	SENT_11	[p1l442t1675r525b1705],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l539t1675r590b1699],
10	transcriptionally	RB	O	transcriptionally	advmod	11	SENT_11	[p1l603t1675r840b1705],
11	regulates	VBZ	O	regulate	conj_and	1	SENT_11	[p1l854t1675r983b1705],
12	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	14	SENT_11	[p1l997t1675r1130b1699],
13	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	14	SENT_11	[p1l1144t1676r1254b1699],
14	expression	NN	O	expression	dobj	11	SENT_11	[p1l1267t1675r1426b1705],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1267t1675r1426b1705],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_12	[p1l1439t1677r1487b1699],
2	genotyped	VBD	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l6t1715r155b1745],
3	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	4	SENT_12	[p1l172t1717r228b1739],
4	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	dobj	2	SENT_12	[p1l244t1715r466b1745],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l482t1715r534b1739],
6	determined	VBD	O	determine	conj_and	2	SENT_12	[p1l550t1715r714b1739],
7	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	8	SENT_12	[p1l730t1715r798b1739],
8	associations	NNS	O	association	dobj	6	SENT_12	[p1l813t1715r984b1739],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l999t1715r1065b1739],
10	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	11	SENT_12	[p1l1080t1715r1213b1739],
11	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	prep_with	6	SENT_12	[p1l1229t1716r1339b1739],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1355t1715r1406b1739],
13	with	IN	O	with	conj_and	2	SENT_12	[p1l1422t1715r1487b1739],
14	midazolam	NN	O	midazolam	nn	15	SENT_12	[p1l6t1755r165b1779],
15	pharmacokinetics	NNS	O	pharmacokinetic	pobj	13	SENT_12	[p1l175t1755r435b1785],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l175t1755r435b1785],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l445t1755r496b1779],
18	whether	IN	O	whether	dep	22	SENT_12	[p1l506t1755r627b1779],
19	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	21	SENT_12	[p1l636t1755r769b1779],
20	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	21	SENT_12	[p1l779t1756r889b1779],
21	levels/activity	NN	O	levels/activity	nsubj	22	SENT_12	[p1l899t1755r1098b1785],
22	varied	VBD	O	vary	conj_and	13	SENT_12	[p1l1107t1755r1195b1779],
23	seasonally	RB	O	seasonally	advmod	22	SENT_12	[p1l1206t1755r1359b1785],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1206t1755r1359b1785],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_13	[p1l1368t1755r1420b1779],
2	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	3	SENT_13	[p1l1431t1756r1487b1779],
3	Keywords	NNS	O	keyword	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l6t1810r132b1837],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l6t1810r132b1837],
5	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	9	SENT_13	[p1l7t1847r105b1867],
6	Vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	9	SENT_13	[p1l6t1882r108b1903],
7	D	NN	O	d	nn	9	SENT_13	[p1l119t1883r137b1903],
8	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	9	SENT_13	[p1l6t1918r62b1939],
9	Polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	dep	3	SENT_13	[p1l8t1953r192b1980],
10	Seasonal	JJ	O	seasonal	amod	11	SENT_13	[p1l7t1989r116b2010],
11	variation	NN	O	variation	dep	9	SENT_13	[p1l126t1989r240b2010],

1	BsmIG	NN	O	bsmig	nsubj	2	SENT_14	[p1l6t2119r140b2143],
2	>	JJR	O	>	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l6t2119r140b2143],
3	A	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_14	[p1l6t2119r140b2143],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_14	[p1l156t2118r330b2148],
5	rs1544410	NN	O	rs1544410	nn	7	SENT_14	[p1l156t2118r330b2148],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	7	SENT_14	[p1l156t2118r330b2148],
7	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	nsubjpass	10	SENT_14	[p1l348t2118r557b2148],
8	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_14	[p1l573t2125r628b2142],
9	signiﬁcantly	RB	O	signiﬁcantly	advmod	10	SENT_14	[p1l646t2118r821b2148],
10	associated	VBN	O	associate	rcmod	2	SENT_14	[p1l837t2118r984b2142],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1001t2118r1066b2142],
12	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	14	SENT_14	[p1l1083t2119r1194b2142],
13	jejunal	NN	O	jejunal	nn	14	SENT_14	[p1l1207t2118r1307b2148],
14	expression	NN	O	expression	prep_with	10	SENT_14	[p1l1324t2118r1487b2148],
15	/	:	O	/	punct	32	SENT_14	[p1l1324t2118r1487b2148],
16	activity	NN	O	activity	dep	32	SENT_14	[p1l7t2158r119b2188],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l7t2158r119b2188],
18	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l134t2158r199b2182],
19	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	21	SENT_14	[p1l215t2159r325b2182],
20	duodenal	JJ	O	duodenal	amod	21	SENT_14	[p1l341t2158r472b2182],
21	mRNA	NN	O	mrna	prep_with	16	SENT_14	[p1l488t2159r584b2186],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l488t2159r584b2186],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l600t2158r651b2182],
24	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l667t2158r732b2182],
25	midazolam	NN	O	midazolam	nn	26	SENT_14	[p1l748t2158r906b2182],
26	area	NN	O	area	conj_and	21	SENT_14	[p1l922t2165r981b2182],
27	under	IN	O	under	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l997t2158r1080b2182],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_14	[p1l1095t2158r1140b2182],
29	curve	NN	O	curve	prep_under	26	SENT_14	[p1l1155t2165r1232b2182],
30	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	32	SENT_14	[p1l1248t2158r1338b2188],
31	AUC	NN	O	auc	nn	32	SENT_14	[p1l1248t2158r1338b2188],
32	)	NN	O	)	parataxis	2	SENT_14	[p1l1248t2158r1338b2188],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1248t2158r1338b2188],

1	Intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	3	SENT_15	[p1l1354t2158r1488b2182],
2	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	3	SENT_15	[p1l7t2199r117b2222],
3	expression/activity	NN	O	expression/activity	nsubj	15	SENT_15	[p1l127t2198r399b2228],
4	was	VBD	O	be	cop	15	SENT_15	[p1l409t2205r463b2222],
5	signiﬁcantly	RB	O	signiﬁcantly	advmod	6	SENT_15	[p1l475t2198r649b2228],
6	higher	JJR	O	higher	amod	15	SENT_15	[p1l659t2198r751b2228],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l761t2199r787b2222],
8	biopsies	NNS	O	biopsy	prep_in	6	SENT_15	[p1l797t2198r912b2228],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l922t2198r987b2222],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_15	[p1l998t2198r1043b2222],
11	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	14	SENT_15	[p1l1054t2200r1110b2222],
12	promoter	NN	O	promoter	nn	14	SENT_15	[p1l1121t2202r1255b2228],
13	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nn	14	SENT_15	[p1l1265t2198r1487b2228],
14	Cdx2-3731G	NN	O	cdx2-3731g	prep_with	8	SENT_15	[p1l7t2238r230b2263],
15	>	JJR	O	>	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l7t2238r230b2263],
16	A	DT	O	a	dep	15	SENT_15	[p1l7t2238r230b2263],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l244t2238r295b2262],
18	GATA-1012A	NN	O	gata-1012a	conj_and	16	SENT_15	[p1l310t2239r540b2263],
19	>	JJR	O	>	amod	20	SENT_15	[p1l310t2239r540b2263],
20	G	NN	O	g	dep	16	SENT_15	[p1l310t2239r540b2263],
21	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	22	SENT_15	[p1l554t2238r612b2262],
22	increase	VBP	O	increase	rcmod	15	SENT_15	[p1l626t2238r742b2262],
23	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	24	SENT_15	[p1l755t2240r818b2262],
24	activation	NN	O	activation	dobj	22	SENT_15	[p1l831t2238r972b2262],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l987t2238r1016b2262],
26	target	NN	O	target	nn	27	SENT_15	[p1l1027t2242r1111b2268],
27	genes	NNS	O	gene	prep_of	24	SENT_15	[p1l1124t2245r1212b2268],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1124t2245r1212b2268],

1	Duodenal	JJ	O	duodenal	amod	3	SENT_16	[p1l1227t2238r1362b2262],
2	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	3	SENT_16	[p1l1378t2239r1488b2262],
3	mRNA	NN	O	mrna	nsubj	6	SENT_16	[p1l7t2279r97b2302],
4	was	VBD	O	be	cop	6	SENT_16	[p1l115t2285r170b2302],
5	signiﬁcantly	RB	O	signiﬁcantly	advmod	6	SENT_16	[p1l190t2278r364b2308],
6	higher	JJR	O	higher	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l383t2278r475b2308],
7	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l493t2278r615b2302],
8	April	NNP	DATE	April	prep_between	6	SENT_16	[p1l633t2278r702b2308],
9	and	CC	DATE	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l722t2278r773b2302],
10	September	NNP	DATE	September	conj_and	8	SENT_16	[p1l793t2278r947b2308],
11	than	IN	O	than	prep	6	SENT_16	[p1l965t2278r1029b2302],
12	between	IN	O	between	pcomp	11	SENT_16	[p1l1047t2278r1170b2302],
13	October	NNP	DATE	October	pobj	12	SENT_16	[p1l1189t2278r1302b2302],
14	and	CC	DATE	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1320t2278r1371b2302],
15	March	NNP	DATE	March	conj_and	13	SENT_16	[p1l1391t2278r1487b2302],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1391t2278r1487b2302],

1	Midazolam	NNP	O	Midazolam	nn	3	SENT_17	[p1l7t2318r166b2342],
2	p.o.	NN	O	p.o.	nn	3	SENT_17	[p1l177t2325r226b2348],
3	AUC	NN	O	auc	nsubj	7	SENT_17	[p1l237t2319r298b2342],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l309t2318r361b2342],
5	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	6	SENT_17	[p1l373t2318r426b2342],
6	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	conj_and	3	SENT_17	[p1l438t2318r641b2348],
7	trended	VBD	O	trend	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l652t2318r763b2342],
8	higher	JJR	O	higher	acomp	7	SENT_17	[p1l775t2318r867b2348],
9	October	NNP	DATE	October	tmod	7	SENT_17	[p1l878t2318r990b2342],
10	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1001t2318r1114b2348],
11	March	NNP	DATE	March	prep_through	7	SENT_17	[p1l1126t2318r1216b2342],
12	compared	VBN	O	compare	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1227t2318r1369b2348],
13	to	TO	O	to	prepc_compared_to	7	SENT_17	[p1l1380t2321r1408b2342],
14	April	NNP	DATE	April	pobj	7	SENT_17	[p1l1418t2318r1487b2348],
15	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l6t2358r120b2388],
16	September	NNP	DATE	September	prep_through	14	SENT_17	[p1l128t2358r288b2388],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l128t2358r288b2388],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_18	[p1l296t2358r377b2382],
2	data	NNS	O	datum	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l386t2358r447b2382],
3	suggest	VBP	O	suggest	rcmod	2	SENT_18	[p1l455t2361r562b2388],
4	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	5	SENT_18	[p1l570t2359r626b2382],
5	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubj	7	SENT_18	[p1l635t2358r857b2388],
6	are	VBP	O	be	cop	7	SENT_18	[p1l866t2365r909b2382],
7	predictors	NNS	O	predictor	ccomp	3	SENT_18	[p1l918t2358r1061b2388],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1070t2358r1099b2382],
9	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	10	SENT_18	[p1l1104t2358r1237b2382],
10	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	prep_of	7	SENT_18	[p1l1246t2359r1363b2386],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1246t2359r1363b2386],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1371t2358r1423b2382],
13	that	IN	O	that	conj_and	2	SENT_18	[p1l1431t2358r1488b2382],

1	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	3	SENT_19	[p1l674t2398r784b2421],
2	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	3	SENT_19	[p1l798t2397r931b2421],
3	expression	NN	O	expression	nsubj	4	SENT_19	[p1l945t2397r1098b2427],
4	varies	VBZ	O	vary	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1110t2397r1193b2421],
5	seasonally	RB	O	seasonally	advmod	6	SENT_19	[p1l1208t2397r1355b2427],
6	—	JJ	O	—	acomp	4	SENT_19	[p1l1368t2411r1384b2414],
7	likely	JJ	O	likely	amod	8	SENT_19	[p1l1398t2397r1475b2427],
8	related	JJ	O	related	dep	6	SENT_19	[p1l1489t2397r1587b2421],
9	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1601t2401r1628b2421],
10	annual	JJ	SET	annual	amod	11	SENT_19	[p1l1642t2397r1737b2421],
11	changes	NNS	O	change	prep_to	6	SENT_19	[p1l1752t2397r1865b2427],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1879t2397r1905b2421],
13	UV	NN	O	uv	nn	14	SENT_19	[p1l1919t2399r1961b2421],
14	sunlight	NN	O	sunlight	prep_in	11	SENT_19	[p1l1974t2397r2090b2427],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l2103t2397r2154b2421],
16	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	18	SENT_19	[p1l6t2437r116b2462],
17	D	NN	O	d	nn	18	SENT_19	[p1l129t2439r148b2462],
18	levels	NNS	O	level	prep_in	11	SENT_19	[p1l162t2437r248b2462],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l162t2437r248b2462],

1	©	RB	O	©	advmod	2	SENT_20	[p1l1580t2481r1601b2501],
2	2012	CD	DATE	2012	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1615t2478r1685b2501],
3	Elsevier	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Elsevier	nn	4	SENT_20	[p1l1698t2477r1809b2501],
4	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	dep	2	SENT_20	[p1l1821t2478r1869b2501],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1821t2478r1869b2501],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	2	SENT_21	[p1l1881t2477r1919b2501],
2	rights	NNS	O	rights	nsubj	3	SENT_21	[p1l1932t2477r2013b2507],
3	reserved	VBN	O	reserve	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l2026t2477r2154b2501],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l2026t2477r2154b2501],

1	*	NN	O	*	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l29t2609r37b2618],
2	Corresponding	VBG	O	correspond	partmod	1	SENT_22	[p1l54t2609r239b2636],
3	author	NN	O	author	dobj	2	SENT_22	[p1l250t2609r334b2631],
4	at	IN	O	at	prep	2	SENT_22	[p1l344t2612r375b2631],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l344t2612r375b2631],
6	262	CD	NUMBER	262	num	9	SENT_22	[p1l388t2610r433b2631],
7	Danny	NNP	PERSON	Danny	nn	9	SENT_22	[p1l446t2610r527b2636],
8	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	Thomas	nn	9	SENT_22	[p1l536t2609r635b2631],
9	Place	NNP	PERSON	Place	dep	1	SENT_22	[p1l647t2609r717b2634],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l647t2609r717b2634],
11	Mailstop	NNP	O	Mailstop	appos	9	SENT_22	[p1l728t2609r838b2636],
12	313	CD	NUMBER	313	num	11	SENT_22	[p1l849t2610r902b2634],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l849t2610r902b2634],
14	Memphis	NNP	LOCATION	Memphis	appos	9	SENT_22	[p1l913t2609r1037b2636],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l913t2609r1037b2636],
16	TN	NN	O	tn	appos	9	SENT_22	[p1l1047t2610r1082b2631],
17	38105	CD	NUMBER	38105	num	16	SENT_22	[p1l1093t2610r1178b2634],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1093t2610r1178b2634],
19	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	20	SENT_22	[p1l1189t2609r1273b2631],
20	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	appos	9	SENT_22	[p1l1284t2610r1365b2631],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1284t2610r1365b2631],

1	Tel.	NNP	O	Tel.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1375t2609r1427b2631],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1375t2609r1427b2631],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_23	[p1l1440t2610r1466b2631],
4	9015952205	CD	NUMBER	9015952205	dep	1	SENT_23	[p1l1481t2610r1647b2634],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1481t2610r1647b2634],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_23	[p1l1661t2609r1705b2631],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1661t2609r1705b2631],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_23	[p1l1718t2610r1744b2631],
9	9015953125	CD	NUMBER	9015953125	dep	6	SENT_23	[p1l1759t2610r1924b2631],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1759t2610r1924b2631],

1	E	NN	O	e	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l55t2644r134b2666],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	4	SENT_24	[p1l55t2644r134b2666],
3	mail	NN	O	mail	nn	4	SENT_24	[p1l55t2644r134b2666],
4	addresses	NNS	O	address	dep	1	SENT_24	[p1l142t2644r265b2666],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l142t2644r265b2666],
6	Ranjit.thirumaran@stjude.org	NN	O	ranjit.thirumaran@stjude.org	dep	1	SENT_24	[p1l274t2644r648b2671],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_24	[p1l656t2644r712b2671],
8	R.K.	NNP	PERSON	R.K.	nn	10	SENT_24	[p1l656t2644r712b2671],
9	Thirumaran	NNP	PERSON	Thirumaran	nn	10	SENT_24	[p1l720t2644r886b2671],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	6	SENT_24	[p1l720t2644r886b2671],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l720t2644r886b2671],
12	lamba004@umn.edu	NN	O	lamba004@umn.edu	nn	17	SENT_24	[p1l895t2644r1154b2666],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_24	[p1l1163t2644r1211b2671],
14	_	CD	NUMBER	_	num	17	SENT_24	[p1l1163t2644r1211b2671],
15	l.K.	NNP	PERSON	l.K.	nn	17	SENT_24	[p1l1163t2644r1211b2671],
16	Lamba	NNP	PERSON	Lamba	nn	17	SENT_24	[p1l1220t2644r1318b2671],
17	)	NNP	O	)	appos	10	SENT_24	[p1l1220t2644r1318b2671],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1220t2644r1318b2671],
19	Richard.kim@lhsc.on.ca	NNP	O	Richard.kim@lhsc.on.ca	nn	23	SENT_24	[p1l1327t2644r1624b2666],
20	(	NNP	O	(	nn	23	SENT_24	[p1l1632t2644r1687b2671],
21	R.B.	NNP	PERSON	R.B.	nn	23	SENT_24	[p1l1632t2644r1687b2671],
22	Kim	NNP	PERSON	Kim	nn	23	SENT_24	[p1l1696t2644r1762b2671],
23	)	NN	O	)	appos	10	SENT_24	[p1l1696t2644r1762b2671],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1696t2644r1762b2671],
25	brad.urquhart@schulich.uwo.ca	NN	O	brad.urquhart@schulich.uwo.ca	nn	27	SENT_24	[p1l6t2679r406b2706],
26	(	NN	O	(	nn	27	SENT_24	[p1l416t2679r468b2706],
27	B	NN	O	b	appos	10	SENT_24	[p1l416t2679r468b2706],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l416t2679r468b2706],
29	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	nn	31	SENT_24	[p1l416t2679r468b2706],
30	Urquhart	NNP	PERSON	Urquhart	nn	31	SENT_24	[p1l476t2679r607b2706],
31	)	NNP	O	)	appos	10	SENT_24	[p1l476t2679r607b2706],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l476t2679r607b2706],
33	]	CD	NUMBER	]	num	34	SENT_24	[p1l612t2679r919b2706],
34	amie.gregor@lhsc.on.ca	NN	O	amie.gregor@lhsc.on.ca	appos	10	SENT_24	[p1l612t2679r919b2706],
35	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	36	SENT_24	[p1l927t2679r974b2706],
36	]	NN	O	]	dep	34	SENT_24	[p1l927t2679r974b2706],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l927t2679r974b2706],

1	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	3	SENT_25	[p1l927t2679r974b2706],
2	Gregor	NNP	PERSON	Gregor	nn	3	SENT_25	[p1l982t2679r1083b2706],
3	)	NNP	O	)	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l982t2679r1083b2706],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l982t2679r1083b2706],
5	nilesh.chande@lhsc.on.ca	JJ	O	nilesh.chande@lhsc.on.ca	amod	9	SENT_25	[p1l1092t2679r1410b2701],
6	(	NN	O	(	nn	9	SENT_25	[p1l1418t2679r1453b2705],
7	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	9	SENT_25	[p1l1418t2679r1453b2705],
8	Chande	NNP	PERSON	Chande	nn	9	SENT_25	[p1l1462t2679r1571b2706],
9	)	NNP	O	)	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l1462t2679r1571b2706],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1462t2679r1571b2706],
11	yiping,fan@stjude.org	NN	O	yiping,fan@stjude.org	nn	15	SENT_25	[p1l1579t2679r1853b2706],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_25	[p1l1861t2679r1892b2706],
13	Y.	NNP	PERSON	Y.	nn	15	SENT_25	[p1l1861t2679r1892b2706],
14	Fan	NNP	PERSON	Fan	nn	15	SENT_25	[p1l1901t2679r1960b2706],
15	)	NNP	O	)	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l1901t2679r1960b2706],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1901t2679r1960b2706],
17	qi.an@stjude.org	NN	O	qi.an@stjude.org	nn	19	SENT_25	[p1l6t2713r215b2740],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	19	SENT_25	[p1l223t2714r255b2740],
19	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l223t2714r255b2740],
20	Qi	NNP	PERSON	Qi	nn	21	SENT_25	[p1l264t2714r306b2740],
21	)	NNP	O	)	dep	19	SENT_25	[p1l264t2714r306b2740],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l264t2714r306b2740],
23	cheng.cheng@stjude.org	NN	O	cheng.cheng@stjude.org	nn	27	SENT_25	[p1l314t2713r620b2740],
24	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	27	SENT_25	[p1l630t2713r662b2740],
25	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	27	SENT_25	[p1l630t2713r662b2740],
26	Cheng	NNP	PERSON	Cheng	nn	27	SENT_25	[p1l673t2713r767b2740],
27	)	NNP	O	)	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l673t2713r767b2740],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l673t2713r767b2740],
29	thummel@u.washington.edu	FW	O	thummel@u.washington.edu	nn	33	SENT_25	[p1l778t2713r1142b2740],
30	(	FW	O	(	nn	33	SENT_25	[p1l1153t2713r1208b2740],
31	K.E.	FW	PERSON	k.e.	nn	33	SENT_25	[p1l1153t2713r1208b2740],
32	Thummel	FW	PERSON	thummel	nn	33	SENT_25	[p1l1219t2713r1357b2740],
33	)	FW	O	)	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l1219t2713r1357b2740],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1219t2713r1357b2740],
35	hallst@lilly.com	NNP	O	hallst@lilly.com	nn	38	SENT_25	[p1l1368t2713r1568b2740],
36	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	38	SENT_25	[p1l1579t2713r1634b2740],
37	S.D.	NNP	O	S.D.	nn	38	SENT_25	[p1l1579t2713r1634b2740],
38	Hall	NNP	O	Hall	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l1646t2713r1712b2740],
39	)	NN	O	)	dep	38	SENT_25	[p1l1646t2713r1712b2740],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1646t2713r1712b2740],
41	erin.schuetz@stjude.org	NN	O	erin.schuetz@stjude.org	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l1723t2713r2025b2740],
42	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	45	SENT_25	[p1l2036t2713r2092b2740],
43	E.G.	NNP	PERSON	E.G.	nn	45	SENT_25	[p1l2036t2713r2092b2740],
44	Schuetz	NNP	PERSON	Schuetz	nn	45	SENT_25	[p1l6t2748r120b2774],
45	)	NN	O	)	dep	41	SENT_25	[p1l6t2748r120b2774],
46	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l6t2748r120b2774],

1	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	2	SENT_26	[p1l31t2779r38b2793],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l55t2783r163b2805],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l55t2783r163b2805],
4	262	CD	NUMBER	262	num	7	SENT_26	[p1l176t2784r221b2805],
5	Danny	NNP	PERSON	Danny	nn	7	SENT_26	[p1l234t2784r315b2810],
6	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	Thomas	nn	7	SENT_26	[p1l324t2783r423b2805],
7	Place	NNP	PERSON	Place	dep	2	SENT_26	[p1l435t2783r505b2808],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l435t2783r505b2808],
9	Mailstop	NNP	O	Mailstop	appos	7	SENT_26	[p1l517t2783r626b2810],
10	313	CD	NUMBER	313	num	9	SENT_26	[p1l636t2784r690b2808],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l636t2784r690b2808],
12	Memphis	NNP	LOCATION	Memphis	appos	7	SENT_26	[p1l701t2783r825b2810],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l701t2783r825b2810],
14	TN	NN	O	tn	appos	7	SENT_26	[p1l835t2784r870b2805],
15	38105	CD	NUMBER	38105	num	14	SENT_26	[p1l881t2784r966b2808],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l881t2784r966b2808],
17	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	18	SENT_26	[p1l977t2783r1061b2805],
18	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	appos	7	SENT_26	[p1l1072t2784r1153b2805],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1072t2784r1153b2805],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1163t2783r1208b2805],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1163t2783r1208b2805],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_27	[p1l1222t2784r1248b2805],
4	9015953612	CD	NUMBER	9015953612	dep	1	SENT_27	[p1l1262t2784r1429b2808],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1262t2784r1429b2808],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_27	[p1l1442t2783r1487b2805],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1442t2783r1487b2805],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_27	[p1l1500t2784r1526b2805],
9	9015953125	CD	NUMBER	9015953125	dep	6	SENT_27	[p1l1540t2784r1705b2805],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1540t2784r1705b2805],

1	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	2	SENT_28	[p1l30t2814r40b2828],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l55t2818r163b2840],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l55t2818r163b2840],
4	7-115	CD	NUMBER	7-115	num	5	SENT_28	[p1l176t2819r249b2840],
5	Weaver	NNP	PERSON	Weaver	dep	2	SENT_28	[p1l260t2818r484b2840],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l260t2818r484b2840],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l260t2818r484b2840],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l260t2818r484b2840],

1	Densford	NNP	LOCATION	Densford	nn	3	SENT_30	[p1l260t2818r484b2840],
2	Hall	NNP	LOCATION	Hall	nn	3	SENT_30	[p1l495t2818r545b2840],
3	Minneapolis	NNP	LOCATION	Minneapolis	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l556t2818r717b2845],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l556t2818r717b2845],
5	MN	NN	O	mn	appos	3	SENT_30	[p1l729t2819r773b2840],
6	55455	CD	NUMBER	55455	num	5	SENT_30	[p1l785t2819r869b2843],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l785t2819r869b2843],
8	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	9	SENT_30	[p1l880t2818r964b2840],
9	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	appos	5	SENT_30	[p1l975t2819r1056b2840],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l975t2819r1056b2840],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1066t2818r1112b2840],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1066t2818r1112b2840],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_31	[p1l1125t2819r1151b2839],
4	6126266095	CD	NUMBER	6126266095	dep	1	SENT_31	[p1l1166t2819r1332b2843],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1166t2819r1332b2843],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_31	[p1l1345t2818r1390b2840],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1345t2818r1390b2840],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_31	[p1l1403t2819r1429b2839],
9	6126253927	CD	NUMBER	6126253927	dep	6	SENT_31	[p1l1444t2819r1609b2840],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1444t2819r1609b2840],

1	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	2	SENT_32	[p1l30t2849r40b2863],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l55t2853r163b2875],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l55t2853r163b2875],
4	339	CD	NUMBER	339	dep	2	SENT_32	[p1l175t2854r222b2875],
5	Windermere	NNP	LOCATION	Windermere	nn	6	SENT_32	[p1l233t2853r393b2875],
6	Road	NNP	LOCATION	Road	dep	2	SENT_32	[p1l404t2853r472b2878],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l404t2853r472b2878],
8	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	appos	2	SENT_32	[p1l483t2853r582b2878],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l483t2853r582b2878],
10	ON	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l593t2854r631b2875],
11	N6A	NN	O	n6a	nn	12	SENT_32	[p1l643t2854r696b2875],
12	5A5	NN	O	5a5	prep_on	2	SENT_32	[p1l707t2854r761b2878],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l707t2854r761b2878],
14	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	appos	12	SENT_32	[p1l772t2853r870b2875],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l772t2853r870b2875],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l880t2853r925b2875],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l880t2853r925b2875],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_33	[p1l938t2854r964b2875],
4	5196633553	CD	NUMBER	5196633553	dep	1	SENT_33	[p1l979t2854r1146b2878],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l979t2854r1146b2878],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_33	[p1l1159t2853r1204b2875],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1159t2853r1204b2875],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_33	[p1l1217t2854r1243b2875],
9	5196633232	CD	NUMBER	5196633232	dep	6	SENT_33	[p1l1258t2854r1423b2875],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1258t2854r1423b2875],

1	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	2	SENT_34	[p1l29t2884r41b2898],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l55t2888r163b2910],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l55t2888r163b2910],
4	1151	CD	DATE	1151	dep	2	SENT_34	[p1l177t2889r235b2910],
5	Richmond	NNP	LOCATION	Richmond	nn	6	SENT_34	[p1l250t2888r377b2910],
6	Street	NNP	LOCATION	Street	dep	2	SENT_34	[p1l388t2889r467b2913],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l388t2889r467b2913],
8	MSB	NN	ORGANIZATION	msb	nn	9	SENT_34	[p1l479t2889r534b2910],
9	room	NN	O	room	appos	2	SENT_34	[p1l545t2894r611b2910],
10	216	CD	NUMBER	216	dep	9	SENT_34	[p1l622t2889r675b2913],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l622t2889r675b2913],
12	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	appos	2	SENT_34	[p1l686t2888r785b2913],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l686t2888r785b2913],
14	ON	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l796t2889r834b2910],
15	N6A	NN	O	n6a	nn	16	SENT_34	[p1l846t2889r899b2910],
16	5C1	NN	O	5c1	prep_on	2	SENT_34	[p1l910t2889r963b2913],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l910t2889r963b2913],
18	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	appos	16	SENT_34	[p1l974t2888r1071b2910],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l974t2888r1071b2910],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1082t2888r1127b2910],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1082t2888r1127b2910],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_35	[p1l1140t2889r1166b2910],
4	5196613756	CD	NUMBER	5196613756	dep	1	SENT_35	[p1l1181t2889r1348b2913],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1181t2889r1348b2913],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_35	[p1l1361t2888r1405b2910],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1361t2888r1405b2910],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_35	[p1l1418t2889r1444b2910],
9	5196613786	CD	NUMBER	5196613786	dep	6	SENT_35	[p1l1459t2889r1624b2910],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1459t2889r1624b2910],

1	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	2	SENT_36	[p1l30t2919r40b2932],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l55t2923r163b2945],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l55t2923r163b2945],
4	800	CD	NUMBER	800	num	5	SENT_36	[p1l176t2924r222b2945],
5	Commissioners	NNS	O	commissioner	dep	2	SENT_36	[p1l233t2923r425b2945],
6	Road	NNP	LOCATION	Road	nn	7	SENT_36	[p1l437t2923r498b2945],
7	East	NNP	LOCATION	East	dep	2	SENT_36	[p1l510t2924r566b2948],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l510t2924r566b2948],
9	E2	NN	O	e2	nn	10	SENT_36	[p1l578t2924r673b2948],
10	—	NN	O	—	appos	2	SENT_36	[p1l578t2924r673b2948],
11	317	CD	NUMBER	317	dep	10	SENT_36	[p1l578t2924r673b2948],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l578t2924r673b2948],
13	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	appos	2	SENT_36	[p1l685t2923r783b2948],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l685t2923r783b2948],
15	ON	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l795t2924r833b2945],
16	N6A	NN	O	n6a	nn	17	SENT_36	[p1l844t2924r898b2945],
17	4G5	NN	O	4g5	prep_on	2	SENT_36	[p1l907t2924r964b2948],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l907t2924r964b2948],
19	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	appos	17	SENT_36	[p1l975t2923r1072b2945],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l975t2923r1072b2945],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1083t2923r1128b2945],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1083t2923r1128b2945],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_37	[p1l1141t2924r1167b2944],
4	5196676843	CD	NUMBER	5196676843	dep	1	SENT_37	[p1l1182t2924r1349b2948],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1182t2924r1349b2948],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_37	[p1l1362t2923r1407b2945],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1362t2923r1407b2945],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_37	[p1l1420t2924r1446b2944],
9	5196676820	CD	NUMBER	5196676820	dep	6	SENT_37	[p1l1461t2924r1625b2945],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1461t2924r1625b2945],

1	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	2	SENT_38	[p1l30t2954r41b2968],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l55t2958r163b2980],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l55t2958r163b2980],
4	375	CD	NUMBER	375	num	6	SENT_38	[p1l175t2959r221b2980],
5	South	NNP	O	South	nn	6	SENT_38	[p1l234t2958r305b2980],
6	Street	NNP	O	Street	dep	2	SENT_38	[p1l316t2959r396b2983],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l316t2959r396b2983],
8	PO	NNP	O	PO	nn	9	SENT_38	[p1l407t2959r440b2980],
9	Box	NNP	O	Box	appos	6	SENT_38	[p1l452t2960r498b2980],
10	5375	CD	NUMBER	5375	num	9	SENT_38	[p1l508t2959r577b2983],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l508t2959r577b2983],
12	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	appos	6	SENT_38	[p1l588t2958r687b2983],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l588t2958r687b2983],
14	ON	NNP	O	ON	nn	16	SENT_38	[p1l698t2959r736b2980],
15	NGA	NNP	O	NGA	nn	16	SENT_38	[p1l748t2959r802b2980],
16	4G5	NN	O	4g5	appos	6	SENT_38	[p1l811t2959r868b2983],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l811t2959r868b2983],
18	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	appos	6	SENT_38	[p1l879t2958r976b2980],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l879t2958r976b2980],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l987t2958r1032b2980],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l987t2958r1032b2980],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_39	[p1l1045t2959r1071b2980],
4	5196676582	CD	NUMBER	5196676582	dep	1	SENT_39	[p1l1086t2959r1253b2983],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1086t2959r1253b2983],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_39	[p1l1266t2958r1310b2980],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1266t2958r1310b2980],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_39	[p1l1323t2959r1349b2980],
9	5196676820	CD	NUMBER	5196676820	dep	6	SENT_39	[p1l1364t2959r1529b2980],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1364t2959r1529b2980],

1	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	2	SENT_40	[p1l30t2989r40b3003],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l55t2993r163b3015],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l55t2993r163b3015],
4	262	CD	NUMBER	262	num	7	SENT_40	[p1l176t2994r221b3015],
5	Danny	NNP	PERSON	Danny	nn	7	SENT_40	[p1l234t2994r315b3020],
6	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	Thomas	nn	7	SENT_40	[p1l324t2993r423b3015],
7	Place	NNP	PERSON	Place	dep	2	SENT_40	[p1l435t2993r505b3018],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l435t2993r505b3018],
9	Mailstop	NNP	O	Mailstop	appos	7	SENT_40	[p1l517t2993r626b3020],
10	312	CD	NUMBER	312	num	9	SENT_40	[p1l636t2994r690b3018],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l636t2994r690b3018],
12	Memphis	NNP	LOCATION	Memphis	appos	7	SENT_40	[p1l701t2993r825b3020],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l701t2993r825b3020],
14	TN	NN	O	tn	appos	7	SENT_40	[p1l835t2994r870b3015],
15	38105	CD	NUMBER	38105	num	14	SENT_40	[p1l881t2994r966b3018],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l881t2994r966b3018],
17	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	18	SENT_40	[p1l977t2993r1061b3015],
18	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	appos	7	SENT_40	[p1l1072t2994r1153b3015],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l1072t2994r1153b3015],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1163t2993r1208b3015],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1163t2993r1208b3015],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_41	[p1l1222t2994r1248b3015],
4	9015953188	CD	NUMBER	9015953188	dep	1	SENT_41	[p1l1262t2994r1429b3018],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1262t2994r1429b3018],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_41	[p1l1442t2993r1487b3015],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1442t2993r1487b3015],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_41	[p1l1500t2994r1526b3015],
9	9015953135	CD	NUMBER	9015953135	dep	6	SENT_41	[p1l1540t2994r1705b3015],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1540t2994r1705b3015],

1	8	CD	NUMBER	8	num	2	SENT_42	[p1l30t3024r40b3038],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l55t3028r163b3050],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l55t3028r163b3050],
4	R2035	NN	O	r2035	nn	6	SENT_42	[p1l176t3029r254b3050],
5	Longionotti	NNP	O	Longionotti	nn	6	SENT_42	[p1l267t3028r410b3055],
6	Building	NNP	O	Building	dep	2	SENT_42	[p1l422t3028r532b3055],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l422t3028r532b3055],
8	Mailstop	NNP	O	Mailstop	appos	6	SENT_42	[p1l544t3028r653b3055],
9	723	CD	NUMBER	723	num	8	SENT_42	[p1l665t3029r717b3053],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l665t3029r717b3053],
11	Memphis	NNP	LOCATION	Memphis	appos	6	SENT_42	[p1l728t3028r852b3055],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l728t3028r852b3055],
13	TN	NN	O	tn	appos	6	SENT_42	[p1l863t3029r898b3049],
14	38105	CD	NUMBER	38105	num	13	SENT_42	[p1l908t3029r993b3053],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l908t3029r993b3053],
16	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	17	SENT_42	[p1l1004t3028r1088b3050],
17	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	appos	6	SENT_42	[p1l1100t3029r1180b3050],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l1100t3029r1180b3050],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1191t3028r1236b3050],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1191t3028r1236b3050],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_43	[p1l1249t3029r1275b3049],
4	9015954584	CD	NUMBER	9015954584	dep	1	SENT_43	[p1l1290t3029r1457b3053],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1290t3029r1457b3053],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_43	[p1l1470t3028r1514b3050],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1470t3028r1514b3050],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_43	[p1l1527t3029r1554b3049],
9	9015954585	CD	NUMBER	9015954585	dep	6	SENT_43	[p1l1568t3029r1733b3050],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l1568t3029r1733b3050],

1	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	2	SENT_44	[p1l30t3059r40b3073],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l55t3063r163b3085],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l55t3063r163b3085],
4	R6035	NN	O	r6035	nn	6	SENT_44	[p1l176t3064r254b3085],
5	Longionotti	NNP	O	Longionotti	nn	6	SENT_44	[p1l267t3063r410b3090],
6	Building	NNP	O	Building	dep	2	SENT_44	[p1l422t3063r532b3090],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l422t3063r532b3090],
8	Mailstop	NNP	O	Mailstop	appos	6	SENT_44	[p1l544t3063r653b3090],
9	723	CD	NUMBER	723	num	8	SENT_44	[p1l665t3064r717b3088],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l665t3064r717b3088],
11	Memphis	NNP	LOCATION	Memphis	appos	6	SENT_44	[p1l728t3063r852b3090],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l728t3063r852b3090],
13	TN	NN	O	tn	appos	6	SENT_44	[p1l862t3064r897b3084],
14	38105	CD	NUMBER	38105	num	13	SENT_44	[p1l908t3064r993b3088],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l908t3064r993b3088],
16	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	17	SENT_44	[p1l1004t3063r1088b3085],
17	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	appos	6	SENT_44	[p1l1100t3064r1180b3085],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l1100t3064r1180b3085],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1190t3063r1236b3085],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1190t3063r1236b3085],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_45	[p1l1249t3064r1275b3084],
4	9015952935	CD	NUMBER	9015952935	dep	1	SENT_45	[p1l1289t3064r1456b3088],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1289t3064r1456b3088],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_45	[p1l1469t3063r1514b3085],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1469t3063r1514b3085],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_45	[p1l1527t3064r1553b3084],
9	901 595 8845	CD	NUMBER	901 595 8845	dep	6	SENT_45	[p1l1683t3064r1751b3085],[p1l1568t3064r1611b3085],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1683t3064r1751b3085],

1	‘	NN	O	‘	nn	3	SENT_46	[p1l19t3093r41b3107],
2	O	NN	O	o	nn	3	SENT_46	[p1l19t3093r41b3107],
3	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l55t3097r163b3119],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l55t3097r163b3119],
5	Health	NNP	O	Health	nn	7	SENT_46	[p1l176t3097r259b3119],
6	Science	NNP	O	Science	nn	7	SENT_46	[p1l270t3098r363b3119],
7	Building	NNP	O	Building	dep	3	SENT_46	[p1l374t3097r484b3124],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l374t3097r484b3124],
9	Box	NNP	O	Box	appos	7	SENT_46	[p1l496t3099r542b3119],
10	357610	CD	NUMBER	357610	num	9	SENT_46	[p1l552t3098r653b3122],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l552t3098r653b3122],
12	Seattle	NNP	LOCATION	Seattle	appos	7	SENT_46	[p1l664t3097r755b3122],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l664t3097r755b3122],
14	WA	NNP	LOCATION	WA	appos	7	SENT_46	[p1l765t3098r812b3119],
15	98195	CD	NUMBER	98195	num	14	SENT_46	[p1l822t3098r907b3122],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l822t3098r907b3122],
17	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	18	SENT_46	[p1l918t3097r1003b3119],
18	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	appos	7	SENT_46	[p1l1014t3098r1094b3119],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l1014t3098r1094b3119],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l1105t3097r1150b3119],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l1105t3097r1150b3119],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_47	[p1l1163t3098r1189b3119],
4	2065430819	CD	NUMBER	2065430819	dep	1	SENT_47	[p1l1203t3098r1370b3122],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l1203t3098r1370b3122],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_47	[p1l1383t3097r1428b3119],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l1383t3097r1428b3119],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_47	[p1l1441t3098r1467b3119],
9	2065433204	CD	NUMBER	2065433204	dep	6	SENT_47	[p1l1481t3098r1646b3119],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l1481t3098r1646b3119],

1	“	NN	O	“	nn	2	SENT_48	[p1l19t3128r38b3142],
2	Address	NN	O	address	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l55t3132r163b3154],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l55t3132r163b3154],
4	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Lilly	nn	6	SENT_48	[p1l176t3132r229b3159],
5	Corporate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Corporate	nn	6	SENT_48	[p1l239t3133r363b3159],
6	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	2	SENT_48	[p1l374t3133r462b3157],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l374t3133r462b3157],
8	Indianapolis	NNP	LOCATION	Indianapolis	appos	2	SENT_48	[p1l474t3132r634b3159],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l474t3132r634b3159],
10	IN	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l646t3133r673b3154],
11	46285	CD	NUMBER	46285	prep_in	2	SENT_48	[p1l683t3133r769b3157],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l683t3133r769b3157],
13	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	14	SENT_48	[p1l780t3132r864b3154],
14	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	appos	11	SENT_48	[p1l875t3133r956b3154],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l875t3133r956b3154],

1	Tel	NNP	O	Tel	_	0	SENT_49	[p1l966t3132r1011b3154],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_49	[p1l966t3132r1011b3154],
3	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	4	SENT_49	[p1l1024t3133r1050b3154],
4	3172770338	CD	NUMBER	3172770338	dep	1	SENT_49	[p1l1065t3133r1232b3157],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p1l1065t3133r1232b3157],
6	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	4	SENT_49	[p1l1245t3132r1290b3154],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_49	[p1l1245t3132r1290b3154],
8	+1	CD	NUMBER	+1	number	9	SENT_49	[p1l1303t3133r1329b3154],
9	3174339287	CD	NUMBER	3174339287	dep	6	SENT_49	[p1l1343t3133r1509b3154],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p1l1343t3133r1509b3154],

1	‘	NN	O	‘	nn	4	SENT_50	[p1l19t3163r40b3177],
2	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	4	SENT_50	[p1l19t3163r40b3177],
3	Drs.	NNP	O	Drs.	nn	4	SENT_50	[p1l56t3168r103b3189],
4	Thirumaran	NNP	PERSON	Thirumaran	nsubj	7	SENT_50	[p1l114t3167r264b3189],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p1l275t3167r320b3189],
6	Lamba	NNP	PERSON	Lamba	conj_and	4	SENT_50	[p1l332t3167r414b3189],
7	contributed	VBD	O	contribute	_	0	SENT_50	[p1l425t3167r572b3189],
8	equally	RB	O	equally	advmod	7	SENT_50	[p1l584t3167r676b3194],
9	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_50	[p1l686t3170r710b3189],
10	this	DT	O	this	det	11	SENT_50	[p1l721t3167r767b3189],
11	work	NN	O	work	prep_to	7	SENT_50	[p1l778t3167r848b3189],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p1l778t3167r848b3189],

1	0006-2952	CD	DURATION	0006-2952	_	0	SENT_51	[p1l6t3240r167b3268],
2	/	:	O	/	punct	1	SENT_51	[p1l6t3240r167b3268],
3	$	$	MONEY	$	nsubj	5	SENT_51	[p1l6t3240r167b3268],
4	—	CD	MONEY	—	num	3	SENT_51	[p1l179t3253r192b3256],
5	see	VBP	O	see	dep	1	SENT_51	[p1l204t3247r243b3262],
6	front	JJ	O	front	amod	7	SENT_51	[p1l254t3240r316b3262],
7	matter	NN	O	matter	dobj	5	SENT_51	[p1l326t3244r412b3262],
8	©	CD	NUMBER	©	num	11	SENT_51	[p1l423t3244r442b3263],
9	2012	CD	DATE	2012	num	11	SENT_51	[p1l454t3242r516b3262],
10	Elsevier	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Elsevier	nn	11	SENT_51	[p1l528t3241r626b3262],
11	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	dep	7	SENT_51	[p1l637t3242r679b3263],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p1l637t3242r679b3263],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	2	SENT_52	[p1l690t3241r723b3262],
2	rights	NNS	O	rights	nsubj	3	SENT_52	[p1l735t3241r806b3268],
3	reserved	VBN	O	reserve	_	0	SENT_52	[p1l818t3241r931b3263],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p1l818t3241r931b3263],

1	http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.bcp.2012.03.017	NN	O	http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.bcp.2012.03.017	_	0	SENT_53	[p1l6t3276r560b3303],

1	R.K.	NNP	PERSON	R.K.	nn	2	SENT_54	[p1l324t3379r367b3400],
2	Thirumaran	NNP	PERSON	Thirumaran	_	0	SENT_54	[p1l380t3378r522b3400],
3	et	FW	O	et	nn	4	SENT_54	[p1l533t3381r556b3400],
4	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	2	SENT_54	[p1l565t3378r756b3405],
5	/	:	O	/	punct	2	SENT_54	[p1l565t3378r756b3405],
6	Biochemical	JJ	O	biochemical	amod	7	SENT_54	[p1l565t3378r756b3405],
7	Pharmacology	NN	O	pharmacology	dep	2	SENT_54	[p1l766t3378r937b3405],
8	84	CD	NUMBER	84	number	9	SENT_54	[p1l948t3379r977b3400],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_54	[p1l988t3378r1068b3405],
10	2012	CD	DATE	2012	dep	7	SENT_54	[p1l988t3378r1068b3405],
11	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	12	SENT_54	[p1l988t3378r1068b3405],
12	104-112 105	CD	NUMBER	104-112 105	num	10	SENT_54	[p1l1794t3379r1836b3400],[p1l1081t3379r1185b3400],

1	1	LS	NUMBER	1	_	0	SENT_55	[p1l11t3516r65b3567],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p1l11t3516r65b3567],

1	Introduction	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_56	[p1l104t3513r538b3567],

1	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nsubjpass	4	SENT_57	[p2l112t70r366b123],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_57	[p2l399t69r446b123],
3	highly	RB	O	highly	advmod	4	SENT_57	[p2l481t68r687b137],
4	expressed	VBN	O	express	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l719t68r1045b137],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l1079t69r1140b123],
6	human	JJ	O	human	amod	7	SENT_57	[p2l1172t68r1401b123],
7	duodenal	JJ	O	duodenal	prep_in	4	SENT_57	[p2l1434t68r1737b123],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l1771t68r1889b123],
9	jejunal	JJ	O	jejunal	amod	10	SENT_57	[p2l1915t68r2145b137],
10	mucosal	JJ	O	mucosal	amod	11	SENT_57	[p2l10t158r281b213],
11	epithelium	NN	O	epithelium	prep_in	4	SENT_57	[p2l308t158r668b226],
12	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	13	SENT_57	[p2l697t157r859b226],
13	1,2	CD	NUMBER	1,2	num	14	SENT_57	[p2l697t157r859b226],
14	]	NN	O	]	dep	7	SENT_57	[p2l697t157r859b226],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l697t157r859b226],

1	Inter	NNP	O	Inter	nsubj	11	SENT_58	[p2l887t158r1408b213],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	4	SENT_58	[p2l887t158r1408b213],
3	individual	JJ	O	individual	amod	4	SENT_58	[p2l887t158r1408b213],
4	differences	NNS	O	difference	dep	1	SENT_58	[p2l1436t157r1795b213],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1824t158r1883b212],
6	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	8	SENT_58	[p2l1910t158r2146b213, p2l10t246r107b301],
7	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	8	SENT_58	[p2l128t249r382b301],
8	expression	NN	O	expression	prep_in	1	SENT_58	[p2l401t247r754b315],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l773t246r891b301],
10	activity	NN	O	activity	conj_and	8	SENT_58	[p2l911t247r1157b315],
11	contribute	VBP	O	contribute	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1176t246r1518b301],
12	signiﬁcantly	NN	O	signiﬁcantly	dobj	11	SENT_58	[p2l1539t246r1943b315],
13	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1961t255r2023b301],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_58	[p2l2043t246r2146b301],
15	low	JJ	O	low	amod	19	SENT_58	[p2l10t336r130b391],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l174t336r292b391],
17	variable	JJ	O	variable	conj_and	15	SENT_58	[p2l336t336r601b391],
18	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	19	SENT_58	[p2l647t336r770b391],
19	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	prep_to	11	SENT_58	[p2l817t336r1289b404],
20	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1334t336r1426b391],
21	many	JJ	O	many	amod	24	SENT_58	[p2l1469t352r1652b404],
22	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	24	SENT_58	[p2l1697t338r1951b391],
23	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	24	SENT_58	[p2l1997t336r2148b404],
24	substrates	NNS	O	substrate	prep_for	19	SENT_58	[p2l11t425r363b480],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l11t425r363b480],

1	For	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l390t428r492b480],
2	example	NN	O	example	prep_for	6	SENT_59	[p2l515t425r809b493],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l515t425r809b493],
4	it	PRP	O	it	nsubjpass	6	SENT_59	[p2l835t426r879b480],
5	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_59	[p2l901t441r1027b480],
6	estimated	VBN	O	estimate	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l1053t425r1378b480],
7	that	IN	O	that	complm	10	SENT_59	[p2l1402t425r1534b480],
8	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	9	SENT_59	[p2l1558t425r1867b480],
9	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nsubj	10	SENT_59	[p2l1892t427r2146b480],
10	catalyzes	VBZ	O	catalyze	ccomp	6	SENT_59	[p2l10t513r309b582],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_59	[p2l329t513r432b568],
12	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	nn	14	SENT_59	[p2l452t513r581b568],
13	pass	NN	O	pass	nn	14	SENT_59	[p2l600t529r739b582],
14	loss	NN	O	loss	dobj	10	SENT_59	[p2l760t513r880b568],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l901t513r968b568],
16	>	JJR	O	>	amod	31	SENT_59	[p2l983t516r1157b570],
17	40	CD	PERCENT	40	num	18	SENT_59	[p2l983t516r1157b570],
18	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	16	SENT_59	[p2l983t516r1157b570],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	16	SENT_59	[p2l1177t513r1283b582],
20	on	IN	O	on	dep	19	SENT_59	[p2l1177t513r1283b582],
21	average	JJ	O	average	amod	22	SENT_59	[p2l1302t513r1582b582],
22	)	NN	O	)	pobj	20	SENT_59	[p2l1302t513r1582b582],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l1602t513r1668b568],
24	an	DT	O	a	det	26	SENT_59	[p2l1680t529r1756b568],
25	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	26	SENT_59	[p2l1776t513r1899b568],
26	dose	NN	O	dose	prep_of	22	SENT_59	[p2l1920t513r2067b568],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l2087t513r2154b568],
28	midazolam	NN	O	midazolam	prep_of	26	SENT_59	[p2l10t602r376b657],
29	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	30	SENT_59	[p2l441t602r602b671],
30	3,4	CD	NUMBER	3,4	num	28	SENT_59	[p2l441t602r602b671],
31	]	NN	O	]	prep_of	14	SENT_59	[p2l441t602r602b671],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l441t602r602b671],

1	Moreover	RB	O	moreover	advmod	15	SENT_60	[p2l666t605r997b665],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l666t605r997b665],
3	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l1060t602r1150b657],
4	midazolam	NN	O	midazolam	prep_for	15	SENT_60	[p2l1210t602r1592b666],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l1210t602r1592b666],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_60	[p2l1653t602r1757b657],
7	extent	NN	O	extent	nsubj	15	SENT_60	[p2l1818t610r2027b657],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l2087t602r2154b657],
9	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	10	SENT_60	[p2l10t691r318b746],
10	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	prep_of	7	SENT_60	[p2l360t691r661b760],
11	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	13	SENT_60	[p2l360t691r661b760],
12	pass	NN	O	pass	nn	13	SENT_60	[p2l360t691r661b760],
13	extraction	NN	O	extraction	dep	10	SENT_60	[p2l701t692r1037b746],
14	can	MD	O	can	aux	15	SENT_60	[p2l1075t707r1185b746],
15	vary	VB	O	vary	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l1222t707r1365b760],
16	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l1402t691r1685b746],
17	negligible	JJ	O	negligible	amod	26	SENT_60	[p2l1723t691r2045b760],
18	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l2083t700r2146b746],
19	as	RB	O	as	quantmod	23	SENT_60	[p2l10t796r73b835],
20	much	JJ	O	much	quantmod	23	SENT_60	[p2l92t780r273b835],
21	as	IN	O	as	quantmod	23	SENT_60	[p2l290t796r353b835],
22	75	CD	PERCENT	75	number	23	SENT_60	[p2l372t783r495b835],
23	%	NN	PERCENT	%	num	25	SENT_60	[p2l372t783r495b835],
24	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	25	SENT_60	[p2l515t780r617b849],
25	4	CD	NUMBER	4	prep_to	17	SENT_60	[p2l515t780r617b849],
26	]	NN	O	]	prep_between	15	SENT_60	[p2l515t780r617b849],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l515t780r617b849],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_61	[p2l632t780r767b835],
2	result	NN	O	result	nsubj	4	SENT_61	[p2l786t780r973b835],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	4	SENT_61	[p2l989t781r1036b835],
4	consistent	JJ	O	consistent	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1054t781r1391b835],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1405t780r1555b835],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_61	[p2l1571t780r1674b835],
7	more	JJR	O	more	amod	23	SENT_61	[p2l1691t796r1859b835],
8	than	IN	O	than	mark	19	SENT_61	[p2l1875t780r2023b835],
9	20fold	JJ	O	20fold	amod	11	SENT_61	[p2l2039t783r2146b835, p2l10t870r134b924],
10	inter-individual	JJ	O	inter-individual	amod	11	SENT_61	[p2l174t870r695b924],
11	differences	NNS	O	difference	nsubj	19	SENT_61	[p2l735t870r1095b924],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1137t871r1196b923],
13	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	14	SENT_61	[p2l1236t872r1489b924],
14	content	NN	O	content	prep_in	11	SENT_61	[p2l1529t878r1779b924],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1818t871r1878b923],
16	human	JJ	O	human	amod	18	SENT_61	[p2l1917t870r2147b924],
17	duodenal	JJ	O	duodenal	amod	18	SENT_61	[p2l10t958r314b1013],
18	enterocytes	NNS	O	enterocyte	prep_in	14	SENT_61	[p2l369t966r750b1026],
19	[	VBP	O	[	ccomp	7	SENT_61	[p2l809t958r995b1026],
20	5	CD	NUMBER	5	dobj	19	SENT_61	[p2l809t958r995b1026],
21	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	22	SENT_61	[p2l809t958r995b1026],
22	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	23	SENT_61	[p2l809t958r995b1026],
23	]	NN	O	]	prep_with	4	SENT_61	[p2l809t958r995b1026],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l809t958r995b1026],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_62	[p2l1048t958r1237b1013],
2	ﬁndings	NNS	O	ﬁndings	nsubj	3	SENT_62	[p2l1291t958r1553b1026],
3	have	VBP	O	have	dep	21	SENT_62	[p2l1609t958r1760b1013],
4	important	JJ	O	important	amod	6	SENT_62	[p2l1815t959r2147b1026],
5	therapeutic	JJ	O	therapeutic	amod	6	SENT_62	[p2l9t1046r389b1115],
6	implications	NNS	O	implication	dobj	3	SENT_62	[p2l422t1046r828b1115],
7	because	IN	O	because	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l862t1046r1123b1101],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_62	[p2l1155t1046r1259b1101],
9	large	JJ	O	large	amod	13	SENT_62	[p2l1292t1046r1452b1115],
10	inter	NN	O	inter	nn	13	SENT_62	[p2l1487t1047r1909b1115],
11	—	NN	O	—	nn	13	SENT_62	[p2l1487t1047r1909b1115],
12	patient	NN	O	patient	nn	13	SENT_62	[p2l1487t1047r1909b1115],
13	differences	NNS	O	difference	prep_because	3	SENT_62	[p2l1941t1046r2146b1101, p2l10t1151r189b1190],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l248t1136r308b1189],
15	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	nn	17	SENT_62	[p2l366t1135r668b1204],
16	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	17	SENT_62	[p2l366t1135r668b1204],
17	pass	NN	O	pass	prep_in	13	SENT_62	[p2l366t1135r668b1204],
18	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	20	SENT_62	[p2l727t1135r1037b1190],
19	extraction	NN	O	extraction	nn	20	SENT_62	[p2l1095t1136r1430b1190],
20	efﬁciency	NN	O	efﬁciency	nsubj	21	SENT_62	[p2l1488t1135r1802b1204],
21	leads	VBZ	O	lead	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1860t1135r2025b1190],
22	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l2083t1143r2146b1190],
23	differences	NNS	O	difference	prep_to	21	SENT_62	[p2l10t1224r369b1279],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l417t1225r476b1279],
25	systemic	JJ	O	systemic	amod	26	SENT_62	[p2l523t1225r810b1293],
26	exposure	NN	O	exposure	prep_in	23	SENT_62	[p2l854t1240r1152b1293],
27	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1197t1233r1260b1279],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_62	[p2l1305t1224r1408b1279],
29	parent	NN	O	parent	nn	30	SENT_62	[p2l1454t1233r1668b1293],
30	drug	NN	O	drug	prep_to	21	SENT_62	[p2l1712t1224r1862b1293],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1906t1224r2024b1279],
32	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	33	SENT_62	[p2l2071t1225r2145b1279],
33	metabolites	NNS	O	metabolite	prep_to	21	SENT_62	[p2l10t1313r414b1369],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l10t1313r414b1369],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_63	[p2l454t1313r643b1368],
2	differences	NNS	O	difference	nsubj	5	SENT_63	[p2l685t1313r1045b1368],
3	are	VBP	O	be	cop	5	SENT_63	[p2l1088t1329r1187b1368],
4	important	JJ	O	important	amod	5	SENT_63	[p2l1230t1314r1562b1382],
5	determinants	NNS	O	determinant	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1603t1313r2043b1368],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l2087t1313r2154b1368],
7	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	8	SENT_63	[p2l10t1403r160b1471],
8	efﬁcacy	NN	O	efﬁcacy	prep_of	5	SENT_63	[p2l188t1403r438b1471],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l465t1403r583b1458],
10	toxicity	NN	O	toxicity	prep_of	5	SENT_63	[p2l612t1404r877b1471],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l612t1404r877b1471],
12	and	CC	O	and	cc	5	SENT_63	[p2l906t1403r1024b1458],
13	hence	RB	O	hence	advmod	5	SENT_63	[p2l1055t1403r1244b1458],
14	therapeutic	JJ	O	therapeutic	amod	15	SENT_63	[p2l1274t1403r1653b1471],
15	outcome	NN	O	outcome	dep	5	SENT_63	[p2l1681t1411r1966b1458],
16	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1995t1403r2148b1458],
17	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	19	SENT_63	[p2l10t1492r133b1547],
18	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	19	SENT_63	[p2l161t1492r312b1560],
19	administration	NN	O	administration	prep_after	15	SENT_63	[p2l337t1492r842b1547],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l337t1492r842b1547],

1	Inter	NNP	O	Inter	nsubj	11	SENT_64	[p2l112t1580r621b1635],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	4	SENT_64	[p2l112t1580r621b1635],
3	individual	JJ	O	individual	amod	4	SENT_64	[p2l112t1580r621b1635],
4	differences	NNS	O	difference	nsubj	10	SENT_64	[p2l641t1580r993b1635],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l1014t1581r1073b1635],
6	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	8	SENT_64	[p2l1093t1580r1394b1635],
7	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	8	SENT_64	[p2l1415t1583r1664b1635],
8	expression	NN	O	expression	prep_in	4	SENT_64	[p2l1684t1581r2029b1649],
9	are	VBP	O	be	cop	10	SENT_64	[p2l2049t1596r2146b1635],
10	likely	JJ	O	likely	rcmod	1	SENT_64	[p2l10t1669r185b1738],
11	governed	VBN	O	govern	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l238t1669r537b1738],
12	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l592t1669r670b1738],
13	both	CC	O	both	preconj	14	SENT_64	[p2l723t1669r870b1724],
14	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	prep_by	11	SENT_64	[p2l923t1670r1157b1738],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l1211t1669r1327b1724],
16	environmental	JJ	O	environmental	amod	17	SENT_64	[p2l1383t1669r1857b1724],
17	factors	NNS	O	factor	prep_by	11	SENT_64	[p2l1914t1669r2145b1725],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l1914t1669r2145b1725],

1	However	RB	O	however	advmod	6	SENT_65	[p2l10t1761r314b1820],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l10t1761r314b1820],
3	numerous	JJ	O	numerous	amod	4	SENT_65	[p2l368t1773r692b1811],
4	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	6	SENT_65	[p2l746t1757r971b1811],
5	have	VBP	O	have	aux	6	SENT_65	[p2l1026t1757r1175b1811],
6	revealed	VBN	O	reveal	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l1229t1757r1500b1811],
7	that	IN	O	that	complm	14	SENT_65	[p2l1552t1757r1682b1811],
8	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	10	SENT_65	[p2l1733t1760r1983b1811],
9	cisnucleotide	NN	O	cisnucleotide	nn	10	SENT_65	[p2l2035t1758r2145b1811, p2l10t1845r349b1900],
10	variation	NN	O	variation	nsubj	14	SENT_65	[p2l371t1846r661b1900],
11	can	MD	O	can	aux	14	SENT_65	[p2l684t1854r903b1900],
12	not	RB	O	not	neg	14	SENT_65	[p2l684t1854r903b1900],
13	fully	RB	O	fully	advmod	14	SENT_65	[p2l927t1845r1071b1914],
14	explain	VB	O	explain	ccomp	6	SENT_65	[p2l1094t1845r1329b1914],
15	variable	JJ	O	variable	amod	17	SENT_65	[p2l1351t1845r1609b1900],
16	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	17	SENT_65	[p2l1634t1848r1883b1900],
17	expression	NN	O	expression	dobj	14	SENT_65	[p2l1908t1861r2146b1914, p2l11t1935r141b1988],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l172t1935r232b1987],
19	liver	NN	O	liver	prep_in	17	SENT_65	[p2l263t1934r419b1996],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l263t1934r419b1996],
21	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l451t1950r517b1988],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_65	[p2l545t1934r647b1988],
23	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	26	SENT_65	[p2l679t1934r799b1988],
24	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l832t1950r897b1988],
25	intravenous	JJ	O	intravenous	conj_or	23	SENT_65	[p2l927t1935r1308b1988],
26	clearance	NN	O	clearance	dobj	14	SENT_65	[p2l1340t1934r1643b1988],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l1675t1934r1741b1988],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_65	[p2l1763t1934r1865b1988],
29	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	31	SENT_65	[p2l1897t1936r2146b1988],
30	substrate	NN	O	substrate	nn	31	SENT_65	[p2l11t2022r307b2077],
31	midazolam	NN	O	midazolam	prep_of	26	SENT_65	[p2l363t2022r722b2077],
32	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	33	SENT_65	[p2l780t2022r880b2090],
33	8	CD	NUMBER	8	num	34	SENT_65	[p2l780t2022r880b2090],
34	]	NN	O	]	dep	26	SENT_65	[p2l780t2022r880b2090],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l780t2022r880b2090],

1	Genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	2	SENT_66	[p2l937t2023r1181b2077],
2	variation	NN	O	variation	nsubj	19	SENT_66	[p2l1233t2023r1522b2077],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l1578t2023r1636b2076],
4	liver	NN	O	liver	nn	5	SENT_66	[p2l1692t2022r2146b2077],
5	—	NN	O	—	prep_in	2	SENT_66	[p2l1692t2022r2146b2077],
6	enriched	JJ	O	enriched	amod	8	SENT_66	[p2l1692t2022r2146b2077],
7	transcription	NN	O	transcription	nn	8	SENT_66	[p2l9t2111r428b2179],
8	factors	NNS	O	factor	nsubj	9	SENT_66	[p2l473t2110r688b2165],
9	(	VBP	O	(	rcmod	5	SENT_66	[p2l735t2110r874b2179],
10	e.g.	FW	O	e.g.	nsubj	16	SENT_66	[p2l735t2110r874b2179],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l735t2110r874b2179],
12	PXR	NN	O	pxr	conj_and	10	SENT_66	[p2l921t2114r1049b2165],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l1091t2110r1208b2165],
14	FoxA2	NN	O	foxa2	conj_and	10	SENT_66	[p2l1254t2110r1477b2179],
15	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	14	SENT_66	[p2l1254t2110r1477b2179],
16	regulating	VBG	O	regulate	dep	9	SENT_66	[p2l1523t2110r1852b2179],
17	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	18	SENT_66	[p2l1897t2113r2146b2165],
18	expression	NN	O	expression	dobj	16	SENT_66	[p2l10t2200r356b2268],
19	appears	VBZ	O	appear	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l388t2215r636b2268],
20	to	TO	O	to	aux	21	SENT_66	[p2l670t2207r732b2254],
21	explain	VB	O	explain	xcomp	19	SENT_66	[p2l765t2199r1000b2268],
22	some	DT	O	some	dobj	21	SENT_66	[p2l1033t2215r1201b2254],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l1234t2199r1300b2254],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_66	[p2l1324t2199r1426b2254],
25	variability	NN	O	variability	prep_of	22	SENT_66	[p2l1457t2199r1788b2268],
26	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l1820t2200r1879b2253],
27	hepatic	JJ	O	hepatic	amod	29	SENT_66	[p2l1912t2199r2147b2268],
28	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	29	SENT_66	[p2l10t2291r260b2343],
29	expression	NN	O	expression	prep_in	21	SENT_66	[p2l288t2289r634b2357],
30	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	31	SENT_66	[p2l666t2288r864b2357],
31	9,10	CD	NUMBER	9,10	num	32	SENT_66	[p2l666t2288r864b2357],
32	]	NN	O	]	dep	21	SENT_66	[p2l666t2288r864b2357],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l666t2288r864b2357],

1	This	DT	O	this	nsubj	2	SENT_67	[p2l891t2288r1023b2343],
2	suggests	VBZ	O	suggest	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l1054t2297r1324b2357],
3	that	IN	O	that	complm	14	SENT_67	[p2l1354t2288r1483b2343],
4	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	5	SENT_67	[p2l1510t2289r1743b2357],
5	variation	NN	O	variation	nsubj	14	SENT_67	[p2l1769t2289r2059b2343],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l2087t2289r2146b2343],
7	transcription	NN	O	transcription	nn	8	SENT_67	[p2l9t2378r428b2446],
8	factors	NNS	O	factor	prep_in	5	SENT_67	[p2l485t2377r699b2432],
9	governing	VBG	O	govern	partmod	8	SENT_67	[p2l755t2378r1080b2446],
10	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	12	SENT_67	[p2l1136t2377r1437b2432],
11	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	12	SENT_67	[p2l1495t2380r1745b2432],
12	expression	NN	O	expression	dobj	9	SENT_67	[p2l1801t2378r2146b2446],
13	might	MD	O	might	aux	14	SENT_67	[p2l10t2467r201b2535],
14	contribute	VB	O	contribute	ccomp	2	SENT_67	[p2l239t2467r574b2522],
15	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l613t2475r674b2522],
16	inter-individual	JJ	O	inter-individual	amod	17	SENT_67	[p2l715t2467r1223b2522],
17	differences	NNS	O	difference	prep_to	14	SENT_67	[p2l1263t2467r1614b2522],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l1656t2468r1715b2521],
19	gut	NN	O	gut	nn	21	SENT_67	[p2l1753t2475r1858b2535],
20	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	21	SENT_67	[p2l1897t2469r2146b2522],
21	expression	NN	O	expression	prep_in	17	SENT_67	[p2l10t2557r371b2624],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l10t2557r371b2624],

1	There	EX	O	there	expl	2	SENT_68	[p2l109t2644r295b2699],
2	are	VBP	O	be	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l326t2660r425b2699],
3	multiple	JJ	O	multiple	amod	4	SENT_68	[p2l457t2644r735b2713],
4	lines	NNS	O	line	nsubj	2	SENT_68	[p2l767t2644r917b2699],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l950t2644r1016b2699],
6	evidence	NN	O	evidence	prep_of	4	SENT_68	[p2l1041t2644r1329b2699],
7	supporting	VBG	O	support	partmod	6	SENT_68	[p2l1362t2645r1721b2713],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_68	[p2l1750t2644r1853b2699],
9	hypothesis	NN	O	hypothesis	dobj	7	SENT_68	[p2l1885t2644r2146b2713, p2l10t2734r128b2788],
10	that	IN	O	that	complm	16	SENT_68	[p2l153t2733r285b2788],
11	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	13	SENT_68	[p2l309t2735r563b2788],
12	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	13	SENT_68	[p2l589t2733r898b2788],
13	expression	NN	O	expression	nsubjpass	16	SENT_68	[p2l924t2734r1277b2802],
14	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_68	[p2l1302t2734r1349b2788],
15	highly	RB	O	highly	advmod	16	SENT_68	[p2l1376t2733r1582b2802],
16	regulated	VBN	O	regulate	ccomp	7	SENT_68	[p2l1606t2733r1917b2802],
17	by	IN	O	by	prep	16	SENT_68	[p2l1941t2733r2020b2802],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_68	[p2l2043t2733r2146b2788],
19	biologically	RB	O	biologically	advmod	20	SENT_68	[p2l9t2822r391b2891],
20	active	JJ	O	active	amod	21	SENT_68	[p2l416t2823r609b2877],
21	form	NN	O	form	dep	30	SENT_68	[p2l637t2822r792b2877],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l819t2822r886b2877],
23	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	24	SENT_68	[p2l903t2823r1158b2877],
24	D3	NN	O	d3	prep_of	21	SENT_68	[p2l1185t2825r1269b2877],
25	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	26	SENT_68	[p2l1300t2822r2147b2891],
26	1a	NN	O	1a	dep	30	SENT_68	[p2l1300t2822r2147b2891],
27	,25	CD	NUMBER	,25	num	30	SENT_68	[p2l1300t2822r2147b2891],
28	—	NN	O	—	nn	30	SENT_68	[p2l1300t2822r2147b2891],
29	dihydroxyvitamin	NN	O	dihydroxyvitamin	nn	30	SENT_68	[p2l1300t2822r2147b2891],
30	D3	NN	O	d3	dep	34	SENT_68	[p2l10t2915r94b2967],
31	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	32	SENT_68	[p2l144t2912r377b2980],
32	VD3	NN	O	vd3	dep	30	SENT_68	[p2l144t2912r377b2980],
33	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	34	SENT_68	[p2l144t2912r377b2980],
34	)	NN	O	)	dep	17	SENT_68	[p2l144t2912r377b2980],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l144t2912r377b2980],

1	Treatment	NN	O	treatment	nsubj	7	SENT_69	[p2l422t2915r768b2967],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p2l813t2912r881b2967],
3	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	4	SENT_69	[p2l920t2912r1229b2967],
4	cells	NNS	O	cell	prep_of	1	SENT_69	[p2l1277t2912r1418b2967],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_69	[p2l1465t2912r1616b2967],
6	VD3	NN	O	vd3	prep_with	4	SENT_69	[p2l1659t2915r1794b2967],
7	increases	VBZ	O	increase	_	0	SENT_69	[p2l1845t2913r2145b2967],
8	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	9	SENT_69	[p2l10t3003r264b3056],
9	expression	NN	O	expression	nsubj	12	SENT_69	[p2l309t3002r662b3069],
10	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	11	SENT_69	[p2l709t3001r854b3069],
11	11	CD	NUMBER	11	num	12	SENT_69	[p2l709t3001r854b3069],
12	]	NN	O	]	xcomp	7	SENT_69	[p2l709t3001r854b3069],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p2l709t3001r854b3069],

1	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	2	SENT_70	[p2l900t3003r1153b3056],
2	transcription	NN	O	transcription	nsubjpass	4	SENT_70	[p2l1198t3002r1626b3069],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_70	[p2l1671t3002r1718b3056],
4	induced	VBN	O	induce	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l1764t3001r2025b3056],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l2069t3001r2148b3069],
6	VD3	NN	O	vd3	agent	4	SENT_70	[p2l7t3092r142b3144],
7	activating	VBG	O	activate	partmod	6	SENT_70	[p2l187t3090r513b3158],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_70	[p2l552t3089r655b3144],
9	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	12	SENT_70	[p2l695t3090r950b3144],
10	D	NN	O	d	nn	12	SENT_70	[p2l991t3093r1036b3144],
11	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nn	12	SENT_70	[p2l1077t3097r1354b3158],
12	(	NN	O	(	dobj	7	SENT_70	[p2l1392t3089r1584b3157],
13	VDR	NN	O	vdr	tmod	7	SENT_70	[p2l1392t3089r1584b3157],
14	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	13	SENT_70	[p2l1392t3089r1584b3157],
15	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	16	SENT_70	[p2l1624t3089r1825b3144],
16	binds	VBZ	O	bind	rcmod	13	SENT_70	[p2l1865t3089r2041b3144],
17	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l2083t3097r2146b3144],
18	proximal	JJ	O	proximal	amod	19	SENT_70	[p2l10t3178r305b3247],
19	elements	NNS	O	element	prep_to	16	SENT_70	[p2l335t3178r633b3233],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l664t3179r724b3233],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_70	[p2l753t3178r856b3233],
22	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	23	SENT_70	[p2l886t3181r1140b3233],
23	promoter	NN	O	promoter	prep_in	19	SENT_70	[p2l1169t3186r1479b3247],
24	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	25	SENT_70	[p2l1510t3178r1635b3247],
25	12	CD	NUMBER	12	num	26	SENT_70	[p2l1510t3178r1635b3247],
26	]	NN	O	]	dep	23	SENT_70	[p2l1510t3178r1635b3247],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l1669t3178r1786b3233],
28	distal	JJ	O	distal	amod	29	SENT_70	[p2l1817t3178r1994b3233],
29	ER6	NN	O	er6	conj_and	23	SENT_70	[p2l2026t3181r2145b3233],
30	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l10t3268r128b3323],
31	CLEM4	NN	O	clem4	nn	34	SENT_70	[p2l172t3270r396b3323],
32	ER6	NN	O	er6	nn	34	SENT_70	[p2l439t3270r560b3323],
33	response	NN	O	response	nn	34	SENT_70	[p2l604t3283r894b3336],
34	element	NN	O	element	conj_and	23	SENT_70	[p2l938t3268r1206b3323],
35	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	36	SENT_70	[p2l1251t3267r1477b3336],
36	13,14	CD	NUMBER	13,14	num	37	SENT_70	[p2l1251t3267r1477b3336],
37	]	NN	O	]	dep	34	SENT_70	[p2l1251t3267r1477b3336],
38	to	TO	O	to	aux	39	SENT_70	[p2l1524t3276r1586b3323],
39	induce	VB	O	induce	xcomp	16	SENT_70	[p2l1631t3268r1848b3323],
40	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	41	SENT_70	[p2l1892t3270r2146b3323],
41	transcription	NN	O	transcription	dobj	39	SENT_70	[p2l9t3357r454b3425],
42	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l9t3357r454b3425],

1	In	FW	O	in	nn	2	SENT_71	[p2l500t3360r559b3411],
2	vivo	FW	O	vivo	nsubj	11	SENT_71	[p2l605t3357r751b3420],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l605t3357r751b3420],
4	treatment	NN	O	treatment	appos	2	SENT_71	[p2l798t3365r1129b3411],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1174t3356r1241b3411],
6	rats	NNS	O	rat	prep_of	4	SENT_71	[p2l1281t3365r1400b3411],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1448t3356r1566b3411],
8	mice	NNS	O	mouse	prep_of	4	SENT_71	[p2l1614t3357r1768b3411],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1813t3356r1964b3411],
10	VD3	NN	O	vd3	prep_with	6	SENT_71	[p2l2007t3359r2142b3411],
11	increases	VBZ	O	increase	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l10t3447r310b3501],
12	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	15	SENT_71	[p2l348t3446r656b3501],
13	CYP3A	NN	O	cyp3a	nn	15	SENT_71	[p2l694t3448r908b3501],
14	protein	NN	O	protein	nn	15	SENT_71	[p2l942t3447r1180b3514],
15	expression	NN	O	expression	dobj	11	SENT_71	[p2l1215t3447r1569b3514],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1604t3446r1722b3501],
17	activity	NN	O	activity	dobj	11	SENT_71	[p2l1758t3447r2004b3514],
18	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	19	SENT_71	[p2l2042t3446r2144b3514],
19	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	20	SENT_71	[p2l2042t3446r2144b3514],
20	]	NN	O	]	dep	17	SENT_71	[p2l2042t3446r2144b3514],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l2042t3446r2144b3514],

1	Likewise	RB	O	likewise	advmod	9	SENT_72	[p2l10t3535r310b3598],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l10t3535r310b3598],
3	humans	NNS	O	human	nsubj	9	SENT_72	[p2l334t3535r593b3590],
4	treated	VBN	O	treat	partmod	3	SENT_72	[p2l617t3535r851b3590],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l873t3535r1023b3590],
6	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	8	SENT_72	[p2l1044t3536r1299b3590],
7	D	NN	O	d	nn	8	SENT_72	[p2l1322t3538r1366b3589],
8	supplementation	NN	O	supplementation	prep_with	4	SENT_72	[p2l1391t3535r1952b3603],
9	show	VBP	O	show	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l1975t3535r2148b3590],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_72	[p2l10t3639r42b3677],
11	decreased	VBN	O	decrease	amod	12	SENT_72	[p2l67t3623r393b3677],
12	AUC	NN	O	auc	dobj	9	SENT_72	[p2l415t3626r556b3677],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l580t3623r698b3677],
14	increased	VBD	O	increase	amod	15	SENT_72	[p2l723t3623r1034b3677],
15	clearance	NN	O	clearance	dobj	9	SENT_72	[p2l1060t3623r1369b3677],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l1394t3623r1460b3677],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_72	[p2l1477t3623r1581b3677],
18	CYP3A	NN	O	cyp3a	nn	20	SENT_72	[p2l1605t3626r1820b3677],
19	substrate	NN	O	substrate	nn	20	SENT_72	[p2l1843t3623r2146b3677],
20	atorvastatin	NN	O	atorvastatin	prep_of	15	SENT_72	[p3l10t25r407b79],
21	[	CD	NUMBER	[	number	22	SENT_72	[p3l432t24r577b93],
22	15	CD	NUMBER	15	num	23	SENT_72	[p3l432t24r577b93],
23	]	NN	O	]	dep	20	SENT_72	[p3l432t24r577b93],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l432t24r577b93],

1	Finally	RB	O	finally	advmod	6	SENT_73	[p3l601t24r836b93],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l601t24r836b93],
3	it	PRP	O	it	nsubjpass	6	SENT_73	[p3l860t25r905b79],
4	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_73	[p3l925t40r1051b79],
5	recently	RB	DATE	recently	advmod	6	SENT_73	[p3l1075t24r1343b93],
6	shown	VBN	O	show	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1365t24r1580b79],
7	that	IN	O	that	complm	14	SENT_73	[p3l1602t24r1733b79],
8	blood	NN	O	blood	nn	9	SENT_73	[p3l1755t24r1937b79],
9	levels	NNS	O	level	nsubj	14	SENT_73	[p3l1961t24r2145b79],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l10t113r77b169],
11	tacrolimus	NN	O	tacrolimus	prep_of	9	SENT_73	[p3l101t114r451b169],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l485t114r603b169],
13	sirolimus	NN	O	sirolimus	prep_of	9	SENT_73	[p3l636t114r940b169],
14	showed	VBD	O	show	ccomp	6	SENT_73	[p3l974t114r1226b169],
15	striking	JJ	O	striking	amod	17	SENT_73	[p3l1260t114r1510b182],
16	seasonal	JJ	O	seasonal	amod	17	SENT_73	[p3l1543t114r1819b169],
17	variation	NN	O	variation	nsubj	31	SENT_73	[p3l1851t114r2146b169],
18	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	19	SENT_73	[p3l9t202r141b257],
19	correlated	VBD	O	correlate	rcmod	17	SENT_73	[p3l173t202r505b257],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l537t202r687b257],
21	documented	VBN	O	document	amod	22	SENT_73	[p3l719t202r1130b257],
22	levels	NNS	O	level	prep_with	19	SENT_73	[p3l1162t202r1346b257],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1380t202r1446b257],
24	ultraviolet	JJ	O	ultraviolet	amod	25	SENT_73	[p3l1471t202r1815b257],
25	light	NN	O	light	prep_of	22	SENT_73	[p3l1848t202r1997b271],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l2028t202r2146b257],
27	serum	NN	O	serum	nn	30	SENT_73	[p3l11t308r214b347],
28	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	30	SENT_73	[p3l241t293r496b347],
29	D3	NN	O	d3	nn	30	SENT_73	[p3l526t295r610b347],
30	levels	NNS	O	level	conj_and	25	SENT_73	[p3l644t292r828b347],
31	[	VBP	O	[	ccomp	14	SENT_73	[p3l862t292r987b360],
32	16	CD	NUMBER	16	number	33	SENT_73	[p3l862t292r987b360],
33	]	CD	NUMBER	]	dobj	31	SENT_73	[p3l862t292r987b360],
34	further	JJ	O	further	quantmod	33	SENT_73	[p3l1021t292r1252b347],
35	supporting	VBG	O	support	xcomp	31	SENT_73	[p3l1281t293r1639b360],
36	the	DT	O	the	det	37	SENT_73	[p3l1667t292r1770b347],
37	role	NN	O	role	dobj	35	SENT_73	[p3l1801t292r1925b347],
38	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1954t292r2021b347],
39	the	DT	O	the	det	42	SENT_73	[p3l2043t292r2146b347],
40	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	42	SENT_73	[p3l8t382r263b436],
41	D	NN	O	d	nn	42	SENT_73	[p3l325t384r370b435],
42	receptor	NN	O	receptor	prep_of	37	SENT_73	[p3l435t389r711b449],
43	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l771t397r834b436],
44	an	DT	O	a	det	46	SENT_73	[p3l898t397r973b436],
45	important	JJ	O	important	amod	46	SENT_73	[p3l1037t382r1369b449],
46	regulator	NN	O	regulator	prep_as	35	SENT_73	[p3l1431t381r1735b449],
47	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1795t381r1862b436],
48	human	JJ	O	human	amod	51	SENT_73	[p3l1917t381r2147b436],
49	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	51	SENT_73	[p3l10t469r318b524],
50	CYP3A	NN	O	cyp3a	nn	51	SENT_73	[p3l353t472r568b524],
51	expression	NN	O	expression	prep_of	46	SENT_73	[p3l598t470r968b538],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l598t470r968b538],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l112t562r172b613],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_74	[p3l189t558r291b613],
3	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	4	SENT_74	[p3l310t566r551b627],
4	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	6	SENT_74	[p3l568t558r746b627],
5	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	6	SENT_74	[p3l760t574r855b613],
6	tested	VBD	O	test	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l872t558r1067b613],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_74	[p3l1085t558r1187b613],
8	hypothesis	NN	O	hypothesis	dobj	6	SENT_74	[p3l1205t558r1553b627],
9	that	IN	O	that	complm	30	SENT_74	[p3l1571t558r1701b613],
10	common	JJ	O	common	amod	12	SENT_74	[p3l1718t574r2000b613],
11	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	12	SENT_74	[p3l2019t562r2147b613],
12	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubjpass	30	SENT_74	[p3l10t648r531b716],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l10t648r531b716],
14	each	DT	O	each	appos	12	SENT_74	[p3l556t648r702b703],
15	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	16	SENT_74	[p3l727t648r1064b716],
16	associated	VBN	O	associate	partmod	14	SENT_74	[p3l1087t648r1419b703],
17	with	IN	O	with	dep	16	SENT_74	[p3l1442t648r1590b703],
18	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	19	SENT_74	[p3l1612t651r1754b702],
19	expression	NN	O	expression	pobj	17	SENT_74	[p3l1776t647r2145b716],
20	/	:	O	/	punct	21	SENT_74	[p3l1776t647r2145b716],
21	function	NN	O	function	dep	19	SENT_74	[p3l10t735r279b789],
22	in	FW	O	in	prep	21	SENT_74	[p3l309t737r363b789],
23	vitro	FW	O	vitro	pobj	22	SENT_74	[p3l393t737r535b789],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l566t735r682b789],
25	in	FW	O	in	nn	26	SENT_74	[p3l713t737r768b789],
26	vivo	FW	O	vivo	dep	16	SENT_74	[p3l798t736r940b798],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l798t736r940b798],
28	would	MD	O	would	aux	30	SENT_74	[p3l969t735r1172b789],
29	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	30	SENT_74	[p3l1201t735r1275b789],
30	associated	VBN	O	associate	ccomp	6	SENT_74	[p3l1305t735r1636b789],
31	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1666t735r1814b789],
32	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	34	SENT_74	[p3l1844t735r2146b789],
33	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	34	SENT_74	[p3l10t826r260b879],
34	expression	NN	O	expression	prep_with	30	SENT_74	[p3l278t825r624b892],
35	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l642t824r758b879],
36	activity	NN	O	activity	conj_and	34	SENT_74	[p3l777t825r1031b892],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l777t825r1031b892],
38	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1051t824r1167b879],
39	further	RB	O	further	advmod	30	SENT_74	[p3l1186t824r1413b879],
40	that	IN	O	that	complm	50	SENT_74	[p3l1428t824r1558b879],
41	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	43	SENT_74	[p3l1576t824r1877b879],
42	CYP3A4	NN	O	cyp3a4	nn	43	SENT_74	[p3l1897t826r2146b879],
43	expression	NN	O	expression	nsubj	50	SENT_74	[p3l10t914r356b981],
44	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l413t913r530b968],
45	midazolam	NN	O	midazolam	nn	46	SENT_74	[p3l589t913r948b968],
46	disposition	NN	O	disposition	conj_and	43	SENT_74	[p3l1006t913r1361b981],
47	in	FW	O	in	prep	43	SENT_74	[p3l1419t914r1474b968],
48	vivo	FW	O	vivo	pobj	47	SENT_74	[p3l1532t914r1658b968],
49	would	MD	O	would	aux	50	SENT_74	[p3l1715t913r1918b968],
50	show	VB	O	show	conj_and	30	SENT_74	[p3l1978t913r2148b968],
51	seasonal	JJ	O	seasonal	amod	52	SENT_74	[p3l11t1001r281b1056],
52	variation	NN	O	variation	dobj	50	SENT_74	[p3l331t1002r621b1056],
53	correlating	VBG	O	correlate	partmod	52	SENT_74	[p3l671t1001r1022b1070],
54	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1069t1001r1218b1056],
55	the	DT	O	the	det	58	SENT_74	[p3l1268t1001r1369b1056],
56	documented	VBN	O	document	amod	58	SENT_74	[p3l1420t1001r1823b1056],
57	seasonal	JJ	O	seasonal	amod	58	SENT_74	[p3l1874t1001r2145b1056],
58	availability	NN	O	availability	prep_with	53	SENT_74	[p3l10t1090r368b1159],
59	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l396t1090r462b1145],
60	ultraviolet	JJ	O	ultraviolet	amod	61	SENT_74	[p3l482t1090r819b1145],
61	light	NN	O	light	prep_of	58	SENT_74	[p3l846t1090r992b1159],
62	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1019t1090r1135b1145],
63	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	65	SENT_74	[p3l1162t1091r1412b1145],
64	D	NN	O	d	nn	65	SENT_74	[p3l1440t1093r1485b1144],
65	levels	NNS	O	level	prep_of	58	SENT_74	[p3l1514t1090r1711b1145],
66	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1514t1090r1711b1145],

1	2	LS	NUMBER	2	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l9t1271r65b1323],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l9t1271r65b1323],

1	Materials	NNPS	O	Materials	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l104t1268r420b1323],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l446t1268r573b1322],
3	methods	NNS	O	method	conj_and	1	SENT_76	[p3l600t1268r897b1323],

1	2.1	CD	NUMBER	2.1	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l6t1449r112b1501],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l6t1449r112b1501],

1	Study	NNP	O	Study	nn	2	SENT_78	[p3l153t1446r328b1514],
2	populations	NNS	O	population	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l350t1446r715b1514],

1	Institutional	JJ	O	institutional	amod	3	SENT_79	[p3l112t1624r508b1679],
2	Review	NN	O	review	nn	3	SENT_79	[p3l544t1625r778b1679],
3	Boards	NNS	O	board	nsubj	25	SENT_79	[p3l812t1624r1027b1679],
4	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l1063t1632r1123b1679],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_79	[p3l1157t1624r1259b1679],
6	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_at	3	SENT_79	[p3l1293t1625r1628b1693],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l1662t1624r1728b1679],
8	Washington	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Washington	prep_of	6	SENT_79	[p3l1753t1624r2147b1693],
9	approved	VBD	O	approve	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l10t1713r310b1782],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_79	[p3l336t1713r437b1768],
11	use	NN	O	use	dobj	9	SENT_79	[p3l462t1729r569b1768],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l594t1713r660b1768],
13	tissue	NN	O	tissue	nn	14	SENT_79	[p3l677t1714r863b1768],
14	samples	NNS	O	sample	prep_of	11	SENT_79	[p3l889t1713r1148b1782],
15	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l1175t1713r1327b1768],
16	organ	NN	O	organ	nn	17	SENT_79	[p3l1352t1729r1534b1782],
17	donors	NNS	O	donor	prep_from	9	SENT_79	[p3l1559t1713r1794b1777],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l1559t1713r1794b1777],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l1819t1713r1935b1768],
20	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l1961t1722r2021b1768],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_79	[p3l2044t1713r2146b1768],
22	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_at	25	SENT_79	[p3l9t1803r344b1871],
23	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l378t1802r444b1857],
24	Indiana	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Indiana	prep_of	22	SENT_79	[p3l473t1802r712b1857],
25	approved	VBD	O	approve	conj_and	9	SENT_79	[p3l749t1802r1049b1871],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_79	[p3l1085t1802r1187b1857],
27	midazolam	NN	O	midazolam	nn	29	SENT_79	[p3l1224t1802r1583b1857],
28	study	NN	O	study	nn	29	SENT_79	[p3l1620t1802r1797b1871],
29	protocols	NNS	O	protocol	dobj	25	SENT_79	[p3l1832t1802r2145b1871],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l1832t1802r2145b1871],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l10t1892r126b1947],
32	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l152t1900r212b1947],
33	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	nn	35	SENT_79	[p3l238t1895r312b1947],
34	Jude	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jude	nn	35	SENT_79	[p3l331t1892r478b1960],
35	Children	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Children	poss	38	SENT_79	[p3l504t1892r824b1947],
36	's	POS	ORGANIZATION	's	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l504t1892r824b1947],
37	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	38	SENT_79	[p3l851t1892r1137b1947],
38	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	prep_at	39	SENT_79	[p3l1163t1892r1430b1960],
39	approved	VBD	O	approve	conj_and	9	SENT_79	[p3l1456t1892r1757b1960],
40	genotyping	NN	O	genotyping	dobj	39	SENT_79	[p3l1783t1893r2148b1960],
41	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l10t1980r76b2035],
42	DNA	NN	O	dna	prep_of	40	SENT_79	[p3l100t1983r247b2035],
43	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l275t1980r427b2035],
44	anonymous	JJ	O	anonymous	amod	45	SENT_79	[p3l458t1996r832b2049],
45	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_from	39	SENT_79	[p3l865t1980r1140b2049],
46	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l865t1980r1140b2049],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_80	[p3l1170t1980r1287b2035],
2	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	nn	6	SENT_80	[p3l1318t1980r1530b2035],
3	Sciences	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	nn	6	SENT_80	[p3l1561t1981r1829b2035],
4	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	6	SENT_80	[p3l1861t1980r2147b2035],
5	Ethics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ethics	nn	6	SENT_80	[p3l10t2071r199b2126],
6	Board	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Board	nsubj	13	SENT_80	[p3l233t2071r418b2126],
7	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_80	[p3l451t2079r511b2126],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_80	[p3l541t2071r643b2126],
9	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_at	6	SENT_80	[p3l675t2072r1009b2139],
10	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_80	[p3l1041t2071r1107b2126],
11	Western	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Western	nn	12	SENT_80	[p3l1129t2074r1404b2126],
12	Ontario	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ontario	prep_of	9	SENT_80	[p3l1437t2072r1678b2126],
13	approved	VBD	O	approve	_	0	SENT_80	[p3l1710t2071r2011b2139],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_80	[p3l2044t2071r2146b2126],
15	study	NN	O	study	nn	16	SENT_80	[p3l11t2160r188b2229],
16	protocol	NN	O	protocol	dobj	13	SENT_80	[p3l215t2160r497b2229],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_80	[p3l215t2160r497b2229],

1	2.2	CD	NUMBER	2.2	_	0	SENT_81	[p3l6t2341r112b2394],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_81	[p3l6t2341r112b2394],

1	Human	JJ	O	human	amod	2	SENT_82	[p3l153t2342r380b2394],
2	jejunal	NN	O	jejunal	_	0	SENT_82	[p3l397t2338r618b2407],
3	mucosa	NN	O	mucosa	nn	4	SENT_82	[p3l645t2354r877b2394],
4	cohort	NN	O	cohort	dep	2	SENT_82	[p3l905t2339r1103b2394],

1	Human	JJ	O	human	amod	6	SENT_83	[p3l112t2520r348b2572],
2	jejunal	NN	O	jejunal	nn	6	SENT_83	[p3l364t2517r588b2585],
3	mucosa	NN	O	mucosa	nn	6	SENT_83	[p3l615t2533r860b2572],
4	cohort	NN	O	cohort	nn	6	SENT_83	[p3l883t2517r1091b2572],
5	(	NN	O	(	nn	6	SENT_83	[p3l1114t2517r1176b2585],
6	n	NN	O	n	nsubjpass	14	SENT_83	[p3l1114t2517r1176b2585],
7	=	JJ	O	=	amod	6	SENT_83	[p3l1198t2540r1231b2556],
8	30	CD	NUMBER	30	number	9	SENT_83	[p3l1253t2517r1357b2585],
9	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	7	SENT_83	[p3l1253t2517r1357b2585],
10	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1381t2517r1534b2572],
11	White	NNP	O	White	nn	12	SENT_83	[p3l1555t2517r1754b2572],
12	donors	NNS	O	donor	prep_from	9	SENT_83	[p3l1778t2517r1997b2572],
13	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	14	SENT_83	[p3l2020t2533r2145b2572],
14	obtained	VBN	O	obtain	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l10t2606r291b2661],
15	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l321t2606r473b2661],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_83	[p3l502t2606r603b2661],
17	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_from	14	SENT_83	[p3l632t2607r966b2674],
18	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l994t2606r1060b2661],
19	Washington	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Washington	nn	20	SENT_83	[p3l1079t2606r1473b2674],
20	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	prep_of	17	SENT_83	[p3l1502t2606r1710b2661],
21	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1740t2606r1806b2661],
22	Pharmacy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmacy	nn	27	SENT_83	[p3l1828t2606r2147b2674],
23	Human	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Human	nn	27	SENT_83	[p3l10t2698r246b2749],
24	Tissue	NN	ORGANIZATION	tissue	nn	27	SENT_83	[p3l283t2695r485b2749],
25	Bank	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bank	nn	27	SENT_83	[p3l527t2694r684b2749],
26	(	NNP	O	(	nn	27	SENT_83	[p3l723t2694r982b2762],
27	Seattle	NNP	LOCATION	Seattle	prep_of	20	SENT_83	[p3l723t2694r982b2762],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l723t2694r982b2762],
29	WA	NNP	LOCATION	WA	nn	30	SENT_83	[p3l1021t2694r1180b2763],
30	)	NNP	O	)	appos	27	SENT_83	[p3l1021t2694r1180b2763],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l1021t2694r1180b2763],

1	Both	DT	O	both	det	5	SENT_84	[p3l1223t2694r1369b2749],
2	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	5	SENT_84	[p3l1410t2694r1712b2749],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1753t2694r1869b2749],
4	hepatic	JJ	O	hepatic	conj_and	2	SENT_84	[p3l1911t2694r2146b2763],
5	tissues	NNS	O	tissue	nsubjpass	10	SENT_84	[p3l9t2784r226b2838],
6	(	RB	O	(	amod	5	SENT_84	[p3l259t2783r505b2851],
7	below	IN	O	below	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l259t2783r505b2851],
8	)	NN	O	)	prep_below	6	SENT_84	[p3l259t2783r505b2851],
9	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_84	[p3l536t2799r695b2838],
10	obtained	VBN	O	obtain	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l727t2783r1009b2838],
11	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1041t2783r1298b2852],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_84	[p3l1329t2783r1431b2838],
13	solid	JJ	O	solid	amod	16	SENT_84	[p3l1464t2783r1614b2838],
14	organ	NN	O	organ	nn	16	SENT_84	[p3l1646t2799r1828b2852],
15	donation	NN	O	donation	nn	16	SENT_84	[p3l1859t2783r2146b2838],
16	program	NN	O	program	prep_through	10	SENT_84	[p3l10t2888r285b2941],
17	operated	VBN	O	operate	partmod	16	SENT_84	[p3l317t2872r600b2941],
18	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l632t2872r710b2941],
19	Life	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Life	nn	21	SENT_84	[p3l741t2872r853b2927],
20	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	nn	21	SENT_84	[p3l885t2875r1096b2927],
21	Northwest	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Northwest	agent	17	SENT_84	[p3l1127t2872r1482b2936],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1127t2872r1482b2936],
23	following	VBG	O	follow	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1515t2872r1820b2941],
24	informed	VBN	O	inform	amod	25	SENT_84	[p3l1851t2872r2146b2927],
25	consent	NN	O	consent	prep_following	21	SENT_84	[p3l10t2970r260b3016],
26	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l314t2961r392b3030],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_84	[p3l446t2961r547b3016],
28	family	NN	O	family	prep_by	25	SENT_84	[p3l604t2961r808b3030],
29	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l863t2961r952b3016],
30	use	NN	O	use	prep_for	28	SENT_84	[p3l1006t2977r1112b3016],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1168t2961r1235b3016],
32	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_84	[p3l1283t2961r1385b3016],
33	tissues	NNS	O	tissue	prep_of	30	SENT_84	[p3l1440t2962r1657b3016],
34	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1715t2961r1804b3016],
35	research	NN	O	research	prep_for	33	SENT_84	[p3l1858t2961r2144b3017],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l1858t2961r2144b3017],
