1	pharméceuiics	NNS	O	pharméceuiics	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l102t139r559b286],

1	P-Glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l364t372r745b424],
2	Efflux	NN	O	efflux	nn	3	SENT_2	[p1l770t373r916b413],
3	Inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	dep	1	SENT_2	[p1l938t373r1176b413],
4	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1200t373r1259b424],
5	Amphiphilic	NNP	PERSON	Amphiphilic	nn	6	SENT_2	[p1l1279t373r1586b424],
6	Diblock	NNP	PERSON	Diblock	prep_by	3	SENT_2	[p1l1610t373r1802b413],

1	Copolymers	NNS	O	copolymer	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l478t438r802b490],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l478t438r802b490],
3	Relationship	NN	O	relationship	dep	1	SENT_3	[p1l829t439r1149b490],
4	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1171t439r1382b479],
5	Copolymer	NNP	O	Copolymer	nn	6	SENT_3	[p1l1405t438r1685b490],
6	Concentration	NN	O	concentration	prep_between	3	SENT_3	[p1l501t504r863b546],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l885t505r977b545],
8	Substrate	NN	O	substrate	nn	10	SENT_3	[p1l1000t504r1247b546],
9	Hydrophobicity	NN	O	hydrophobicity	nn	10	SENT_3	[p1l1270t504r1662b556],
10	articles	NNS	O	article	prep_between	3	SENT_3	[p1l1841t215r2128b277],

1	Jason	NNP	PERSON	Jason	nn	3	SENT_4	[p1l408t636r510b669],
2	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	3	SENT_4	[p1l524t635r563b665],
3	Zastre	NNP	PERSON	Zastre	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l579t628r719b672],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l579t628r719b672],
5	l	NN	O	l	appos	3	SENT_4	[p1l579t628r719b672],
6	John	NNP	PERSON	John	nn	10	SENT_4	[p1l734t636r821b669],
7	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	nn	10	SENT_4	[p1l837t636r877b665],
8	Jacksonf	NNP	PERSON	Jacksonf	nn	10	SENT_4	[p1l892t628r1061b672],
9	Wesley	NNP	PERSON	Wesley	nn	10	SENT_4	[p1l1076t636r1203b673],
10	Wongf	NNP	PERSON	Wongf	dep	3	SENT_4	[p1l1218t628r1348b673],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1364t636r1430b665],
12	Helen	NNP	PERSON	Helen	nn	14	SENT_4	[p1l1445t636r1548b665],
13	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	14	SENT_4	[p1l1563t636r1611b665],
14	Burt	NNP	PERSON	Burt	dep	3	SENT_4	[p1l1627t628r1753b665],
15	*	CD	NUMBER	*	number	16	SENT_4	[p1l1627t628r1753b665],
16	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	17	SENT_4	[p1l1627t628r1753b665],
17	*	NN	O	*	dep	14	SENT_4	[p1l1627t628r1753b665],

1	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l357t720r541b755],
2	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l552t719r587b755],
3	Pharmaceutical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceutical	nn	6	SENT_5	[p1l593t719r836b747],
4	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l848t719r906b747],
5	Biomedical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Biomedical	nn	6	SENT_5	[p1l917t719r1090b747],
6	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	prep_of	1	SENT_5	[p1l1102t719r1237b751],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1102t719r1237b751],
8	College	NNP	O	College	appos	6	SENT_5	[p1l1255t719r1370b755],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1384t719r1419b755],
10	Pharmacy	NNP	O	Pharmacy	prep_of	8	SENT_5	[p1l1425t719r1587b755],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1425t719r1587b755],
12	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	1	SENT_5	[p1l1607t720r1762b755],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	prep	12	SENT_5	[p1l1775t719r1810b755],

1	Georgia	NNP	LOCATION	Georgia	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l446t767r576b802],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l446t767r576b802],
3	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	7	SENT_6	[p1l592t767r621b794],
4	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	7	SENT_6	[p1l627t767r656b795],
5	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	Wilson	nn	7	SENT_6	[p1l675t766r777b795],
6	Pharmacy	NNP	O	Pharmacy	nn	7	SENT_6	[p1l790t766r946b802],
7	Building	NNP	O	Building	conj_and	1	SENT_6	[p1l958t766r1094b802],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l958t766r1094b802],
9	Athens	NNP	LOCATION	Athens	conj_and	1	SENT_6	[p1l1108t766r1219b799],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1108t766r1219b799],
11	Georgia	NNP	LOCATION	Georgia	conj_and	1	SENT_6	[p1l1236t767r1361b802],
12	30602	CD	NUMBER	30602	num	11	SENT_6	[p1l1374t766r1474b799],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1374t766r1474b799],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1490t766r1549b795],
15	Faculty	NNP	O	Faculty	conj_and	1	SENT_6	[p1l1560t766r1675b802],
16	of	IN	O	of	prep	1	SENT_6	[p1l1688t766r1723b802],

1	Pharmaceutical	NNP	O	Pharmaceutical	nn	2	SENT_7	[p1l504t814r747b842],
2	Sciences	NNPS	O	Sciences	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l759t815r894b847],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l759t815r894b847],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	2	SENT_7	[p1l913t815r1069b850],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1082t814r1117b850],
6	British	NNP	ORGANIZATION	British	nn	7	SENT_7	[p1l1122t814r1225b842],
7	Columbia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Columbia	prep_of	2	SENT_7	[p1l1240t814r1392b847],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1240t814r1392b847],
9	2146	CD	DATE	2146	num	11	SENT_7	[p1l1409t814r1486b842],
10	East	NNP	O	East	nn	11	SENT_7	[p1l1497t815r1566b842],
11	Mall	NN	O	mall	appos	7	SENT_7	[p1l1576t814r1654b847],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1576t814r1654b847],

1	Vancouver	NNP	LOCATION	Vancouver	nn	3	SENT_8	[p1l820t863r989b895],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l820t863r989b895],
3	BC	NNP	O	BC	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1005t863r1060b895],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1005t863r1060b895],
5	V6T	NNP	O	V6T	nn	7	SENT_8	[p1l1079t862r1143b891],
6	1Z3	NNP	O	1Z3	nn	7	SENT_8	[p1l1154t862r1211b890],
7	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	appos	3	SENT_8	[p1l1226t862r1344b891],

1	Received	VBN	O	receive	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l278t938r421b964],
2	October	NNP	DATE	October	tmod	1	SENT_9	[p1l436t937r561b964],
3	5	CD	DATE	5	num	2	SENT_9	[p1l573t939r599b969],
4	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l573t939r599b969],
5	2007	CD	DATE	2007	num	2	SENT_9	[p1l614t938r699b969],
6	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l614t938r699b969],
7	Revised	VBN	O	revise	parataxis	1	SENT_9	[p1l717t938r840b964],
8	Manuscript	NNP	O	Manuscript	nn	9	SENT_9	[p1l856t938r1026b971],
9	Received	NNP	O	Received	dobj	7	SENT_9	[p1l1042t938r1185b964],
10	January	NNP	DATE	January	tmod	9	SENT_9	[p1l1198t938r1324b971],
11	21	CD	DATE	21	num	10	SENT_9	[p1l1337t938r1382b969],
12	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1337t938r1382b969],
13	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	10	SENT_9	[p1l1398t938r1483b969],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1398t938r1483b969],
15	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	dep	9	SENT_9	[p1l1498t938r1643b971],
16	March	NNP	DATE	March	tmod	7	SENT_9	[p1l1659t938r1753b964],
17	5	CD	DATE	5	num	16	SENT_9	[p1l1768t939r1794b969],
18	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1768t939r1794b969],
19	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	16	SENT_9	[p1l1809t938r1886b964],

1	Abstract	JJ	O	abstract	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l257t1078r434b1109],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l257t1078r434b1109],
3	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_10	[p1l450t1079r514b1109],
4	utilization	NN	O	utilization	nsubj	16	SENT_10	[p1l526t1079r678b1109],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l689t1079r720b1109],
6	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_of	4	SENT_10	[p1l730t1079r912b1109],
7	to	TO	O	to	aux	8	SENT_10	[p1l922t1081r953b1109],
8	increase	VB	O	increase	infmod	6	SENT_10	[p1l965t1079r1104b1109],
9	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	10	SENT_10	[p1l1116t1079r1260b1109],
10	absorption	NN	O	absorption	dobj	8	SENT_10	[p1l1272t1079r1445b1117],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1457t1079r1487b1109],
12	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_of	10	SENT_10	[p1l1497t1079r1590b1117],
13	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	16	SENT_10	[p1l1602t1079r1626b1109],
14	a	DT	O	a	det	16	SENT_10	[p1l1637t1087r1657b1109],
15	viable	JJ	O	viable	amod	16	SENT_10	[p1l1666t1079r1763b1109],
16	strategy	NN	O	strategy	dep	1	SENT_10	[p1l1774t1081r1907b1117],
17	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	18	SENT_10	[p1l256t1131r319b1161],
18	benefits	VBZ	O	benefit	rcmod	16	SENT_10	[p1l334t1131r465b1161],
19	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l478t1131r553b1161],
20	increases	NNS	O	increase	prep_from	18	SENT_10	[p1l569t1131r729b1161],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l745t1131r770b1160],
22	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	23	SENT_10	[p1l786t1131r860b1169],
23	solubilization	NN	O	solubilization	prep_in	20	SENT_10	[p1l875t1131r1088b1161],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1104t1131r1165b1161],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_10	[p1l1180t1131r1231b1161],
26	potential	NN	O	potential	nsubj	34	SENT_10	[p1l1247t1131r1386b1169],
27	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1401t1131r1446b1161],
28	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	prep_for	26	SENT_10	[p1l1460t1131r1604b1161],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1620t1131r1651b1161],
30	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	nn	33	SENT_10	[p1l1667t1131r1904b1169],
31	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	33	SENT_10	[p1l258t1183r359b1221],
32	P-gp	NN	O	p-gp	nn	33	SENT_10	[p1l258t1183r359b1221],
33	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	28	SENT_10	[p1l258t1183r359b1221],
34	mediated	VBD	O	mediate	dep	1	SENT_10	[p1l382t1183r535b1213],
35	efflux	NN	O	efflux	dobj	34	SENT_10	[p1l556t1183r653b1213],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l556t1183r653b1213],

1	However	RB	O	however	advmod	14	SENT_11	[p1l677t1183r832b1218],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l677t1183r832b1218],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_11	[p1l854t1183r905b1213],
4	effective	JJ	O	effective	amod	6	SENT_11	[p1l926t1183r1064b1213],
5	concentration	NN	O	concentration	nn	6	SENT_11	[p1l1084t1183r1309b1213],
6	range	NN	O	range	nsubjpass	14	SENT_11	[p1l1332t1190r1426b1221],
7	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1445t1183r1490b1213],
8	P-gp	JJ	O	p-gp	amod	9	SENT_11	[p1l1510t1183r1587b1221],
9	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	prep_for	6	SENT_11	[p1l1609t1183r1753b1213],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1774t1183r1805b1213],
11	most	JJS	O	most	amod	12	SENT_11	[p1l1825t1185r1906b1213],
12	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_of	9	SENT_11	[p1l257t1235r440b1265],
13	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	14	SENT_11	[p1l457t1235r481b1265],
14	defined	VBN	O	define	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l496t1235r619b1265],
15	over	IN	O	over	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l635t1242r709b1265],
16	a	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_11	[p1l722t1243r742b1265],
17	narrow	JJ	O	narrow	amod	19	SENT_11	[p1l758t1242r873b1265],
18	concentration	NN	O	concentration	nn	19	SENT_11	[p1l887t1235r1112b1265],
19	range	NN	O	range	prep_over	14	SENT_11	[p1l1130t1242r1232b1273],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1130t1242r1232b1273],
21	below	IN	O	below	advmod	19	SENT_11	[p1l1250t1235r1348b1265],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_11	[p1l1362t1235r1413b1265],
23	critical	JJ	O	critical	amod	25	SENT_11	[p1l1428t1235r1532b1265],
24	micelle	NN	O	micelle	nn	25	SENT_11	[p1l1549t1235r1664b1265],
25	concentration	NN	O	concentration	pobj	21	SENT_11	[p1l1679t1235r1904b1265],
26	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	27	SENT_11	[p1l258t1286r376b1324],
27	CMC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CMC	dep	19	SENT_11	[p1l258t1286r376b1324],
28	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	27	SENT_11	[p1l258t1286r376b1324],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l258t1286r376b1324],
30	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l394t1294r432b1317],
31	a	DT	O	a	det	32	SENT_11	[p1l447t1294r467b1317],
32	result	NN	O	result	prep_as	14	SENT_11	[p1l484t1287r573b1317],
33	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l588t1286r619b1317],
34	significant	JJ	O	significant	amod	36	SENT_11	[p1l633t1286r800b1325],
35	micelle	NN	O	micelle	nn	36	SENT_11	[p1l816t1287r931b1317],
36	sequestration	NN	O	sequestration	prep_of	32	SENT_11	[p1l946t1287r1171b1324],
37	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1187t1286r1218b1317],
38	drug	NN	O	drug	prep_of	36	SENT_11	[p1l1232t1287r1315b1325],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1232t1287r1315b1325],

1	Therefore	RB	O	therefore	advmod	8	SENT_12	[p1l1331t1286r1503b1322],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1331t1286r1503b1322],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_12	[p1l1520t1287r1572b1317],
4	objectives	NNS	O	objective	nsubj	8	SENT_12	[p1l1587t1287r1754b1324],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1769t1286r1800b1317],
6	these	DT	O	these	det	7	SENT_12	[p1l1813t1287r1905b1317],
7	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	4	SENT_12	[p1l257t1338r375b1368],
8	were	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l389t1346r471b1368],
9	to	TO	O	to	aux	10	SENT_12	[p1l484t1340r515b1368],
10	assess	VB	O	assess	xcomp	8	SENT_12	[p1l530t1346r646b1368],
11	if	IN	O	if	mark	20	SENT_12	[p1l662t1338r678b1367],
12	association	NN	O	association	nsubj	20	SENT_12	[p1l692t1338r878b1368],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l894t1338r925b1368],
14	P-gp	NN	MISC	p-gp	nn	15	SENT_12	[p1l940t1338r1017b1376],
15	substrates	NNS	O	substrate	prep_of	12	SENT_12	[p1l1031t1338r1205b1368],
16	differing	VBG	O	differ	partmod	15	SENT_12	[p1l1219t1338r1350b1376],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1367t1338r1392b1367],
18	hydrophobicity	NN	O	hydrophobicity	prep_in	16	SENT_12	[p1l1409t1338r1651b1376],
19	will	MD	O	will	aux	20	SENT_12	[p1l1664t1338r1714b1367],
20	impact	VB	O	impact	advcl	10	SENT_12	[p1l1730t1338r1840b1376],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_12	[p1l1853t1338r1905b1368],
22	effective	JJ	O	effective	amod	24	SENT_12	[p1l257t1389r396b1419],
23	concentration	NN	O	concentration	nn	24	SENT_12	[p1l418t1389r642b1419],
24	range	NN	O	range	dobj	20	SENT_12	[p1l667t1396r761b1427],
25	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l782t1389r827b1419],
26	P-gp	JJ	O	p-gp	amod	27	SENT_12	[p1l849t1389r926b1427],
27	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	prep_for	24	SENT_12	[p1l949t1389r1094b1419],
28	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1118t1389r1156b1427],
29	amphiphilic	JJ	O	amphiphilic	amod	31	SENT_12	[p1l1178t1389r1366b1427],
30	diblock	NN	O	diblock	nn	31	SENT_12	[p1l1387t1389r1504b1419],
31	copolymers	NNS	O	copolymer	prep_by	20	SENT_12	[p1l1525t1389r1718b1427],
32	based	VBN	O	base	partmod	31	SENT_12	[p1l1741t1389r1842b1419],
33	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1864t1396r1904b1419],
34	methoxypolyethylene	NN	O	methoxypolyethylene	nn	35	SENT_12	[p1l258t1441r612b1478],
35	glycol-block-polycaprolatone	NN	O	glycol-block-polycaprolatone	prep_on	32	SENT_12	[p1l635t1441r1110b1478],
36	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	38	SENT_12	[p1l1134t1440r1420b1478],
37	MePEG-b-PCL	NN	O	mepeg-b-pcl	nn	38	SENT_12	[p1l1134t1440r1420b1478],
38	)	NN	O	)	dep	35	SENT_12	[p1l1134t1440r1420b1478],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1134t1440r1420b1478],

1	Comparisons	NNS	O	comparison	nsubjpass	11	SENT_13	[p1l1444t1440r1667b1478],
2	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1690t1441r1831b1470],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_13	[p1l1853t1441r1905b1470],
4	micelle	JJ	O	micelle	amod	5	SENT_13	[p1l258t1492r373b1521],
5	association	NN	O	association	prep_between	1	SENT_13	[p1l398t1492r585b1521],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l611t1492r672b1521],
7	Caco-2	NN	O	caco-2	nn	9	SENT_13	[p1l698t1491r819b1521],
8	cellular	JJ	O	cellular	amod	9	SENT_13	[p1l844t1492r963b1521],
9	accumulation	NN	O	accumulation	prep_between	1	SENT_13	[p1l987t1492r1208b1521],
10	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_13	[p1l1233t1499r1315b1521],
11	evaluated	VBN	O	evaluate	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1340t1492r1502b1521],
12	using	VBG	O	use	conj_and	12	SENT_13	[p1l1529t1492r1616b1529],
13	two	CD	NUMBER	two	dobj	12	SENT_13	[p1l1641t1494r1700b1521],
14	structurally	RB	O	structurally	advmod	15	SENT_13	[p1l1725t1492r1906b1529],
15	homologous	JJ	O	homologous	amod	17	SENT_13	[p1l258t1543r463b1581],
16	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	17	SENT_13	[p1l484t1543r561b1581],
17	substrates	NNS	O	substrate	npadvmod	12	SENT_13	[p1l580t1543r762b1578],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l580t1543r762b1578],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_13	[p1l782t1543r834b1573],
20	relatively	RB	O	relatively	advmod	21	SENT_13	[p1l855t1543r1000b1581],
21	hydrophobic	JJ	O	hydrophobic	amod	22	SENT_13	[p1l1020t1543r1225b1581],
22	R-6G	NN	O	r-6g	npadvmod	12	SENT_13	[p1l1245t1542r1331b1573],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1352t1543r1413b1573],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_13	[p1l1432t1543r1484b1573],
25	hydrophilic	JJ	O	hydrophilic	amod	26	SENT_13	[p1l1505t1543r1683b1581],
26	R-123	NN	O	r-123	npadvmod	12	SENT_13	[p1l1703t1543r1812b1578],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1703t1543r1812b1578],
28	over	IN	O	over	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1833t1550r1907b1573],
29	concentrations	NNS	O	concentration	prep_over	12	SENT_13	[p1l257t1595r500b1624],
30	above	IN	O	above	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l511t1595r613b1624],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l624t1595r685b1624],
32	below	IN	O	below	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l697t1595r794b1624],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	34	SENT_13	[p1l803t1595r855b1624],
34	CMC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CMC	prep_above	12	SENT_13	[p1l866t1594r951b1624],
35	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l961t1594r1005b1624],
36	MePEG-b-PCL	NNP	O	MePEG-b-PCL	nn	38	SENT_13	[p1l1016t1594r1268b1624],
37	diblock	NN	O	diblock	nn	38	SENT_13	[p1l1278t1595r1395b1624],
38	copolymers	NNS	O	copolymer	prep_for	34	SENT_13	[p1l1404t1595r1604b1632],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1404t1595r1604b1632],

1	An	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_14	[p1l1616t1595r1661b1624],
2	approximately	RB	O	approximately	advmod	3	SENT_14	[p1l1673t1595r1906b1632],
3	3.75-fold	JJ	O	3.75-fold	amod	4	SENT_14	[p1l257t1646r402b1676],
4	enhancement	NN	O	enhancement	nsubj	8	SENT_14	[p1l417t1646r648b1676],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l662t1646r692b1676],
6	R-123	NN	MISC	r-123	nn	7	SENT_14	[p1l709t1646r809b1676],
7	accumulation	NN	O	accumulation	prep_of	4	SENT_14	[p1l824t1646r1045b1676],
8	occurred	VBD	O	occur	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1061t1646r1206b1676],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1221t1646r1286b1676],
10	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	12	SENT_14	[p1l1302t1647r1321b1676],
11	mM	NN	O	mm	nn	12	SENT_14	[p1l1338t1646r1398b1676],
12	MePEG17-b-PCL5	NN	O	mepeg17-b-pcl5	prep_with	8	SENT_14	[p1l1416t1646r1720b1681],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1416t1646r1720b1681],
14	compared	VBN	O	compare	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1737t1646r1904b1684],
15	to	TO	O	to	prepc_compared_to	8	SENT_14	[p1l256t1699r287b1727],
16	approximately	RB	O	approximately	advmod	17	SENT_14	[p1l299t1698r534b1735],
17	1.25-fold	RB	O	1.25-fold	amod	19	SENT_14	[p1l548t1697r690b1727],
18	for	IN	O	for	prep	17	SENT_14	[p1l702t1697r747b1727],
19	R-6G	NN	O	r-6g	pobj	8	SENT_14	[p1l760t1697r856b1727],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l760t1697r856b1727],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_15	[p1l869t1698r940b1727],
2	decrease	NN	O	decrease	nsubj	7	SENT_15	[p1l952t1698r1107b1727],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1120t1698r1145b1726],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_15	[p1l1158t1698r1209b1727],
5	accumulation	NN	O	accumulation	nn	6	SENT_15	[p1l1222t1698r1443b1727],
6	enhancement	NN	O	enhancement	prep_in	2	SENT_15	[p1l1456t1698r1686b1727],
7	corresponds	VBZ	O	correspond	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1697t1698r1905b1735],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l256t1749r322b1778],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_15	[p1l337t1749r388b1778],
10	higher	JJR	O	higher	amod	12	SENT_15	[p1l405t1749r509b1786],
11	R-6G	NN	O	r-6g	nn	12	SENT_15	[p1l524t1748r610b1778],
12	fraction	NN	O	fraction	prep_with	7	SENT_15	[p1l626t1748r748b1778],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_15	[p1l765t1748r859b1786],
14	0.75	CD	NUMBER	0.75	num	15	SENT_15	[p1l765t1748r859b1786],
15	)	NN	O	)	dobj	7	SENT_15	[p1l765t1748r859b1786],
16	associated	VBN	O	associate	partmod	15	SENT_15	[p1l876t1749r1055b1778],
17	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1070t1751r1101b1778],
18	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	20	SENT_15	[p1l1115t1749r1134b1778],
19	mM	NN	O	mm	nn	20	SENT_15	[p1l1151t1749r1211b1778],
20	MePEG17-b-PCL5	NN	O	mepeg17-b-pcl5	prep_at	16	SENT_15	[p1l1229t1748r1525b1783],
21	compared	VBN	O	compare	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1539t1749r1707b1786],
22	with	IN	O	with	prepc_compared_with	20	SENT_15	[p1l1722t1749r1787b1778],
23	R-123	NN	O	r-123	pobj	20	SENT_15	[p1l1805t1749r1905b1778],
24	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	23	SENT_15	[p1l258t1799r362b1837],
25	0.25	CD	NUMBER	0.25	num	26	SENT_15	[p1l258t1799r362b1837],
26	)	NN	O	)	dep	23	SENT_15	[p1l258t1799r362b1837],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l258t1799r362b1837],

1	Interestingly	RB	O	interestingly	advmod	6	SENT_16	[p1l383t1800r590b1837],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l383t1800r590b1837],
3	R-6G	NN	O	r-6g	nn	4	SENT_16	[p1l610t1799r697b1829],
4	accumulation	NN	O	accumulation	nsubjpass	6	SENT_16	[p1l714t1800r935b1829],
5	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_16	[p1l952t1807r1019b1829],
6	enhanced	VBN	O	enhance	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1035t1800r1200b1829],
7	over	IN	O	over	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1217t1807r1291b1829],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_16	[p1l1306t1807r1326b1829],
9	very	RB	O	very	advmod	10	SENT_16	[p1l1341t1807r1412b1837],
10	broad	JJ	O	broad	amod	11	SENT_16	[p1l1428t1800r1522b1829],
11	range	NN	O	range	prep_over	6	SENT_16	[p1l1541t1807r1635b1837],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1651t1799r1682b1829],
13	MePEG17bPCL5	NN	O	mepeg17bpcl5	nn	14	SENT_16	[p1l1699t1799r1905b1834, p1l259t1850r345b1886],
14	concentrations	NNS	O	concentration	prep_of	11	SENT_16	[p1l365t1851r610b1881],
15	below	IN	O	below	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l631t1851r729b1881],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_16	[p1l747t1851r799b1881],
17	CMC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CMC	prep_below	6	SENT_16	[p1l820t1850r914b1881],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l820t1850r914b1881],

1	This	DT	O	this	nsubj	2	SENT_17	[p1l935t1851r1006b1881],
2	was	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1026t1858r1093b1881],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1114t1851r1140b1880],
4	contrast	NN	O	contrast	prep_in	2	SENT_17	[p1l1161t1853r1295b1881],
5	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1313t1853r1344b1881],
6	R-123	NN	O	r-123	prep_to	2	SENT_17	[p1l1366t1851r1475b1886],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1366t1851r1475b1886],
8	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	9	SENT_17	[p1l1496t1851r1592b1881],
9	demonstrated	VBD	O	demonstrate	rcmod	6	SENT_17	[p1l1613t1851r1843b1881],
10	no	DT	O	no	det	11	SENT_17	[p1l1865t1858r1905b1881],
11	enhancement	NN	O	enhancement	dobj	9	SENT_17	[p1l257t1903r487b1932],
12	below	IN	O	below	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l503t1903r600b1932],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_17	[p1l614t1903r666b1932],
14	CMC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CMC	prep_below	9	SENT_17	[p1l681t1902r775b1932],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l681t1902r775b1932],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_18	[p1l792t1903r817b1932],
2	similar	JJ	O	similar	amod	3	SENT_18	[p1l832t1903r940b1932],
3	concentration	NN	O	concentration	nsubjpass	8	SENT_18	[p1l954t1903r1179b1932],
4	dependent	JJ	O	dependent	amod	6	SENT_18	[p1l1195t1903r1374b1940],
5	accumulation	NN	O	accumulation	nn	6	SENT_18	[p1l1389t1903r1610b1932],
6	profile	NN	O	profile	dep	3	SENT_18	[p1l1627t1902r1727b1940],
7	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_18	[p1l1742t1910r1809b1932],
8	seen	VBN	O	see	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1824t1910r1904b1932],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l256t1954r320b1984],
10	other	JJ	O	other	amod	11	SENT_18	[p1l331t1954r416b1984],
11	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_with	8	SENT_18	[p1l424t1954r604b1984],
12	such	JJ	O	such	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l614t1954r690b1984],
13	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l701t1962r740b1984],
14	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	16	SENT_18	[p1l749t1954r864b1984],
15	E	NN	O	e	nn	16	SENT_18	[p1l877t1954r899b1983],
16	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	prep_such_as	11	SENT_18	[p1l908t1954r1011b1984],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1021t1954r1082b1984],
18	Cremophor	NNP	O	Cremophor	nn	19	SENT_18	[p1l1093t1954r1280b1992],
19	EL	NNP	O	EL	prep_such_as	11	SENT_18	[p1l1290t1954r1334b1983],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1343t1954r1404b1984],
21	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1414t1954r1478b1984],
22	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	25	SENT_18	[p1l1488t1956r1546b1984],
23	other	JJ	O	other	amod	25	SENT_18	[p1l1556t1954r1640b1984],
24	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	25	SENT_18	[p1l1651t1954r1726b1992],
25	substrates	NNS	O	substrate	prep_with	8	SENT_18	[p1l1736t1954r1906b1984],
26	differing	VBG	O	differ	partmod	25	SENT_18	[p1l257t2005r388b2043],
27	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l411t2005r436b2034],
28	hydrophobicity	NN	O	hydrophobicity	prep_in	26	SENT_18	[p1l459t2005r708b2043],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l459t2005r708b2043],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_18	[p1l730t2005r782b2035],
31	relatively	RB	O	relatively	advmod	32	SENT_18	[p1l804t2005r950b2043],
32	hydrophobic	JJ	O	hydrophobic	amod	33	SENT_18	[p1l970t2005r1175b2043],
33	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	conj_and	11	SENT_18	[p1l1196t2005r1349b2043],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1371t2005r1432b2035],
35	hydrophilic	JJ	O	hydrophilic	amod	36	SENT_18	[p1l1455t2005r1633b2043],
36	doxorubicin	NN	O	doxorubicin	conj_and	25	SENT_18	[p1l1653t2005r1853b2035],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1653t2005r1853b2035],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1878t2005r1904b2034],
2	conclusion	NN	O	conclusion	prep_in	10	SENT_19	[p1l257t2057r443b2092],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l257t2057r443b2092],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_19	[p1l458t2057r510b2087],
5	effective	JJ	O	effective	amod	7	SENT_19	[p1l524t2057r662b2087],
6	concentration	NN	O	concentration	nn	7	SENT_19	[p1l676t2057r901b2087],
7	range	NN	O	range	nsubj	10	SENT_19	[p1l918t2064r1011b2095],
8	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1025t2057r1069b2087],
9	surfactant	NN	O	surfactant	prep_for	7	SENT_19	[p1l1082t2057r1247b2087],
10	mediated	VBD	O	mediate	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1261t2057r1414b2087],
11	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	nsubj	14	SENT_19	[p1l1430t2057r1574b2087],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1589t2057r1620b2087],
13	P-gp	NN	O	p-gp	prep_of	11	SENT_19	[p1l1635t2057r1712b2095],
14	appears	VBZ	O	appear	ccomp	10	SENT_19	[p1l1726t2064r1862b2095],
15	to	TO	O	to	aux	16	SENT_19	[p1l1875t2059r1905b2087],
16	depend	VB	O	depend	xcomp	14	SENT_19	[p1l257t2109r382b2146],
17	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l397t2116r436b2138],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_19	[p1l451t2109r503b2138],
19	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	21	SENT_19	[p1l519t2109r595b2146],
20	substrate	NN	O	substrate	nn	21	SENT_19	[p1l609t2109r764b2138],
21	hydrophobicity	NN	O	hydrophobicity	prep_on	16	SENT_19	[p1l779t2109r1028b2146],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l779t2109r1028b2146],

1	Keywords	NNPS	O	Keywords	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l259t2164r455b2201],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l259t2164r455b2201],
3	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	dep	1	SENT_20	[p1l486t2164r743b2201],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l486t2164r743b2201],
5	diblock	NN	O	diblock	nn	6	SENT_20	[p1l761t2164r883b2193],
6	copolymer	NN	O	copolymer	dep	3	SENT_20	[p1l897t2164r1086b2201],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l897t2164r1086b2201],
8	surfactant	NN	O	surfactant	dep	3	SENT_20	[p1l1104t2163r1284b2198],
9	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1104t2163r1284b2198],
10	Caco-2	NN	O	caco-2	dep	8	SENT_20	[p1l1302t2163r1427b2193],

1	Introduction	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l12t2406r574b2479],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_22	[p1l92t2556r228b2619],
2	localization	NN	O	localization	nn	5	SENT_22	[p1l272t2556r687b2619],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l733t2556r859b2619],
4	functional	JJ	O	functional	conj_and	2	SENT_22	[p1l901t2556r1261b2619],
5	expression	NN	O	expression	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1306t2556r1686b2638],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1730t2556r1807b2619],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_22	[p1l1845t2556r1951b2619],
8	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	10	SENT_22	[p1l1996t2556r2151b2638],
9	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	nn	10	SENT_22	[p1l8t2666r206b2729],
10	transporter	NN	O	transporter	prep_of	5	SENT_22	[p1l238t2676r622b2748],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l238t2676r622b2748],
12	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	nn	15	SENT_22	[p1l657t2666r1164b2748],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_22	[p1l1198t2667r1430b2748],
14	P-gp	NN	O	p-gp	nn	15	SENT_22	[p1l1198t2667r1430b2748],
15	)	NN	O	)	appos	10	SENT_22	[p1l1198t2667r1430b2748],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1198t2667r1430b2748],
17	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1466t2686r1550b2729],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_22	[p1l1582t2667r1685b2729],
19	apical	JJ	O	apical	amod	21	SENT_22	[p1l1718t2666r1919b2748],
20	mem	NN	O	mem	nn	21	SENT_22	[p1l1951t2686r2149b2729, p1l56t2934r86b2968],
21	*	NN	O	*	prep_on	5	SENT_22	[p1l1951t2686r2149b2729, p1l56t2934r86b2968],

1	Mailing	VBG	O	mail	dep	4	SENT_24	[p1l1626t2933r1874b3006],
2	address	NN	O	address	dobj	1	SENT_24	[p1l1897t2933r2148b2990],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1897t2933r2148b2990],
4	Faculty	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Faculty	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l172t3031r411b3104],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l456t3031r526b3087],
6	Pharmaceutical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pharmaceutical	nn	7	SENT_24	[p1l564t3031r1058b3087],
7	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	prep_of	4	SENT_24	[p1l1104t3031r1398b3098],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1104t3031r1398b3098],
9	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	4	SENT_24	[p1l1445t3031r1782b3104],
10	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1828t3031r1897b3087],
11	British	NNP	ORGANIZATION	British	nn	12	SENT_24	[p1l1935t3031r2152b3087],
12	Columbia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Columbia	prep_of	9	SENT_24	[p1l173t3130r501b3197],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l173t3130r501b3197],
14	2146	CD	DATE	2146	num	16	SENT_24	[p1l526t3130r681b3187],
15	East	NNP	LOCATION	East	nn	16	SENT_24	[p1l703t3131r840b3186],
16	Mall	NN	LOCATION	mall	appos	12	SENT_24	[p1l859t3130r1025b3197],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l859t3130r1025b3197],
18	Vancouver	NNP	LOCATION	Vancouver	appos	12	SENT_24	[p1l1049t3131r1412b3197],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1049t3131r1412b3197],
20	BC	NNP	O	BC	appos	12	SENT_24	[p1l1437t3130r1558b3197],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1437t3130r1558b3197],
22	V6T	NNP	O	V6T	nn	24	SENT_24	[p1l1582t3130r1727b3187],
23	1Z3	NNP	O	1Z3	nn	24	SENT_24	[p1l1756t3130r1871b3187],
24	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	appos	20	SENT_24	[p1l1897t3130r2148b3187],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1897t3130r2148b3187],

1	Phone	NN	O	phone	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l172t3228r389b3284],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l172t3228r389b3284],
3	604-822-2440	CD	NUMBER	604-822-2440	dep	1	SENT_25	[p1l440t3227r911b3284],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l440t3227r911b3284],

1	Fax	NN	O	fax	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l958t3229r1095b3284],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l958t3229r1095b3284],
3	604-822-3035	CD	NUMBER	604-822-3035	dep	1	SENT_26	[p1l1146t3227r1617b3284],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1146t3227r1617b3284],

1	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1664t3227r1900b3284],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1664t3227r1900b3284],
3	burt	NN	O	burt	dep	1	SENT_27	[p1l1948t3228r2144b3284],
4	@	IN	O	@	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1948t3228r2144b3284],
5	interchange	NN	O	interchange	prep_@	3	SENT_27	[p1l172t3325r790b3398],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l172t3325r790b3398],

1	ubc	NN	O	ubc	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l172t3325r790b3398],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l172t3325r790b3398],

1	ca	MD	O	can	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l172t3325r790b3398],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l172t3325r790b3398],

1	T	NN	O	t	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l54t3412r78b3453],
2	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	1	SENT_30	[p1l103t3424r440b3497],
3	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l471t3424r540b3480],
4	Georgia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Georgia	prep_of	2	SENT_30	[p1l565t3424r837b3497],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l565t3424r837b3497],

1	*	NNP	O	*	nn	2	SENT_31	[p1l54t3510r78b3551],
2	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l103t3522r440b3595],
3	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l471t3522r540b3578],
4	British	NNP	ORGANIZATION	British	nn	5	SENT_31	[p1l563t3522r781b3578],
5	Columbia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Columbia	prep_of	2	SENT_31	[p1l811t3522r1141b3578],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l811t3522r1141b3578],

1	10.1021	CD	NUMBER	10.1021	num	3	SENT_32	[p1l10t3678r586b3737],
2	lmp7001347	NN	O	lmp7001347	nn	3	SENT_32	[p1l10t3678r586b3737],
3	CCC	NN	O	ccc	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l613t3678r762b3725],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l613t3678r762b3725],
5	$	$	MONEY	$	dep	3	SENT_32	[p1l793t3675r981b3732],
6	40.75	CD	MONEY	40.75	number	5	SENT_32	[p1l793t3675r981b3732],
7	©	CD	MONEY	©	number	5	SENT_32	[p1l1009t3681r1053b3725],
8	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	11	SENT_32	[p1l1081t3679r1217b3725],
9	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	11	SENT_32	[p1l1244t3678r1524b3725],
10	Chemical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chemical	nn	11	SENT_32	[p1l1555t3678r1827b3725],
11	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	dep	5	SENT_32	[p1l1857t3678r2076b3737],
12	Published	VBN	O	publish	partmod	5	SENT_32	[p1l11t3752r316b3805],
13	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l346t3765r419b3805],
14	Web	NN	O	web	prep_on	12	SENT_32	[p1l448t3752r592b3805],
15	04/02/2008	CD	DATE	04/02/2008	num	14	SENT_32	[p1l620t3750r974b3805],

1	brane	NN	O	brane	nsubj	6	SENT_33	[p2l6t41r195b104],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l231t41r307b104],
3	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	4	SENT_33	[p2l334t41r644b104],
4	epithelia	NN	O	epithelium	prep_of	1	SENT_33	[p2l679t41r971b122],
5	can	MD	O	can	aux	6	SENT_33	[p2l1005t61r1123b104],
6	pose	VB	O	pose	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1155t61r1312b122],
7	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_33	[p2l1349t61r1386b104],
8	formidable	JJ	O	formidable	amod	9	SENT_33	[p2l1419t41r1792b104],
9	barrier	NN	O	barrier	dobj	6	SENT_33	[p2l1825t41r2054b104],
10	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l2086t51r2150b104],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_33	[p2l7t152r110b215],
12	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	13	SENT_33	[p2l165t152r295b215],
13	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	prep_to	6	SENT_33	[p2l348t152r838b233],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l894t152r969b215],
15	many	JJ	O	many	amod	18	SENT_33	[p2l1017t171r1207b233],
16	therapeutically	RB	O	therapeutically	advmod	17	SENT_33	[p2l1262t152r1766b233],
17	important	JJ	O	important	amod	18	SENT_33	[p2l1820t152r2153b233],
18	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_of	13	SENT_33	[p2l8t245r310b343],
19	.1	CD	NUMBER	.1	num	22	SENT_33	[p2l8t245r310b343],
20	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	num	22	SENT_33	[p2l8t245r310b343],
21	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	22	SENT_33	[p2l8t245r310b343],
22	Compounds	NNS	O	compound	nsubj	40	SENT_33	[p2l338t262r751b343],
23	such	JJ	O	such	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l779t262r933b324],
24	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l958t281r1024b324],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_33	[p2l1049t261r1152b324],
26	anticancer	JJ	O	anticancer	amod	28	SENT_33	[p2l1178t261r1527b324],
27	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	28	SENT_33	[p2l1550t261r1704b343],
28	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	prep_such_as	22	SENT_33	[p2l1727t261r2058b343],
29	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l2082t281r2153b324],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_33	[p2l7t374r110b437],
31	antiretroviral	JJ	O	antiretroviral	amod	33	SENT_33	[p2l153t374r592b437],
32	agent	NN	O	agent	nn	33	SENT_33	[p2l635t383r819b455],
33	saquinavir	NN	O	saquinavir	prep_such_as	22	SENT_33	[p2l861t374r1230b455],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l861t374r1230b455],
35	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1276t394r1507b455],
36	many	JJ	O	many	amod	37	SENT_33	[p2l1548t394r1739b455],
37	others	NNS	O	other	prep_among	40	SENT_33	[p2l1781t374r2005b449],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1781t374r2005b449],
39	are	VBP	O	be	cop	40	SENT_33	[p2l2050t394r2151b437],
40	susceptible	JJ	O	susceptible	rcmod	18	SENT_33	[p2l10t484r384b565],
41	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l413t493r477b546],
42	P	NN	O	p	nn	44	SENT_33	[p2l507t485r667b565],
43	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	44	SENT_33	[p2l507t485r667b565],
44	gp	NN	O	gp	prep_to	40	SENT_33	[p2l507t485r667b565],
45	mediated	VBN	O	mediate	partmod	44	SENT_33	[p2l697t484r1011b546],
46	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	dobj	45	SENT_33	[p2l1039t483r1254b547],
47	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1039t483r1254b547],

1	Using	VBG	O	use	dep	17	SENT_34	[p2l1287t484r1490b565],
2	a	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_34	[p2l1522t503r1558b546],
3	mdrla	NN	O	mdrlum	nsubj	4	SENT_34	[p2l1586t484r1806b546],
4	knockout	JJ	O	knockout	ccomp	1	SENT_34	[p2l1833t483r2153b546],
5	mouse	NN	O	mouse	nn	6	SENT_34	[p2l7t616r231b659],
6	model	NN	O	model	iobj	4	SENT_34	[p2l265t596r479b659],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_34	[p2l516t596r660b674],
8	i.e.	FW	O	i.e.	dobj	4	SENT_34	[p2l516t596r660b674],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l516t596r660b674],
10	lacking	VBG	O	lack	partmod	17	SENT_34	[p2l698t596r948b678],
11	P-gp	JJ	O	p-gp	amod	12	SENT_34	[p2l983t597r1189b678],
12	)	NN	O	)	dobj	10	SENT_34	[p2l983t597r1189b678],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l983t597r1189b678],
14	Sparreboom	NNP	PERSON	Sparreboom	nsubj	17	SENT_34	[p2l1229t596r1647b678],
15	et	FW	O	et	nn	16	SENT_34	[p2l1680t605r1742b659],
16	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	14	SENT_34	[p2l1776t596r1851b659],
17	demonstrated	VBD	O	demonstrate	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1890t596r2149b659, p2l10t707r233b770],
18	an	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_34	[p2l262t727r340b770],
19	increase	NN	O	increase	dobj	17	SENT_34	[p2l368t707r646b770],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l674t707r739b769],
21	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	nn	23	SENT_34	[p2l765t707r1096b788],
22	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	23	SENT_34	[p2l1125t707r1255b770],
23	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	prep_in	17	SENT_34	[p2l1281t707r1772b788],
24	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1800t707r1967b770],
25	11	CD	PERCENT	11	num	26	SENT_34	[p2l2002t707r2148b770],
26	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_from	23	SENT_34	[p2l2002t707r2148b770],
27	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l7t816r73b878],
28	wild	JJ	O	wild	amod	30	SENT_34	[p2l111t816r263b880],
29	type	NN	O	type	nn	30	SENT_34	[p2l301t826r447b898],
30	mice	NNS	O	mouse	prep_in	26	SENT_34	[p2l487t816r652b879],
31	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l692t826r756b879],
32	35	CD	PERCENT	35	num	33	SENT_34	[p2l798t816r950b880],
33	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_to	17	SENT_34	[p2l798t816r950b880],
34	when	WRB	O	when	advmod	35	SENT_34	[p2l993t816r1179b880],
35	given	VBN	O	give	advcl	17	SENT_34	[p2l1219t816r1407b898],
36	to	TO	O	to	aux	37	SENT_34	[p2l1446t826r1510b879],
37	mdr1a	VB	O	mdr1a	xcomp	35	SENT_34	[p2l1551t816r1891b894],
38	(	NN	O	(	dobj	37	SENT_34	[p2l1551t816r1891b894],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1551t816r1891b894],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1551t816r1891b894],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1551t816r1891b894],
3	)	SYM	O	)	dep	1	SENT_35	[p2l1551t816r1891b894],

1	mice	NNS	O	mouse	nn	2	SENT_36	[p2l1933t800r2151b879],
2	.2	NN	NUMBER	.2	ccomp	8	SENT_36	[p2l1933t800r2151b879],
3	Similarly	RB	O	similarly	advmod	2	SENT_36	[p2l9t929r341b1010],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l9t929r341b1010],
5	Huisman	NNP	PERSON	Huisman	nsubj	8	SENT_36	[p2l376t929r687b992],
6	et	FW	O	et	nn	7	SENT_36	[p2l720t938r780b992],
7	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	5	SENT_36	[p2l813t929r888b992],
8	demonstrated	VBD	O	demonstrate	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l926t929r1386b992],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_36	[p2l1419t949r1456b992],
10	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	amod	11	SENT_36	[p2l1490t929r1843b1010],
11	increase	NN	O	increase	dobj	8	SENT_36	[p2l1874t929r2151b992],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l7t1039r72b1101],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_36	[p2l98t1039r202b1101],
14	plasma	NN	O	plasma	nn	15	SENT_36	[p2l227t1039r472b1120],
15	AUC	NN	O	auc	prep_in	8	SENT_36	[p2l496t1039r678b1102],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l707t1039r782b1101],
17	saquinavir	NN	O	saquinavir	prep_of	15	SENT_36	[p2l806t1038r1159b1120],
18	when	WRB	O	when	advmod	19	SENT_36	[p2l1184t1039r1369b1102],
19	administered	VBN	O	administer	advcl	8	SENT_36	[p2l1397t1039r1837b1101],
20	orally	RB	O	orally	advmod	22	SENT_36	[p2l1863t1039r2059b1120],
21	to	TO	O	to	aux	22	SENT_36	[p2l2086t1048r2151b1101],
22	mdr1a	VB	O	mdr1a	xcomp	19	SENT_36	[p2l7t1151r251b1215],
23	/	:	O	/	punct	27	SENT_36	[p2l7t1151r251b1215],
24	lb	NN	O	lb	nn	26	SENT_36	[p2l258t1151r334b1214],
25	knockout	NN	O	knockout	nn	26	SENT_36	[p2l361t1151r682b1214],
26	mice	NNS	O	mouse	nsubj	27	SENT_36	[p2l708t1151r873b1214],
27	(	VBP	O	(	parataxis	22	SENT_36	[p2l904t1152r1055b1229],
28	349	CD	NUMBER	349	num	30	SENT_36	[p2l904t1152r1055b1229],
29	ng/mL	NN	O	ng/ml	nn	30	SENT_36	[p2l1085t1152r1339b1233],
30	)	NN	O	)	dobj	27	SENT_36	[p2l1085t1152r1339b1233],
31	compared	VBN	O	compare	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1369t1151r1708b1232],
32	to	TO	O	to	prepc_compared_to	27	SENT_36	[p2l1734t1161r1798b1214],
33	wild	JJ	O	wild	amod	34	SENT_36	[p2l1827t1151r1978b1214],
34	type	NN	O	type	pobj	27	SENT_36	[p2l2005t1161r2151b1233],
35	VOL	NNP	O	VOL	dobj	22	SENT_36	[p2l64t1270r220b1325],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l64t1270r220b1325],

1	5	CD	NUMBER	5	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l252t1274r304b1334],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l252t1274r304b1334],
3	NO.	NNP	O	NO.	appos	1	SENT_37	[p2l338t1270r455b1325],
4	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	3	SENT_37	[p2l486t1273r538b1334],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l486t1273r538b1334],
6	643-653	CD	NUMBER	643-653	num	3	SENT_37	[p2l570t1273r844b1325],
7	MOLECULAR	NNP	O	MOLECULAR	nn	8	SENT_37	[p2l891t1270r1340b1325],
8	PHARMACEUTICS	NN	O	pharmaceutic	dep	1	SENT_37	[p2l1372t1270r1993b1325],
9	643	CD	NUMBER	643	num	8	SENT_37	[p2l2038t1273r2152b1325],

1	articles	NNS	O	article	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l31t1409r218b1449],
2	Zastre	NNP	O	Zastre	dep	1	SENT_38	[p2l1923t1421r2028b1449],
3	et	FW	O	et	nn	4	SENT_38	[p2l2044t1425r2074b1449],
4	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	2	SENT_38	[p2l2088t1420r2126b1449],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l2088t1420r2126b1449],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	3	SENT_39	[p2l10t1626r159b1704],
2	215	CD	NUMBER	215	num	3	SENT_39	[p2l10t1626r159b1704],
3	ng/mL	NN	O	ng/ml	nsubj	55	SENT_39	[p2l187t1610r495b1708],
4	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	5	SENT_39	[p2l187t1610r495b1708],
5	.6	CD	NUMBER	.6	num	8	SENT_39	[p2l187t1610r495b1708],
6	The	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_39	[p2l520t1626r653b1689],
7	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	8	SENT_39	[p2l678t1626r808b1689],
8	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	nsubj	38	SENT_39	[p2l831t1626r1320b1708],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1347t1626r1421b1689],
10	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	prep_of	8	SENT_39	[p2l1438t1626r1768b1708],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1793t1626r1858b1689],
12	humans	NNS	O	human	prep_in	10	SENT_39	[p2l1881t1627r2146b1689],
13	increased	VBN	O	increase	partmod	12	SENT_39	[p2l7t1733r328b1795],
14	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l356t1733r523b1795],
15	9.3	CD	PERCENT	9.3	number	19	SENT_39	[p2l551t1734r725b1796],
16	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	19	SENT_39	[p2l551t1734r725b1796],
17	to	TO	O	to	dep	19	SENT_39	[p2l757t1743r821b1795],
18	67	CD	PERCENT	67	number	19	SENT_39	[p2l852t1733r1004b1796],
19	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_from	13	SENT_39	[p2l852t1733r1004b1796],
20	when	WRB	O	when	advmod	24	SENT_39	[p2l1037t1733r1223b1796],
21	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	nsubj	24	SENT_39	[p2l1249t1733r1580b1814],
22	was	VBD	O	be	cop	24	SENT_39	[p2l1609t1753r1739b1796],
23	coadrI1inis	JJ	O	coadri1inis	amod	24	SENT_39	[p2l1770t1733r2146b1795],
24	—	NN	O	—	advcl	13	SENT_39	[p2l1770t1733r2146b1795],
25	tered	VBN	O	ter	partmod	24	SENT_39	[p2l7t1839r177b1902],
26	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l211t1839r362b1902],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_39	[p2l396t1840r498b1902],
28	P	NN	O	p	nn	32	SENT_39	[p2l533t1841r693b1921],
29	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	32	SENT_39	[p2l533t1841r693b1921],
30	gp	NN	O	gp	nn	32	SENT_39	[p2l533t1841r693b1921],
31	inhibitor	NN	O	inhibitor	nn	32	SENT_39	[p2l729t1839r1022b1902],
32	cyclosporin	NN	O	cyclosporin	prep_with	25	SENT_39	[p2l1055t1839r1452b1921],
33	A.	NN	O	a.	dep	32	SENT_39	[p2l1486t1823r1598b1902],
34	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	33	SENT_39	[p2l1486t1823r1598b1902],
35	These	DT	O	these	det	36	SENT_39	[p2l1635t1840r1838b1902],
36	ﬁndings	NNS	O	ﬁndings	dep	33	SENT_39	[p2l1874t1839r2146b1921],
37	clearly	RB	O	clearly	advmod	38	SENT_39	[p2l8t1946r236b2027],
38	demonstrate	VBP	O	demonstrate	rcmod	3	SENT_39	[p2l281t1946r696b2008],
39	that	IN	O	that	complm	42	SENT_39	[p2l739t1946r867b2008],
40	strategies	NNS	O	strategy	nsubj	42	SENT_39	[p2l912t1946r1226b2027],
41	to	TO	O	to	aux	42	SENT_39	[p2l1271t1956r1335b2008],
42	avoid	VB	O	avoid	ccomp	38	SENT_39	[p2l1381t1946r1569b2009],
43	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1612t1966r1683b2008],
44	inhibit	VB	O	inhibit	conj_or	42	SENT_39	[p2l1724t1946r1945b2008],
45	P	NN	O	p	nn	47	SENT_39	[p2l1987t1948r2147b2027],
46	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	47	SENT_39	[p2l1987t1948r2147b2027],
47	gp	NN	O	gp	dobj	42	SENT_39	[p2l1987t1948r2147b2027],
48	mediated	VBN	O	mediate	partmod	47	SENT_39	[p2l7t2052r320b2114],
49	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	50	SENT_39	[p2l345t2052r499b2133],
50	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	dobj	48	SENT_39	[p2l525t2052r723b2114],
51	can	MD	O	can	aux	55	SENT_39	[p2l748t2072r866b2114],
52	be	VB	O	be	cop	55	SENT_39	[p2l889t2052r970b2114],
53	an	DT	O	a	det	55	SENT_39	[p2l996t2072r1075b2114],
54	attractive	JJ	O	attractive	amod	55	SENT_39	[p2l1100t2052r1412b2114],
55	approach	NN	O	approach	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1439t2052r1750b2133],
56	to	TO	O	to	aux	57	SENT_39	[p2l1774t2062r1838b2114],
57	improve	VB	O	improve	infmod	55	SENT_39	[p2l1863t2052r2148b2133],
58	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	60	SENT_39	[p2l8t2158r162b2239],
59	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	60	SENT_39	[p2l193t2158r322b2220],
60	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	dobj	57	SENT_39	[p2l350t2158r856b2239],
61	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l350t2158r856b2239],

1	Although	IN	O	although	mark	8	SENT_40	[p2l92t2265r424b2345],
2	P	NN	O	p	nsubjpass	8	SENT_40	[p2l448t2266r612b2345],
3	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	5	SENT_40	[p2l448t2266r612b2345],
4	gp	NN	O	gp	nn	5	SENT_40	[p2l448t2266r612b2345],
5	inhibitors	NNS	O	inhibitor	dep	2	SENT_40	[p2l637t2264r972b2327],
6	have	VBP	O	have	aux	8	SENT_40	[p2l997t2265r1162b2327],
7	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_40	[p2l1186t2265r1352b2327],
8	developed	VBN	O	develop	advcl	18	SENT_40	[p2l1377t2265r1738b2345],
9	that	IN	O	that	complm	10	SENT_40	[p2l1761t2265r1893b2327],
10	reduce	VB	O	reduce	dep	8	SENT_40	[p2l1915t2265r2149b2327],
11	P	NN	O	p	dobj	10	SENT_40	[p2l7t2372r168b2451],
12	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	15	SENT_40	[p2l7t2372r168b2451],
13	gp	NN	O	gp	nn	15	SENT_40	[p2l7t2372r168b2451],
14	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	nn	15	SENT_40	[p2l192t2371r392b2433],
15	activity	NN	O	activity	nsubj	10	SENT_40	[p2l416t2371r689b2451],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l416t2371r689b2451],
17	there	EX	O	there	expl	18	SENT_40	[p2l714t2371r885b2433],
18	are	VBP	O	be	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l909t2390r1011b2433],
19	numerous	JJ	O	numerous	amod	20	SENT_40	[p2l1033t2390r1372b2433],
20	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	18	SENT_40	[p2l1399t2371r1632b2433],
21	demonstrating	VBG	O	demonstrate	partmod	20	SENT_40	[p2l1657t2371r2148b2451],
22	effective	JJ	O	effective	amod	23	SENT_40	[p2l8t2477r316b2539],
23	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	dobj	21	SENT_40	[p2l349t2477r694b2539],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l727t2477r804b2539],
25	P	NN	O	p	nn	27	SENT_40	[p2l829t2478r995b2557],
26	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	27	SENT_40	[p2l829t2478r995b2557],
27	gp	NN	O	gp	prep_of	23	SENT_40	[p2l829t2478r995b2557],
28	using	VBG	O	use	partmod	27	SENT_40	[p2l1027t2477r1218b2557],
29	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	dobj	28	SENT_40	[p2l1254t2476r1653b2539],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1254t2476r1653b2539],

1	Amphiphiles	NNS	O	amphiphile	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1689t2477r2146b2557],
2	such	JJ	O	such	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l10t2583r168b2645],
3	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l197t2602r264b2645],
4	polysorbates	NNS	O	polysorbate	prep_such_as	1	SENT_41	[p2l292t2583r740b2663],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_41	[p2l771t2583r1122b2659],
6	Tweens	NNS	O	tween	dep	7	SENT_41	[p2l771t2583r1122b2659],
7	)	RB	O	)	amod	4	SENT_41	[p2l771t2583r1122b2659],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l771t2583r1122b2659],
9	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	11	SENT_41	[p2l1152t2583r1422b2645],
10	E	NN	O	e	nn	11	SENT_41	[p2l1448t2584r1500b2644],
11	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	appos	4	SENT_41	[p2l1527t2583r1762b2656],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1527t2583r1762b2656],
13	Pluronics	NNP	O	Pluronics	appos	4	SENT_41	[p2l1791t2582r2145b2656],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1791t2582r2145b2656],
15	Solutols	NNP	O	Solutols	appos	13	SENT_41	[p2l9t2689r316b2762],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l9t2689r316b2762],
17	and	CC	O	and	dep	1	SENT_41	[p2l355t2689r481b2751],
18	Cremophor	NNP	LOCATION	Cremophor	nn	19	SENT_41	[p2l515t2689r920b2769],
19	EL	NNP	LOCATION	EL	dep	1	SENT_41	[p2l951t2690r1059b2750],
20	have	VBP	O	have	aux	22	SENT_41	[p2l1092t2689r1258b2751],
21	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	22	SENT_41	[p2l1291t2689r1459b2751],
22	shown	VBN	O	show	rcmod	19	SENT_41	[p2l1496t2689r1723b2751],
23	to	TO	O	to	aux	24	SENT_41	[p2l1757t2698r1823b2751],
24	enhance	VB	O	enhance	xcomp	22	SENT_41	[p2l1859t2689r2148b2751],
25	cellular	JJ	O	cellular	amod	26	SENT_41	[p2l8t2795r266b2857],
26	accumulation	NN	O	accumulation	dobj	24	SENT_41	[p2l289t2795r753b2857],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l777t2795r900b2857],
28	increase	NN	O	increase	dobj	24	SENT_41	[p2l922t2795r1204b2857],
29	transepithelial	JJ	O	transepithelial	amod	30	SENT_41	[p2l1227t2795r1714b2875],
30	ﬂux	NN	O	ﬂux	dep	35	SENT_41	[p2l1738t2795r1871b2857],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1895t2795r1971b2857],
32	P	NN	O	p	prep_of	30	SENT_41	[p2l1987t2796r2149b2875],
33	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	34	SENT_41	[p2l1987t2796r2149b2875],
34	gp	NN	O	gp	dep	35	SENT_41	[p2l1987t2796r2149b2875],
35	substrates	NNS	O	substrate	dep	38	SENT_41	[p2l10t2884r510b2964],
36	.7	CD	NUMBER	.7	dep	35	SENT_41	[p2l10t2884r510b2964],
37	"	``	O	"	punct	38	SENT_41	[p2l10t2884r510b2964],
38	13	CD	NUMBER	13	dep	19	SENT_41	[p2l10t2884r510b2964],
39	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	42	SENT_41	[p2l537t2902r659b2964],
40	have	VBP	O	have	aux	42	SENT_41	[p2l684t2901r850b2964],
41	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	42	SENT_41	[p2l874t2901r1249b2982],
42	developed	VBN	O	develop	rcmod	38	SENT_41	[p2l1276t2901r1641b2982],
43	a	DT	O	a	det	45	SENT_41	[p2l1666t2921r1703b2963],
44	novel	JJ	O	novel	amod	45	SENT_41	[p2l1726t2901r1922b2964],
45	series	NN	O	series	dobj	42	SENT_41	[p2l1950t2901r2147b2964],
46	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l8t3008r85b3070],
47	low	JJ	O	low	amod	52	SENT_41	[p2l119t3008r249b3070],
48	molecular	JJ	O	molecular	amod	52	SENT_41	[p2l290t3008r646b3070],
49	weight	NN	O	weight	nn	52	SENT_41	[p2l684t3008r926b3088],
50	amphiphilic	JJ	O	amphiphilic	amod	52	SENT_41	[p2l966t3008r1387b3088],
51	diblock	NN	O	diblock	nn	52	SENT_41	[p2l1429t3008r1696b3070],
52	copolymers	NNS	O	copolymer	prep_of	45	SENT_41	[p2l1734t3008r2146b3088],
53	based	VBN	O	base	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l6t3114r209b3176],
54	on	IN	O	on	prepc_based_on	38	SENT_41	[p2l264t3133r350b3176],
55	methoxy	NN	O	methoxy	nn	56	SENT_41	[p2l406t3114r715b3194],
56	poly	NN	O	poly	pobj	38	SENT_41	[p2l770t3114r1259b3194],
57	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	59	SENT_41	[p2l770t3114r1259b3194],
58	ethylene	NN	O	ethylene	nn	59	SENT_41	[p2l770t3114r1259b3194],
59	glycol	NN	O	glycol	dep	56	SENT_41	[p2l1317t3114r1563b3194],
60	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	61	SENT_41	[p2l1317t3114r1563b3194],
61	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	63	SENT_41	[p2l1624t3114r1964b3190],
62	MePEG	NN	O	mepeg	nn	63	SENT_41	[p2l1624t3114r1964b3190],
63	)	NN	O	)	dep	59	SENT_41	[p2l1624t3114r1964b3190],
64	and	CC	O	and	advmod	63	SENT_41	[p2l2024t3114r2149b3176],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l47t3331r129b3397],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	3	SENT_42	[p2l47t3331r129b3397],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_42	[p2l47t3331r129b3397],
4	Hunter	NNP	O	Hunter	nn	6	SENT_42	[p2l171t3332r396b3394],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l171t3332r396b3394],
6	J	NNP	O	J	dep	3	SENT_42	[p2l421t3332r449b3384],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l455t3348r486b3394],

1	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l455t3348r486b3394],
2	Hirst	NNP	PERSON	Hirst	nn	5	SENT_43	[p2l513t3331r678b3394],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l513t3331r678b3394],
4	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	appos	5	SENT_43	[p2l704t3332r767b3384],
5	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l794t3332r884b3394],
6	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l794t3332r884b3394],
7	Simmons	NNP	PERSON	Simmons	dep	5	SENT_43	[p2l912t3331r1211b3394],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l912t3331r1211b3394],
9	N.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	N.	nn	12	SENT_43	[p2l1236t3332r1304b3384],
10	L.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	L.	nn	12	SENT_43	[p2l1331t3332r1390b3384],
11	Drug	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Drug	nn	12	SENT_43	[p2l1417t3332r1570b3400],
12	absorption	NN	O	absorption	appos	5	SENT_43	[p2l1595t3331r1913b3400],
13	limited	VBN	O	limit	partmod	12	SENT_43	[p2l1935t3331r2149b3384],
14	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l170t3424r244b3493],
15	P	NN	O	p	agent	13	SENT_43	[p2l279t3424r1034b3493],
16	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	20	SENT_43	[p2l279t3424r1034b3493],
17	glycoprotein-mediated	JJ	O	glycoprotein-mediated	amod	20	SENT_43	[p2l279t3424r1034b3493],
18	secretory	JJ	O	secretory	amod	20	SENT_43	[p2l1070t3433r1344b3493],
19	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	20	SENT_43	[p2l1380t3424r1515b3493],
20	transport	NN	O	transport	dobj	13	SENT_43	[p2l1550t3432r1820b3493],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1853t3424r1910b3477],
22	human	JJ	O	human	amod	27	SENT_43	[p2l1943t3424r2149b3478],
23	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	27	SENT_43	[p2l171t3519r440b3572],
24	epithelial	JJ	O	epithelial	amod	27	SENT_43	[p2l460t3519r733b3588],
25	Caco-2	NN	O	caco-2	nn	27	SENT_43	[p2l754t3519r965b3572],
26	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	27	SENT_43	[p2l986t3519r1090b3572],
27	layers	NNS	O	layer	prep_in	20	SENT_43	[p2l1110t3519r1300b3588],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1110t3519r1300b3588],

1	Pharm	NNP	O	Pharm	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1322t3519r1536b3572],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1322t3519r1536b3572],

1	Res	NNP	O	Res	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1560t3521r1679b3572],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1560t3521r1679b3572],

1	1993	CD	DATE	1993	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1709t3518r1869b3582],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1709t3518r1869b3582],
3	Io	NNP	O	Io	appos	1	SENT_46	[p2l1893t3519r1979b3582],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1893t3519r1979b3582],
5	743749	CD	NUMBER	743749	appos	3	SENT_46	[p2l2002t3519r2150b3572, p2l172t3613r300b3666],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l2002t3519r2150b3572, p2l172t3613r300b3666],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l47t3707r129b3773],
2	2	CD	NUMBER	2	number	3	SENT_47	[p2l47t3707r129b3773],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	4	SENT_47	[p2l47t3707r129b3773],
4	Sparreboom	NN	O	sparreboom	dep	1	SENT_47	[p2l173t3707r556b3776],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l173t3707r556b3776],
6	A.	NN	O	a.	appos	1	SENT_47	[p2l592t3707r682b3770],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l592t3707r682b3770],
8	van	NN	PERSON	van	dep	1	SENT_47	[p2l718t3723r826b3760],
9	Asperen	NNP	PERSON	Asperen	nn	11	SENT_47	[p2l858t3707r1125b3776],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l858t3707r1125b3776],
11	J	NNP	O	J	dep	8	SENT_47	[p2l1161t3708r1188b3760],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1195t3724r1226b3770],

1	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1195t3724r1226b3770],
2	Mayer	NNP	PERSON	Mayer	nn	4	SENT_48	[p2l1261t3708r1474b3776],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1261t3708r1474b3776],
4	U.	NNP	PERSON	U.	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1510t3708r1599b3770],
5	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1510t3708r1599b3770],
6	Schinkel	NNP	PERSON	Schinkel	nn	9	SENT_48	[p2l1637t3707r1915b3770],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1637t3707r1915b3770],
8	A.	NNP	O	A.	appos	9	SENT_48	[p2l1951t3707r2019b3760],
9	H.	NNP	O	H.	dep	4	SENT_48	[p2l2056t3708r2146b3770],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l2056t3708r2146b3770],

1	Smit	NNP	PERSON	Smit	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l173t19r329b83],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l173t19r329b83],
3	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	4	SENT_49	[p3l363t21r405b73],
4	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	appos	1	SENT_49	[p3l440t21r547b82],
5	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l440t21r547b82],
6	Meijer	NNP	PERSON	Meijer	dep	1	SENT_49	[p3l581t19r798b88],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l581t19r798b88],
8	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	9	SENT_49	[p3l832t21r900b73],
9	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	appos	6	SENT_49	[p3l936t21r1025b82],
10	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l936t21r1025b82],
11	Borst	NNP	PERSON	Borst	dep	1	SENT_49	[p3l1059t21r1238b83],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1059t21r1238b83],
13	P.	NNP	O	P.	appos	11	SENT_49	[p3l1272t21r1349b82],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1272t21r1349b82],
15	Nooijen	NNP	LOCATION	Nooijen	dep	1	SENT_49	[p3l1383t19r1643b88],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1383t19r1643b88],
17	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	18	SENT_49	[p3l1676t21r1761b73],
18	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	appos	15	SENT_49	[p3l1796t21r1861b82],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1796t21r1861b82],
20	Beijnen	NNP	O	Beijnen	dep	1	SENT_49	[p3l1895t19r2146b88],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1895t19r2146b88],
22	J	NNP	O	J	appos	20	SENT_49	[p3l171t115r199b167],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l205t158r214b167],

1	H.	NN	O	h.	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l248t115r337b177],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l248t115r337b177],
3	van	NN	PERSON	van	nn	4	SENT_50	[p3l371t130r479b167],
4	Tellingen	NNP	PERSON	Tellingen	dep	1	SENT_50	[p3l509t114r814b183],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l509t114r814b183],
6	o.	NNP	O	o.	nn	9	SENT_50	[p3l848t114r915b167],
7	Limited	NNP	O	Limited	nn	9	SENT_50	[p3l949t114r1188b167],
8	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	9	SENT_50	[p3l1219t114r1334b167],
9	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	conj_and	4	SENT_50	[p3l1363t114r1800b183],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l1833t114r1940b167],
11	active	JJ	O	active	amod	13	SENT_50	[p3l1971t114r2148b167],
12	epithelial	JJ	O	epithelial	amod	13	SENT_50	[p3l172t207r447b276],
13	excretion	NN	O	excretion	dep	1	SENT_50	[p3l467t207r743b261],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l763t207r828b261],
15	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	nn	18	SENT_50	[p3l842t207r1131b276],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_50	[p3l1153t207r1371b273],
17	Taxol	NN	O	taxol	nn	18	SENT_50	[p3l1153t207r1371b273],
18	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	13	SENT_50	[p3l1153t207r1371b273],
19	caused	VBN	O	cause	partmod	13	SENT_50	[p3l1394t207r1595b261],
20	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l1614t207r1688b276],
21	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	agent	19	SENT_50	[p3l1708t207r2150b276],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l171t302r228b354],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_50	[p3l260t302r350b355],
24	intestine	NN	O	intestine	prep_in	21	SENT_50	[p3l382t302r653b355],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l382t302r653b355],

1	Proc	NNP	O	Proc	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l687t304r845b355],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l687t304r845b355],

1	Natl.	NNP	O	Natl.	nn	2	SENT_52	[p3l882t302r1025b355],
2	Acad	NNP	O	Acad	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1059t302r1230b355],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1059t302r1230b355],

1	Sci	NNP	O	Sci	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1269t303r1371b355],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1269t303r1371b355],

1	U.S.A.	NNP	O	U.S.A.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1416t303r1597b355],
2	1997	CD	DATE	1997	num	1	SENT_54	[p3l1639t301r1801b364],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1639t301r1801b364],
4	94	CD	NUMBER	94	num	1	SENT_54	[p3l1837t302r1926b364],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1837t302r1926b364],
6	20312035	CD	NUMBER	20312035	appos	1	SENT_54	[p3l1962t302r2150b355, p3l172t394r338b448],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1962t302r2150b355, p3l172t394r338b448],

1	(	NN	O	(	nsubj	33	SENT_55	[p3l47t489r129b555],
2	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	3	SENT_55	[p3l47t489r129b555],
3	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_55	[p3l47t489r129b555],
4	Van	NNP	PERSON	Van	nn	5	SENT_55	[p3l171t490r296b542],
5	Asperen	NNP	PERSON	Asperen	dep	1	SENT_55	[p3l341t489r609b558],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l341t489r609b558],
7	J.	NNP	O	J.	appos	5	SENT_55	[p3l658t490r722b552],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l658t490r722b552],
9	van	NNP	PERSON	van	nn	10	SENT_55	[p3l772t505r880b542],
10	Tellingen	NNP	PERSON	Tellingen	dep	5	SENT_55	[p3l926t489r1231b558],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l926t489r1231b558],
12	o.	NNP	O	o.	appos	10	SENT_55	[p3l1281t489r1370b552],
13	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1281t489r1370b552],
14	van	NNP	PERSON	van	nn	16	SENT_55	[p3l1419t505r1527b542],
15	der	NNP	PERSON	der	nn	16	SENT_55	[p3l1574t489r1669b542],
16	Valk	NNP	PERSON	Valk	dep	5	SENT_55	[p3l1714t489r1876b552],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1714t489r1876b552],
18	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	19	SENT_55	[p3l1925t490r2005b542],
19	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	appos	16	SENT_55	[p3l2055t489r2146b552],
20	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l2055t489r2146b552],
21	Rozenhart	NNP	PERSON	Rozenhart	dep	5	SENT_55	[p3l171t582r497b646],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l171t582r497b646],
23	M.	NNP	O	M.	appos	21	SENT_55	[p3l541t584r644b646],
24	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l541t584r644b646],
25	Beijnen	NNP	LOCATION	Beijnen	dep	5	SENT_55	[p3l689t582r939b651],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l689t582r939b651],
27	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	28	SENT_55	[p3l983t584r1026b636],
28	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	25	SENT_55	[p3l1071t584r1139b636],
29	Enhanced	VBD	O	enhance	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1184t582r1482b636],
30	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	31	SENT_55	[p3l1525t582r1639b636],
31	absorption	NN	O	absorption	dobj	29	SENT_55	[p3l1682t582r2000b651],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l2042t582r2149b636],
33	decreased	VBD	O	decrease	conj_and	29	SENT_55	[p3l172t677r469b730],
34	elimination	NN	O	elimination	dobj	33	SENT_55	[p3l503t677r847b730],
35	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l882t677r947b730],
36	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	prep_of	34	SENT_55	[p3l976t677r1270b746],
37	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1304t677r1362b729],
38	mice	NNS	O	mouse	prep_in	33	SENT_55	[p3l1396t677r1541b730],
39	cotreated	VBN	O	cotreate	partmod	38	SENT_55	[p3l1576t677r1852b730],
40	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1887t677r2020b730],
41	cyclosporin	NN	O	cyclosporin	nn	43	SENT_55	[p3l2054t693r2146b746, p3l172t770r452b839],
42	A.	NN	O	a.	nn	43	SENT_55	[p3l479t771r547b824],
43	Clin	NNP	O	Clin	prep_with	39	SENT_55	[p3l582t770r719b824],
44	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l582t770r719b824],

1	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l757t771r986b824],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l757t771r986b824],

1	Res	NNP	O	Res	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1019t772r1140b824],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1019t772r1140b824],

1	1998	CD	DATE	1998	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1178t770r1341b834],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1178t770r1341b834],
3	4	CD	NUMBER	4	appos	1	SENT_58	[p3l1370t771r1423b833],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1370t771r1423b833],
5	2293-2297	CD	DATE	2293-2297	appos	3	SENT_58	[p3l1454t771r1810b825],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1454t771r1810b825],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	5	SENT_59	[p3l47t865r129b931],
2	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	5	SENT_59	[p3l47t865r129b931],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	5	SENT_59	[p3l47t865r129b931],
4	Van	NNP	PERSON	Van	nn	5	SENT_59	[p3l171t866r296b918],
5	Asperen	NNP	PERSON	Asperen	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l326t865r593b934],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l326t865r593b934],
7	J	NNP	O	J	appos	5	SENT_59	[p3l626t866r654b918],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l660t882r691b928],

1	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l660t882r691b928],
2	van	NN	PERSON	van	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l725t881r832b918],
3	Tellingen	NNP	PERSON	Tellingen	dep	2	SENT_60	[p3l862t865r1168b934],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l862t865r1168b934],
5	o.	NNP	O	o.	appos	2	SENT_60	[p3l1202t865r1290b928],
6	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1202t865r1290b928],
7	Sparreboom	NNP	PERSON	Sparreboom	dep	5	SENT_60	[p3l1326t865r1709b934],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1326t865r1709b934],
9	A.	NN	O	a.	appos	7	SENT_60	[p3l1742t865r1832b928],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1742t865r1832b928],
11	Schinkel	NNP	PERSON	Schinkel	dep	2	SENT_60	[p3l1868t865r2146b928],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1868t865r2146b928],
13	A.	NNP	O	A.	nn	14	SENT_60	[p3l171t959r239b1012],
14	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	11	SENT_60	[p3l275t960r364b1021],
15	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l275t960r364b1021],
16	Borst	NNP	PERSON	Borst	dep	2	SENT_60	[p3l399t960r578b1022],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l399t960r578b1022],
18	P.	NNP	O	P.	appos	16	SENT_60	[p3l612t960r689b1022],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l612t960r689b1022],
20	Nooijen	NNP	LOCATION	Nooijen	dep	2	SENT_60	[p3l724t958r983b1027],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l724t958r983b1027],
22	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	23	SENT_60	[p3l1017t960r1102b1012],
23	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	appos	20	SENT_60	[p3l1138t960r1202b1021],
24	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1138t960r1202b1021],
25	Beijnen	NNP	O	Beijnen	dep	2	SENT_60	[p3l1237t958r1487b1027],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1237t958r1487b1027],
27	J	NNP	O	J	appos	25	SENT_60	[p3l1521t960r1549b1012],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1556t1003r1564b1012],

1	H.	NNP	O	H.	nsubj	2	SENT_61	[p3l1600t960r1668b1012],
2	Enhanced	VBD	O	enhance	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1703t958r2001b1012],
3	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	4	SENT_61	[p3l2033t958r2148b1012],
4	bioavailability	NN	O	bioavailability	dobj	2	SENT_61	[p3l170t1053r595b1122],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l616t1053r680b1106],
6	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	prep_of	4	SENT_61	[p3l693t1053r979b1122],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l998t1053r1055b1105],
8	mice	NNS	O	mouse	prep_in	2	SENT_61	[p3l1074t1053r1216b1106],
9	treated	VBN	O	treat	partmod	8	SENT_61	[p3l1236t1053r1436b1106],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1455t1053r1585b1106],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_61	[p3l1604t1053r1692b1106],
12	P-glycoprotein	NN	MISC	p-glycoprotein	nn	15	SENT_61	[p3l1712t1053r2150b1122],
13	blocker	NN	O	blocker	nn	15	SENT_61	[p3l170t1146r398b1199],
14	SDZ	NN	O	sdz	nn	15	SENT_61	[p3l426t1147r566b1200],
15	PSC	NN	O	psc	prep_with	9	SENT_61	[p3l593t1147r724b1200],
16	833	CD	NUMBER	833	advmod	9	SENT_61	[p3l756t1147r880b1200],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l756t1147r880b1200],

1	Br	NN	O	br	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l909t1148r997b1199],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l909t1148r997b1199],

1	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	2	SENT_63	[p3l1030t1148r1075b1200],
2	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1113t1147r1334b1200],
3	1997	CD	DATE	1997	num	2	SENT_63	[p3l1362t1146r1524b1209],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1362t1146r1524b1209],
5	76	CD	NUMBER	76	num	2	SENT_63	[p3l1559t1146r1644b1209],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1559t1146r1644b1209],
7	1181-1183	CD	DATE	1181-1183	appos	2	SENT_63	[p3l1682t1147r2032b1200],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1682t1147r2032b1200],

1	(	NN	O	(	nn	5	SENT_64	[p3l47t1240r129b1306],
2	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	5	SENT_64	[p3l47t1240r129b1306],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	5	SENT_64	[p3l47t1240r129b1306],
4	Meerum	NNP	O	Meerum	nn	5	SENT_64	[p3l171t1241r427b1293],
5	Terwogt	NNP	O	Terwogt	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l463t1241r734b1309],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l463t1241r734b1309],
7	J	NNP	O	J	appos	5	SENT_64	[p3l773t1241r801b1293],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l808t1284r816b1293],

1	M.	NN	O	m.	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l856t1241r959b1303],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l856t1241r959b1303],
3	Beijnen	NNP	LOCATION	Beijnen	dep	1	SENT_65	[p3l999t1240r1249b1309],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l999t1240r1249b1309],
5	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	6	SENT_65	[p3l1288t1241r1331b1293],
6	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	appos	3	SENT_65	[p3l1372t1241r1462b1303],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1372t1241r1462b1303],
8	ten	CD	NUMBER	ten	num	10	SENT_65	[p3l1501t1247r1592b1293],
9	Bokkel	NNP	PERSON	Bokkel	nn	10	SENT_65	[p3l1629t1240r1846b1293],
10	Huinink	NNP	PERSON	Huinink	dep	1	SENT_65	[p3l1883t1240r2146b1303],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1883t1240r2146b1303],
12	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	13	SENT_65	[p3l170t1335r256b1387],
13	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	appos	10	SENT_65	[p3l311t1335r419b1397],
14	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l311t1335r419b1397],
15	Rosing	NNP	PERSON	Rosing	dep	1	SENT_65	[p3l473t1333r703b1402],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l473t1333r703b1402],
17	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	15	SENT_65	[p3l758t1335r847b1396],
18	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l758t1335r847b1396],
19	Schellens	NNP	O	Schellens	dep	1	SENT_65	[p3l905t1333r1208b1397],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l905t1333r1208b1397],
21	J	NNP	O	J	appos	19	SENT_65	[p3l1262t1335r1290b1387],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1296t1378r1305b1387],

1	H.	NNP	O	H.	nn	2	SENT_66	[p3l1361t1335r1429b1387],
2	Co	NNP	O	Co	nsubj	7	SENT_66	[p3l1486t1333r2035b1387],
3	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	4	SENT_66	[p3l1486t1333r2035b1387],
4	administration	NN	O	administration	dep	2	SENT_66	[p3l1486t1333r2035b1387],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l2088t1333r2154b1387],
6	cyclosporin	NN	O	cyclosporin	prep_of	2	SENT_66	[p3l172t1428r515b1497],
7	enables	VBZ	O	enable	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l534t1428r752b1481],
8	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	9	SENT_66	[p3l774t1428r886b1481],
9	therapy	NN	O	therapy	dobj	7	SENT_66	[p3l906t1428r1125b1497],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1146t1428r1276b1481],
11	paclitaxel	NN	O	paclitaxel	prep_with	7	SENT_66	[p3l1294t1428r1594b1497],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1294t1428r1594b1497],

1	Lancet	NNP	O	Lancet	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1616t1430r1820b1481],
2	1998	CD	DATE	1998	num	1	SENT_67	[p3l1840t1427r1999b1491],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1840t1427r1999b1491],
4	352	CD	NUMBER	352	num	1	SENT_67	[p3l2021t1428r2147b1491],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l2021t1428r2147b1491],
6	285	CD	NUMBER	285	appos	1	SENT_67	[p3l172t1521r300b1575],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l172t1521r300b1575],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l47t1616r129b1681],
2	6	CD	NUMBER	6	number	3	SENT_68	[p3l47t1616r129b1681],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_68	[p3l47t1616r129b1681],
4	Huisman	NNP	PERSON	Huisman	nn	7	SENT_68	[p3l171t1616r460b1678],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l171t1616r460b1678],
6	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	7	SENT_68	[p3l502t1617r583b1668],
7	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	dep	3	SENT_68	[p3l627t1617r708b1678],
8	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l627t1617r708b1678],
9	Smit	NNP	PERSON	Smit	dep	3	SENT_68	[p3l753t1616r909b1678],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l753t1616r909b1678],
11	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	12	SENT_68	[p3l952t1617r994b1669],
12	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	appos	9	SENT_68	[p3l1038t1617r1145b1678],
13	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l1038t1617r1145b1678],
14	Wiltshire	NNP	LOCATION	Wiltshire	dep	3	SENT_68	[p3l1188t1616r1485b1678],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l1188t1616r1485b1678],
16	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	17	SENT_68	[p3l1528t1617r1596b1668],
17	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	appos	14	SENT_68	[p3l1640t1617r1726b1678],
18	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l1640t1617r1726b1678],
19	Hoetelmans	NNP	PERSON	Hoetelmans	dep	3	SENT_68	[p3l1769t1616r2146b1678],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l1769t1616r2146b1678],
21	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	23	SENT_68	[p3l171t1710r235b1762],
22	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	23	SENT_68	[p3l266t1710r347b1762],
23	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	appos	19	SENT_68	[p3l378t1710r485b1771],
24	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l378t1710r485b1771],
25	Beijnen	NNP	PERSON	Beijnen	dep	3	SENT_68	[p3l516t1708r766b1777],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l516t1708r766b1777],
27	J	NNP	O	J	appos	25	SENT_68	[p3l796t1710r824b1762],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l830t1753r839b1762],

1	H.	NN	O	h.	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l871t1710r960b1771],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l871t1710r960b1771],
3	Schinkel	NNP	PERSON	Schinkel	conj_and	1	SENT_69	[p3l993t1708r1271b1772],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l993t1708r1271b1772],
5	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	8	SENT_69	[p3l1302t1709r1370b1762],
6	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	8	SENT_69	[p3l1401t1710r1469b1762],
7	P-glycoprotein	NN	PERSON	p-glycoprotein	nn	8	SENT_69	[p3l1500t1708r1950b1777],
8	limits	NNS	O	limit	conj_and	1	SENT_69	[p3l1978t1708r2147b1762],
9	oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	10	SENT_69	[p3l172t1803r287b1856],
10	availability	NN	O	availability	dep	8	SENT_69	[p3l318t1803r672b1872],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l318t1803r672b1872],
12	brain	NN	O	brain	conj_and	1	SENT_69	[p3l703t1803r874b1866],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l703t1803r874b1866],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l907t1803r1014b1856],
15	fetal	JJ	O	fetal	amod	16	SENT_69	[p3l1043t1803r1176b1856],
16	penetration	NN	O	penetration	conj_and	1	SENT_69	[p3l1204t1803r1544b1872],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1574t1803r1640b1856],
18	saquinavir	NN	O	saquinavir	prep_of	16	SENT_69	[p3l1666t1803r1979b1872],
19	even	RB	O	even	advmod	18	SENT_69	[p3l2008t1819r2149b1856],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l171t1896r304b1950],
21	high	JJ	O	high	amod	22	SENT_69	[p3l337t1896r471b1965],
22	doses	NNS	O	dose	prep_with	18	SENT_69	[p3l504t1896r669b1950],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l705t1896r770b1950],
24	ritonavir	NN	O	ritonavir	prep_of	22	SENT_69	[p3l797t1896r1073b1950],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l797t1896r1073b1950],

1	Mol	NNP	O	Mol	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1107t1896r1242b1950],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1107t1896r1242b1950],

1	Pharmacol	NNP	O	Pharmacol	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l1281t1896r1630b1950],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l1281t1896r1630b1950],

1	2001	CD	DATE	2001	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1670t1896r1836b1960],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1670t1896r1836b1960],
3	59	CD	NUMBER	59	appos	1	SENT_72	[p3l1872t1897r1962b1959],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l1872t1897r1962b1959],
5	806813	CD	NUMBER	806813	appos	3	SENT_72	[p3l2002t1896r2150b1950, p3l174t1991r301b2044],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l2002t1896r2150b1950, p3l174t1991r301b2044],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l47t2085r129b2149],
2	7	CD	NUMBER	7	number	3	SENT_73	[p3l47t2085r129b2149],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_73	[p3l47t2085r129b2149],
4	Nerurkar	NNP	PERSON	Nerurkar	nn	7	SENT_73	[p3l171t2084r459b2147],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l171t2084r459b2147],
6	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	7	SENT_73	[p3l498t2086r579b2137],
7	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	dep	3	SENT_73	[p3l619t2086r722b2147],
8	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l619t2086r722b2147],
9	Burton	NNP	PERSON	Burton	dep	3	SENT_73	[p3l761t2086r987b2147],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l761t2086r987b2147],
11	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	12	SENT_73	[p3l1026t2086r1081b2137],
12	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	appos	9	SENT_73	[p3l1124t2085r1198b2147],
13	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1124t2085r1198b2147],
14	Borchardt	NNP	PERSON	Borchardt	dep	1	SENT_73	[p3l1238t2084r1556b2147],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1238t2084r1556b2147],
16	R.	NNP	O	R.	nn	19	SENT_73	[p3l1595t2086r1659b2137],
17	T.	NNP	O	T.	nn	19	SENT_73	[p3l1699t2086r1759b2137],
18	The	NNP	O	The	nn	19	SENT_73	[p3l1799t2084r1914b2137],
19	use	NN	O	use	appos	14	SENT_73	[p3l1951t2101r2050b2137],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l2088t2084r2153b2137],
21	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_of	19	SENT_73	[p3l174t2178r488b2231],
22	to	TO	O	to	aux	23	SENT_73	[p3l509t2186r564b2231],
23	enhance	VB	O	enhance	infmod	21	SENT_73	[p3l585t2178r825b2231],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_73	[p3l845t2178r933b2231],
25	permeability	NN	O	permeability	dobj	23	SENT_73	[p3l952t2178r1324b2247],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1346t2178r1410b2231],
27	peptides	NNS	O	peptide	prep_of	25	SENT_73	[p3l1423t2178r1667b2247],
28	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1688t2178r1918b2247],
29	Caco-2	NN	O	caco-2	nn	30	SENT_73	[p3l1937t2178r2149b2231],
30	cells	NNS	O	cell	prep_through	23	SENT_73	[p3l172t2271r306b2325],
31	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l329t2271r404b2340],
32	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	prep_by	23	SENT_73	[p3l426t2271r719b2325],
33	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l742t2271r808b2325],
34	an	DT	O	a	det	38	SENT_73	[p3l826t2288r894b2325],
35	apically	RB	O	apically	amod	38	SENT_73	[p3l917t2271r1153b2340],
36	polarized	VBN	O	polarize	dep	35	SENT_73	[p3l1175t2271r1457b2340],
37	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	nn	38	SENT_73	[p3l1479t2271r1653b2325],
38	system	NN	O	system	prep_of	32	SENT_73	[p3l1678t2279r1899b2340],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1678t2279r1899b2340],

1	Pharm	NNP	O	Pharm	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1924t2271r2141b2325],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1924t2271r2141b2325],

1	Res	NNP	O	Res	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l169t2368r290b2419],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l169t2368r290b2419],

1	1996	CD	DATE	1996	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l329t2365r491b2428],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l329t2365r491b2428],
3	13	CD	NUMBER	13	appos	1	SENT_76	[p3l524t2366r611b2428],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l524t2366r611b2428],
5	528-534	CD	NUMBER	528-534	appos	3	SENT_76	[p3l642t2365r923b2419],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p3l642t2365r923b2419],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l47t2459r129b2524],
2	8	CD	NUMBER	8	number	3	SENT_77	[p3l47t2459r129b2524],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_77	[p3l47t2459r129b2524],
4	Lo	NNP	O	Lo	nn	7	SENT_77	[p3l171t2460r270b2522],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l171t2460r270b2522],
6	Y.	NNP	PERSON	Y.	appos	7	SENT_77	[p3l305t2460r373b2512],
7	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	dep	3	SENT_77	[p3l409t2460r491b2522],
8	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l409t2460r491b2522],
9	Hsu	NNP	PERSON	Hsu	dep	3	SENT_77	[p3l527t2460r663b2521],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l527t2460r663b2521],
11	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	12	SENT_77	[p3l699t2459r762b2512],
12	Y.	NNP	PERSON	Y.	appos	9	SENT_77	[p3l799t2460r888b2521],
13	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l799t2460r888b2521],
14	Huang	NNP	PERSON	Huang	dep	3	SENT_77	[p3l924t2460r1140b2527],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l924t2460r1140b2527],
16	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	18	SENT_77	[p3l1175t2460r1218b2512],
17	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	18	SENT_77	[p3l1255t2460r1322b2512],
18	Comparison	NN	PERSON	comparison	appos	14	SENT_77	[p3l1360t2458r1729b2527],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l1762t2458r1827b2512],
20	effects	NNS	O	effect	prep_of	18	SENT_77	[p3l1855t2458r2053b2512],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l2088t2458r2154b2512],
22	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_of	20	SENT_77	[p3l174t2553r496b2606],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l539t2553r672b2606],
24	other	JJ	O	other	amod	25	SENT_77	[p3l712t2553r867b2606],
25	MDR	NN	O	mdr	prep_with	22	SENT_77	[p3l905t2554r1077b2605],
26	reversing	VBG	O	reverse	partmod	1	SENT_77	[p3l1116t2553r1396b2622],
27	agents	NNS	O	agent	dobj	26	SENT_77	[p3l1439t2561r1628b2622],
28	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l1670t2569r1744b2606],
29	intracellular	JJ	O	intracellular	amod	30	SENT_77	[p3l1784t2553r2150b2606],
30	uptake	NN	O	uptake	prep_on	26	SENT_77	[p3l171t2646r371b2715],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l402t2646r468b2700],
32	epirubicin	NN	O	epirubicin	prep_of	30	SENT_77	[p3l494t2646r799b2715],
33	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l829t2646r886b2699],
34	Caco-2	NN	O	caco-2	nn	36	SENT_77	[p3l917t2647r1133b2700],
35	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	36	SENT_77	[p3l1164t2646r1270b2700],
36	line	NN	O	line	prep_in	32	SENT_77	[p3l1301t2646r1428b2700],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p3l1301t2646r1428b2700],

1	Anticancer	JJ	O	anticancer	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l1457t2647r1796b2700],
2	Res	NNP	O	Res	dep	1	SENT_78	[p3l1821t2648r1942b2700],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_78	[p3l1821t2648r1942b2700],

1	1998	CD	DATE	1998	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l1983t2646r2146b2709],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l1983t2646r2146b2709],
3	18	CD	NUMBER	18	appos	1	SENT_79	[p3l174t2740r261b2802],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l174t2740r261b2802],
5	3005-3009	CD	DURATION	3005-3009	appos	3	SENT_79	[p3l293t2740r648b2794],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_79	[p3l293t2740r648b2794],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_80	[p3l47t2834r129b2899],
2	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	4	SENT_80	[p3l47t2834r129b2899],
3	)	NN	O	)	nn	4	SENT_80	[p3l47t2834r129b2899],
4	Dintaman	NNP	O	Dintaman	dep	1	SENT_80	[p3l171t2833r485b2896],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_80	[p3l171t2833r485b2896],
6	J	NNP	O	J	appos	4	SENT_80	[p3l519t2835r547b2887],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_80	[p3l553t2878r562b2887],

1	M.	NN	O	m.	_	0	SENT_81	[p3l597t2835r700b2897],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_81	[p3l597t2835r700b2897],
3	Silverman	NNP	PERSON	Silverman	nn	5	SENT_81	[p3l737t2833r1061b2896],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_81	[p3l737t2833r1061b2896],
5	J	NNP	O	J	dep	1	SENT_81	[p3l1095t2835r1123b2887],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_81	[p3l1129t2878r1138b2887],

1	A.	NN	O	a.	nn	2	SENT_82	[p3l1173t2834r1241b2887],
2	Inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	_	0	SENT_82	[p3l1277t2833r1575b2887],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_82	[p3l1607t2833r1673b2887],
4	P-glycoprotein	NN	O	p-glycoprotein	prep_of	2	SENT_82	[p3l1699t2833r2149b2902],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_82	[p3l170t2928r243b2997],
6	D-alpha-tocopheryl	NN	O	d-alpha-tocopheryl	nn	8	SENT_82	[p3l264t2928r832b2997],
7	polyethylene	NN	O	polyethylene	nn	8	SENT_82	[p3l852t2928r1227b2997],
8	glycol	NN	O	glycol	prep_by	4	SENT_82	[p3l1248t2928r1428b2997],
9	1000	CD	DATE	1000	num	11	SENT_82	[p3l1456t2928r1594b2981],
10	succinate	JJ	O	succinate	amod	11	SENT_82	[p3l1617t2928r1883b2981],
11	(	NN	O	(	dep	2	SENT_82	[p3l1906t2928r2145b2994],
12	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	nn	13	SENT_82	[p3l1906t2928r2145b2994],
13	)	NN	O	)	dep	11	SENT_82	[p3l1906t2928r2145b2994],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_82	[p3l1906t2928r2145b2994],

1	Pharm	NNP	O	Pharm	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l170t3021r388b3074],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_83	[p3l170t3021r388b3074],

1	Res	NNP	O	Res	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l420t3023r541b3074],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_84	[p3l420t3023r541b3074],

1	1999	CD	DATE	1999	_	0	SENT_85	[p3l579t3021r742b3084],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_85	[p3l579t3021r742b3084],
3	16	CD	NUMBER	16	appos	1	SENT_85	[p3l774t3021r862b3084],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_85	[p3l774t3021r862b3084],
5	1550-1556	CD	DATE	1550-1556	appos	3	SENT_85	[p3l900t3021r1249b3075],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_85	[p3l900t3021r1249b3075],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l9t3115r129b3181],
2	10	CD	NUMBER	10	number	3	SENT_86	[p3l9t3115r129b3181],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_86	[p3l9t3115r129b3181],
4	Buckingham	NNP	LOCATION	Buckingham	nn	7	SENT_86	[p3l171t3115r573b3184],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l171t3115r573b3184],
6	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	appos	7	SENT_86	[p3l598t3116r658b3168],
7	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l684t3116r765b3178],
8	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l684t3116r765b3178],
9	Balasubramanian	NNP	PERSON	Balasubramanian	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l791t3115r1332b3178],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l791t3115r1332b3178],
11	M.	NNP	O	M.	appos	9	SENT_86	[p3l1357t3116r1460b3178],
12	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1357t3116r1460b3178],
13	Safa	NNP	O	Safa	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l1487t3115r1634b3178],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1487t3115r1634b3178],
15	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	16	SENT_86	[p3l1659t3115r1727b3168],
16	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	appos	13	SENT_86	[p3l1753t3116r1839b3178],
17	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1753t3116r1839b3178],
18	Shah	NNP	PERSON	Shah	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l1867t3115r2031b3178],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1867t3115r2031b3178],
20	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	18	SENT_86	[p3l2056t3116r2146b3178],
21	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l2056t3116r2146b3178],
22	Komarov	NNP	PERSON	Komarov	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l172t3210r472b3271],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l172t3210r472b3271],
24	P.	NNP	O	P.	appos	22	SENT_86	[p3l505t3210r583b3271],
25	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l505t3210r583b3271],
26	Emanuele	NNP	PERSON	Emanuele	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l616t3208r933b3271],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l616t3208r933b3271],
28	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	29	SENT_86	[p3l967t3210r1031b3261],
29	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	26	SENT_86	[p3l1065t3210r1167b3271],
30	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1065t3210r1167b3271],
31	Coon	NNP	PERSON	Coon	dep	3	SENT_86	[p3l1202t3209r1379b3271],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1202t3209r1379b3271],
33	J	NNP	O	J	appos	31	SENT_86	[p3l1412t3210r1440b3262],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_86	[p3l1446t3252r1455b3261],

1	S.	NNP	O	S.	nn	2	SENT_87	[p3l1491t3209r1545b3262],
2	Reversal	NN	O	reversal	_	0	SENT_87	[p3l1579t3208r1842b3261],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_87	[p3l1874t3208r1940b3261],
4	multidrug	JJ	O	multidrug	amod	5	SENT_87	[p3l1965t3208r2146b3261, p3l172t3302r307b3371],
5	resistance	NN	O	resistance	prep_of	2	SENT_87	[p3l330t3302r628b3355],
6	in	FW	O	in	nn	7	SENT_87	[p3l650t3302r707b3354],
7	vitro	FW	O	vitro	rcmod	5	SENT_87	[p3l730t3302r870b3355],
8	by	IN	O	by	dep	7	SENT_87	[p3l892t3302r966b3371],
9	fatty	NN	O	fatty	nn	12	SENT_87	[p3l990t3302r1126b3371],
10	acid-PEG-fatty	JJ	O	acid-peg-fatty	amod	12	SENT_87	[p3l1151t3302r1606b3371],
11	acid	NN	O	acid	nn	12	SENT_87	[p3l1631t3302r1754b3355],
12	diesters	NNS	O	diester	pobj	8	SENT_87	[p3l1777t3302r2021b3355],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_87	[p3l1777t3302r2021b3355],

1	Int	NN	O	int	_	0	SENT_88	[p3l2045t3304r2141b3355],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_88	[p3l2045t3304r2141b3355],

1	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	2	SENT_89	[p3l170t3397r215b3449],
2	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	_	0	SENT_89	[p3l253t3396r474b3449],
3	1996	CD	DATE	1996	num	2	SENT_89	[p3l501t3395r664b3458],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_89	[p3l501t3395r664b3458],
5	65	CD	NUMBER	65	num	2	SENT_89	[p3l695t3395r784b3458],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_89	[p3l695t3395r784b3458],
7	74-79	CD	NUMBER	74-79	appos	2	SENT_89	[p3l815t3396r1019b3449],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_89	[p3l815t3396r1019b3449],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l9t3489r129b3554],
2	11	CD	NUMBER	11	number	3	SENT_90	[p3l9t3489r129b3554],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_90	[p3l9t3489r129b3554],
4	Woodcock	NNP	PERSON	Woodcock	nn	7	SENT_90	[p3l170t3489r514b3552],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l170t3489r514b3552],
6	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	appos	7	SENT_90	[p3l541t3490r609b3542],
7	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l637t3490r739b3552],
8	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l637t3490r739b3552],
9	Jefferson	NNP	PERSON	Jefferson	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l766t3489r1059b3552],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l766t3489r1059b3552],
11	S.	NNP	O	S.	appos	9	SENT_90	[p3l1088t3489r1163b3552],
12	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1088t3489r1163b3552],
13	Linsenmeyer	NNP	PERSON	Linsenmeyer	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l1190t3489r1601b3558],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1190t3489r1601b3558],
15	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	16	SENT_90	[p3l1627t3490r1708b3542],
16	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	appos	13	SENT_90	[p3l1736t3490r1818b3552],
17	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1736t3490r1818b3552],
18	Crowther	NNP	PERSON	Crowther	dep	3	SENT_90	[p3l1846t3489r2146b3552],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l1846t3489r2146b3552],
20	P.	NNP	O	P.	nn	21	SENT_90	[p3l171t3584r226b3636],
21	J	NNP	O	J	appos	18	SENT_90	[p3l255t3584r283b3636],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_90	[p3l289t3599r320b3645],

1	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l289t3599r320b3645],
2	Chojnowski	NNP	PERSON	Chojnowski	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l350t3582r730b3651],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l350t3582r730b3651],
4	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	5	SENT_91	[p3l759t3583r826b3636],
5	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	2	SENT_91	[p3l855t3584r958b3645],
6	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l855t3584r958b3645],
7	Williams	NNP	PERSON	Williams	dep	2	SENT_91	[p3l985t3582r1278b3646],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l985t3582r1278b3646],
9	B.	NNP	O	B.	appos	7	SENT_91	[p3l1307t3584r1392b3646],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l1307t3584r1392b3646],
11	Bertoncello	NNP	O	Bertoncello	dep	2	SENT_91	[p3l1421t3582r1789b3646],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l1421t3582r1789b3646],
13	I.	NNP	O	I.	nn	14	SENT_91	[p3l1817t3584r1856b3636],
14	Reversal	NN	O	reversal	appos	11	SENT_91	[p3l1885t3582r2149b3636],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l172t3677r238b3730],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_91	[p3l272t3677r362b3730],
17	multidrug	JJ	O	multidrug	amod	19	SENT_91	[p3l402t3677r699b3746],
18	resistance	NN	O	resistance	nn	19	SENT_91	[p3l738t3677r1036b3730],
19	phenotype	NN	O	phenotype	prep_of	2	SENT_91	[p3l1075t3677r1389b3746],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l1429t3677r1563b3730],
21	cremophor	NN	O	cremophor	nn	22	SENT_91	[p3l1602t3677r1930b3746],
22	EL	NN	O	el	prep_with	19	SENT_91	[p3l1967t3678r2075b3740],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_91	[p3l1967t3678r2075b3740],
24	a	DT	O	a	det	26	SENT_91	[p3l2118t3693r2150b3730],
25	common	JJ	O	common	amod	26	SENT_91	[p4l172t36r435b73],
26	vehicle	NN	O	vehicle	appos	22	SENT_91	[p4l456t19r673b73],
27	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_91	[p4l694t19r782b73],
28	water	NN	O	water	npadvmod	30	SENT_91	[p4l802t19r1271b73],
29	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	28	SENT_91	[p4l802t19r1271b73],
30	insoluble	JJ	O	insoluble	amod	31	SENT_91	[p4l802t19r1271b73],
31	vitamins	NNS	O	vitamin	prep_for	26	SENT_91	[p4l1293t19r1551b73],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_91	[p4l1575t19r1681b73],
33	drugs	NNS	O	drug	prep_for	26	SENT_91	[p4l1703t19r1883b88],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_91	[p4l1703t19r1883b88],

1	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	_	0	SENT_92	[p4l1912t20r2142b73],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_92	[p4l1912t20r2142b73],

1	Res	NNP	O	Res	_	0	SENT_93	[p4l169t116r290b167],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_93	[p4l169t116r290b167],

1	1990	CD	DATE	1990	_	0	SENT_94	[p4l329t113r491b176],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_94	[p4l329t113r491b176],
3	50	CD	NUMBER	50	appos	1	SENT_94	[p4l521t114r611b176],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_94	[p4l521t114r611b176],
5	4199-4203	CD	DURATION	4199-4203	appos	3	SENT_94	[p4l641t114r999b168],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_94	[p4l641t114r999b168],

1	644	CD	NUMBER	644	_	0	SENT_95	[p4l8t262r123b314],
2	MOLECULAR	NNP	O	MOLECULAR	nn	4	SENT_95	[p4l229t259r678b314],
3	PHARMACEUTICS	NNP	O	PHARMACEUTICS	nn	4	SENT_95	[p4l709t259r1329b314],
4	VOL	NNP	O	VOL	dep	1	SENT_95	[p4l1372t259r1528b314],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_95	[p4l1372t259r1528b314],

1	5	CD	NUMBER	5	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1560t263r1612b321],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1560t263r1612b321],
3	NO.	NNP	O	NO.	appos	1	SENT_96	[p4l1647t259r1763b314],
4	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	3	SENT_96	[p4l1794t262r1830b313],
5	poly	NN	O	poly	nn	7	SENT_96	[p4l6t358r676b439],
6	(	NN	O	(	nn	7	SENT_96	[p4l6t358r676b439],
7	caprolactone	NN	O	caprolactone	nsubjpass	58	SENT_96	[p4l6t358r676b439],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	9	SENT_96	[p4l6t358r676b439],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_96	[p4l710t359r947b435],
10	PCL	NN	O	pcl	nn	11	SENT_96	[p4l710t359r947b435],
11	)	NN	O	)	dep	7	SENT_96	[p4l710t359r947b435],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l710t359r947b435],
13	MePEG	NN	O	mepeg	nn	15	SENT_96	[p4l979t358r1551b432],
14	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	15	SENT_96	[p4l979t358r1551b432],
15	b-PCL	NN	O	b-pcl	appos	7	SENT_96	[p4l979t358r1551b432],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l979t358r1551b432],
17	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	19	SENT_96	[p4l1583t358r1716b420],
18	are	VBP	O	be	cop	19	SENT_96	[p4l1745t378r1849b420],
19	capable	JJ	O	capable	rcmod	7	SENT_96	[p4l1878t358r2148b439],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l8t467r84b529],
21	increasing	VBG	O	increase	prepc_of	19	SENT_96	[p4l102t467r461b547],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_96	[p4l486t467r591b529],
23	cellular	JJ	O	cellular	amod	24	SENT_96	[p4l616t467r879b529],
24	accumulation	NN	O	accumulation	dobj	21	SENT_96	[p4l903t467r1375b529],
25	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1399t467r1524b529],
26	decreasing	VBG	O	decrease	prepc_of	19	SENT_96	[p4l1548t467r1921b547],
27	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	nn	28	SENT_96	[p4l1947t467r2149b529],
28	transport	NN	O	transport	dobj	26	SENT_96	[p4l7t584r314b655],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l336t575r412b637],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_96	[p4l428t575r532b637],
31	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	32	SENT_96	[p4l555t576r717b655],
32	substrate	NN	O	substrate	prep_of	28	SENT_96	[p4l743t575r1064b648],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l743t575r1064b648],
34	rhodamine	NN	O	rhodamine	appos	32	SENT_96	[p4l1089t575r1459b637],
35	123	CD	NUMBER	123	number	36	SENT_96	[p4l1491t575r1607b637],
36	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	37	SENT_96	[p4l1637t575r1898b651],
37	R-123	NN	O	r-123	dep	34	SENT_96	[p4l1637t575r1898b651],
38	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1637t575r1898b651],
39	Figure	NNP	O	Figure	dep	34	SENT_96	[p4l1924t575r2149b655],
40	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	41	SENT_96	[p4l15t668r242b762],
41	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	39	SENT_96	[p4l15t668r242b762],
42	.14	CD	NUMBER	.14	num	48	SENT_96	[p4l15t668r242b762],
43	’15	CD	NUMBER	’15	num	48	SENT_96	[p4l15t668r242b762],
44	Currently	NNP	DATE	Currently	nn	48	SENT_96	[p4l269t684r618b766],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l269t684r618b766],
46	several	JJ	O	several	amod	48	SENT_96	[p4l647t684r889b747],
47	potential	JJ	O	potential	amod	48	SENT_96	[p4l911t684r1214b765],
48	mechanisms	NNS	O	mechanism	dep	41	SENT_96	[p4l1237t684r1665b747],
49	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1691t684r1792b747],
50	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	prep_for	26	SENT_96	[p4l1813t684r2150b747],
51	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l8t792r85b854],
52	P-gp	JJ	O	p-gp	amod	53	SENT_96	[p4l108t793r273b872],
53	efﬂux	NN	O	efﬂux	prep_of	50	SENT_96	[p4l304t792r509b854],
54	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l537t792r625b872],
55	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_by	26	SENT_96	[p4l658t792r1037b854],
56	have	VBP	O	have	aux	58	SENT_96	[p4l1068t792r1234b854],
57	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	58	SENT_96	[p4l1263t792r1430b854],
58	proposed	VBN	O	propose	dep	1	SENT_96	[p4l1458t792r1785b872],
59	including	VBG	O	include	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1813t792r2147b872],
60	alterations	NNS	O	alteration	prep_including	58	SENT_96	[p4l9t899r374b961],
61	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l403t899r471b961],
62	membrane	NN	O	membrane	nn	63	SENT_96	[p4l498t899r872b961],
63	ﬂuidity	NN	O	ﬂuidity	prep_in	60	SENT_96	[p4l900t899r1174b980],
64	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l900t899r1174b980],
65	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	dep	82	SENT_96	[p4l1204t899r1550b961],
66	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1577t899r1654b961],
67	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	69	SENT_96	[p4l1675t901r1840b980],
68	ATPase	NN	MISC	atpase	nn	69	SENT_96	[p4l1868t900r2148b961],
69	activity	NN	O	activity	prep_of	65	SENT_96	[p4l9t1008r288b1089],
70	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l9t1008r288b1089],
71	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l318t1008r442b1071],
72	depletion	NN	O	depletion	conj_and	65	SENT_96	[p4l467t1008r793b1089],
73	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l818t1008r895b1071],
74	cellular	JJ	O	cellular	amod	76	SENT_96	[p4l914t1008r1177b1071],
75	ATP	NN	O	atp	nn	76	SENT_96	[p4l1199t1009r1365b1070],
76	stores	NNS	O	store	prep_of	72	SENT_96	[p4l1392t991r1781b1071],
77	.16	CD	NUMBER	.16	number	78	SENT_96	[p4l1392t991r1781b1071],
78	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	num	79	SENT_96	[p4l1392t991r1781b1071],
79	2O	NN	O	2o	dep	82	SENT_96	[p4l1392t991r1781b1071],
80	However	RB	O	however	advmod	79	SENT_96	[p4l1805t1010r2147b1083],
81	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1805t1010r2147b1083],
82	understanding	VBG	O	understand	dep	1	SENT_96	[p4l6t1117r510b1197],
83	the	DT	O	the	det	84	SENT_96	[p4l538t1117r644b1179],
84	mechanisms	NNS	O	mechanism	nsubjpass	92	SENT_96	[p4l672t1117r1109b1179],
85	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1140t1117r1216b1179],
86	action	NN	O	action	prep_of	84	SENT_96	[p4l1240t1117r1454b1179],
87	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l1481t1117r1584b1179],
88	P-gp	JJ	O	p-gp	amod	89	SENT_96	[p4l1609t1118r1775b1197],
89	inhibition	NN	O	inhibition	prep_for	86	SENT_96	[p4l1803t1117r2149b1179],
90	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	92	SENT_96	[p4l6t1225r121b1287],
91	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	92	SENT_96	[p4l181t1225r349b1287],
92	hampered	VBN	O	hamper	ccomp	82	SENT_96	[p4l407t1225r758b1305],
93	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l814t1225r902b1306],
94	seemingly	RB	O	seemingly	advmod	95	SENT_96	[p4l964t1225r1326b1306],
95	contradictory	JJ	O	contradictory	amod	96	SENT_96	[p4l1386t1225r1858b1306],
96	results	NNS	O	result	agent	92	SENT_96	[p4l1917t1225r2146b1287],
97	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l6t1333r302b1395],
98	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_between	96	SENT_96	[p4l356t1333r756b1395],
99	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_96	[p4l356t1333r756b1395],

1	MePEG-I9-PCL	NN	O	mepeg-i9-pcl	nn	3	SENT_97	[p4l812t1333r1365b1395],
2	diblock	NN	O	diblock	nn	3	SENT_97	[p4l1418t1333r1684b1395],
3	copolymers	NNS	O	copolymer	nsubjpass	5	SENT_97	[p4l1735t1333r2146b1413],
4	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_97	[p4l7t1461r177b1503],
5	shown	VBN	O	show	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l207t1441r434b1503],
6	to	TO	O	to	aux	7	SENT_97	[p4l460t1450r525b1503],
7	stimulate	VB	O	stimulate	xcomp	5	SENT_97	[p4l557t1441r875b1503],
8	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	10	SENT_97	[p4l903t1443r1066b1522],
9	ATPase	NN	MISC	atpase	nn	10	SENT_97	[p4l1095t1442r1373b1503],
10	activity	NN	O	activity	dobj	7	SENT_97	[p4l1402t1441r1662b1522],
11	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l1692t1451r1753b1503],
12	concentrations	NNS	O	concentration	nsubj	13	SENT_97	[p4l1779t1451r2147b1503, p4l7t1549r172b1611],
13	corresponding	VBG	O	correspond	dep	18	SENT_97	[p4l201t1549r697b1629],
14	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l725t1549r878b1611],
15	enhanced	VBN	O	enhance	amod	16	SENT_97	[p4l905t1549r1233b1611],
16	R-123	NN	MISC	r-123	prep_with	13	SENT_97	[p4l1259t1549r1471b1611],
17	cellular	JJ	O	cellular	amod	18	SENT_97	[p4l1502t1549r1763b1611],
18	accumulation	NN	O	accumulation	prep_at	7	SENT_97	[p4l1789t1549r2147b1611, p4l7t1641r227b1719],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_97	[p4l1789t1549r2147b1611, p4l7t1641r227b1719],

1	”	NN	O	”	nsubj	10	SENT_98	[p4l1789t1549r2147b1611, p4l7t1641r227b1719],
2	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l257t1659r329b1719],
3	contrast	NN	O	contrast	prep_in	10	SENT_98	[p4l354t1667r651b1731],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l354t1667r651b1731],
5	Pluronics	NNP	PERSON	Pluronics	conj_and	3	SENT_98	[p4l679t1657r1012b1719],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1040t1657r1165b1719],
7	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	9	SENT_98	[p4l1189t1657r1459b1720],
8	E	NN	O	e	nn	9	SENT_98	[p4l1483t1659r1536b1719],
9	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	conj_and	3	SENT_98	[p4l1560t1658r1772b1720],
10	decreased	VBD	O	decrease	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1801t1657r2150b1719],
11	P-gp	JJ	MISC	p-gp	amod	13	SENT_98	[p4l7t1767r172b1846],
12	ATPase	NN	MISC	atpase	nn	13	SENT_98	[p4l198t1765r477b1828],
13	activity	NN	O	activity	dobj	10	SENT_98	[p4l504t1748r938b1846],
14	.16	CD	NUMBER	.16	number	15	SENT_98	[p4l504t1748r938b1846],
15	’18	CD	NUMBER	’18	num	16	SENT_98	[p4l504t1748r938b1846],
16	Differences	NNS	O	difference	nsubjpass	24	SENT_98	[p4l965t1765r1377b1828],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1403t1765r1470b1827],
18	membrane	NN	O	membrane	nn	20	SENT_98	[p4l1495t1765r1869b1828],
19	ﬂuidity	NN	O	ﬂuidity	nn	20	SENT_98	[p4l1895t1765r2149b1846],
20	changes	NNS	O	change	prep_in	16	SENT_98	[p4l8t1874r289b1955],
21	have	VBP	O	have	aux	24	SENT_98	[p4l314t1874r480b1936],
22	also	RB	O	also	advmod	24	SENT_98	[p4l507t1874r644b1936],
23	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	24	SENT_98	[p4l668t1874r836b1936],
24	observed	VBN	O	observe	rcmod	13	SENT_98	[p4l861t1874r1179b1936],
25	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1203t1874r1359b1936],
26	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_with	24	SENT_98	[p4l1385t1874r1783b1948],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1385t1874r1783b1948],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1813t1874r1938b1936],
29	it	PRP	O	it	nsubjpass	32	SENT_98	[p4l1961t1874r2009b1936],
30	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	32	SENT_98	[p4l2032t1874r2147b1936],
31	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	32	SENT_98	[p4l6t1982r173b2044],
32	shown	VBN	O	show	conj_and	10	SENT_98	[p4l214t1982r442b2044],
33	that	IN	O	that	complm	42	SENT_98	[p4l480t1982r613b2044],
34	Cremophor	NNP	O	Cremophor	nn	35	SENT_98	[p4l650t1982r1055b2062],
35	EL	NNP	O	EL	nsubj	42	SENT_98	[p4l1091t1983r1217b2055],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1091t1983r1217b2055],
37	Tween	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tween	nsubj	42	SENT_98	[p4l1258t1983r1499b2044],
38	80	CD	NUMBER	80	num	37	SENT_98	[p4l1540t1982r1642b2055],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1540t1982r1642b2055],
40	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1685t1982r1811b2044],
41	Pluronic	NNP	O	Pluronic	nsubj	42	SENT_98	[p4l1848t1982r2147b2044],
42	increased	VBD	O	increase	ccomp	32	SENT_98	[p4l7t2090r343b2152],
43	membrane	NN	O	membrane	nn	44	SENT_98	[p4l383t2090r758b2152],
44	ﬂuidity	NN	O	ﬂuidity	dobj	42	SENT_98	[p4l801t2090r1075b2171],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l801t2090r1075b2171],
46	while	IN	O	while	mark	52	SENT_98	[p4l1120t2090r1316b2152],
47	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	49	SENT_98	[p4l1358t2090r1629b2152],
48	E	NN	O	e	nn	49	SENT_98	[p4l1669t2092r1722b2151],
49	TPGS	NN	O	tpg	nsubj	52	SENT_98	[p4l1764t2091r1975b2153],
50	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l2024t2090r2149b2152],
51	MePEG-I9-PCL	NN	O	mepeg-i9-pcl	nsubj	52	SENT_98	[p4l7t2198r559b2260],
52	had	VBD	O	have	advcl	42	SENT_98	[p4l586t2198r714b2260],
53	no	DT	O	no	det	54	SENT_98	[p4l740t2217r826b2260],
54	effect	NN	O	effect	dobj	52	SENT_98	[p4l855t2198r1056b2260],
55	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_98	[p4l1083t2217r1155b2260],
56	decreased	VBN	O	decrease	amod	58	SENT_98	[p4l1182t2198r1531b2260],
57	membrane	NN	O	membrane	nn	58	SENT_98	[p4l1558t2198r1930b2260],
58	ﬂuid	NN	O	ﬂuid	dobj	52	SENT_98	[p4l1960t2198r2147b2260, p4l9t2446r127b2512],
59	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	60	SENT_98	[p4l1960t2198r2147b2260, p4l9t2446r127b2512],
60	12	CD	NUMBER	12	dep	54	SENT_98	[p4l1960t2198r2147b2260, p4l9t2446r127b2512],
61	)	NN	O	)	dep	60	SENT_98	[p4l1960t2198r2147b2260, p4l9t2446r127b2512],

1	Woodcock	NNP	PERSON	Woodcock	nn	4	SENT_99	[p4l167t2446r506b2509],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l167t2446r506b2509],
3	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	appos	4	SENT_99	[p4l528t2447r596b2499],
4	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l619t2447r720b2509],
5	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l619t2447r720b2509],
6	Linsenmeyer	NNP	PERSON	Linsenmeyer	dep	4	SENT_99	[p4l743t2446r1147b2515],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l743t2446r1147b2515],
8	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	9	SENT_99	[p4l1169t2447r1249b2499],
9	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	appos	6	SENT_99	[p4l1273t2447r1353b2509],
10	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1273t2447r1353b2509],
11	Chojnowski	NNP	PERSON	Chojnowski	dep	4	SENT_99	[p4l1377t2446r1750b2515],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1377t2446r1750b2515],
13	G.	NNP	O	G.	appos	11	SENT_99	[p4l1774t2446r1861b2509],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1774t2446r1861b2509],
15	Kriegler	NNP	PERSON	Kriegler	dep	4	SENT_99	[p4l1886t2446r2147b2515],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1886t2446r2147b2515],
17	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	18	SENT_99	[p4l171t2540r239b2593],
18	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	appos	15	SENT_99	[p4l279t2541r365b2602],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l279t2541r365b2602],
20	Nink	NNP	O	Nink	dep	4	SENT_99	[p4l404t2539r570b2603],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l404t2539r570b2603],
22	V.	NNP	O	V.	appos	20	SENT_99	[p4l609t2541r699b2603],
23	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l609t2541r699b2603],
24	Webster	NNP	PERSON	Webster	dep	4	SENT_99	[p4l738t2539r1006b2602],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l738t2539r1006b2602],
26	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	nn	27	SENT_99	[p4l1044t2541r1104b2593],
27	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	appos	24	SENT_99	[p4l1146t2541r1234b2603],
28	;	:	PERSON	;	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1146t2541r1234b2603],
29	Sawyer	NNP	PERSON	Sawyer	dep	4	SENT_99	[p4l1275t2540r1515b2608],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l1275t2540r1515b2608],
31	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	33	SENT_99	[p4l1554t2541r1639b2593],
32	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	33	SENT_99	[p4l1680t2541r1747b2593],
33	Reversal	NN	PERSON	reversal	appos	29	SENT_99	[p4l1787t2539r2051b2593],
34	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l2088t2539r2154b2593],
35	multidrug	JJ	O	multidrug	amod	36	SENT_99	[p4l171t2634r468b2703],
36	resistance	NN	O	resistance	prep_of	33	SENT_99	[p4l493t2634r791b2687],
37	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l815t2634r889b2703],
38	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_by	36	SENT_99	[p4l917t2634r1256b2687],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_99	[p4l917t2634r1256b2687],

1	Br	NN	O	br	_	0	SENT_100	[p4l1283t2636r1371b2687],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_100	[p4l1283t2636r1371b2687],

1	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	2	SENT_101	[p4l1401t2636r1447b2688],
2	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	_	0	SENT_101	[p4l1482t2635r1703b2688],
3	1992	CD	DATE	1992	num	2	SENT_101	[p4l1729t2633r1891b2697],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_101	[p4l1729t2633r1891b2697],
5	66	CD	NUMBER	66	num	2	SENT_101	[p4l1920t2633r2009b2697],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_101	[p4l1920t2633r2009b2697],
7	6268	CD	NUMBER	6268	appos	2	SENT_101	[p4l2038t2634r2150b2687, p4l172t2726r262b2780],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_101	[p4l2038t2634r2150b2687, p4l172t2726r262b2780],

1	(	RB	O	(	advmod	2	SENT_102	[p4l9t2822r129b2887],
2	13	CD	NUMBER	13	_	0	SENT_102	[p4l9t2822r129b2887],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	6	SENT_102	[p4l9t2822r129b2887],
4	Bogman	NNP	O	Bogman	nn	6	SENT_102	[p4l171t2823r442b2891],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p4l171t2823r442b2891],
6	K.	NNP	O	K.	dep	2	SENT_102	[p4l477t2823r566b2885],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_102	[p4l477t2823r566b2885],
8	Eme-Brand	NNP	O	Eme-Brand	dep	2	SENT_102	[p4l599t2822r968b2885],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p4l599t2822r968b2885],
10	F.	NNP	O	F.	appos	8	SENT_102	[p4l1000t2823r1078b2885],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_102	[p4l1000t2823r1078b2885],
12	Alsenz	NNP	PERSON	Alsenz	dep	2	SENT_102	[p4l1111t2822r1336b2885],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p4l1111t2822r1336b2885],
14	J	NNP	O	J	appos	12	SENT_102	[p4l1369t2823r1397b2875],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_102	[p4l1403t2839r1434b2885],

1	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_103	[p4l1403t2839r1434b2885],
2	Drewe	NNP	PERSON	Drewe	_	0	SENT_103	[p4l1468t2823r1684b2885],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_103	[p4l1468t2823r1684b2885],
4	J	NNP	O	J	appos	2	SENT_103	[p4l1717t2823r1745b2875],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_103	[p4l1751t2866r1760b2875],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_104	[p4l1795t2822r1910b2875],
2	role	NN	O	role	nsubj	11	SENT_104	[p4l1940t2822r2057b2875],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_104	[p4l2088t2822r2154b2875],
4	surfactants	NNS	O	surfactant	prep_of	2	SENT_104	[p4l174t2915r496b2969],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_104	[p4l549t2915r606b2968],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_104	[p4l657t2915r747b2969],
7	reversal	NN	O	reversal	prep_in	4	SENT_104	[p4l797t2915r1036b2969],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_104	[p4l1088t2915r1153b2969],
9	active	JJ	O	active	amod	10	SENT_104	[p4l1201t2915r1378b2969],
10	transport	NN	O	transport	prep_of	7	SENT_104	[p4l1429t2923r1698b2984],
11	mediated	VBN	O	mediate	_	0	SENT_104	[p4l1748t2915r2024b2969],
12	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_104	[p4l2074t2915r2148b2984],
13	multidrug	JJ	O	multidrug	amod	15	SENT_104	[p4l171t3010r462b3079],
14	resistance	NN	O	resistance	nn	15	SENT_104	[p4l481t3010r772b3063],
15	proteins	NNS	O	protein	prep_by	11	SENT_104	[p4l790t3010r1043b3079],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_104	[p4l790t3010r1043b3079],

1	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	2	SENT_105	[p4l1064t3012r1109b3064],
2	Pharm	NNP	PERSON	Pharm	_	0	SENT_105	[p4l1134t3010r1348b3063],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_105	[p4l1134t3010r1348b3063],

1	Sci	NNP	O	Sci	_	0	SENT_106	[p4l1375t3011r1475b3064],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_106	[p4l1375t3011r1475b3064],

1	2003	CD	DATE	2003	_	0	SENT_107	[p4l1501t3009r1664b3073],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_107	[p4l1501t3009r1664b3073],
3	92	CD	NUMBER	92	appos	1	SENT_107	[p4l1687t3010r1775b3073],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_107	[p4l1687t3010r1775b3073],
5	1250-1261	CD	DATE	1250-1261	appos	3	SENT_107	[p4l1804t3010r2145b3063],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_107	[p4l1804t3010r2145b3063],
