1	Int	NN	O	int	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l79t82r128b108],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l79t82r128b108],

1	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	2	SENT_2	[p1l139t82r164b108],
2	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l177t82r296b108],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l177t82r296b108],
4	118	CD	NUMBER	118	dep	2	SENT_2	[p1l310t81r372b114],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l310t81r372b114],
6	2281-2284	CD	DATE	2281-2284	number	7	SENT_2	[p1l383t82r550b108],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	appos	2	SENT_2	[p1l562t81r658b114],
8	2006	CD	DATE	2006	dep	7	SENT_2	[p1l562t81r658b114],
9	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	10	SENT_2	[p1l562t81r658b114],
10	©	CD	NUMBER	©	dep	2	SENT_2	[p1l81t128r105b152],
11	2005	CD	DATE	2005	num	14	SENT_2	[p1l125t126r196b152],
12	Wiley-Liss	NNP	O	Wiley-Liss	nn	14	SENT_2	[p1l208t126r382b160],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l208t126r382b160],
14	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	dep	10	SENT_2	[p1l394t127r448b152],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l394t127r448b152],

1	Tamoxifen	NN	MISC	tamoxifen	nn	5	SENT_3	[p1l81t234r328b272],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l357t235r441b272],
3	contralateral	JJ	O	contralateral	conj_and	1	SENT_3	[p1l471t235r769b272],
4	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	5	SENT_3	[p1l799t235r941b272],
5	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nsubj	13	SENT_3	[p1l970t246r1120b272],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1150t234r1193b271],
7	BRCA1	NN	O	brca1	nn	10	SENT_3	[p1l1220t234r1387b272],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1420t235r1504b272],
9	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	nn	10	SENT_3	[p1l1531t234r1700b272],
10	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	prep_in	5	SENT_3	[p1l81t296r277b335],
11	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l81t296r277b335],
12	an	DT	O	a	dep	10	SENT_3	[p1l310t308r364b335],
13	update	VBP	O	update	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l394t297r550b345],

1	Jacek	NNP	PERSON	Jacek	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l80t382r171b411],
2	Gronwaldl	NNP	PERSON	Gronwaldl	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l184t374r367b415],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l184t374r367b415],
4	Nadine	NNP	PERSON	Nadine	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l380t382r492b409],
5	Tungz	NNP	PERSON	Tungz	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l505t374r612b416],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l505t374r612b416],
7	William	NNP	PERSON	William	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l625t382r752b409],
8	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l765t382r799b409],
9	Foulkes3	NN	PERSON	foulkes3	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l812t374r958b415],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l812t374r958b415],
11	Kenneth	NNP	PERSON	Kenneth	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l972t382r1107b409],
12	Ofﬁt4	NNP	PERSON	Ofﬁt4	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1120t374r1216b415],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1120t374r1216b415],
14	Ruth	NNP	PERSON	Ruth	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1229t382r1308b409],
15	Gershonis	NNP	PERSON	Gershonis	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1322t374r1490b415],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1322t374r1490b415],
17	Mary	NNP	PERSON	Mary	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1503t382r1591b416],
18	Daly6	NNP	PERSON	Daly6	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1604t374r1700b416],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1604t374r1700b416],
20	Charmaine	NNP	PERSON	Charmaine	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1714t382r1892b409],
21	Kim-Sing7	NNP	PERSON	Kim-Sing7	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1905t374r2080b416],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1905t374r2080b416],
23	Hakan	NNP	PERSON	Hakan	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t424r187b450],
24	Olssons	NNP	PERSON	Olssons	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l201t416r329b457],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l201t416r329b457],
26	Peter	NNP	PERSON	Peter	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l342t424r426b450],
27	Ainsworthg	NNP	PERSON	Ainsworthg	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l439t416r628b457],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l439t416r628b457],
29	Andrea	NNP	PERSON	Andrea	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l641t424r760b450],
30	Eisenm	NNP	PERSON	Eisenm	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l773t416r896b457],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l773t416r896b457],
32	Howard	NNP	PERSON	Howard	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l909t424r1038b450],
33	Saalll	NNP	PERSON	Saalll	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1051t416r1154b457],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1051t416r1154b457],
35	Eitan	NNP	PERSON	Eitan	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1168t424r1253b450],
36	Friedman	NNP	PERSON	Friedman	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1266t416r1460b457],
37	”	NNP	O	”	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1266t416r1460b457],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1266t416r1460b457],
39	Olufunmilayo	NNP	O	Olufunmilayo	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1473t424r1693b458],
40	Olopade13	NNP	O	Olopade13	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1707t416r1877b458],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1707t416r1877b458],
42	Michael	NNP	PERSON	Michael	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t465r208b492],
43	Osborne	NNP	PERSON	Osborne	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l222t457r394b498],
44	“	NNP	O	“	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l222t457r394b498],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l222t457r394b498],
46	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	Jeffrey	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l406t465r518b500],
47	Weitzells	NNP	PERSON	Weitzells	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l530t457r687b498],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l530t457r687b498],
49	Henry	NNP	PERSON	Henry	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l700t466r801b500],
50	Lynch	NNP	PERSON	Lynch	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l813t457r950b500],
51	“	NNP	O	“	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l813t457r950b500],
52	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l813t457r950b500],
53	Parviz	NNP	PERSON	Parviz	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l964t466r1066b492],
54	Ghadirian	NNP	PERSON	Ghadirian	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1080t457r1281b498],
55	”	NN	O	”	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1080t457r1281b498],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1080t457r1281b498],
57	Jan	NNP	PERSON	Jan	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1293t466r1350b495],
58	Lubinskil	NNP	PERSON	Lubinskil	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1363t457r1527b498],
59	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1363t457r1527b498],
60	Ping	NNP	PERSON	Ping	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1541t465r1612b499],
61	Sunls	NNP	PERSON	Sunls	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1625t457r1722b498],
62	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1625t457r1722b498],
63	Steven	NNP	PERSON	Steven	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t507r185b534],
64	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l198t507r232b534],
65	Narod18	NNP	O	Narod18	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l245t499r391b534],
66	*	NN	O	*	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l245t499r391b534],
67	and	CC	O	and	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l405t508r463b534],
68	The	DT	O	the	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l476t507r536b534],
69	Hereditary	JJ	O	hereditary	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l550t507r725b541],
70	Breast	NN	O	breast	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l738t507r840b534],
71	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l854t507r967b534],
72	Clinical	JJ	O	clinical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l981t507r1104b534],
73	Study	NNP	O	Study	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1117t507r1208b541],
74	Group	NNP	O	Group	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1221t507r1325b541],
75	1Hereditary	NNP	O	1Hereditary	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t553r258b594],
76	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l273t561r382b587],
77	Center	NNP	O	Center	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l397t561r505b591],
78	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l397t561r505b591],
79	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l519t562r699b594],
80	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l713t561r747b594],
81	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l756t561r885b587],
82	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l900t561r956b587],
83	Pathology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pathology	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l968t561r1130b594],
84	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l968t561r1130b594],
85	Pomeranian	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pomeranian	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1145t562r1330b587],
86	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1343t561r1467b587],
87	Academy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Academy	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1479t561r1625b594],
88	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1479t561r1625b594],
89	Szczecin	NNP	LOCATION	Szczecin	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1641t561r1775b591],
90	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1641t561r1775b591],
91	Poland	NNP	LOCATION	Poland	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1790t561r1900b587],
92	2Beth	NNP	O	2Beth	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t594r162b629],
93	Israel	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Israel	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l175t602r264b629],
94	Deaconness	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Deaconness	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l276t603r457b629],
95	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l470t602r594b629],
96	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l609t603r717b633],
97	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l609t603r717b633],
98	Boston	NNP	LOCATION	Boston	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l731t603r844b633],
99	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l731t603r844b633],
100	MA	NNP	O	MA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l858t603r920b633],
101	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l858t603r920b633],
102	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l939t603r1003b629],
103	3Division	NNP	O	3Division	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t635r220b669],
104	of	IN	O	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l235t643r269b676],
105	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l276t643r400b669],
106	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l414t643r552b673],
107	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l414t643r552b673],
108	Montreal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Montreal	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l567t643r707b669],
109	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	General	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l721t643r843b669],
110	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l855t643r992b676],
111	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l855t643r992b676],
112	Montreal	NNP	LOCATION	Montreal	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1007t643r1155b673],
113	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1007t643r1155b673],
114	QC	NNP	O	QC	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1171t643r1229b675],
115	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1171t643r1229b675],
116	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1246t643r1362b669],
117	4Department	NN	O	4department	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l80t676r273b718],
118	of	IN	O	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l287t684r321b718],
119	Human	JJ	ORGANIZATION	human	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l328t685r437b710],
120	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l453t684r582b711],
121	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l597t684r654b710],
122	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l665t684r813b715],
123	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l665t684r813b715],
124	Memorial	NNP	O	Memorial	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l828t684r976b711],
125	Sloan	NNP	O	Sloan	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l990t684r1074b711],
126	Kettering	NNP	O	Kettering	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1088t685r1229b718],
127	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1245t684r1354b711],
128	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1368t684r1476b715],
129	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1368t684r1476b715],
130	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1490t685r1558b710],
131	York	NNP	LOCATION	York	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1573t684r1650b715],
132	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1573t684r1650b715],
133	NY	NNP	O	NY	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1664t685r1718b715],
134	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1664t685r1718b715],
135	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1736t684r1800b711],
136	5Rambam	NNP	O	5Rambam	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t718r226b752],
137	Medical	NNP	O	Medical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l239t726r363b752],
138	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l378t726r486b756],
139	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l378t726r486b756],
140	Haifa	NNP	LOCATION	Haifa	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l501t726r594b759],
141	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l501t726r594b759],
142	Israel	NNP	LOCATION	Israel	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l609t726r697b752],
143	6Fox	NNP	O	6Fox	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t759r153b794],
144	Chase	NNP	O	Chase	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l167t767r258b794],
145	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l274t768r383b794],
146	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l398t768r506b798],
147	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l398t768r506b798],
148	Cheltenham	NNP	LOCATION	Cheltenham	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l522t767r709b798],
149	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l522t767r709b798],
150	PA	NN	ORGANIZATION	pa	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l724t768r778b798],
151	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l724t768r778b798],
152	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l796t768r860b794],
153	7Vancouver	NNP	O	7Vancouver	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t802r257b836],
154	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l271t810r379b840],
155	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l271t810r379b840],
156	BC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	BC	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l393t810r442b836],
157	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l457t810r566b836],
158	Agency	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Agency	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l578t810r697b843],
159	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l578t810r697b843],
160	Vancouver	NNP	LOCATION	Vancouver	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l714t810r882b840],
161	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l714t810r882b840],
162	BC	NNP	O	BC	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l897t810r953b840],
163	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l897t810r953b840],
164	Canada	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Canada	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l970t809r1086b836],
165	8Jubileum	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8Jubileum	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t843r231b878],
166	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l244t852r375b881],
167	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l244t852r375b881],
168	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l390t852r570b884],
169	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l584t851r617b884],
170	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l627t851r778b885],
171	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l627t851r778b885],
172	Lund	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Lund	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l793t851r872b877],
173	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l887t852r1039b885],
174	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1052t851r1190b884],
175	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1052t851r1190b884],
176	Lund	NNP	PERSON	Lund	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1204t851r1289b881],
177	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1204t851r1289b881],
178	Sweden	NNP	LOCATION	Sweden	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1305t851r1418b878],
179	9London	NNP	O	9London	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l81t884r207b919],
180	Health	NNP	O	Health	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l220t892r322b919],
181	Sciences	NNPS	O	Sciences	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l337t893r466b919],
182	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l481t893r589b923],
183	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l481t893r589b923],
184	London	NNP	LOCATION	London	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l603t892r726b923],
185	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l603t892r726b923],
186	ON	NNP	O	ON	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l743t893r800b923],
187	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l743t893r800b923],
188	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l817t892r933b919],
189	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t926r287b967],
190	°	NNP	O	°	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t926r287b967],
191	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t926r287b967],
192	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l301t934r335b967],
193	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l342t934r466b960],
194	Oncology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oncology	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l481t934r632b967],
195	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l481t934r632b967],
196	Sunnybrook	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sunnybrook	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l648t934r827b967],
197	and	CC	O	and	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l840t934r897b960],
198	Women	NNP	O	Women	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l911t934r1048b960],
199	’s	POS	O	’s	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l911t934r1048b960],
200	College	NNP	O	College	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1063t934r1177b967],
201	Health	NNP	O	Health	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1191t934r1293b960],
202	Sciences	NNPS	O	Sciences	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1308t934r1436b960],
203	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1451t934r1559b964],
204	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1451t934r1559b964],
205	Toronto	NNP	LOCATION	Toronto	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1576t935r1702b964],
206	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1576t935r1702b964],
207	ON	NNP	O	ON	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1719t934r1777b964],
208	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1719t934r1777b964],
209	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1793t934r1910b960],
210	“	NNP	O	“	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t968r229b1002],
211	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t968r229b1002],
212	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l244t976r381b1006],
213	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l244t976r381b1006],
214	Children	NNP	O	Children	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l398t975r556b1002],
215	’s	POS	O	’s	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l398t975r556b1002],
216	Hospital	NNP	O	Hospital	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l569t975r699b1009],
217	Medical	NNP	O	Medical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l711t975r835b1002],
218	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l850t976r958b1006],
219	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l850t976r958b1006],
220	Cincinnati	NNP	LOCATION	Cincinnati	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l975t976r1139b1006],
221	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l975t976r1139b1006],
222	OH	NN	O	oh	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1156t976r1216b1006],
223	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1156t976r1216b1006],
224	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1234t976r1298b1002],
225	120ncogenetics	NNPS	O	120ncogenetics	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1009r311b1051],
226	Unit	NNP	O	Unit	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l328t1018r399b1047],
227	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l328t1018r399b1047],
228	Chaim	NNP	PERSON	Chaim	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l416t1017r514b1044],
229	Sheba	NNP	PERSON	Sheba	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l528t1017r619b1044],
230	Medical	NNP	O	Medical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l632t1017r756b1043],
231	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l770t1017r878b1047],
232	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l770t1017r878b1047],
233	Tel-Hashomer	NNP	O	Tel-Hashomer	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l895t1017r1117b1047],
234	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l895t1017r1117b1047],
235	Israel	NNP	LOCATION	Israel	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1131t1017r1219b1043],
236	“	NNP	O	“	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1050r209b1085],
237	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1050r209b1085],
238	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l218t1058r267b1092],
239	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l282t1059r402b1085],
240	Cancer	NN	ORGANIZATION	cancer	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l416t1059r526b1085],
241	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l540t1059r677b1089],
242	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l540t1059r677b1089],
243	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l695t1059r848b1092],
244	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l863t1058r896b1092],
245	Chicago	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chicago	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l906t1059r1039b1092],
246	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l906t1059r1039b1092],
247	Chicago	NNP	LOCATION	Chicago	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1056t1059r1189b1092],
248	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1056t1059r1189b1092],
249	IL	NN	O	il	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1203t1059r1245b1089],
250	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1203t1059r1245b1089],
251	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1263t1059r1327b1085],
252	14Strang	NNP	O	14Strang	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1092r207b1133],
253	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l222t1100r332b1126],
254	Prevention	NNP	O	Prevention	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l344t1101r508b1126],
255	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l524t1100r632b1130],
256	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l524t1100r632b1130],
257	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l646t1101r714b1126],
258	York	NNP	LOCATION	York	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l729t1100r805b1130],
259	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l729t1100r805b1130],
260	NY	NNP	O	NY	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l820t1101r874b1130],
261	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l820t1101r874b1130],
262	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l892t1100r956b1126],
263	15City	NN	O	15city	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1134r170b1176],
264	of	IN	O	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l185t1142r219b1175],
265	Hope	NNP	O	Hope	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l226t1143r307b1176],
266	National	NNP	O	National	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l320t1142r452b1168],
267	Medical	NNP	O	Medical	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l465t1142r589b1168],
268	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l604t1142r712b1172],
269	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l604t1142r712b1172],
270	Duarte	NNP	PERSON	Duarte	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l726t1143r840b1172],
271	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l726t1143r840b1172],
272	CA	NNP	LOCATION	CA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l857t1142r911b1172],
273	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l857t1142r911b1172],
274	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l929t1142r993b1169],
275	16Department	NN	O	16department	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1175r287b1217],
276	of	IN	O	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l301t1183r335b1217],
277	Preventive	NNP	O	Preventive	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l342t1184r502b1210],
278	Medicine	NNP	O	Medicine	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l516t1184r656b1210],
279	and	CC	O	and	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l671t1184r727b1210],
280	Public	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Public	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l739t1184r837b1210],
281	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l850t1184r961b1214],
282	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l850t1184r961b1214],
283	Creighton	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Creighton	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l977t1184r1127b1217],
284	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1144t1184r1296b1217],
285	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1311t1184r1413b1210],
286	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1427t1183r1460b1217],
287	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1468t1184r1616b1214],
288	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1468t1184r1616b1214],
289	Omaha	NNP	LOCATION	Omaha	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1633t1184r1749b1214],
290	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1633t1184r1749b1214],
291	NE	NN	O	ne	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1763t1184r1819b1214],
292	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1763t1184r1819b1214],
293	USA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	USA	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1837t1184r1901b1210],
294	“	CD	ORGANIZATION	“	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1217r315b1259],
295	Epidemiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Epidemiology	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1217r315b1259],
296	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l328t1225r468b1251],
297	Unit	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Unit	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l485t1226r557b1256],
298	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l485t1226r557b1256],
299	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l573t1226r673b1252],
300	Hopitalier	NNP	O	Hopitalier	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l686t1225r844b1259],
301	de	IN	O	de	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l857t1225r891b1251],
302	l’Universite	NNP	O	l’Universite	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l907t1225r1084b1252],
303	de	IN	ORGANIZATION	de	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1099t1225r1132b1251],
304	Montreal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Montreal	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1146t1225r1286b1251],
305	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1301t1226r1442b1257],
306	CHUM	NNP	MISC	CHUM	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1301t1226r1442b1257],
307	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1301t1226r1442b1257],
308	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1301t1226r1442b1257],
309	Hotel-Dieu	NNP	O	Hotel-Dieu	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1456t1225r1633b1256],
310	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1456t1225r1633b1256],
311	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1651t1226r1804b1259],
312	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1819t1225r1853b1259],
313	Montreal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Montreal	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1860t1225r2008b1256],
314	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1860t1225r2008b1256],
315	Montreal	NNP	LOCATION	Montreal	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l79t1266r227b1297],
316	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l79t1266r227b1297],
317	QC	NNP	O	QC	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l243t1267r301b1299],
318	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l243t1267r301b1299],
319	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l318t1266r434b1293],
320	“	NNP	O	“	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1300r209b1334],
321	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l83t1300r209b1334],
322	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l218t1307r267b1341],
323	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l279t1308r419b1334],
324	in	IN	O	in	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l435t1308r462b1334],
325	Women	NNP	O	Women	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l477t1308r614b1334],
326	’s	POS	O	’s	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l477t1308r614b1334],
327	Health	NNP	O	Health	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l627t1308r738b1338],
328	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l627t1308r738b1338],
329	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l756t1308r908b1341],
330	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l923t1307r957b1341],
331	Toronto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Toronto	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l966t1308r1093b1338],
332	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l966t1308r1093b1338],
333	Toronto	NNP	LOCATION	Toronto	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1109t1308r1236b1338],
334	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1109t1308r1236b1338],
335	ON	NNP	O	ON	dep	337	SENT_4	[p1l1253t1308r1311b1338],
336	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1253t1308r1311b1338],
337	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1327t1308r1443b1334],

1	Women	NNS	O	woman	nsubj	9	SENT_5	[p1l9t1503r258b1555],
2	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l285t1502r424b1555],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_5	[p1l452t1518r487b1555],
4	mutation	NN	O	mutation	prep_with	1	SENT_5	[p1l514t1502r803b1555],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l831t1502r891b1554],
6	BRCA1	NN	O	brca1	prep_in	4	SENT_5	[p1l914t1503r1149b1555],
7	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1181t1518r1249b1555],
8	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	prep_in	4	SENT_5	[p1l1273t1503r1509b1555],
9	face	VBP	O	face	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1539t1502r1666b1555],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_5	[p1l1694t1518r1729b1555],
11	lifetime	NN	O	lifetime	nn	12	SENT_5	[p1l1756t1502r1996b1555],
12	risk	NN	O	risk	dobj	9	SENT_5	[p1l2025t1502r2147b1555],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l10t1576r75b1629],
14	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	15	SENT_5	[p1l105t1577r304b1629],
15	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	12	SENT_5	[p1l339t1592r550b1629],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l586t1576r651b1629],
17	~	NN	O	~	prep_of	15	SENT_5	[p1l683t1576r905b1641],
18	80	CD	PERCENT	80	number	19	SENT_5	[p1l683t1576r905b1641],
19	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	17	SENT_5	[p1l683t1576r905b1641],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l683t1576r905b1641],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l941t1577r1059b1629],
22	following	VBG	O	follow	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1095t1576r1389b1644],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_5	[p1l1425t1577r1522b1629],
24	ﬁrst	NN	O	ﬁrst	nn	25	SENT_5	[p1l1558t1576r1685b1629],
25	diagnosis	NN	O	diagnosis	prep_following	34	SENT_5	[p1l1721t1576r2014b1643],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_5	[p1l2049t1577r2146b1629],
27	10-year	JJ	DURATION	10-year	amod	28	SENT_5	[p1l12t1650r250b1718],
28	risk	NN	O	risk	nsubj	34	SENT_5	[p1l282t1650r404b1703],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l435t1650r501b1703],
30	contralateral	JJ	O	contralateral	amod	32	SENT_5	[p1l526t1652r943b1703],
31	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	32	SENT_5	[p1l975t1652r1173b1703],
32	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	28	SENT_5	[p1l1204t1667r1415b1703],
33	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	34	SENT_5	[p1l1447t1650r1493b1703],
34	~	JJ	O	~	conj_and	9	SENT_5	[p1l1527t1650r1749b1703],
35	30	CD	PERCENT	30	num	36	SENT_5	[p1l1527t1650r1749b1703],
36	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	34	SENT_5	[p1l1527t1650r1749b1703],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1527t1650r1749b1703],

1	It	PRP	O	it	nsubjpass	4	SENT_6	[p1l1780t1651r1832b1703],
2	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	4	SENT_6	[p1l1863t1652r1968b1703],
3	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_6	[p1l2000t1652r2147b1703],
4	shown	VBN	O	show	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l10t1726r211b1778],
5	that	IN	O	that	complm	10	SENT_6	[p1l241t1726r368b1778],
6	both	CC	O	both	preconj	7	SENT_6	[p1l398t1726r540b1778],
7	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	nsubj	10	SENT_6	[p1l570t1725r890b1778],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l921t1726r1038b1778],
9	oophorectomy	NN	O	oophorectomy	nsubj	10	SENT_6	[p1l1068t1726r1526b1792],
10	prevent	VBP	O	prevent	ccomp	4	SENT_6	[p1l1557t1729r1801b1792],
11	contralateral	JJ	O	contralateral	amod	13	SENT_6	[p1l1831t1726r2145b1778, p1l10t1802r132b1854],
12	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	13	SENT_6	[p1l160t1802r358b1854],
13	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dobj	10	SENT_6	[p1l386t1817r615b1866],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l386t1817r615b1866],
15	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l642t1802r748b1854],
16	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	19	SENT_6	[p1l774t1800r818b1854],
17	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	19	SENT_6	[p1l844t1800r891b1854],
18	not	RB	O	not	neg	19	SENT_6	[p1l919t1805r1020b1854],
19	clear	JJ	O	clear	conj_but	4	SENT_6	[p1l1047t1802r1203b1854],
20	whether	IN	O	whether	complm	22	SENT_6	[p1l1230t1802r1491b1854],
21	there	EX	O	there	expl	22	SENT_6	[p1l1518t1802r1683b1854],
22	is	VBZ	O	be	ccomp	19	SENT_6	[p1l1711t1800r1757b1854],
23	a	DT	O	a	det	24	SENT_6	[p1l1784t1817r1819b1854],
24	beneﬁt	NN	O	beneﬁt	nsubj	22	SENT_6	[p1l1846t1800r2061b1854],
25	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l2088t1800r2147b1853],
26	giving	VBG	O	give	prepc_in	24	SENT_6	[p1l10t1874r204b1942],
27	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	dobj	26	SENT_6	[p1l242t1874r562b1927],
28	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l601t1878r661b1927],
29	Women	NNS	O	woman	prep_to	26	SENT_6	[p1l699t1890r926b1927],
30	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	33	SENT_6	[p1l964t1875r1095b1927],
31	have	VBP	O	have	aux	33	SENT_6	[p1l1134t1875r1281b1927],
32	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	33	SENT_6	[p1l1321t1874r1653b1942],
33	undergone	VBN	O	undergo	rcmod	29	SENT_6	[p1l1692t1875r2031b1942],
34	an	DT	O	a	det	35	SENT_6	[p1l2071t1890r2147b1927],
35	oophorectomy	NN	O	oophorectomy	dobj	33	SENT_6	[p1l10t1950r485b2016],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l10t1950r485b2016],

1	Furthermore	RB	O	furthermore	advmod	16	SENT_7	[p1l518t1949r958b2014],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l518t1949r958b2014],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_7	[p1l991t1950r1088b2001],
4	relative	JJ	O	relative	amod	5	SENT_7	[p1l1120t1948r1360b2001],
5	degree	NN	O	degree	nsubj	16	SENT_7	[p1l1393t1950r1603b2016],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1636t1948r1701b2001],
7	protection	NN	O	protection	prep_of	5	SENT_7	[p1l1727t1948r2055b2016],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l2087t1948r2147b2000],
9	BRCA1	NN	O	brca1	nn	12	SENT_7	[p1l6t2023r240b2075],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l288t2024r405b2075],
11	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	nn	12	SENT_7	[p1l444t2023r681b2075],
12	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	prep_in	7	SENT_7	[p1l726t2022r980b2075],
13	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	16	SENT_7	[p1l1022t2024r1127b2075],
14	not	RB	O	not	neg	16	SENT_7	[p1l1170t2027r1272b2075],
15	been	VBN	O	be	cop	16	SENT_7	[p1l1313t2024r1461b2075],
16	Well	UH	O	well	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1501t2024r1629b2075],
17	evaluated	VBN	O	evaluate	dep	16	SENT_7	[p1l1673t2024r1997b2075],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1673t2024r1997b2075],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_8	[p1l2040t2023r2147b2075],
2	studied	VBD	O	study	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l10t2096r240b2149],
3	285	CD	NUMBER	285	num	4	SENT_8	[p1l270t2096r379b2149],
4	women	NNS	O	woman	dobj	2	SENT_8	[p1l408t2112r636b2149],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l665t2096r805b2149],
6	bilateral	JJ	O	bilateral	amod	8	SENT_8	[p1l835t2096r1104b2149],
7	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	8	SENT_8	[p1l1134t2097r1333b2149],
8	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_with	4	SENT_8	[p1l1362t2112r1572b2149],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1602t2097r1720b2149],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_8	[p1l1750t2112r1785b2149],
11	BRCA1	NN	O	brca1	nn	14	SENT_8	[p1l1810t2096r2044b2149],
12	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l2079t2112r2146b2149],
13	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	conj_or	11	SENT_8	[p1l6t2172r243b2225],
14	mutation	NN	O	mutation	prep_with	4	SENT_8	[p1l279t2171r586b2237],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l279t2171r586b2237],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l620t2173r738b2225],
17	751	CD	NUMBER	751	num	19	SENT_8	[p1l770t2171r878b2225],
18	control	NN	O	control	nn	19	SENT_8	[p1l912t2173r1140b2225],
19	Women	NNS	O	woman	conj_and	4	SENT_8	[p1l1172t2188r1400b2225],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1431t2171r1571b2225],
21	unilateral	JJ	O	unilateral	amod	23	SENT_8	[p1l1604t2171r1916b2225],
22	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	23	SENT_8	[p1l1949t2173r2147b2225],
23	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_with	19	SENT_8	[p1l10t2261r221b2298],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l250t2246r367b2298],
25	a	DT	O	a	det	29	SENT_8	[p1l395t2261r431b2298],
26	BRCA1	NN	O	brca1	nn	29	SENT_8	[p1l454t2246r689b2298],
27	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l722t2261r790b2298],
28	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	conj_or	26	SENT_8	[p1l815t2246r1051b2298],
29	mutation	NN	O	mutation	prep_with	19	SENT_8	[p1l1082t2245r1372b2298],
30	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1400t2245r1460b2297],
31	a	DT	O	a	det	34	SENT_8	[p1l1488t2261r1523b2298],
32	matched	VBN	O	match	amod	34	SENT_8	[p1l1551t2246r1824b2298],
33	casecontrol	NN	O	casecontrol	nn	34	SENT_8	[p1l1852t2261r2145b2298, p1l10t2321r124b2372],
34	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	2	SENT_8	[p1l154t2321r343b2387],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l154t2321r343b2387],

1	Control	NN	O	control	nn	2	SENT_9	[p1l375t2319r621b2372],
2	women	NNS	O	woman	nsubj	3	SENT_9	[p1l650t2336r878b2372],
3	were	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l906t2336r1059b2372],
4	of	IN	O	of	dep	3	SENT_9	[p1l1089t2319r1154b2372],
5	similar	JJ	O	similar	amod	6	SENT_9	[p1l1177t2319r1401b2372],
6	age	NN	O	age	pobj	4	SENT_9	[p1l1431t2336r1536b2387],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1566t2321r1683b2372],
8	had	VBD	O	have	conj_and	4	SENT_9	[p1l1712t2321r1830b2372],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_9	[p1l1860t2336r1894b2372],
10	similar	JJ	O	similar	amod	11	SENT_9	[p1l1923t2319r2146b2372],
11	age	NN	O	age	dobj	8	SENT_9	[p1l10t2409r115b2461],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l138t2393r203b2446],
13	diagnosis	NN	O	diagnosis	prep_of	11	SENT_9	[p1l220t2393r513b2461],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l535t2393r601b2446],
15	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	16	SENT_9	[p1l617t2394r815b2446],
16	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	13	SENT_9	[p1l837t2409r1048b2446],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1070t2394r1188b2446],
18	had	VBD	O	have	aux	20	SENT_9	[p1l1210t2394r1328b2446],
19	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_9	[p1l1350t2394r1497b2446],
20	followed	VBN	O	follow	conj_and	8	SENT_9	[p1l1519t2393r1788b2446],
21	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1811t2393r1904b2446],
22	as	RB	O	as	advmod	23	SENT_9	[p1l1926t2409r1990b2446],
23	long	JJ	O	long	prepc_for	20	SENT_9	[p1l2012t2394r2148b2461],
24	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l10t2484r73b2521],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_9	[p1l110t2469r207b2521],
26	case	NN	O	case	prep_as	23	SENT_9	[p1l244t2484r375b2521],
27	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l412t2467r505b2520],
28	a	DT	DURATION	a	det	32	SENT_9	[p1l542t2484r577b2521],
29	second	JJ	DURATION	second	amod	32	SENT_9	[p1l614t2469r828b2521],
30	primary	JJ	O	primary	amod	32	SENT_9	[p1l865t2467r1130b2535],
31	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	32	SENT_9	[p1l1167t2469r1365b2521],
32	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_for	26	SENT_9	[p1l1401t2484r1630b2521],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1401t2484r1630b2521],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_10	[p1l1669t2468r1790b2521],
2	history	NN	O	history	nsubjpass	13	SENT_10	[p1l1828t2467r2051b2535],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l2088t2467r2153b2520],
4	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	nn	5	SENT_10	[p1l10t2541r329b2594],
5	use	NN	O	use	prep_of	2	SENT_10	[p1l363t2557r464b2594],
6	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l497t2541r590b2594],
7	treating	VBG	O	treat	prepc_for	5	SENT_10	[p1l624t2541r877b2608],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_10	[p1l910t2542r1007b2594],
9	ﬁrst	JJ	O	ﬁrst	amod	11	SENT_10	[p1l1041t2541r1168b2594],
10	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	11	SENT_10	[p1l1201t2542r1399b2594],
11	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dobj	7	SENT_10	[p1l1432t2557r1642b2594],
12	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_10	[p1l1675t2557r1794b2594],
13	compared	VBN	O	compare	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1827t2542r2147b2609],
14	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l10t2616r270b2668],
15	bilateral	JJ	O	bilateral	amod	18	SENT_10	[p1l294t2615r563b2668],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l586t2616r704b2668],
17	unilateral	JJ	O	unilateral	conj_and	15	SENT_10	[p1l726t2615r1037b2668],
18	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_between	13	SENT_10	[p1l1061t2631r1238b2668],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1061t2631r1238b2668],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_11	[p1l1262t2615r1383b2668],
2	multivariate	JJ	O	multivariate	amod	4	SENT_11	[p1l1407t2615r1802b2668],
3	odds	NNS	O	odds	nn	4	SENT_11	[p1l1825t2616r1972b2668],
4	ratio	NN	O	ratio	nsubj	14	SENT_11	[p1l1995t2615r2147b2668],
5	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l9t2689r103b2742],
6	contralateral	JJ	O	contralateral	amod	8	SENT_11	[p1l130t2690r546b2742],
7	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	8	SENT_11	[p1l575t2690r773b2742],
8	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_for	4	SENT_11	[p1l799t2705r1010b2742],
9	associated	VBN	O	associate	partmod	8	SENT_11	[p1l1038t2689r1361b2742],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1387t2689r1527b2742],
11	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	nn	12	SENT_11	[p1l1554t2689r1874b2742],
12	use	NN	O	use	prep_with	9	SENT_11	[p1l1901t2705r2002b2742],
13	was	VBD	O	be	cop	14	SENT_11	[p1l2028t2705r2147b2742],
14	0.50	CD	NUMBER	0.50	dep	36	SENT_11	[p1l10t2764r139b2818],
15	for	IN	O	for	mark	20	SENT_11	[p1l175t2764r268b2818],
16	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	nsubj	20	SENT_11	[p1l306t2764r559b2818],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l597t2764r663b2818],
18	BRCA1	NN	O	brca1	nn	19	SENT_11	[p1l690t2765r925b2818],
19	mutations	NNS	O	mutation	prep_of	16	SENT_11	[p1l967t2764r1286b2818],
20	(	VBP	O	(	advcl	14	SENT_11	[p1l1324t2764r1488b2829],
21	95	CD	PERCENT	95	number	22	SENT_11	[p1l1324t2764r1488b2829],
22	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	23	SENT_11	[p1l1324t2764r1488b2829],
23	CI	NN	O	ci	dobj	20	SENT_11	[p1l1533t2764r1630b2830],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1533t2764r1630b2830],
25	0.30-0	CD	NUMBER	0.30-0	number	26	SENT_11	[p1l1668t2764r1990b2829],
26	.85	CD	NUMBER	.85	num	27	SENT_11	[p1l1668t2764r1990b2829],
27	)	NN	O	)	appos	23	SENT_11	[p1l1668t2764r1990b2829],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l2029t2766r2147b2818],
29	was	VBD	O	be	cop	30	SENT_11	[p1l9t2856r127b2893],
30	0.42	CD	NUMBER	0.42	conj_and	20	SENT_11	[p1l163t2839r291b2893],
31	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l326t2839r419b2893],
32	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	prep_for	30	SENT_11	[p1l454t2839r708b2893],
33	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l743t2839r808b2893],
34	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	nn	35	SENT_11	[p1l834t2840r1071b2893],
35	mutations	NNS	O	mutation	prep_of	32	SENT_11	[p1l1109t2839r1428b2893],
36	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1464t2839r1559b2904],
37	95	CD	PERCENT	95	num	38	SENT_11	[p1l1464t2839r1559b2904],
38	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dobj	36	SENT_11	[p1l1570t2839r1628b2892],
39	CI	NN	O	ci	nsubj	36	SENT_11	[p1l1672t2839r1769b2905],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1672t2839r1769b2905],
41	0.17-1	CD	NUMBER	0.17-1	number	42	SENT_11	[p1l1804t2839r2145b2904],
42	.02	CD	NUMBER	.02	num	43	SENT_11	[p1l1804t2839r2145b2904],
43	)	NN	O	)	appos	39	SENT_11	[p1l1804t2839r2145b2904],
44	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1804t2839r2145b2904],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_12	[p1l10t2913r131b2966],
2	protective	JJ	O	protective	amod	3	SENT_12	[p1l171t2913r491b2981],
3	effect	NN	O	effect	nsubjpass	8	SENT_12	[p1l530t2913r704b2966],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l742t2913r807b2966],
5	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	prep_of	3	SENT_12	[p1l839t2913r1159b2966],
6	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_12	[p1l1197t2929r1316b2966],
7	not	RB	O	not	neg	8	SENT_12	[p1l1354t2917r1456b2966],
8	seen	VBN	O	see	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1494t2929r1628b2966],
9	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1667t2929r1882b2981],
10	women	NNS	O	woman	prep_among	8	SENT_12	[p1l1919t2929r2147b2966],
11	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	13	SENT_12	[p1l9t2988r140b3040],
12	had	VBD	O	have	aux	13	SENT_12	[p1l169t2988r287b3040],
13	undergone	VBN	O	undergo	rcmod	10	SENT_12	[p1l315t2988r655b3054],
14	an	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_12	[p1l685t3003r760b3040],
15	oophorectomy	NN	O	oophorectomy	nn	17	SENT_12	[p1l789t2988r1247b3054],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_12	[p1l1278t2986r1400b3051],
17	OR	NN	O	or	dobj	13	SENT_12	[p1l1278t2986r1400b3051],
18	=	JJ	O	=	amod	17	SENT_12	[p1l1437t3004r1484b3027],
19	0.83	CD	NUMBER	0.83	tmod	18	SENT_12	[p1l1520t2987r1670b3052],
20	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1520t2987r1670b3052],
21	95	CD	PERCENT	95	number	22	SENT_12	[p1l1702t2986r1951b3052],
22	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	23	SENT_12	[p1l1702t2986r1951b3052],
23	CI	NN	O	ci	dep	10	SENT_12	[p1l1702t2986r1951b3052],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1702t2986r1951b3052],
25	0.242.89	CD	NUMBER	0.242.89	num	26	SENT_12	[p1l1981t2987r2149b3040, p1l9t3061r161b3125],
26	)	NN	O	)	appos	23	SENT_12	[p1l1981t2987r2149b3040, p1l9t3061r161b3125],
27	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l190t3062r295b3114],
28	this	DT	O	this	det	29	SENT_12	[p1l319t3061r433b3114],
29	subgroup	NN	O	subgroup	nsubj	31	SENT_12	[p1l459t3062r759b3129],
30	was	VBD	O	be	cop	31	SENT_12	[p1l785t3077r903b3114],
31	small	JJ	O	small	conj_but	8	SENT_12	[p1l929t3062r1115b3114],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l929t3062r1115b3114],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1141t3062r1209b3113],
2	contrast	NN	O	contrast	prep_in	11	SENT_13	[p1l1234t3065r1513b3126],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1234t3065r1513b3126],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_13	[p1l1539t3077r1574b3114],
5	strong	JJ	O	strong	amod	7	SENT_13	[p1l1599t3066r1800b3129],
6	protective	JJ	O	protective	amod	7	SENT_13	[p1l1827t3061r2146b3129],
7	effect	NN	O	effect	nsubj	11	SENT_13	[p1l10t3135r184b3189],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l209t3135r274b3188],
9	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	prep_of	7	SENT_13	[p1l293t3135r613b3189],
10	was	VBD	O	be	cop	11	SENT_13	[p1l636t3152r755b3189],
11	apparent	JJ	O	apparent	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l780t3140r1071b3203],
12	among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1095t3152r1309b3203],
13	Women	NNS	O	woman	prep_among	11	SENT_13	[p1l1333t3152r1561b3189],
14	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	16	SENT_13	[p1l1586t3137r1717b3188],
15	were	VBD	O	be	cop	16	SENT_13	[p1l1741t3152r1893b3189],
16	premenopausal	JJ	O	premenopausal	dep	11	SENT_13	[p1l1919t3152r2145b3203, p1l10t3211r295b3277],
17	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l325t3226r392b3262],
18	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	20	SENT_13	[p1l421t3211r552b3262],
19	had	VBD	O	have	aux	20	SENT_13	[p1l581t3211r699b3262],
20	undergone	VBN	O	undergo	dep	11	SENT_13	[p1l728t3211r1067b3277],
21	natural	JJ	O	natural	amod	22	SENT_13	[p1l1098t3211r1333b3262],
22	menopause	NN	O	menopause	dobj	20	SENT_13	[p1l1363t3226r1719b3277],
23	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	24	SENT_13	[p1l1750t3209r1873b3274],
24	OR	NN	O	or	dep	22	SENT_13	[p1l1750t3209r1873b3274],
25	=	JJ	O	=	amod	24	SENT_13	[p1l1911t3226r1957b3250],
26	0.44	CD	NUMBER	0.44	tmod	25	SENT_13	[p1l1993t3209r2143b3275],
27	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1993t3209r2143b3275],
28	95	CD	PERCENT	95	number	29	SENT_13	[p1l10t3283r150b3337],
29	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	30	SENT_13	[p1l10t3283r150b3337],
30	CI	NN	O	ci	dep	22	SENT_13	[p1l181t3283r278b3349],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l181t3283r278b3349],
32	0.27-0	CD	NUMBER	0.27-0	num	34	SENT_13	[p1l301t3283r642b3348],
33	.65	CD	NUMBER	.65	num	34	SENT_13	[p1l301t3283r642b3348],
34	)	NN	O	)	appos	30	SENT_13	[p1l301t3283r642b3348],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l301t3283r642b3348],

1	©	RB	O	©	advmod	2	SENT_14	[p1l10t3363r58b3411],
2	2005	CD	DATE	2005	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l98t3358r246b3411],
3	Wiley	NNP	PERSON	Wiley	dep	2	SENT_14	[p1l270t3358r602b3426],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l270t3358r602b3426],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l270t3358r602b3426],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l270t3358r602b3426],

1	Liss	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Liss	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l270t3358r602b3426],
2	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l270t3358r602b3426],
3	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	appos	1	SENT_16	[p1l622t3360r735b3411],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l622t3360r735b3411],

1	Key	NN	O	key	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l10t3570r137b3637],
2	words	NNS	O	word	dep	1	SENT_17	[p1l164t3571r379b3623],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l164t3571r379b3623],
4	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	5	SENT_17	[p1l424t3570r601b3622],
5	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	1	SENT_17	[p1l620t3587r826b3632],
6	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l620t3587r826b3632],
7	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	dep	5	SENT_17	[p1l851t3570r1166b3632],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l851t3570r1166b3632],
9	oophorectomy	NN	O	oophorectomy	dep	7	SENT_17	[p1l1191t3570r1631b3638],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1191t3570r1631b3638],
11	BRCA1	NN	O	brca1	dep	9	SENT_17	[p1l1652t3570r1893b3632],
12	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1652t3570r1893b3632],
13	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	dep	5	SENT_17	[p1l1915t3570r2136b3623],

1	The	DT	O	the	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l89t88r211b143],
2	lifetime	NN	O	lifetime	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l237t88r483b143],
3	risk	NN	O	risk	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l508t88r628b143],
4	of	IN	O	of	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l652t87r720b143],
5	breast	NN	O	breast	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l739t88r929b143],
6	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l954t105r1162b143],
7	in	IN	O	in	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1186t88r1246b143],
8	women	NNS	O	woman	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1270t105r1503b143],
9	who	WP	O	who	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1527t88r1661b143],
10	carry	VBP	O	carry	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1687t105r1848b160],
11	a	DT	O	a	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1875t105r1908b143],
12	deleterious	JJ	O	deleterious	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1931t88r2145b143, p2l8t168r165b224],
13	BRCAI	NN	O	brcaus	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l188t168r422b225],
14	or	CC	O	or	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l455t186r520b224],
15	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l540t168r777b225],
16	mutation	NN	O	mutation	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l805t168r1089b224],
17	is	VBZ	O	be	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1114t168r1163b224],
18	~	VBN	O	~	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1192t151r1439b234],
19	80	CD	PERCENT	80	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1192t151r1439b234],
20	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1192t151r1439b234],
21	,1	CD	NUMBER	,1	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1192t151r1439b234],
22	and	CC	O	and	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1471t168r1583b224],
23	following	VBG	O	follow	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1607t168r1915b240],
24	an	DT	O	a	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1942t186r2014b224],
25	initial	JJ	O	initial	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l2038t168r2145b223, p2l9t246r110b302],
26	diagnosis	NN	O	diagnosis	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l154t246r452b319],
27	of	IN	O	of	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l497t246r566b302],
28	breast	NN	O	breast	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l603t247r794b302],
29	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l836t264r1045b302],
30	the	DT	O	the	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1086t247r1181b302],
31	annual	JJ	SET	annual	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1227t246r1436b302],
32	risk	NN	O	risk	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1479t246r1598b302],
33	of	IN	O	of	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1641t246r1710b302],
34	contralateral	JJ	O	contralateral	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1748t246r2146b302],
35	breast	NN	O	breast	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l9t326r199b382],
36	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l234t344r441b382],
37	is	VBZ	O	be	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l475t326r524b382],
38	~	NN	O	~	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l563t310r775b383],
39	3	CD	PERCENT	3	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l563t310r775b383],
40	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l563t310r775b383],
41	.2	NN	NUMBER	.2	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l563t310r775b383],
42	Both	CC	O	both	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l811t327r964b382],
43	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l998t326r1322b382],
44	and	CC	O	and	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1357t326r1470b382],
45	oophorectomy	NN	O	oophorectomy	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1504t327r1963b399],
46	have	VBP	O	have	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1998t327r2146b382],
47	been	VBN	O	be	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l9t407r159b463],
48	shown	VBN	O	show	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l184t407r388b463],
49	to	TO	O	to	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l410t415r470b463],
50	reduce	VB	O	reduce	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l493t407r705b463],
51	the	DT	O	the	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l728t407r824b463],
52	risk	NN	O	risk	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l847t407r967b463],
53	of	IN	O	of	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l989t407r1058b463],
54	contralateral	JJ	O	contralateral	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1077t407r1475b463],
55	breast	NN	O	breast	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1498t407r1689b463],
56	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1712t425r1920b463],
57	in	IN	O	in	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1942t407r2002b462],
58	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l2026t425r2145b463, p2l8t488r147b544],
59	of	IN	O	of	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l177t488r245b544],
60	BRCAI	NN	O	brcaus	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l263t488r497b545],
61	or	CC	O	or	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l532t506r597b544],
62	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l619t488r856b545],
63	mutations	NNS	O	mutation	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l886t471r1293b544],
64	.2	NN	NUMBER	.2	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l886t471r1293b544],
65	’	CD	NUMBER	’	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l886t471r1293b544],
66	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l886t471r1293b544],
67	In	IN	O	in	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1322t490r1387b543],
68	our	PRP$	O	we	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1414t506r1518b544],
69	previous	JJ	O	previous	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1542t488r1815b561],
70	casecontrol	NN	O	casecontrol	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1843t506r2145b544, p2l9t568r118b624],
71	study	NN	O	study	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l158t568r326b640],
72	of	IN	O	of	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l364t568r433b624],
73	209	CD	NUMBER	209	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l465t569r580b625],
74	bilateral	JJ	O	bilateral	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l619t568r880b624],
75	cases	NNS	O	case	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l918t586r1082b624],
76	and	CC	O	and	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1123t568r1235b624],
77	384	CD	NUMBER	384	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1273t568r1387b624],
78	unilateral	JJ	O	unilateral	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1425t568r1726b624],
79	controls	NNS	O	control	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1765t568r2018b624],
80	we	PRP	O	we	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l2057t586r2147b624],
81	reported	VBD	O	report	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l8t648r275b720],
82	a	DT	O	a	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l316t666r349b704],
83	reduction	NN	O	reduction	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l386t648r688b704],
84	in	IN	O	in	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l728t648r788b703],
85	contralateral	JJ	O	contralateral	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l828t648r1226b704],
86	breast	NN	O	breast	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1266t648r1456b704],
87	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1496t665r1704b704],
88	risk	NN	O	risk	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1741t648r1861b704],
89	of	IN	O	of	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1900t648r1969b704],
90	51	CD	PERCENT	51	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l2004t648r2144b704],
91	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l2004t648r2144b704],
92	associated	VBN	O	associate	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l11t728r337b784],
93	with	IN	O	with	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l367t728r508b784],
94	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l537t728r861b784],
95	use	NN	O	use	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l890t746r1012b794],
96	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l890t746r1012b794],
97	but	CC	O	but	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1044t728r1145b784],
98	the	DT	O	the	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1175t728r1270b784],
99	observed	VBN	O	observe	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1302t728r1587b784],
100	protective	JJ	O	protective	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1616t728r1935b800],
101	effect	NN	O	effect	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l1967t728r2148b784],
102	was	VBD	O	be	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l10t825r129b863],
103	signiﬁcant	JJ	O	signiﬁcant	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l158t808r488b880],
104	only	RB	O	only	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l512t808r651b880],
105	in	IN	O	in	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l677t808r737b863],
106	BRCA1	NN	O	brca1	dep	107	SENT_18	[p2l757t808r991b864],
107	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l1024t808r1277b864],
108	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p2l1024t808r1277b864],

1	Since	IN	O	since	mark	5	SENT_19	[p2l1308t808r1480b864],
2	this	DT	O	this	det	3	SENT_19	[p2l1506t808r1618b863],
3	report	NN	O	report	nsubjpass	5	SENT_19	[p2l1643t817r1834b880],
4	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_19	[p2l1857t825r1977b863],
5	published	VBN	O	publish	advcl	11	SENT_19	[p2l2002t808r2145b880, p2l9t888r199b943],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l226t888r286b943],
7	2000	CD	DATE	2000	prep_in	5	SENT_19	[p2l314t888r488b954],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l314t888r488b954],
9	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	11	SENT_19	[p2l518t905r608b943],
10	have	VBP	O	have	aux	11	SENT_19	[p2l635t888r784b943],
11	continued	VBN	O	continue	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l813t888r1126b943],
12	to	TO	O	to	aux	13	SENT_19	[p2l1153t896r1212b943],
13	accrue	VB	O	accrue	xcomp	11	SENT_19	[p2l1242t905r1447b943],
14	study	NN	O	study	nn	15	SENT_19	[p2l1478t888r1645b960],
15	subjects	NNS	O	subject	dobj	13	SENT_19	[p2l1676t888r1927b960],
16	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1956t896r2015b943],
17	our	PRP$	O	we	prep_to	13	SENT_19	[p2l2044t905r2149b943],

1	Publication	NN	O	publication	nn	2	SENT_20	[p2l451t1084r710b1121],
2	ofthe	NN	O	ofthe	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l727t1084r855b1121],
3	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	International	nn	4	SENT_20	[p2l872t1084r1167b1121],
4	Union	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Union	dep	2	SENT_20	[p2l1186t1084r1323b1121],
5	Against	IN	ORGANIZATION	against	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1339t1084r1519b1130],
6	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	prep_against	4	SENT_20	[p2l1533t1084r1694b1121],

1	BRCA	NNP	O	BRCA	nn	3	SENT_21	[p2l9t1453r224b1509],
2	carrier	NN	O	carrier	nn	3	SENT_21	[p2l247t1453r455b1508],
3	registry	NN	O	registry	nsubj	23	SENT_21	[p2l476t1453r719b1525],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l744t1453r856b1508],
5	we	PRP	O	we	conj_and	3	SENT_21	[p2l879t1470r968b1508],
6	are	VBP	O	be	cop	7	SENT_21	[p2l994t1470r1088b1508],
7	able	JJ	O	able	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1113t1453r1242b1508],
8	to	TO	O	to	aux	9	SENT_21	[p2l1266t1461r1325b1508],
9	readdress	VB	O	readdress	xcomp	7	SENT_21	[p2l1348t1453r1647b1508],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_21	[p2l1672t1453r1767b1508],
11	question	NN	O	question	dobj	9	SENT_21	[p2l1791t1453r2060b1525],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l2083t1452r2152b1508],
13	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	nn	14	SENT_21	[p2l9t1532r332b1588],
14	protection	NN	O	protection	prep_of	11	SENT_21	[p2l366t1533r691b1605],
15	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l727t1533r867b1588],
16	a	DT	O	a	det	18	SENT_21	[p2l904t1550r937b1588],
17	greater	JJR	O	greater	amod	18	SENT_21	[p2l972t1541r1193b1605],
18	degree	NN	O	degree	prep_with	9	SENT_21	[p2l1229t1533r1438b1605],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1476t1532r1544b1588],
20	precision	NN	O	precision	prep_of	18	SENT_21	[p2l1573t1533r1866b1605],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1904t1533r2016b1588],
22	are	VBP	O	be	cop	23	SENT_21	[p2l2053t1550r2146b1588],
23	able	JJ	O	able	conj_and	7	SENT_21	[p2l10t1613r140b1669],
24	to	TO	O	to	aux	25	SENT_21	[p2l170t1621r229b1669],
25	evaluate	VB	O	evaluate	xcomp	23	SENT_21	[p2l260t1613r524b1669],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_21	[p2l555t1613r650b1669],
27	magnitude	NN	O	magnitude	dobj	25	SENT_21	[p2l680t1613r1016b1685],
28	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1047t1613r1115b1669],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_21	[p2l1139t1613r1234b1669],
30	protective	JJ	O	protective	amod	31	SENT_21	[p2l1263t1613r1583b1685],
31	effect	NN	O	effect	prep_of	27	SENT_21	[p2l1614t1613r1795b1669],
32	separately	RB	O	separately	advmod	25	SENT_21	[p2l1827t1613r2146b1685],
33	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l9t1692r101b1748],
34	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	prep_for	25	SENT_21	[p2l128t1692r363b1748],
35	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l393t1692r462b1748],
36	BRCAI	NN	O	brcaus	nn	39	SENT_21	[p2l480t1692r714b1749],
37	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l750t1693r863b1748],
38	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	nn	39	SENT_21	[p2l885t1692r1123b1749],
39	mutations	NNS	O	mutation	prep_of	34	SENT_21	[p2l1154t1692r1485b1748],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1154t1692r1485b1748],

1	It	PRP	O	it	nsubj	2	SENT_22	[p2l1516t1694r1564b1748],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1590t1692r1639b1748],
3	also	RB	O	also	advmod	2	SENT_22	[p2l1669t1693r1793b1748],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1822t1692r1891b1748],
5	interest	NN	O	interest	prep_of	2	SENT_22	[p2l1913t1692r2148b1748],
6	to	TO	O	to	aux	7	SENT_22	[p2l9t1781r68b1828],
7	establish	VB	O	establish	ccomp	2	SENT_22	[p2l92t1772r370b1828],
8	whether	IN	O	whether	complm	12	SENT_22	[p2l393t1772r649b1828],
9	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l672t1790r737b1828],
10	not	RB	O	not	conj_or	12	SENT_22	[p2l757t1781r859b1828],
11	there	EX	O	there	expl	12	SENT_22	[p2l880t1772r1038b1828],
12	is	VBZ	O	be	ccomp	7	SENT_22	[p2l1062t1772r1111b1828],
13	a	DT	O	a	det	15	SENT_22	[p2l1137t1790r1170b1828],
14	protective	JJ	O	protective	amod	15	SENT_22	[p2l1190t1772r1509b1845],
15	effect	NN	O	effect	nsubj	12	SENT_22	[p2l1533t1772r1715b1828],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1738t1772r1807b1828],
17	tamoxifen	NN	O	tamoxifen	prep_of	15	SENT_22	[p2l1823t1772r2147b1828],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l9t1853r69b1908],
19	women	NNS	O	woman	prep_in	17	SENT_22	[p2l100t1871r333b1909],
20	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	23	SENT_22	[p2l363t1853r496b1909],
21	have	VBP	O	have	aux	23	SENT_22	[p2l527t1853r676b1909],
22	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	23	SENT_22	[p2l706t1853r1042b1925],
23	undergone	VBN	O	undergo	rcmod	19	SENT_22	[p2l1073t1853r1408b1925],
24	an	DT	O	a	det	25	SENT_22	[p2l1441t1871r1513b1909],
25	oophorectomy	NN	O	oophorectomy	dobj	23	SENT_22	[p2l1544t1853r2003b1925],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l2035t1853r2148b1909],
27	to	TO	O	to	aux	28	SENT_22	[p2l9t1942r68b1989],
28	evaluate	VB	O	evaluate	ccomp	2	SENT_22	[p2l98t1933r362b1989],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_22	[p2l391t1933r486b1989],
30	protective	JJ	O	protective	amod	31	SENT_22	[p2l514t1933r833b2006],
31	effect	NN	O	effect	dobj	28	SENT_22	[p2l862t1933r1044b1989],
32	separately	RB	O	separately	advmod	28	SENT_22	[p2l1074t1933r1394b2006],
33	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1423t1933r1515b1989],
34	pre	JJ	O	pre	amod	37	SENT_22	[p2l1540t1951r1640b2006],
35	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1671t1933r1783b1989],
36	postmenopausal	JJ	O	postmenopausal	conj_and	34	SENT_22	[p2l1810t1942r2145b2006, p2l8t2014r211b2087],
37	women	NNS	O	woman	prep_for	28	SENT_22	[p2l234t2032r483b2070],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l234t2032r483b2070],

1	Material	NN	O	material	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l9t2159r304b2216],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l341t2161r465b2216],
3	methods	NNS	O	method	conj_and	1	SENT_23	[p2l501t2161r785b2216],

1	Study	NNP	O	Study	nn	2	SENT_24	[p2l8t2266r184b2338],
2	subjects	NNS	O	subject	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l207t2266r462b2338],

1	Information	NN	O	information	nsubjpass	9	SENT_25	[p2l88t2367r469b2423],
2	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l500t2385r577b2423],
3	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_on	1	SENT_25	[p2l605t2367r852b2440],
4	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l883t2367r1023b2423],
5	hereditary	JJ	O	hereditary	amod	7	SENT_25	[p2l1052t2367r1375b2439],
6	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	7	SENT_25	[p2l1404t2367r1595b2423],
7	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_with	3	SENT_25	[p2l1624t2385r1832b2423],
8	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_25	[p2l1861t2385r1980b2423],
9	submitted	VBN	O	submit	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l2014t2367r2145b2423, p2l8t2451r213b2507],
10	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l237t2460r296b2507],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_25	[p2l321t2451r417b2507],
12	study	NN	O	study	nn	13	SENT_25	[p2l445t2451r613b2523],
13	center	NN	O	center	prep_to	9	SENT_25	[p2l639t2460r833b2507],
14	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l856t2451r934b2523],
15	investigators	NNS	O	investigator	agent	9	SENT_25	[p2l959t2451r1365b2523],
16	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1392t2460r1448b2507],
17	each	DT	O	each	prep_at	15	SENT_25	[p2l1473t2451r1617b2507],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1643t2451r1711b2507],
19	49	CD	NUMBER	49	num	21	SENT_25	[p2l1730t2451r1807b2508],
20	contributing	VBG	O	contribute	amod	21	SENT_25	[p2l1833t2451r2145b2507, p2l9t2535r108b2607],
21	centers	NNS	O	center	prep_of	17	SENT_25	[p2l136t2544r359b2591],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l388t2535r449b2590],
23	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	24	SENT_25	[p2l482t2535r552b2591],
24	countries	NNS	O	country	prep_in	21	SENT_25	[p2l579t2535r886b2591],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l579t2535r886b2591],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_26	[p2l917t2535r1106b2591],
2	centers	NNS	O	center	nsubjpass	4	SENT_26	[p2l1134t2544r1356b2591],
3	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_26	[p2l1386t2553r1538b2591],
4	requested	VBN	O	request	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1564t2535r1871b2607],
5	to	TO	O	to	aux	6	SENT_26	[p2l1897t2543r1956b2591],
6	complete	VB	O	complete	xcomp	4	SENT_26	[p2l1985t2553r2145b2591, p2l7t2619r162b2691],
7	data	NNS	O	datum	nn	8	SENT_26	[p2l206t2619r338b2675],
8	forms	NNS	O	form	dobj	6	SENT_26	[p2l379t2619r561b2675],
9	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l605t2619r697b2675],
10	all	DT	O	all	det	12	SENT_26	[p2l739t2619r816b2675],
11	known	JJ	O	known	amod	12	SENT_26	[p2l856t2619r1074b2675],
12	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_for	6	SENT_26	[p2l1115t2636r1280b2675],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1324t2619r1393b2675],
14	female	JJ	O	female	amod	16	SENT_26	[p2l1430t2619r1645b2675],
15	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	16	SENT_26	[p2l1688t2619r1878b2675],
16	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	12	SENT_26	[p2l1920t2636r2144b2685],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1920t2636r2144b2685],
18	unilateral	JJ	O	unilateral	prep_of	12	SENT_26	[p2l8t2703r310b2759],
19	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l336t2721r401b2759],
20	bilateral	JJ	O	bilateral	prep_of	12	SENT_26	[p2l424t2703r703b2769],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l424t2703r703b2769],
22	carrying	VBG	O	carry	partmod	6	SENT_26	[p2l732t2703r995b2775],
23	a	DT	O	a	det	25	SENT_26	[p2l1022t2720r1055b2759],
24	veriﬁed	JJ	O	veriﬁed	amod	25	SENT_26	[p2l1079t2703r1322b2759],
25	BRCAI	NN	O	brcaus	dobj	22	SENT_26	[p2l1343t2703r1578b2760],
26	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1611t2721r1675b2759],
27	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	nn	28	SENT_26	[p2l1695t2703r1933b2760],
28	mutation	NN	O	mutation	dobj	22	SENT_26	[p2l1962t2711r2145b2759, p2l9t2787r147b2843],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1962t2711r2145b2759, p2l9t2787r147b2843],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_27	[p2l182t2787r304b2842],
2	majority	NN	O	majority	nsubjpass	7	SENT_27	[p2l335t2787r605b2859],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l638t2786r707b2842],
4	these	DT	O	these	det	5	SENT_27	[p2l732t2787r894b2842],
5	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	2	SENT_27	[p2l926t2804r1091b2842],
6	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_27	[p2l1124t2804r1275b2842],
7	identiﬁed	VBN	O	identiﬁed	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1308t2786r1609b2842],
8	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1639t2787r1886b2859],
9	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	prep_through	7	SENT_27	[p2l1918t2787r2146b2859],

1	Other	JJ	O	other	amod	2	SENT_28	[p2l161t3064r321b3113],
2	members	NNS	O	member	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l364t3064r621b3113],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l668t3064r729b3113],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_28	[p2l769t3064r854b3113],
5	Hereditary	JJ	O	hereditary	amod	10	SENT_28	[p2l899t3064r1201b3128],
6	Breast	NN	O	breast	nn	10	SENT_28	[p2l1247t3065r1427b3113],
7	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	10	SENT_28	[p2l1472t3064r1672b3113],
8	Clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	10	SENT_28	[p2l1716t3064r1939b3113],
9	Study	NNP	O	Study	nn	10	SENT_28	[p2l1986t3064r2147b3128],
10	Group	NNP	O	Group	prep_of	2	SENT_28	[p2l9t3134r203b3198],
11	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l9t3134r203b3198],
12	D	NNP	ORGANIZATION	D	nn	13	SENT_28	[p2l229t3135r277b3182],
13	Gilchrist	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Gilchrist	dep	2	SENT_28	[p2l300t3134r562b3192],
14	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l300t3134r562b3192],
15	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	13	SENT_28	[p2l586t3134r883b3197],
16	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l906t3134r967b3183],
17	Alberta	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Alberta	prep_of	15	SENT_28	[p2l983t3134r1211b3192],
18	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l983t3134r1211b3192],
19	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	20	SENT_28	[p2l1236t3135r1296b3183],
20	Weber	NNP	PERSON	Weber	dep	2	SENT_28	[p2l1320t3134r1510b3183],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1531t3134r1631b3183],
22	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	nn	23	SENT_28	[p2l1652t3135r1708b3183],
23	Rebbeck	NNP	PERSON	Rebbeck	dep	2	SENT_28	[p2l1732t3134r1996b3192],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1732t3134r1996b3192],
25	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	20	SENT_28	[p2l2019t3134r2146b3183, p2l8t3203r200b3266],
26	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l222t3203r283b3252],
27	Pennsylvania	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pennsylvania	prep_of	25	SENT_28	[p2l298t3203r691b3266],
28	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l298t3203r691b3266],
29	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	30	SENT_28	[p2l717t3203r776b3252],
30	Isaacs	NNP	PERSON	Isaacs	dep	2	SENT_28	[p2l800t3204r987b3261],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l800t3204r987b3261],
32	Lombardi	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Lombardi	nn	34	SENT_28	[p2l1009t3203r1289b3252],
33	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	34	SENT_28	[p2l1311t3203r1511b3252],
34	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	appos	30	SENT_28	[p2l1531t3203r1734b3261],
35	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1531t3203r1734b3261],
36	S	NN	O	s	nn	39	SENT_28	[p2l1760t3203r1793b3252],
37	Neuhausen	NNP	PERSON	Neuhausen	nn	39	SENT_28	[p2l1816t3203r2146b3261],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1816t3203r2146b3261],
39	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	2	SENT_28	[p2l8t3271r307b3335],
40	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l330t3271r391b3321],
41	Califomia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Califomia	nn	43	SENT_28	[p2l411t3271r713b3330],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l411t3271r713b3330],
43	Irvine	NNP	LOCATION	Irvine	prep_of	39	SENT_28	[p2l738t3271r922b3330],
44	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l738t3271r922b3330],
45	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	46	SENT_28	[p2l949t3273r989b3321],
46	Garber	NNP	PERSON	Garber	dep	2	SENT_28	[p2l1017t3272r1227b3330],
47	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1017t3272r1227b3330],
48	Dana	NNP	PERSON	Dana	nn	51	SENT_28	[p2l1252t3273r1401b3321],
49	Farber	NNP	PERSON	Farber	nn	51	SENT_28	[p2l1423t3272r1608b3321],
50	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	nn	51	SENT_28	[p2l1631t3272r1831b3321],
51	Center	NNP	O	Center	appos	46	SENT_28	[p2l1854t3272r2056b3330],
52	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1854t3272r2056b3330],
53	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	54	SENT_28	[p2l2084t3273r2143b3321],
54	Karlan	NNP	PERSON	Karlan	dep	2	SENT_28	[p2l9t3341r216b3400],
55	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l9t3341r216b3400],
56	Cedars	NNP	MISC	Cedars	appos	54	SENT_28	[p2l247t3341r611b3391],
57	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l247t3341r611b3391],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l247t3341r611b3391],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l247t3341r611b3391],

1	Sinai	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sinai	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l247t3341r611b3391],
2	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l639t3341r870b3391],
3	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l899t3341r1102b3400],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l899t3341r1102b3400],
5	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1134t3342r1197b3391],
6	Fishman	NNP	PERSON	Fishman	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1228t3341r1487b3400],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1228t3341r1487b3400],
8	Northwestern	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Northwestern	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1516t3341r1902b3391],
9	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1928t3341r2146b3391, p2l11t3410r125b3474],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1928t3341r2146b3391, p2l11t3410r125b3474],
11	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l158t3410r207b3460],
12	Merajver	NNP	PERSON	Merajver	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l237t3410r511b3474],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l237t3410r511b3474],
14	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l539t3410r837b3474],
15	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l864t3410r925b3459],
16	Michigan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Michigan	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l947t3410r1218b3474],
17	Comprehensive	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Comprehensive	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1245t3410r1686b3474],
18	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1714t3410r1915b3459],
19	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1940t3410r2143b3469],
20	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1940t3410r2143b3469],
21	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l8t3481r88b3529],
22	McKinnon	NNP	PERSON	McKinnon	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l116t3480r422b3529],
23	and	CC	O	and	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l447t3480r547b3529],
24	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l571t3481r646b3529],
25	Wood	NNP	PERSON	Wood	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l673t3480r862b3538],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l673t3480r862b3538],
27	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l888t3480r1186b3543],
28	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1211t3480r1272b3529],
29	Vermont	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Vermont	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1293t3481r1558b3538],
30	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1293t3481r1558b3538],
31	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1588t3480r1650b3529],
32	Evans	NNP	PERSON	Evans	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1678t3481r1866b3538],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1678t3481r1866b3538],
34	Regional	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Regional	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1892t3480r2148b3544],
35	Genetics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genetics	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l9t3549r254b3598],
36	Service	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Service	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l278t3549r503b3607],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l278t3549r503b3607],
38	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l527t3549r597b3598],
39	Mary	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mary	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l621t3549r822b3613],
40	’s	POS	ORGANIZATION	’s	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l621t3549r822b3613],
41	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l843t3549r1098b3613],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l843t3549r1098b3613],
43	Manchester	NNP	LOCATION	Manchester	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1120t3549r1465b3607],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1120t3549r1465b3607],
45	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1488t3550r1603b3607],
46	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1488t3550r1603b3607],
47	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1627t3550r1679b3598],
48	Moller	NNP	PERSON	Moller	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1703t3549r1910b3607],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1703t3549r1910b3607],
50	N	NNP	O	N	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1932t3550r1982b3598],
51	orwe	VBP	O	orwe	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1985t3565r2146b3598],
52	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1985t3565r2146b3598],
53	gian	JJ	O	gian	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l9t3617r130b3681],
54	Radium	NN	ORGANIZATION	radium	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l150t3617r374b3667],
55	Hospital	NN	ORGANIZATION	hospital	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l396t3617r650b3681],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l396t3617r650b3681],
57	Oslo	NNP	LOCATION	Oslo	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l675t3618r821b3676],
58	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l675t3618r821b3676],
59	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l847t3619r906b3667],
60	Pasini	NNP	PERSON	Pasini	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l931t3617r1119b3676],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l931t3617r1119b3676],
62	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1142t3617r1440b3681],
63	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1463t3617r1523b3667],
64	Genoa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Genoa	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1541t3618r1739b3676],
65	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1541t3618r1739b3676],
66	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1765t3619r1828b3667],
67	Sweet	NNP	PERSON	Sweet	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1855t3618r2026b3667],
68	and	CC	O	and	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l2048t3618r2148b3667],
69	C.	NNP	O	C.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l10t3687r68b3736],
70	Eng	NNP	O	Eng	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l92t3688r221b3750],
71	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l92t3688r221b3750],
72	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l244t3687r542b3750],
73	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l564t3687r625b3736],
74	Ohio	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ohio	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l642t3687r797b3745],
75	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l642t3687r797b3745],
76	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l823t3687r885b3736],
77	Rennert	NNP	PERSON	Rennert	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l910t3688r1150b3745],
78	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l910t3688r1150b3745],
79	Technion	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Technion	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1173t3687r1455b3745],
80	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1173t3687r1455b3745],
81	Haifa	NNP	LOCATION	Haifa	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1478t3687r1649b3745],
82	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1478t3687r1649b3745],
83	Israel	NNP	LOCATION	Israel	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1673t3687r1845b3745],
84	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1673t3687r1845b3745],
85	F.	NNP	LOCATION	F.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1869t3688r1921b3736],
86	Couch	NNP	LOCATION	Couch	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1947t3687r2146b3745],
87	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1947t3687r2146b3745],
88	Mayo	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mayo	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l9t3756r171b3819],
89	Clinic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Clinic	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l202t3755r389b3814],
90	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l202t3755r389b3814],
91	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l421t3756r461b3805],
92	McLennan	NNP	PERSON	McLennan	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l494t3756r814b3814],
93	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l494t3756r814b3814],
94	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l845t3755r1143b3819],
95	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1172t3755r1233b3804],
96	San	NNP	ORGANIZATION	San	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1259t3756r1362b3805],
97	Francisco	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Francisco	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1389t3755r1680b3814],
98	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1389t3755r1680b3814],
99	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	dep	100	SENT_30	[p2l1713t3756r1776b3805],
100	Provencher	NNP	PERSON	Provencher	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1807t3755r2146b3814],
101	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1807t3755r2146b3814],

1	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l9t10r306b74],
2	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l327t10r388b59],
3	Montreal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Montreal	prep_of	1	SENT_31	[p3l403t10r676b59],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l403t10r676b59],

1	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	nn	2	SENT_32	[p3l80t78r240b127],
2	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l268t94r499b142],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l268t94r499b142],
4	US	NNP	ORGANIZATION	US	nn	6	SENT_32	[p3l531t78r616b128],
5	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	6	SENT_32	[p3l646t78r889b127],
6	Institutes	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Institutes	dep	2	SENT_32	[p3l916t78r1173b127],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1202t78r1263b127],
8	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	prep_of	6	SENT_32	[p3l1285t78r1489b137],
9	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1285t78r1489b137],
10	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	2	SENT_32	[p3l1521t78r1680b127],
11	numbers	NNS	O	number	dep	10	SENT_32	[p3l1706t78r1964b127],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1706t78r1964b127],
13	1R01	NN	O	1r01	nn	14	SENT_32	[p3l2002t78r2141b127],
14	CA63682	NN	O	ca63682	dep	2	SENT_32	[p3l10t148r298b206],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l10t148r298b206],
16	CA63678	NN	O	ca63678	appos	14	SENT_32	[p3l348t148r636b206],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l348t148r636b206],
18	CA57601	NN	O	ca57601	appos	14	SENT_32	[p3l686t147r974b206],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l686t147r974b206],
20	CA61231	NN	O	ca61231	appos	14	SENT_32	[p3l1024t148r1313b206],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1024t148r1313b206],
22	CA74415	NN	O	ca74415	appos	14	SENT_32	[p3l1363t147r1651b206],
23	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1363t147r1651b206],
24	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	dep	2	SENT_32	[p3l1703t148r1863b197],
25	sponsor	NN	O	sponsor	dep	24	SENT_32	[p3l1912t163r2143b212],
26	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1912t163r2143b212],
27	Canadian	JJ	O	canadian	amod	30	SENT_32	[p3l10t216r276b266],
28	Breast	NN	ORGANIZATION	breast	nn	30	SENT_32	[p3l296t217r473b265],
29	Cancer	NN	ORGANIZATION	cancer	nn	30	SENT_32	[p3l491t217r688b266],
30	Alliance	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Alliance	dep	2	SENT_32	[p3l705t216r955b275],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l705t216r955b275],
32	The	NNP	O	The	nn	33	SENT_32	[p3l975t216r1082b265],
33	Department	NNP	O	Department	appos	30	SENT_32	[p3l1102t217r1429b280],
34	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1449t216r1509b265],
35	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_32	[p3l1523t216r1606b265],
36	Army	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Army	prep_of	33	SENT_32	[p3l1626t217r1803b280],
37	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1626t217r1803b280],
38	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	nn	39	SENT_32	[p3l1826t217r1983b266],
39	numbers	NNS	O	number	dep	2	SENT_32	[p3l2001t232r2146b265, p3l8t287r137b336],
40	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l2001t232r2146b265, p3l8t287r137b336],
41	DAMD17	NN	O	damd17	dep	39	SENT_32	[p3l161t287r758b345],
42	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l161t287r758b345],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l161t287r758b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l161t287r758b345],

1	94	CD	NUMBER	94	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l161t287r758b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l161t287r758b345],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l161t287r758b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l161t287r758b345],

1	J	NN	O	j	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l161t287r758b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l161t287r758b345],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l161t287r758b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l161t287r758b345],

1	4299	CD	NUMBER	4299	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l161t287r758b345],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l161t287r758b345],
3	DAMD	NN	O	damd	nn	4	SENT_38	[p3l779t287r990b336],
4	l7	NN	O	l7	appos	1	SENT_38	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_39	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],

1	94	CD	NUMBER	94	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],

1	J	NN	O	j	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],

1	4260	CD	NUMBER	4260	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1016t286r1395b345],
3	DAMD	NN	O	damd	nn	4	SENT_44	[p3l1417t287r1627b335],
4	l7	NN	O	l7	appos	1	SENT_44	[p3l1653t287r1857b337],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1653t287r1857b337],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1653t287r1857b337],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1653t287r1857b337],

1	97	CD	NUMBER	97	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1653t287r1857b337],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p3l1653t287r1857b337],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1653t287r1857b337],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p3l1653t287r1857b337],

1	J	NNP	O	J	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1653t287r1857b337],
2	4340	CD	NUMBER	4340	dep	1	SENT_48	[p3l1874t287r2025b336],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p3l1874t287r2025b336],

1	*	NN	O	*	nn	2	SENT_49	[p3l84t353r608b419],
2	Correspondence	NN	O	correspondence	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l84t353r608b419],
3	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l630t359r705b405],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l630t359r705b405],
5	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	prep_to	2	SENT_49	[p3l731t356r917b405],
6	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l938t355r1020b404],
7	Research	NNP	O	Research	prep_for	5	SENT_49	[p3l1038t355r1298b404],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1317t355r1371b404],
9	Women	NNP	O	Women	poss	11	SENT_49	[p3l1390t356r1663b405],
10	’s	POS	O	’s	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1390t356r1663b405],
11	Health	NNP	O	Health	prep_in	7	SENT_49	[p3l1685t355r1888b414],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1685t355r1888b414],
13	790	CD	NUMBER	790	num	15	SENT_49	[p3l1911t356r2015b405],
14	Bay	NNP	O	Bay	nn	15	SENT_49	[p3l2035t357r2147b419],
15	Street	NNP	O	Street	appos	5	SENT_49	[p3l10t426r188b484],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l10t426r188b484],
17	7th	NNP	ORDINAL	7th	nn	18	SENT_49	[p3l213t426r302b475],
18	Floor	NNP	O	Floor	appos	15	SENT_49	[p3l324t425r492b484],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l324t425r492b484],
20	Toronto	NNP	LOCATION	Toronto	appos	15	SENT_49	[p3l515t427r758b484],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l515t427r758b484],
22	ON	NNP	O	ON	appos	15	SENT_49	[p3l784t426r898b484],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l784t426r898b484],
24	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	nn	26	SENT_49	[p3l924t426r1135b475],
25	M5G	NN	O	m5g	nn	26	SENT_49	[p3l1157t425r1304b475],
26	1N8	NN	O	1n8	appos	15	SENT_49	[p3l1333t426r1460b475],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p3l1333t426r1460b475],

1	FaX	NN	O	fax	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l1485t427r1662b475],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l1485t427r1662b475],
3	+	CC	O	+	dep	4	SENT_50	[p3l1485t427r1662b475],
4	1-416-351-3767	CD	NUMBER	1-416-351-3767	dep	1	SENT_50	[p3l1678t425r2144b475],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p3l1678t425r2144b475],

1	E	NN	O	e	nn	3	SENT_51	[p3l8t495r216b545],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	3	SENT_51	[p3l8t495r216b545],
3	mail	NN	O	mail	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l8t495r216b545],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l8t495r216b545],
5	steven	NN	O	steven	dep	3	SENT_51	[p3l243t495r659b555],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p3l243t495r659b555],

1	narod	NN	O	narod	nsubj	3	SENT_52	[p3l243t495r659b555],
2	@	SYM	O	@	dep	3	SENT_52	[p3l243t495r659b555],
3	sw	NN	O	sw	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l669t511r825b545],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l669t511r825b545],

1	ca	MD	O	can	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l669t511r825b545],

1	Received	VBN	O	receive	dep	15	SENT_54	[p3l79t565r343b614],
2	24	CD	DATE	24	dobj	1	SENT_54	[p3l363t565r431b613],
3	March	NNP	DATE	March	tmod	2	SENT_54	[p3l451t565r635b614],
4	2005	CD	DATE	2005	num	3	SENT_54	[p3l655t564r810b623],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l655t564r810b623],
6	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	dep	2	SENT_54	[p3l833t565r1101b629],
7	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1121t565r1250b614],
8	revision	NN	O	revision	prep_after	6	SENT_54	[p3l1267t565r1496b614],
9	15	CD	DATE	15	num	8	SENT_54	[p3l1522t565r1580b614],
10	June	NNP	DATE	June	tmod	6	SENT_54	[p3l1603t566r1730b614],
11	2005	CD	DATE	2005	num	10	SENT_54	[p3l1752t564r1888b614],
12	DOI	NNP	O	DOI	tmod	1	SENT_54	[p3l80t634r203b683],
13	10.1002	CD	NUMBER	10.1002	num	12	SENT_54	[p3l230t633r737b697],
14	/	:	O	/	punct	15	SENT_54	[p3l230t633r737b697],
15	ijc	NN	O	ijc	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l230t633r737b697],
16	.21536	CD	NUMBER	.21536	num	15	SENT_54	[p3l230t633r737b697],
17	Published	VBN	O	publish	partmod	15	SENT_54	[p3l79t703r358b752],
18	online	NN	O	online	prep	17	SENT_54	[p3l406t703r580b752],
19	5	CD	DATE	5	dep	18	SENT_54	[p3l629t703r658b752],
20	December	NNP	DATE	December	tmod	17	SENT_54	[p3l709t703r1001b752],
21	2005	CD	DATE	2005	num	20	SENT_54	[p3l1047t703r1183b752],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1234t703r1288b751],
23	Wiley	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wiley	nn	24	SENT_54	[p3l1334t703r1506b767],
24	InterScience	NNP	ORGANIZATION	InterScience	prep_in	17	SENT_54	[p3l1554t703r1907b752],
25	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	26	SENT_54	[p3l1957t703r2144b764],
26	WWW	NNP	O	WWW	dep	24	SENT_54	[p3l1957t703r2144b764],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1957t703r2144b764],

1	interscience.Wiley.com	NNP	O	interscience.Wiley.com	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l9t771r701b835],
2	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_55	[p3l9t771r701b835],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l9t771r701b835],

1	2282	CD	DATE	2282	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l196t910r269b936],
2	GRONWALD	NNP	O	GRONWALD	nn	4	SENT_56	[p3l1089t916r1257b936],
3	ET	NNP	O	ET	nn	4	SENT_56	[p3l1267t916r1303b936],
4	AL.	NNP	O	AL.	dep	1	SENT_56	[p3l1310t916r1350b936],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1310t916r1350b936],

1	TABLE	NN	O	table	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l656t951r746b970],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	1	SENT_57	[p3l761t951r793b970],
3	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l761t951r793b970],
4	CHARACTERISTICS	NNS	O	characteristic	dep	1	SENT_57	[p3l803t951r1046b970],
5	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1061t951r1095b970],
6	BILATERAL	JJ	O	bilateral	amod	7	SENT_57	[p3l1109t951r1258b970],
7	CASES	NNS	O	case	dep	1	SENT_57	[p3l1272t945r1362b970],
8	‘	VBP	O	‘	rcmod	4	SENT_57	[p3l1272t945r1362b970],
9	AND	CC	O	and	nsubj	11	SENT_57	[p3l1379t951r1436b970],
10	UNILATERAL	JJ	O	unilateral	amod	11	SENT_57	[p3l1450t951r1620b970],
11	CONTROLS2	NN	O	controls2	xcomp	8	SENT_57	[p3l1635t945r1786b970],

1	Year	NN	DURATION	year	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l108t1208r301b1275],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l329t1206r415b1275],
3	birth	NN	O	birth	nn	5	SENT_58	[p3l435t1206r623b1275],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_58	[p3l654t1206r928b1291],
5	mean	NN	O	mean	prep_of	1	SENT_58	[p3l654t1206r928b1291],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	7	SENT_58	[p3l654t1206r928b1291],
7	Year	NN	DURATION	year	dep	1	SENT_58	[p3l115t1306r307b1375],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l334t1305r421b1375],
9	diagnosis	NN	O	diagnosis	nn	11	SENT_58	[p3l442t1305r814b1396],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_58	[p3l848t1306r1093b1391],
11	mean	NN	O	mean	prep_of	7	SENT_58	[p3l848t1306r1093b1391],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1131t1311r1190b1371],
13	SD	NN	O	sd	nn	15	SENT_58	[p3l1231t1305r1383b1391],
14	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	15	SENT_58	[p3l1231t1305r1383b1391],
15	Year	NN	DURATION	year	dep	7	SENT_58	[p3l115t1406r307b1474],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l334t1405r421b1474],
17	interview	NN	O	interview	nn	19	SENT_58	[p3l442t1405r816b1474],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	19	SENT_58	[p3l849t1405r1094b1490],
19	mean	NN	O	mean	prep_of	15	SENT_58	[p3l849t1405r1094b1490],
20	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1131t1411r1191b1470],
21	SD	NN	O	sd	nn	23	SENT_58	[p3l1232t1405r1383b1490],
22	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	23	SENT_58	[p3l1232t1405r1383b1490],
23	Age	NN	O	age	dep	7	SENT_58	[p3l113t1504r276b1595],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l306t1504r392b1574],
25	1st	JJ	ORDINAL	1st	amod	29	SENT_58	[p3l423t1505r528b1574],
26	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	29	SENT_58	[p3l555t1504r793b1574],
27	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	29	SENT_58	[p3l820t1527r1080b1574],
28	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	29	SENT_58	[p3l1110t1505r1355b1591],
29	mean	NN	O	mean	prep_of	23	SENT_58	[p3l1110t1505r1355b1591],
30	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1393t1511r1452b1571],
31	SD	NN	O	sd	nn	33	SENT_58	[p3l1493t1504r1645b1591],
32	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	33	SENT_58	[p3l1493t1504r1645b1591],
33	Age	NN	O	age	dep	7	SENT_58	[p3l114t1605r276b1695],
34	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l306t1604r392b1675],
35	2nd	JJ	ORDINAL	2nd	amod	39	SENT_58	[p3l415t1605r561b1675],
36	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	39	SENT_58	[p3l588t1605r826b1675],
37	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	39	SENT_58	[p3l854t1627r1113b1675],
38	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	39	SENT_58	[p3l1144t1605r1389b1691],
39	mean	NN	O	mean	prep_of	33	SENT_58	[p3l1144t1605r1389b1691],
40	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1427t1611r1486b1671],
41	SD	NN	O	sd	nn	42	SENT_58	[p3l1526t1605r1678b1691],
42	)	NN	O	)	dep	7	SENT_58	[p3l1526t1605r1678b1691],
43	Mutation	NN	O	mutation	nn	45	SENT_58	[p3l114t1703r479b1772],
44	BRCAI	NN	O	brcaus	nn	45	SENT_58	[p3l210t1804r503b1875],
45	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	dep	42	SENT_58	[p3l210t1904r507b1974],

1	Place	NN	O	place	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l113t2004r327b2073],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l358t2004r444b2073],
3	residence	NN	O	residence	prep_of	1	SENT_59	[p3l464t2004r862b2086],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l464t2004r862b2086],
5	N	NN	O	n	appos	3	SENT_59	[p3l889t2006r963b2073],

1	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	Canada	nn	5	SENT_60	[p3l216t2103r513b2172],
2	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	5	SENT_60	[p3l214t2201r484b2272],
3	States	NNP	LOCATION	States	nn	5	SENT_60	[p3l514t2202r746b2272],
4	Europe	NNP	LOCATION	Europe	nn	5	SENT_60	[p3l214t2304r499b2392],
5	Israel	NNP	LOCATION	Israel	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l214t2400r433b2469],

1	Smokers	NNS	O	smoker	dobj	7	SENT_61	[p3l116t2501r459b2570],
2	(	CD	PERCENT	(	num	3	SENT_61	[p3l491t2501r632b2587],
3	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	1	SENT_61	[p3l491t2501r632b2587],
4	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	5	SENT_61	[p3l491t2501r632b2587],
5	Parity	NN	O	parity	dep	3	SENT_61	[p3l113t2599r350b2690],
6	(	FW	O	(	nsubj	7	SENT_61	[p3l381t2600r656b2686],
7	mean	VB	O	mean	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l381t2600r656b2686],
8	)	RB	O	)	advmod	11	SENT_61	[p3l381t2600r656b2686],
9	Oral	JJ	O	oral	amod	10	SENT_61	[p3l115t2700r288b2769],
10	contraceptives	NNS	O	contraceptive	nsubj	11	SENT_61	[p3l318t2700r892b2789],
11	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	7	SENT_61	[p3l925t2700r1155b2785],
12	ever	RB	O	ever	advmod	11	SENT_61	[p3l925t2700r1155b2785],
13	)	RB	O	)	advmod	11	SENT_61	[p3l925t2700r1155b2785],

1	Bilateral	JJ	O	bilateral	amod	2	SENT_62	[p3l251t2809r524b2865],
2	cases	NNS	O	case	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l547t2827r711b2865],
3	Unilateral	JJ	O	unilateral	amod	4	SENT_62	[p3l1449t2809r1766b2865],
4	controls	NNS	O	control	dep	2	SENT_62	[p3l1788t2809r2041b2865],

1	40.1	CD	NUMBER	40.1	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l309t3327r480b3400],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l528t3334r591b3396],
3	7.5	CD	NUMBER	7.5	number	4	SENT_63	[p3l631t3327r753b3401],
4	41.0	CD	NUMBER	41.0	dep	1	SENT_63	[p3l1557t3327r1736b3400],
5	i	FW	O	i	dep	4	SENT_63	[p3l1777t3334r1840b3396],
6	7.5	CD	NUMBER	7.5	dep	4	SENT_63	[p3l1879t3327r2002b3401],

1	45.8	CD	NUMBER	45.8	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l309t3452r484b3526],
2	i	FW	O	i	dep	1	SENT_64	[p3l528t3459r591b3522],
3	8.0	CD	NUMBER	8.0	dep	1	SENT_64	[p3l634t3453r757b3526],

1	60.7	CD	PERCENT	60.7	num	2	SENT_65	[p4l311t957r571b1029],
2	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nsubj	12	SENT_65	[p4l311t957r571b1029],
3	62.4	CD	PERCENT	62.4	num	4	SENT_65	[p4l1562t957r1822b1029],
4	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	2	SENT_65	[p4l1562t957r1822b1029],
5	All	DT	O	all	det	6	SENT_65	[p4l387t1068r430b1093],
6	means	NNS	O	means	dep	2	SENT_65	[p4l441t1076r529b1093],
7	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l540t1068r581b1093],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_65	[p4l590t1068r632b1093],
9	controls	NNS	O	control	prep_for	6	SENT_65	[p4l643t1068r755b1093],
10	are	VBP	O	be	cop	12	SENT_65	[p4l766t1076r807b1093],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_65	[p4l818t1068r860b1093],
12	mean	NN	O	mean	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l870t1076r946b1093],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l956t1068r987b1093],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_65	[p4l994t1068r1036b1093],
15	285	CD	NUMBER	285	num	16	SENT_65	[p4l1047t1068r1097b1093],
16	subset	NN	O	subset	prep_of	12	SENT_65	[p4l1110t1068r1196b1093],
17	means	VBZ	O	mean	dep	16	SENT_65	[p4l1205t1076r1302b1093],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p4l1205t1076r1302b1093],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_66	[p4l1314t1068r1367b1093],
2	percentages	NNS	O	percentage	nsubjpass	9	SENT_66	[p4l1377t1072r1543b1100],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l1554t1068r1585b1093],
4	residence	NN	O	residence	prep_of	2	SENT_66	[p4l1592t1068r1725b1093],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l1735t1068r1762b1093],
6	different	JJ	O	different	amod	7	SENT_66	[p4l1772t1068r1821b1093, p4l337t1103r419b1127],
7	countries	NNS	O	country	prep_in	4	SENT_66	[p4l428t1103r556b1127],
8	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_66	[p4l567t1111r634b1127],
9	calculated	VBN	O	calculate	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l645t1103r788b1127],
10	using	VBG	O	use	xcomp	9	SENT_66	[p4l797t1103r873b1135],
11	751	CD	NUMBER	751	num	12	SENT_66	[p4l883t1103r932b1128],
12	individuals	NNS	O	individual	dobj	10	SENT_66	[p4l945t1103r1108b1128],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p4l945t1103r1108b1128],

1	‘	NN	O	‘	nn	2	SENT_67	[p4l375t1131r409b1163],
2	N	NN	O	n	_	0	SENT_67	[p4l375t1131r409b1163],
3	=	JJ	O	=	quantmod	4	SENT_67	[p4l421t1147r442b1155],
4	285	CD	NUMBER	285	num	2	SENT_67	[p4l456t1131r573b1163],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p4l456t1131r573b1163],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p4l456t1131r573b1163],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l456t1131r573b1163],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p4l456t1131r573b1163],

1	2N	NN	O	2n	_	0	SENT_70	[p4l456t1131r573b1163],
2	=	JJ	O	=	amod	3	SENT_70	[p4l584t1147r606b1155],
3	751	CD	NUMBER	751	dep	1	SENT_70	[p4l619t1138r679b1167],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_70	[p4l619t1138r679b1167],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_70	[p4l690t1138r716b1162],
6	285	CD	NUMBER	285	num	7	SENT_70	[p4l727t1138r776b1163],
7	sets	NNS	O	set	prep_in	1	SENT_70	[p4l789t1142r847b1163],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p4l789t1142r847b1163],

1	TABLE	NN	O	table	nn	6	SENT_71	[p4l382t1238r472b1257],
2	II	CD	NUMBER	ii	num	6	SENT_71	[p4l486t1238r507b1257],
3	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	6	SENT_71	[p4l516t1249r529b1252],
4	ASSOCIATION	NNP	O	ASSOCIATION	nn	6	SENT_71	[p4l539t1238r717b1257],
5	BETWEEN	NNP	O	BETWEEN	nn	6	SENT_71	[p4l731t1238r860b1257],
6	TAMOXIFEN	NNP	O	TAMOXIFEN	_	0	SENT_71	[p4l873t1238r1031b1257],
7	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_71	[p4l1045t1238r1102b1257],
8	THE	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_71	[p4l1117t1238r1169b1257],
9	RISK	NN	O	risk	conj_and	6	SENT_71	[p4l1183t1238r1243b1257],
10	OF	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_71	[p4l1258t1238r1291b1257],
11	CONTRALATERAL	JJ	O	contralateral	amod	12	SENT_71	[p4l1305t1238r1538b1257],
12	BREAST	NN	O	breast	prep_of	9	SENT_71	[p4l1552t1238r1655b1257],
13	CANCER	NNP	O	CANCER	dep	6	SENT_71	[p4l1669t1238r1777b1257],

1	Case	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Case	nn	2	SENT_72	[p4l651t1295r702b1313],
2	Co	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Co	dep	9	SENT_72	[p4l808t1294r838b1313],
3	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	5	SENT_72	[p4l882t1294r889b1313],
4	Univariate	JJ	O	univariate	amod	5	SENT_72	[p4l1055t1291r1169b1310],
5	analysis	NN	O	analysis	dep	2	SENT_72	[p4l1177t1291r1262b1315],
6	Multivariate	JJ	O	multivariate	amod	7	SENT_72	[p4l1488t1291r1621b1310],
7	analysis	NN	O	analysis	dep	9	SENT_72	[p4l1629t1291r1714b1315],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	9	SENT_72	[p4l622t1322r649b1345],
9	N	NN	O	n	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l622t1322r649b1345],
10	=	JJ	O	=	dep	9	SENT_72	[p4l658t1328r674b1334],
11	285	CD	NUMBER	285	number	12	SENT_72	[p4l684t1321r732b1345],
12	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	17	SENT_72	[p4l684t1321r732b1345],
13	(	NN	O	(	nn	17	SENT_72	[p4l793t1322r820b1345],
14	N	NN	O	n	nn	17	SENT_72	[p4l793t1322r820b1345],
15	=	JJ	O	=	amod	17	SENT_72	[p4l829t1328r845b1335],
16	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	17	SENT_72	[p4l885t1322r903b1345],
17	)	NN	O	)	dep	10	SENT_72	[p4l885t1322r903b1345],

1	OR	NN	O	or	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l1028t1337r1064b1356],
2	(	CD	PERCENT	(	number	3	SENT_73	[p4l1072t1337r1128b1360],
3	95	CD	PERCENT	95	num	4	SENT_73	[p4l1072t1337r1128b1360],
4	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	1	SENT_73	[p4l1072t1337r1128b1360],
5	CI	NN	O	ci	nn	8	SENT_73	[p4l1137t1337r1171b1360],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	8	SENT_73	[p4l1137t1337r1171b1360],
7	p-value	NN	O	p-value	nn	8	SENT_73	[p4l1263t1337r1346b1361],
8	OR	NN	O	or	dep	4	SENT_73	[p4l1460t1337r1496b1356],
9	(	CD	PERCENT	(	num	12	SENT_73	[p4l1504t1337r1560b1360],
10	95	CD	PERCENT	95	number	11	SENT_73	[p4l1504t1337r1560b1360],
11	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	12	SENT_73	[p4l1504t1337r1560b1360],
12	CI	NN	O	ci	dep	8	SENT_73	[p4l1569t1337r1603b1360],
13	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	14	SENT_73	[p4l1569t1337r1603b1360],
14	p-value	NN	O	p-value	dep	1	SENT_73	[p4l1706t1337r1789b1361],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	2	SENT_74	[p4l370t1394r414b1419],
2	subjects	NNS	O	subject	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l425t1394r536b1426],
3	Never	RB	O	never	dep	6	SENT_74	[p4l405t1430r491b1454],
4	250	CD	NUMBER	250	num	5	SENT_74	[p4l647t1429r698b1454],
5	566	CD	NUMBER	566	pobj	3	SENT_74	[p4l823t1429r874b1454],
6	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	2	SENT_74	[p4l1054t1429r1064b1453],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l1070t1429r1111b1454],

1	oo	NN	O	oo	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l1070t1429r1111b1454],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	1	SENT_75	[p4l1505t1429r1514b1453],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l1521t1429r1562b1454],

1	oo	NN	O	oo	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1521t1429r1562b1454],
2	Ever	RB	O	ever	advmod	5	SENT_76	[p4l405t1470r472b1494],
3	35	CD	NUMBER	35	number	4	SENT_76	[p4l664t1469r695b1494],
4	185	CD	NUMBER	185	pobj	2	SENT_76	[p4l826t1469r873b1494],
5	0.45	CD	NUMBER	0.45	dep	1	SENT_76	[p4l964t1469r1023b1494],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1469r1197b1500],
7	O.	NNP	O	O.	nn	20	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1469r1197b1500],
8	29	CD	NUMBER	29	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1469r1197b1500],
9	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1469r1197b1500],
10	0.70	CD	NUMBER	0.70	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1469r1197b1500],
11	)	NN	O	)	nn	20	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1469r1197b1500],
12	0.0004	CD	NUMBER	0.0004	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1258t1469r1354b1494],
13	0.47	CD	NUMBER	0.47	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1414t1469r1474b1495],
14	(	NN	O	(	nn	20	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1469r1647b1500],
15	0.30	CD	NUMBER	0.30	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1469r1647b1500],
16	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1469r1647b1500],
17	0.74	CD	NUMBER	0.74	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1469r1647b1500],
18	)	NN	O	)	nn	20	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1469r1647b1500],
19	0.001	CD	NUMBER	0.001	num	20	SENT_76	[p4l1710t1469r1785b1494],
20	BRCAI	NN	O	brcaus	rcmod	5	SENT_76	[p4l369t1510r472b1535],
21	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	npadvmod	22	SENT_76	[p4l485t1510r590b1535],
22	Never	RB	O	never	advmod	5	SENT_76	[p4l405t1551r491b1576],
23	204	CD	NUMBER	204	number	24	SENT_76	[p4l647t1551r698b1576],
24	483	CD	NUMBER	483	num	26	SENT_76	[p4l822t1551r872b1576],
25	1.00	CD	NUMBER	1.00	number	26	SENT_76	[p4l1054t1551r1111b1576],
26	1.00	CD	NUMBER	1.00	dep	1	SENT_76	[p4l1262t1551r1319b1576],
27	1.00	CD	NUMBER	1.00	npadvmod	28	SENT_76	[p4l1713t1551r1770b1576],
28	Ever	RB	O	ever	advmod	26	SENT_76	[p4l405t1592r472b1616],
29	24	CD	NUMBER	24	number	30	SENT_76	[p4l663t1591r697b1616],
30	137	CD	NUMBER	137	dep	1	SENT_76	[p4l826t1591r873b1616],
31	0.48	CD	NUMBER	0.48	num	32	SENT_76	[p4l964t1591r1023b1616],
32	(	NN	O	(	dep	30	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1591r1197b1622],
33	0.29	CD	NUMBER	0.29	number	34	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1591r1197b1622],
34	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	1	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1591r1197b1622],
35	0.79	CD	NUMBER	0.79	num	36	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1591r1197b1622],
36	)	NN	O	)	dep	34	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1591r1197b1622],
37	0.004	CD	NUMBER	0.004	num	39	SENT_76	[p4l1258t1591r1336b1616],
38	0.50	CD	NUMBER	0.50	num	39	SENT_76	[p4l1414t1591r1475b1616],
39	(	NN	O	(	dep	1	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1591r1647b1622],
40	0.30	CD	NUMBER	0.30	num	41	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1591r1647b1622],
41	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	39	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1591r1647b1622],
42	0.85	CD	NUMBER	0.85	num	43	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1591r1647b1622],
43	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_76	[p4l1486t1591r1647b1622],
44	0.01	CD	NUMBER	0.01	num	46	SENT_76	[p4l1710t1591r1767b1616],
45	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	nn	46	SENT_76	[p4l369t1632r473b1657],
46	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	tmod	43	SENT_76	[p4l485t1632r590b1657],
47	Never	RB	O	never	advmod	46	SENT_76	[p4l405t1673r491b1698],
48	46	CD	NUMBER	46	num	49	SENT_76	[p4l663t1673r697b1698],
49	83	CD	NUMBER	83	pobj	47	SENT_76	[p4l841t1673r872b1698],
50	1.00	CD	NUMBER	1.00	number	51	SENT_76	[p4l1054t1673r1111b1698],
51	1.00	CD	NUMBER	1.00	dep	1	SENT_76	[p4l1713t1673r1770b1698],
52	Ever	RB	O	ever	prep	51	SENT_76	[p4l405t1715r472b1739],
53	11	CD	NUMBER	11	num	54	SENT_76	[p4l666t1714r694b1739],
54	48	CD	NUMBER	48	pobj	52	SENT_76	[p4l840t1714r873b1739],
55	0.39	CD	NUMBER	0.39	num	56	SENT_76	[p4l964t1714r1024b1739],
56	(	NN	O	(	dep	1	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1714r1197b1745],
57	0.16	CD	NUMBER	0.16	dep	56	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1714r1197b1745],
58	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l1035t1714r1197b1745],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1035t1714r1197b1745],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1035t1714r1197b1745],

1	O.	NNP	O	O.	dep	8	SENT_78	[p4l1035t1714r1197b1745],
2	94	CD	NUMBER	94	number	3	SENT_78	[p4l1035t1714r1197b1745],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_78	[p4l1035t1714r1197b1745],
4	0.03	CD	NUMBER	0.03	num	5	SENT_78	[p4l1258t1714r1317b1739],
5	0.42	CD	NUMBER	0.42	dep	3	SENT_78	[p4l1414t1714r1475b1739],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	8	SENT_78	[p4l1486t1714r1647b1745],
7	0.17	CD	NUMBER	0.17	num	8	SENT_78	[p4l1486t1714r1647b1745],
8	—	NN	O	—	dep	11	SENT_78	[p4l1486t1714r1647b1745],
9	1.02	CD	NUMBER	1.02	dep	8	SENT_78	[p4l1486t1714r1647b1745],
10	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	11	SENT_78	[p4l1486t1714r1647b1745],
11	0.05	CD	NUMBER	0.05	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l1710t1714r1769b1739],

1	TABLE	NN	O	table	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l15t1940r208b1980],
2	III	CD	NUMBER	iii	num	1	SENT_79	[p4l239t1940r304b1980],
3	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	4	SENT_79	[p4l323t1963r353b1969],
4	TAMOXIFEN	NN	O	tamoxifen	dep	1	SENT_79	[p4l372t1940r710b1980],
5	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l740t1940r862b1980],
6	THE	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_79	[p4l893t1941r1004b1980],
7	RISK	NN	O	risk	conj_and	4	SENT_79	[p4l1034t1940r1164b1980],
8	OF	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l1195t1940r1266b1980],
9	BILATERAL	JJ	O	bilateral	amod	11	SENT_79	[p4l1296t1940r1615b1980],
10	BREAST	NN	O	breast	nn	11	SENT_79	[p4l1645t1940r1864b1980],
11	CANCER	NNP	O	CANCER	prep_of	7	SENT_79	[p4l1896t1940r2140b1987],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l1896t1940r2140b1987],

1	BY	IN	O	by	dep	6	SENT_80	[p4l246t1999r325b2037],
2	OOPHORECTOMY	NNP	O	OOPHORECTOMY	nn	3	SENT_80	[p4l356t1998r833b2038],
3	STATUS	NNP	O	STATUS	pobj	1	SENT_80	[p4l864t1998r1076b2038],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_80	[p4l1111t1998r1562b2047],
5	MULTIVARIATE	NNP	O	MULTIVARIATE	nn	6	SENT_80	[p4l1111t1998r1562b2047],
6	ANALYSES	NNS	O	analysis	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l1592t1998r1908b2047],
7	)	IN	O	)	prep	6	SENT_80	[p4l1592t1998r1908b2047],

1	Status	NN	O	status	nn	3	SENT_81	[p4l454t2109r591b2149],
2	Odds	NNS	O	odds	nn	3	SENT_81	[p4l1062t2109r1180b2149],
3	ratio	NN	O	ratio	_	0	SENT_81	[p4l1195t2109r1300b2149],
4	(	CD	PERCENT	(	number	5	SENT_81	[p4l1476t2109r1595b2158],
5	95	CD	PERCENT	95	num	6	SENT_81	[p4l1476t2109r1595b2158],
6	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	3	SENT_81	[p4l1476t2109r1595b2158],
7	CI	NN	O	ci	nn	9	SENT_81	[p4l1614t2109r1687b2158],
8	)	NN	O	)	nn	9	SENT_81	[p4l1614t2109r1687b2158],
9	p	NN	O	p	dep	6	SENT_81	[p4l1874t2109r2050b2160],
10	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	11	SENT_81	[p4l1874t2109r2050b2160],
11	value	NN	O	value	dep	3	SENT_81	[p4l1874t2109r2050b2160],

1	Oophorectomy	NNP	O	Oophorectomy	nn	3	SENT_82	[p4l85t2229r535b2296],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	3	SENT_82	[p4l559t2229r617b2293],
3	n	NN	O	n	dep	11	SENT_82	[p4l559t2229r617b2293],
4	=	JJ	O	=	amod	5	SENT_82	[p4l646t2247r691b2264],
5	26	CD	NUMBER	26	dep	3	SENT_82	[p4l721t2229r816b2293],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	7	SENT_82	[p4l721t2229r816b2293],
7	0.83	CD	NUMBER	0.83	dep	5	SENT_82	[p4l1116t2229r1242b2281],
8	(	NN	O	(	dep	11	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2229r1754b2293],
9	0.24	CD	NUMBER	0.24	num	8	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2229r1754b2293],
10	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	11	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2229r1754b2293],
11	2.89	CD	NUMBER	2.89	dep	22	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2229r1754b2293],
12	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	13	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2229r1754b2293],
13	0.77	CD	NUMBER	0.77	dep	11	SENT_82	[p4l1863t2229r1989b2281],
14	No	DT	O	no	det	17	SENT_82	[p4l88t2305r177b2356],
15	oophorectomy	NN	O	oophorectomy	nn	17	SENT_82	[p4l200t2304r634b2371],
16	(	NN	O	(	nn	17	SENT_82	[p4l657t2304r715b2368],
17	n	NN	O	n	dep	13	SENT_82	[p4l657t2304r715b2368],
18	=	JJ	O	=	amod	13	SENT_82	[p4l745t2322r790b2339],
19	259	CD	NUMBER	259	number	20	SENT_82	[p4l820t2303r953b2368],
20	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	18	SENT_82	[p4l820t2303r953b2368],
21	0.44	CD	NUMBER	0.44	num	22	SENT_82	[p4l1116t2304r1245b2356],
22	(	NN	O	(	dep	26	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2303r1754b2368],
23	0.27	CD	NUMBER	0.27	dep	22	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2303r1754b2368],
24	—	CD	NUMBER	—	number	25	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2303r1754b2368],
25	0.65	CD	NUMBER	0.65	dep	23	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2303r1754b2368],
26	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_82	[p4l1408t2303r1754b2368],
27	0.0009	CD	NUMBER	0.0009	num	26	SENT_82	[p4l1863t2304r2066b2356],

1	counseling	NN	O	counseling	nn	5	SENT_83	[p4l9t2535r352b2607],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l384t2535r496b2591],
3	risk	NN	O	risk	conj_and	1	SENT_83	[p4l524t2535r644b2591],
4	assessment	NN	O	assessment	nn	5	SENT_83	[p4l673t2543r1026b2591],
5	programs	NNS	O	program	nsubjpass	7	SENT_83	[p4l1053t2553r1352b2607],
6	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_83	[p4l1384t2553r1535b2591],
7	offered	VBN	O	offer	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l1567t2535r1795b2591],
8	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l1824t2544r1883b2591],
9	women	NNS	O	woman	prep_to	7	SENT_83	[p4l1914t2553r2147b2591],
10	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l8t2619r162b2675],
11	high-risk	JJ	O	high-risk	amod	12	SENT_83	[p4l185t2619r474b2691],
12	families	NNS	O	family	prep_from	9	SENT_83	[p4l496t2619r768b2675],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l496t2619r768b2675],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_84	[p4l796t2619r918b2675],
2	data	NNS	O	datum	nn	3	SENT_84	[p4l944t2619r1076b2675],
3	center	NN	O	center	nsubj	4	SENT_84	[p4l1099t2628r1294b2675],
4	received	VBD	O	receive	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l1315t2619r1587b2675],
5	information	NN	O	information	dobj	4	SENT_84	[p4l1611t2619r1988b2675],
6	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l2012t2637r2090b2675],
7	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_84	[p4l2114t2637r2148b2675],
8	total	NN	O	total	prep_on	4	SENT_84	[p4l8t2703r148b2759],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l177t2703r246b2759],
10	2,972	CD	NUMBER	2,972	num	11	SENT_84	[p4l269t2703r444b2769],
11	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_of	8	SENT_84	[p4l473t2720r637b2759],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l667t2703r736b2759],
13	invasive	JJ	O	invasive	amod	15	SENT_84	[p4l758t2703r1021b2759],
14	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	15	SENT_84	[p4l1049t2703r1239b2759],
15	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	11	SENT_84	[p4l1266t2721r1474b2759],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l1501t2703r1561b2758],
17	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	prep_in	4	SENT_84	[p4l1588t2703r1824b2759],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l1853t2703r1922b2759],
19	pathogenic	JJ	O	pathogenic	amod	20	SENT_84	[p4l1942t2703r2144b2775, p4l9t2787r178b2859],
20	BRCA1	NN	O	brca1	prep_of	17	SENT_84	[p4l199t2787r433b2844],
21	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l464t2804r529b2843],
22	BRCA2	NN	O	brca2	nn	23	SENT_84	[p4l546t2787r784b2844],
23	mutations	NNS	O	mutation	conj_or	20	SENT_84	[p4l809t2787r1140b2843],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l809t2787r1140b2843],

1	Among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l88t2887r325b2959],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_85	[p4l350t2887r446b2943],
3	2,972	CD	NUMBER	2,972	num	4	SENT_85	[p4l473t2888r648b2953],
4	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_among	7	SENT_85	[p4l674t2905r858b2953],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l674t2905r858b2953],
6	there	EX	O	there	expl	7	SENT_85	[p4l885t2887r1043b2943],
7	were	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l1069t2905r1221b2943],
8	611	CD	NUMBER	611	num	9	SENT_85	[p4l1248t2887r1357b2943],
9	cases	NNS	O	case	nsubj	7	SENT_85	[p4l1390t2905r1554b2943],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l1583t2887r1651b2943],
11	bilateral	JJ	O	bilateral	amod	13	SENT_85	[p4l1670t2887r1932b2943],
12	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	13	SENT_85	[p4l1956t2887r2147b2943],
13	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	9	SENT_85	[p4l9t2989r217b3026],
14	(	CD	PERCENT	(	number	15	SENT_85	[p4l255t2971r526b3039],
15	20.6	CD	PERCENT	20.6	num	16	SENT_85	[p4l255t2971r526b3039],
16	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	13	SENT_85	[p4l255t2971r526b3039],
17	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	16	SENT_85	[p4l255t2971r526b3039],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l255t2971r526b3039],
