1	SHORT	NNP	O	SHORT	nn	2	SENT_1	[p1l700t81r896b122],
2	COMMUNICATION	NNP	O	COMMUNICATION	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l926t81r1446b122],

1	Association	NNP	O	Association	dep	2	SENT_2	[p1l205t198r547b245],
2	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l574t198r828b245],
3	CRHR1	NNP	O	CRHR1	nn	4	SENT_2	[p1l858t197r1057b245],
4	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	pobj	2	SENT_2	[p1l1080t198r1507b256],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1534t198r1640b245],
6	improved	VBD	O	improve	conj_and	2	SENT_2	[p1l1667t198r1945b256],
7	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	8	SENT_2	[p1l281t269r405b327],
8	function	NN	O	function	dobj	6	SENT_2	[p1l429t268r672b315],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l700t269r748b315],
10	response	NN	O	response	prep_in	6	SENT_2	[p1l776t282r1041b327],
11	to	TO	O	to	aux	12	SENT_2	[p1l1063t273r1123b315],
12	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	xcomp	6	SENT_2	[p1l1150t269r1362b315],
13	corticosteroid	NN	O	corticosteroid	dobj	12	SENT_2	[p1l1388t269r1796b315],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1823t269r1871b315],
15	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	13	SENT_2	[p1l782t339r1021b396],
16	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1043t339r1174b385],
17	COPD	NN	O	copd	prep_with	12	SENT_2	[p1l1201t338r1369b385],

1	Woo	NNP	O	Woo	nn	3	SENT_3	[p1l139t474r230b505],
2	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	3	SENT_3	[p1l247t474r278b505],
3	KIM	NNP	O	KIM	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l298t471r395b510],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l298t471r395b510],
5	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	num	8	SENT_3	[p1l298t471r395b510],
6	SEUNG	NNP	O	SEUNG	nn	8	SENT_3	[p1l415t473r535b506],
7	S.	NNP	O	S.	nn	8	SENT_3	[p1l554t473r588b506],
8	SHEEN	NNP	O	SHEEN	appos	3	SENT_3	[p1l607t471r770b510],
9	}	CD	NUMBER	}	num	11	SENT_3	[p1l607t471r770b510],
10	TAE-HYUNG	NNP	O	TAE-HYUNG	nn	11	SENT_3	[p1l786t474r996b505],
11	KIM	NNP	O	KIM	dep	8	SENT_3	[p1l1016t471r1116b510],
12	,3	CD	NUMBER	,3	num	11	SENT_3	[p1l1016t471r1116b510],
13	JIN	NNP	O	JIN	nn	15	SENT_3	[p1l1131t474r1185b505],
14	W.	NNP	O	W.	nn	15	SENT_3	[p1l1203t474r1251b505],
15	HUH	NNP	O	HUH	dep	3	SENT_3	[p1l1271t471r1385b510],
16	,4	CD	NUMBER	,4	num	18	SENT_3	[p1l1271t471r1385b510],
17	JI-HYUN	NNP	O	JI-HYUN	nn	18	SENT_3	[p1l1400t474r1547b505],
18	LEE	NNP	O	LEE	dep	15	SENT_3	[p1l1567t471r1662b510],
19	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	num	21	SENT_3	[p1l1567t471r1662b510],
20	EUN-KYUNG	NNP	O	EUN-KYUNG	nn	21	SENT_3	[p1l1680t474r1892b505],
21	KIM	NNP	O	KIM	dep	15	SENT_3	[p1l1913t471r2012b510],
22	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	num	21	SENT_3	[p1l1913t471r2012b510],

1	JIN	NNP	O	JIN	nn	3	SENT_4	[p1l205t528r259b559],
2	H.	NNP	O	H.	nn	3	SENT_4	[p1l280t528r315b559],
3	LEE	NNP	O	LEE	dep	15	SENT_4	[p1l335t525r431b564],
4	,6	CD	NUMBER	,6	dep	3	SENT_4	[p1l335t525r431b564],
5	SANG-MIN	NNP	O	SANG-MIN	nn	6	SENT_4	[p1l447t527r634b560],
6	LEE	NNP	O	LEE	dep	4	SENT_4	[p1l654t525r748b564],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l654t525r748b564],
8	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	10	SENT_4	[p1l654t525r748b564],
9	SANGYEUB	NNP	O	SANGYEUB	nn	10	SENT_4	[p1l766t527r956b560],
10	LEE	NNP	O	LEE	appos	6	SENT_4	[p1l975t525r1070b564],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l975t525r1070b564],
12	“	CD	NUMBER	“	dep	15	SENT_4	[p1l975t525r1070b564],
13	SEONG	NNP	O	SEONG	nn	15	SENT_4	[p1l1087t527r1208b560],
14	Y.	NNP	O	Y.	nn	15	SENT_4	[p1l1225t528r1255b559],
15	L	NNP	O	L	dep	18	SENT_4	[p1l1276t525r1370b564],
16	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	17	SENT_4	[p1l1276t525r1370b564],
17	M	NN	O	m	dep	15	SENT_4	[p1l1276t525r1370b564],
18	,9	CD	NUMBER	,9	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1276t525r1370b564],
19	TAE	NNP	ORGANIZATION	TAE	nn	21	SENT_4	[p1l1386t528r1453b559],
20	R.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	R.	nn	21	SENT_4	[p1l1472t528r1505b559],
21	SH	NNP	ORGANIZATION	SH	nsubj	22	SENT_4	[p1l1524t525r1662b564],
22	|	VBD	ORGANIZATION	|	rcmod	18	SENT_4	[p1l1524t525r1662b564],
23	N	NN	ORGANIZATION	n	dobj	22	SENT_4	[p1l1524t525r1662b564],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1524t525r1662b564],
25	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	number	26	SENT_4	[p1l1524t525r1662b564],
26	°	CD	NUMBER	°	appos	23	SENT_4	[p1l1524t525r1662b564],
27	Ho	NNP	O	Ho	nn	29	SENT_4	[p1l1680t528r1731b559],
28	I.	NNP	O	I.	nn	29	SENT_4	[p1l1750t528r1767b559],
29	YOON	NNP	O	YOON	dep	26	SENT_4	[p1l1784t525r1944b564],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1784t525r1944b564],
31	“	CD	NUMBER	“	appos	23	SENT_4	[p1l1784t525r1944b564],

1	YEON-MOK	CD	NUMBER	yeon-mok	num	3	SENT_5	[p1l726t582r927b613],
2	OH	NN	O	oh	nn	3	SENT_5	[p1l943t579r1030b613],
3	”	NN	O	”	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l943t579r1030b613],
4	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1045t582r1136b613],
5	SANG	NN	O	sang	conj_and	3	SENT_5	[p1l1153t582r1252b613],
6	D.	NNP	O	D.	nn	7	SENT_5	[p1l1272t582r1307b613],
7	LEE	NNP	O	LEE	dep	3	SENT_5	[p1l1328t579r1424b613],
8	”	IN	O	”	amod	7	SENT_5	[p1l1328t579r1424b613],

1	‘	NNP	O	‘	nn	2	SENT_6	[p1l203t684r426b721],
2	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l203t684r426b721],
3	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l439t685r477b714],
4	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	nn	5	SENT_6	[p1l487t686r621b714],
5	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	prep_of	2	SENT_6	[p1l635t686r803b718],
6	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l635t686r803b718],
7	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	appos	5	SENT_6	[p1l820t685r950b721],
8	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l965t685r1003b714],
9	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	nn	13	SENT_6	[p1l1013t686r1181b718],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1013t686r1181b718],
11	Kangwon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kangwon	appos	13	SENT_6	[p1l1198t686r1363b721],
12	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	13	SENT_6	[p1l1379t686r1528b714],
13	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	prep_of	7	SENT_6	[p1l1543t686r1726b721],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1543t686r1726b721],
15	Chuncheon	NNP	PERSON	Chuncheon	appos	13	SENT_6	[p1l1744t685r1950b718],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1744t685r1950b718],

1	2Department	NN	O	2department	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l106t728r331b765],
2	of	IN	O	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l344t730r381b759],
3	Pulmonary	JJ	O	pulmonary	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l391t731r585b765],
4	and	CC	O	and	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l596t731r663b759],
5	Critical	JJ	O	critical	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l677t730r798b759],
6	Care	NN	O	care	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l812t730r890b759],
7	Medicine	NN	O	medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l905t731r1073b763],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l905t731r1073b763],
9	Ajou	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ajou	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1087t731r1170b765],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1187t731r1366b765],
11	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1379t730r1501b759],
12	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1514t730r1552b759],
13	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1562t731r1730b763],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1562t731r1730b763],
15	Suwon	NNP	LOCATION	Suwon	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1747t730r1878b763],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1747t730r1878b763],
17	3Division	NN	O	3division	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1892t728r2047b759],
18	of	IN	O	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l139t775r177b804],
19	Pulmonology	NNP	O	Pulmonology	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l186t775r427b811],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l186t775r427b811],
21	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l444t775r654b811],
22	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l667t775r705b804],
23	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l714t775r849b804],
24	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l862t775r1030b808],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l862t775r1030b808],
26	Hanyang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hanyang	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1047t775r1203b811],
27	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1220t775r1398b811],
28	Guri	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Guri	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1412t775r1487b804],
29	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1500t775r1652b811],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1500t775r1652b811],
31	Hanyang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hanyang	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1669t775r1825b811],
32	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1841t775r2020b811],
33	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l145t821r274b856],
34	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l289t821r327b849],
35	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l337t821r505b853],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l337t821r505b853],
37	Guri	NNP	LOCATION	Guri	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l523t821r605b853],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l523t821r605b853],
39	‘	NNP	O	‘	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l620t819r844b856],
40	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l620t819r844b856],
41	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l857t821r895b849],
42	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l905t821r1039b849],
43	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1052t821r1221b853],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1052t821r1221b853],
45	llsan	JJ	O	llsan	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1237t821r1317b849],
46	Paik	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Paik	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1333t821r1406b849],
47	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1418t821r1570b856],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1418t821r1570b856],
49	Inje	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inje	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1587t821r1649b856],
50	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1666t821r1849b856],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1666t821r1849b856],
52	Goyang	NNP	O	Goyang	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1867t821r2011b856],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1867t821r2011b856],
54	5Division	NN	O	5division	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l108t864r263b894],
55	of	IN	O	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l279t866r317b894],
56	Pulmonary	JJ	O	pulmonary	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l327t866r520b901],
57	and	CC	O	and	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l532t866r599b894],
58	Critical	JJ	O	critical	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l613t866r733b894],
59	Care	NN	O	care	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l748t866r825b894],
60	Medicine	NN	O	medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l840t866r1009b899],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l840t866r1009b899],
62	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1025t866r1235b901],
63	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1248t866r1286b894],
64	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1296t866r1430b894],
65	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1443t866r1612b899],
66	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1443t866r1612b899],
67	Bundang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bundang	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1628t866r1786b901],
68	CHA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CHA	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1802t866r1876b894],
69	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1892t866r2044b901],
70	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1892t866r2044b901],
71	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l122t910r252b946],
72	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l267t910r305b939],
73	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l315t911r483b943],
74	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l315t911r483b943],
75	Pochon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pochon	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l500t911r630b939],
76	CHA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CHA	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l646t910r721b939],
77	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l739t911r922b946],
78	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l739t911r922b946],
79	Seongnam	NNP	O	Seongnam	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l939t910r1138b946],
80	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l939t910r1138b946],
81	‘	NNP	O	‘	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1152t908r1377b946],
82	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1152t908r1377b946],
83	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1390t910r1428b939],
84	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1438t911r1572b939],
85	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1585t911r1753b943],
86	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1585t911r1753b943],
87	Ewha	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ewha	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1770t911r1865b939],
88	Womans	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Womans	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1883t911r2035b939],
89	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l113t956r292b991],
90	Mokdong	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mokdong	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l305t956r471b991],
91	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l485t956r637b991],
92	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l485t956r637b991],
93	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l655t956r784b991],
94	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l799t956r837b984],
95	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l847t956r1015b989],
96	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l847t956r1015b989],
97	Ewha	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ewha	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1032t956r1127b984],
98	Womans	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Womans	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1145t956r1297b984],
99	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1313t956r1496b991],
100	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1313t956r1496b991],
101	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1513t956r1621b989],
102	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1513t956r1621b989],
103	7Division	NNP	O	7Division	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1635t954r1791b984],
104	of	IN	O	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1807t956r1844b984],
105	Pulmonary	JJ	O	pulmonary	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1854t956r2047b991],
106	and	CC	O	and	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l113t1001r180b1029],
107	Critical	JJ	O	critical	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l194t1000r314b1029],
108	Care	NN	O	care	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l329t1000r406b1029],
109	Medicine	NN	O	medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l421t1001r589b1033],
110	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l421t1001r589b1033],
111	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l606t1001r816b1036],
112	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l829t1000r867b1029],
113	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l877t1001r1011b1029],
114	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1024t1001r1192b1033],
115	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1024t1001r1192b1033],
116	Seoul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Seoul	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1209t1000r1310b1029],
117	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1324t1001r1472b1029],
118	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1488t1001r1667b1036],
119	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1680t1000r1810b1036],
120	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1825t1000r1863b1029],
121	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1873t1001r2041b1033],
122	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1873t1001r2041b1033],
123	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l103t1046r230b1074],
124	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l244t1046r403b1074],
125	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l419t1046r568b1079],
126	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l419t1046r568b1079],
127	Seoul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Seoul	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l585t1046r686b1074],
128	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l700t1046r848b1074],
129	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l863t1046r1042b1081],
130	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1055t1046r1207b1081],
131	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1055t1046r1207b1081],
132	Lung	NN	ORGANIZATION	lung	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1223t1046r1310b1081],
133	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1325t1046r1475b1079],
134	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1325t1046r1475b1079],
135	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1491t1046r1630b1074],
136	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1643t1046r1802b1074],
137	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	139	SENT_7	[p1l1819t1046r1938b1079],
138	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1819t1046r1938b1079],
139	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1954t1046r2055b1074],

1	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l126t1136r336b1171],
2	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l349t1135r387b1164],
3	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l396t1136r530b1164],
4	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l544t1136r712b1168],
5	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l544t1136r712b1168],
6	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l730t1135r859b1171],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l875t1135r913b1164],
8	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l922t1136r1090b1168],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l922t1136r1090b1168],
10	Korea	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Korea	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1107t1136r1208b1164],
11	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1226t1136r1405b1171],
12	Anam	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Anam	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1414t1136r1520b1164],
13	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1536t1136r1687b1171],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1536t1136r1687b1171],
15	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1704t1135r1812b1168],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1704t1135r1812b1168],
17	9Division	NN	O	9division	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1826t1133r1981b1164],
18	of	IN	O	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1998t1135r2035b1164],
19	Pulmonary	JJ	O	pulmonary	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l107t1181r301b1216],
20	and	CC	O	and	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l313t1181r379b1209],
21	Critical	JJ	O	critical	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l393t1180r514b1209],
22	Care	NN	O	care	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l528t1180r606b1209],
23	Medicine	NN	O	medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l621t1181r789b1213],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l621t1181r789b1213],
25	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l806t1181r1016b1216],
26	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1029t1180r1067b1209],
27	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1076t1181r1244b1213],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1076t1181r1244b1213],
29	Kangbuk	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kangbuk	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1261t1181r1417b1216],
30	Samsung	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Samsung	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1430t1180r1596b1216],
31	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1610t1181r1762b1216],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1610t1181r1762b1216],
33	Sungkyunkwan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sungkyunkwan	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1779t1180r2048b1216],
34	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l133t1226r312b1261],
35	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l324t1225r446b1254],
36	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l460t1225r498b1254],
37	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l507t1226r676b1258],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l507t1226r676b1258],
39	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l692t1225r800b1258],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l692t1225r800b1258],
41	“	NNP	O	“	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l816t1223r1052b1261],
42	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l816t1223r1052b1261],
43	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1065t1225r1103b1254],
44	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1113t1226r1247b1254],
45	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1260t1226r1429b1258],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1260t1226r1429b1258],
47	Kangnam	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kangnam	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1445t1226r1612b1261],
48	Sacred	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sacred	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1628t1225r1751b1254],
49	Heart	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Heart	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1763t1226r1859b1254],
50	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1872t1226r2023b1261],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1872t1226r2023b1261],
52	Hallym	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hallym	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l120t1271r241b1306],
53	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l259t1271r438b1306],
54	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l451t1270r581b1306],
55	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l596t1270r634b1299],
56	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l644t1271r812b1303],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l644t1271r812b1303],
58	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l829t1270r936b1303],
59	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l829t1270r936b1303],
60	“	NNP	O	“	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l953t1269r1188b1306],
61	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l953t1269r1188b1306],
62	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1201t1270r1239b1299],
63	Internal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Internal	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1249t1271r1383b1299],
64	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1397t1271r1565b1303],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1397t1271r1565b1303],
66	Seoul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Seoul	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1582t1270r1683b1299],
67	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1696t1271r1845b1299],
68	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1860t1271r2039b1306],
69	Bundang	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bundang	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l93t1316r251b1351],
70	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l265t1316r417b1351],
71	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l265t1316r417b1351],
72	Seoul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Seoul	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l434t1315r535b1344],
73	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l548t1316r697b1344],
74	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l712t1316r891b1351],
75	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l904t1315r1034b1351],
76	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1049t1315r1087b1344],
77	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1097t1316r1265b1348],
78	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1097t1316r1265b1348],
79	Seongnam	NNP	O	Seongnam	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1282t1315r1481b1351],
80	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1282t1315r1481b1351],
81	and	CC	O	and	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1497t1316r1564b1344],
82	“	NNP	O	“	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1576t1313r1812b1351],
83	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1576t1313r1812b1351],
84	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1825t1315r1863b1344],
85	Pulmonary	JJ	ORGANIZATION	pulmonary	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1873t1316r2066b1351],
86	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l153t1360r220b1388],
87	Critical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	critical	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l234t1360r355b1388],
88	Care	NN	ORGANIZATION	care	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l369t1360r447b1388],
89	Medicine	NN	ORGANIZATION	medicine	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l462t1360r630b1393],
90	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l462t1360r630b1393],
91	and	CC	O	and	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l646t1360r713b1388],
92	Clinical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	clinical	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l727t1360r854b1388],
93	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l867t1360r1026b1388],
94	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1043t1360r1158b1388],
95	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1172t1360r1221b1388],
96	Chronic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	chronic	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1234t1360r1369b1388],
97	Obstructive	JJ	ORGANIZATION	obstructive	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1384t1360r1584b1388],
98	Airway	NN	ORGANIZATION	airway	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1596t1360r1724b1395],
99	Diseases	NNS	ORGANIZATION	disease	dep	101	SENT_9	[p1l1736t1360r1898b1393],
100	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1736t1360r1898b1393],
101	Asan	NNP	O	Asan	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1912t1360r2001b1388],

1	ABSTRACT	NN	O	abstract	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l10t1609r583b1683],

1	Background	NN	O	background	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l16t1760r489b1838],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l538t1760r687b1822],
3	objective	NN	O	objective	conj_and	1	SENT_12	[p1l738t1760r1114b1837],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l738t1760r1114b1837],
5	Inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	csubjpass	8	SENT_12	[p1l1198t1759r1497b1822],
6	corticosteroids	NNS	O	corticosteroid	dobj	5	SENT_12	[p1l1549t1759r2132b1822],
7	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_12	[p1l12t1870r132b1913],
8	used	VBN	O	use	dep	1	SENT_12	[p1l172t1850r354b1913],
9	to	TO	O	to	aux	10	SENT_12	[p1l394t1860r469b1913],
10	treat	VB	O	treat	xcomp	8	SENT_12	[p1l511t1860r695b1913],
11	COPD	NNP	O	COPD	dobj	10	SENT_12	[p1l736t1852r970b1914],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1014t1850r1160b1913],
13	asthma	NN	O	asthma	dobj	10	SENT_12	[p1l1201t1850r1509b1913],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1201t1850r1509b1913],

1	An	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_13	[p1l1544t1854r1653b1913],
2	association	NN	O	association	nsubj	17	SENT_13	[p1l1694t1851r2133b1913],
3	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l9t1942r337b2006],
4	sequence	NN	O	sequence	prep_between	2	SENT_13	[p1l400t1962r761b2024],
5	variants	NNS	O	variant	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l820t1944r1139b2006],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1201t1944r1279b2005],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_13	[p1l1341t1942r1465b2006],
8	corticotrophinreleasing	NN	O	corticotrophinreleasing	nn	10	SENT_13	[p1l1528t1942r2129b2024, p1l10t2034r365b2117],
9	hormone	NN	O	hormone	nn	10	SENT_13	[p1l423t2034r785b2098],
10	receptor	NN	O	receptor	prep_in	5	SENT_13	[p1l846t2045r1176b2116],
11	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	12	SENT_13	[p1l1242t2039r1272b2097],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	10	SENT_13	[p1l1346t2037r1676b2108],
13	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	nn	15	SENT_13	[p1l1346t2037r1676b2108],
14	)	NN	O	)	nn	15	SENT_13	[p1l1346t2037r1676b2108],
15	gene	NN	O	gene	dep	12	SENT_13	[p1l1743t2053r1925b2117],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1987t2034r2133b2098],
17	improved	VBD	O	improve	conj_and	5	SENT_13	[p1l10t2126r385b2208],
18	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	19	SENT_13	[p1l432t2126r609b2209],
19	function	NN	O	function	dobj	17	SENT_13	[p1l654t2126r988b2190],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1036t2128r1113b2189],
21	asthmatics	NNS	O	asthmatic	prep_in	17	SENT_13	[p1l1163t2126r1586b2190],
22	treated	VBN	O	treat	partmod	21	SENT_13	[p1l1635t2126r1913b2190],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1957t2126r2133b2190],
24	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	prepc_with	22	SENT_13	[p1l10t2218r307b2282],
25	corticosteroids	NNS	O	corticosteroid	nsubjpass	27	SENT_13	[p1l360t2218r943b2282],
26	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	27	SENT_13	[p1l994t2238r1141b2282],
27	reported	VBN	O	report	ccomp	24	SENT_13	[p1l1196t2218r1535b2300],
28	recently	RB	DATE	recently	advmod	27	SENT_13	[p1l1588t2218r1917b2301],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1588t2218r1917b2301],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_14	[p1l1966t2218r2133b2282],
2	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	3	SENT_14	[p1l11t2311r227b2393],
3	investigated	VBD	O	investigate	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l247t2311r721b2393],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_14	[p1l744t2311r868b2374],
5	association	NN	O	association	dobj	3	SENT_14	[p1l894t2312r1332b2374],
6	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1355t2311r1683b2374],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_14	[p1l1707t2311r1831b2374],
8	change	NN	O	change	prep_between	5	SENT_14	[p1l1855t2311r2133b2393],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l10t2403r88b2465],
10	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	11	SENT_14	[p1l110t2402r286b2485],
11	function	NN	O	function	prep_in	8	SENT_14	[p1l307t2402r640b2465],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l662t2403r739b2465],
13	response	NN	O	response	prep_in	3	SENT_14	[p1l761t2422r1109b2484],
14	to	TO	O	to	aux	15	SENT_14	[p1l1132t2412r1207b2465],
15	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	xcomp	3	SENT_14	[p1l1231t2402r1527b2465],
16	corticosteroids	NNS	O	corticosteroid	dobj	15	SENT_14	[p1l1549t2402r2132b2465],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l12t2494r158b2558],
18	single-nucleotide	JJ	O	single-nucleotide	amod	20	SENT_14	[p1l238t2494r916b2577],
19	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	nn	20	SENT_14	[p1l1001t2497r1271b2558],
20	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	dobj	15	SENT_14	[p1l1358t2494r1974b2577],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l2056t2496r2133b2557],
22	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	15	SENT_14	[p1l10t2588r327b2668],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l348t2586r524b2650],
24	COPD	NN	O	copd	prep_with	22	SENT_14	[p1l548t2589r802b2650],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l548t2589r802b2650],

1	Methods	NNS	O	method	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l16t2680r383b2742],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l16t2680r383b2742],
3	COPD	NN	O	copd	nn	4	SENT_15	[p1l468t2681r702b2742],
4	patients	NNS	O	patient	dep	1	SENT_15	[p1l763t2680r1080b2760],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_15	[p1l1145t2682r1430b2752],
6	n	NN	O	n	npadvmod	7	SENT_15	[p1l1145t2682r1430b2752],
7	=	JJ	O	=	amod	4	SENT_15	[p1l1145t2682r1430b2752],
8	87	CD	NUMBER	87	num	9	SENT_15	[p1l1145t2682r1430b2752],
9	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	16	SENT_15	[p1l1145t2682r1430b2752],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1492t2678r1668b2742],
11	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_15	[p1l1728t2698r1772b2742],
12	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	14	SENT_15	[p1l1827t2680r2133b2760],
13	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	14	SENT_15	[p1l11t2770r348b2853],
14	history	NN	O	history	prep_with	9	SENT_15	[p1l382t2770r663b2853],
15	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_15	[p1l692t2790r878b2834],
16	recruited	VBN	O	recruit	rcmod	4	SENT_15	[p1l914t2770r1273b2834],
17	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1310t2770r1500b2834],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_15	[p1l1537t2770r1660b2834],
19	pulmonary	JJ	O	pulmonary	amod	20	SENT_15	[p1l1696t2770r2137b2853],
20	clinics	NNS	O	clinic	prep_from	16	SENT_15	[p1l11t2863r259b2926],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l292t2863r374b2926],
22	11	CD	NUMBER	11	num	23	SENT_15	[p1l404t2868r481b2925],
23	hospitals	NNS	O	hospital	prep_of	20	SENT_15	[p1l519t2863r874b2945],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l906t2864r983b2925],
25	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	prep_in	23	SENT_15	[p1l1015t2866r1262b2926],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1015t2866r1262b2926],

1	Patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubjpass	3	SENT_16	[p1l1293t2864r1609b2926],
2	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_16	[p1l1638t2883r1824b2926],
3	treated	VBN	O	treat	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1856t2863r2133b2926],
4	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l7t2954r183b3018],
5	ﬂuticasone	NN	O	ﬂuticasone	nn	6	SENT_16	[p1l236t2955r667b3018],
6	propionate	NN	O	propionate	prep_with	3	SENT_16	[p1l720t2956r1155b3037],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1210t2955r1356b3018],
8	salmeterol	NN	O	salmeterol	prep_with	3	SENT_16	[p1l1410t2955r1823b3018],
9	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1877t2954r1990b3018],
10	12	CD	DURATION	12	num	11	SENT_16	[p1l2048t2960r2132b3017],
11	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	prep_for	3	SENT_16	[p1l7t3046r244b3109],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l266t3046r412b3109],
13	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	14	SENT_16	[p1l431t3046r608b3129],
14	function	NN	O	function	nsubjpass	16	SENT_16	[p1l626t3046r959b3109],
15	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_16	[p1l976t3066r1123b3109],
16	measured	VBN	O	measure	conj_and	3	SENT_16	[p1l1144t3046r1529b3109],
17	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1550t3056r1623b3109],
18	baseline	NN	O	baseline	prep_at	16	SENT_16	[p1l1642t3046r1966b3109],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1987t3046r2133b3109],
20	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l12t3138r194b3202],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_16	[p1l243t3138r367b3202],
22	12-week	JJ	DURATION	12-week	amod	23	SENT_16	[p1l422t3138r741b3202],
23	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_after	16	SENT_16	[p1l789t3148r1200b3202],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l789t3148r1200b3202],

1	Eighty-four	CD	NUMBER	eighty-four	nsubjpass	8	SENT_17	[p1l1249t3138r1697b3221],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1745t3138r1827b3202],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_17	[p1l1869t3138r1993b3202],
4	87	CD	NUMBER	87	num	5	SENT_17	[p1l2042t3143r2131b3202],
5	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_of	1	SENT_17	[p1l11t3230r327b3312],
6	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_17	[p1l349t3250r535b3294],
7	successfully	RB	O	successfully	advmod	8	SENT_17	[p1l560t3230r1027b3313],
8	genotyped	VBN	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1047t3230r1476b3313],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1047t3230r1476b3313],

1	Correspondence	NN	O	correspondence	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l101t3460r654b3525],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l101t3460r654b3525],
3	Yeon-Mok	NNP	O	Yeon-Mok	dep	1	SENT_18	[p1l701t3461r1030b3513],
4	Oh	UH	O	oh	dep	6	SENT_18	[p1l1077t3460r1186b3521],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1077t3460r1186b3521],
6	Department	NNP	O	Department	nsubj	17	SENT_18	[p1l1237t3461r1621b3525],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1669t3460r1732b3513],
8	Pulmonary	JJ	O	pulmonary	amod	12	SENT_18	[p1l1779t3461r2133b3525],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l12t3543r128b3594],
10	Critical	JJ	ORGANIZATION	critical	amod	12	SENT_18	[p1l177t3542r395b3594],
11	Care	NN	ORGANIZATION	care	nn	12	SENT_18	[p1l445t3542r590b3594],
12	Medicine	NN	ORGANIZATION	medicine	prep_of	6	SENT_18	[p1l640t3543r952b3602],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l640t3543r952b3602],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l999t3543r1115b3594],
15	Clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	16	SENT_18	[p1l1163t3542r1394b3594],
16	Research	NNP	O	Research	prep_of	6	SENT_18	[p1l1446t3543r1737b3594],
17	Center	NNP	O	Center	rcmod	3	SENT_18	[p1l1787t3542r1999b3594],
18	for	IN	O	for	prep	17	SENT_18	[p1l2041t3542r2133b3594],

1	Chronic	JJ	O	chronic	amod	4	SENT_19	[p2l12t18r262b71],
2	Obstructive	JJ	O	obstructive	amod	4	SENT_19	[p2l290t18r662b71],
3	Airway	NN	O	airway	nn	4	SENT_19	[p2l688t19r919b83],
4	Diseases	NNS	O	disease	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l947t19r1247b79],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l947t19r1247b79],
6	Asan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Asan	nn	8	SENT_19	[p2l1273t19r1433b71],
7	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	8	SENT_19	[p2l1467t19r1714b71],
8	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	appos	4	SENT_19	[p2l1745t18r1970b79],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1745t18r1970b79],
10	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	4	SENT_19	[p2l2001t19r2131b71, p2l10t101r229b166],
11	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l280t100r343b154],
12	Ulsan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ulsan	nn	13	SENT_19	[p2l395t101r573b154],
13	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	prep_of	10	SENT_19	[p2l629t100r870b166],
14	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l924t100r987b154],
15	Medicine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medicine	prep_of	13	SENT_19	[p2l1039t101r1351b161],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1039t101r1351b161],
17	388-1	CD	NUMBER	388-1	num	18	SENT_19	[p2l1404t102r1568b154],
18	Pungnap-dong	NN	O	pungnap-dong	appos	4	SENT_19	[p2l1632t101r2130b166],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l1632t101r2130b166],
20	Sonpa-gu	NN	O	sonpa-gu	appos	4	SENT_19	[p2l12t183r346b249],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l12t183r346b249],
22	Seoul	NNP	LOCATION	Seoul	appos	4	SENT_19	[p2l377t183r557b236],
23	138-736	CD	NUMBER	138-736	num	22	SENT_19	[p2l594t185r858b244],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l594t185r858b244],
25	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	appos	4	SENT_19	[p2l890t184r1092b236],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p2l890t184r1092b236],

1	Email	VB	O	email	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1126t184r1321b236],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1126t184r1321b236],
3	ymoh55@amc.seou	NN	O	ymoh55@amc.seou	nn	4	SENT_20	[p2l1351t183r2105b249],
4	|	NN	O	|	dobj	1	SENT_20	[p2l1351t183r2105b249],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1351t183r2105b249],

1	kr	NN	O	kr	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1351t183r2105b249],
2	Received	VBN	O	receive	partmod	1	SENT_21	[p2l103t268r391b320],
3	18	CD	DATE	18	dobj	2	SENT_21	[p2l424t269r491b320],
4	June	NNP	DATE	June	tmod	2	SENT_21	[p2l515t268r673b320],
5	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	4	SENT_21	[p2l700t269r868b328],
6	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l700t269r868b328],
7	invited	VBN	O	invite	dep	1	SENT_21	[p2l897t268r1112b320],
8	to	TO	O	to	aux	9	SENT_21	[p2l1137t274r1199b320],
9	revise	VB	O	revise	xcomp	7	SENT_21	[p2l1229t268r1417b320],
10	22	CD	DATE	22	dobj	9	SENT_21	[p2l1444t269r1515b319],
11	July	NNP	DATE	July	tmod	9	SENT_21	[p2l1540t268r1678b332],
12	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	11	SENT_21	[p2l1702t269r1870b328],
13	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1702t269r1870b328],
14	revised	VBN	O	revise	parataxis	7	SENT_21	[p2l1900t268r2129b320],
15	1	CD	DATE	1	dobj	14	SENT_21	[p2l17t353r36b402],
16	August	NNP	DATE	August	tmod	14	SENT_21	[p2l92t351r326b416],
17	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	16	SENT_21	[p2l376t352r544b411],
18	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l376t352r544b411],
19	accepted	VBN	O	accept	parataxis	7	SENT_21	[p2l594t351r881b415],
20	13	CD	DATE	13	dobj	19	SENT_21	[p2l938t352r1005b403],
21	August	NNP	DATE	August	nn	25	SENT_21	[p2l1052t351r1287b416],
22	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	25	SENT_21	[p2l1335t352r1485b403],
23	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	25	SENT_21	[p2l1537t351r1869b408],
24	Associate	NNP	O	Associate	nn	25	SENT_21	[p2l1537t351r1869b408],
25	Editor	NNP	O	Editor	dep	20	SENT_21	[p2l1922t351r2129b403],
26	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1922t351r2129b403],
27	Martin	NNP	PERSON	Martin	nn	28	SENT_21	[p2l15t434r220b486],
28	Ko	NNP	PERSON	Ko	dep	20	SENT_21	[p2l255t434r437b491],
29	|	NN	O	|	nn	31	SENT_21	[p2l255t434r437b491],
30	b	NN	O	b	nn	31	SENT_21	[p2l255t434r437b491],
31	)	NN	O	)	dep	28	SENT_21	[p2l255t434r437b491],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l255t434r437b491],

1	SUMMARY	NN	O	summary	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l71t978r642b1053],
2	AT	IN	O	at	dep	1	SENT_22	[p2l694t979r824b1051],
3	A	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_22	[p2l876t979r944b1051],
4	GLANCE	NN	O	glance	pobj	2	SENT_22	[p2l999t978r1433b1053],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_23	[p2l70t1125r221b1193],
2	association	NN	O	association	nsubjpass	20	SENT_23	[p2l261t1127r711b1193],
3	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l747t1125r1088b1193],
4	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	6	SENT_23	[p2l1125t1125r1304b1213],
5	function	NN	O	function	nn	6	SENT_23	[p2l1339t1125r1680b1193],
6	improvement	NN	O	improvement	prep_between	2	SENT_23	[p2l1718t1127r2078b1212, p2l71t1234r282b1291],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l359t1225r436b1290],
8	response	NN	O	response	prep_in	6	SENT_23	[p2l514t1244r871b1310],
9	to	TO	O	to	aux	10	SENT_23	[p2l950t1234r1026b1291],
10	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	infmod	6	SENT_23	[p2l1107t1223r1409b1291],
11	corticosteroids	NNS	O	corticosteroid	dobj	10	SENT_23	[p2l1488t1223r2081b1291],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l72t1321r222b1389],
13	single-nucleotide	JJ	O	single-nucleotide	amod	16	SENT_23	[p2l316t1321r1010b1409],
14	corticotrophin-releasing	JJ	O	corticotrophin-releasing	amod	16	SENT_23	[p2l1106t1321r2085b1409],
15	hormone	NN	O	hormone	nn	16	SENT_23	[p2l70t1419r440b1487],
16	receptor	NN	O	receptor	conj_and	11	SENT_23	[p2l469t1430r805b1507],
17	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	18	SENT_23	[p2l838t1425r868b1486],
18	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	dep	16	SENT_23	[p2l901t1419r1532b1507],
19	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_23	[p2l1558t1441r1709b1487],
20	tested	VBN	O	test	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l1738t1419r1979b1487],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l2006t1422r2084b1486],
22	COPD	NN	O	copd	nn	23	SENT_23	[p2l72t1521r315b1586],
23	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	20	SENT_23	[p2l369t1520r710b1605],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l369t1520r710b1605],

1	Lung	NN	O	lung	nn	3	SENT_24	[p2l766t1522r969b1606],
2	function	NN	O	function	nn	3	SENT_24	[p2l1018t1518r1359b1586],
3	improvement	NN	O	improvement	nsubjpass	10	SENT_24	[p2l1410t1520r1955b1605],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l2006t1520r2084b1585],
5	response	NN	O	response	prep_in	3	SENT_24	[p2l71t1637r428b1703],
6	to	TO	O	to	aux	7	SENT_24	[p2l462t1627r537b1684],
7	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	infmod	5	SENT_24	[p2l573t1616r874b1684],
8	corticosteroids	NNS	O	corticosteroid	dobj	7	SENT_24	[p2l908t1616r1502b1684],
9	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_24	[p2l1533t1637r1684b1684],
10	observed	VBN	O	observe	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1720t1616r2084b1684],
11	only	RB	O	only	advmod	10	SENT_24	[p2l72t1714r247b1802],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l298t1717r376b1781],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_24	[p2l431t1714r556b1782],
14	COPD	NN	MISC	copd	nn	15	SENT_24	[p2l614t1717r856b1782],
15	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	10	SENT_24	[p2l913t1717r1236b1802],
16	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1289t1714r1468b1782],
17	wild-type	JJ	O	wild-type	amod	19	SENT_24	[p2l1520t1714r1900b1802],
18	GG	NNS	O	gg	nn	19	SENT_24	[p2l1957t1717r2084b1782],
19	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	15	SENT_24	[p2l72t1823r439b1901],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l471t1815r548b1879],
21	rs242941	NN	O	rs242941	prep_in	19	SENT_24	[p2l578t1818r949b1891],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l578t1818r949b1891],
23	not	RB	O	not	neg	10	SENT_24	[p2l984t1823r1119b1880],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1147t1815r1225b1879],
25	those	DT	O	those	prep_in	10	SENT_24	[p2l1255t1813r1470b1880],
26	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1499t1813r1677b1880],
27	heterozygous	JJ	O	heterozygous	amod	29	SENT_24	[p2l1706t1813r2078b1901, p2l72t1931r256b1999],
28	GT	NN	O	gt	nn	29	SENT_24	[p2l287t1914r402b1979],
29	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	25	SENT_24	[p2l430t1922r816b1999],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l430t1922r816b1999],

1	Results	NNS	O	result	nsubjpass	22	SENT_25	[p2l15t2208r323b2270],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l15t2208r323b2270],
3	Seventy-one	CD	NUMBER	seventy-one	num	4	SENT_25	[p2l408t2209r888b2289],
4	patients	NNS	O	patient	dep	1	SENT_25	[p2l918t2208r1236b2289],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1264t2207r1440b2270],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_25	[p2l1470t2207r1595b2270],
7	wild-type	JJ	O	wild-type	amod	9	SENT_25	[p2l1622t2207r1995b2289],
8	GG	NNS	O	gg	nn	9	SENT_25	[p2l2026t2209r2144b2270],
9	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	4	SENT_25	[p2l9t2308r369b2381],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l411t2298r558b2361],
11	13	CD	NUMBER	13	num	12	SENT_25	[p2l604t2303r688b2361],
12	patients	NNS	O	patient	conj_and	1	SENT_25	[p2l730t2299r1049b2380],
13	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1087t2298r1264b2361],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_25	[p2l1304t2298r1429b2361],
15	heterozygous	JJ	O	heterozygous	amod	17	SENT_25	[p2l1469t2298r1992b2381],
16	GT	NN	O	gt	nn	17	SENT_25	[p2l2035t2300r2144b2362],
17	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_with	12	SENT_25	[p2l9t2400r369b2473],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l405t2392r483b2453],
19	rs242	NN	O	rs242	prep_in	17	SENT_25	[p2l519t2395r732b2454],
20	941	CD	NUMBER	941	num	19	SENT_25	[p2l759t2395r890b2454],
21	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	22	SENT_25	[p2l930t2410r1118b2454],
22	evaluated	VBN	O	evaluate	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1155t2390r1555b2454],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1155t2390r1555b2454],

1	After	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1586t2390r1784b2454],
2	12-week	JJ	DURATION	12-week	amod	3	SENT_26	[p2l1825t2390r2147b2454],
3	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_after	17	SENT_26	[p2l10t2492r423b2558],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l10t2492r423b2558],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_26	[p2l448t2482r573b2546],
6	change	NN	O	change	nsubj	17	SENT_26	[p2l598t2482r878b2565],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l902t2484r980b2545],
8	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	prep_in	6	SENT_26	[p2l1005t2486r1183b2554],
9	was	VBD	O	be	cop	17	SENT_26	[p2l1208t2502r1356b2546],
10	signiﬁcantly	RB	O	signiﬁcantly	advmod	11	SENT_26	[p2l1382t2482r1868b2565],
11	higher	JJR	O	higher	amod	17	SENT_26	[p2l1888t2482r2145b2565],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l9t2576r87b2637],
13	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	11	SENT_26	[p2l113t2576r432b2656],
14	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l456t2574r633b2638],
15	wild-type	JJ	O	wild-type	amod	16	SENT_26	[p2l656t2574r1028b2657],
16	GG	NNS	O	gg	prep_with	13	SENT_26	[p2l1056t2577r1174b2638],
17	genotype	NN	O	genotype	dep	31	SENT_26	[p2l1201t2585r1560b2657],
18	(	CD	PERCENT	(	number	19	SENT_26	[p2l1593t2577r1731b2648],
19	6.0	CD	PERCENT	6.0	num	17	SENT_26	[p2l1593t2577r1731b2648],
20	1	CD	PERCENT	1	number	22	SENT_26	[p2l1765t2583r1819b2636],
21	0.8	CD	PERCENT	0.8	number	22	SENT_26	[p2l1853t2578r2040b2639],
22	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	17	SENT_26	[p2l1853t2578r2040b2639],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l2070t2574r2152b2638],
24	predicted	VBN	O	predict	amod	26	SENT_26	[p2l9t2666r383b2748],
25	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	nn	26	SENT_26	[p2l414t2670r619b2740],
26	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	17	SENT_26	[p2l414t2670r619b2740],
27	than	IN	O	than	advmod	31	SENT_26	[p2l657t2666r838b2730],
28	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l869t2668r946b2729],
29	GT	NN	O	gt	nn	30	SENT_26	[p2l978t2669r1088b2730],
30	heterozygotes	NNS	O	heterozygote	prep_in	27	SENT_26	[p2l1117t2666r1662b2749],
31	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l1700t2670r1884b2740],
32	-0.8	CD	NUMBER	-0.8	num	33	SENT_26	[p2l1700t2670r1884b2740],
33	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dobj	31	SENT_26	[p2l1918t2675r1972b2729],
34	1.8	CD	NUMBER	1.8	nsubj	31	SENT_26	[p2l2012t2671r2141b2743],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l2012t2671r2141b2743],
36	P	NN	O	p	appos	34	SENT_26	[p2l8t2763r67b2822],
37	=	JJ	O	=	amod	39	SENT_26	[p2l86t2788r134b2812],
38	0.003	CD	NUMBER	0.003	tmod	37	SENT_26	[p2l159t2763r419b2833],
39	)	NN	O	)	dep	36	SENT_26	[p2l159t2763r419b2833],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l159t2763r419b2833],

1	Conclusions	NNS	O	conclusion	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l17t2852r520b2915],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l17t2852r520b2915],
3	Improved	VBN	O	improve	dep	1	SENT_27	[p2l604t2852r984b2934],
4	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	dobj	3	SENT_27	[p2l1009t2855r1187b2924],
5	following	VBG	O	follow	amod	4	SENT_27	[p2l1216t2852r1583b2934],
6	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	partmod	4	SENT_27	[p2l1605t2852r1903b2915],
7	corticosteroid	NN	O	corticosteroid	dobj	6	SENT_27	[p2l1928t2853r2140b2915, p2l10t2943r374b3006],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l403t2943r549b3006],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_27	[p2l578t2963r622b3006],
10	long-acting	JJ	O	long-acting	amod	12	SENT_27	[p2l647t2943r1097b3026],
11	[	NN	O	[	nn	12	SENT_27	[p2l1125t2942r1537b3026],
12	32-agonist	NN	O	32-agonist	nsubjpass	14	SENT_27	[p2l1125t2942r1537b3026],
13	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	14	SENT_27	[p2l1560t2963r1709b3006],
14	associated	VBN	O	associate	conj_and	3	SENT_27	[p2l1739t2943r2144b3006],
15	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l7t3035r183b3099],
16	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	nn	18	SENT_27	[p2l227t3038r500b3099],
17	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	18	SENT_27	[p2l547t3037r829b3118],
18	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	prep_with	14	SENT_27	[p2l869t3035r1454b3118],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1494t3037r1572b3098],
20	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	18	SENT_27	[p2l1611t3037r1930b3117],
21	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l1968t3035r2144b3099],
22	COPD	NN	O	copd	prep_with	20	SENT_27	[p2l11t3131r266b3192],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l11t3131r266b3192],

1	Key	NN	O	key	nn	2	SENT_28	[p2l13t3307r157b3384],
2	words	NNS	O	word	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l209t3307r478b3369],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l209t3307r478b3369],
4	COPD	NNP	O	COPD	dep	2	SENT_28	[p2l530t3308r780b3379],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l530t3308r780b3379],
6	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	appos	4	SENT_28	[p2l844t3308r1126b3379],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l844t3308r1126b3379],
8	corticosteroid	NN	O	corticosteroid	appos	4	SENT_28	[p2l1188t3305r1732b3379],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1188t3305r1732b3379],
10	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	appos	4	SENT_28	[p2l1791t3305r2140b3388, p2l9t3397r266b3479],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l1791t3305r2140b3388, p2l9t3397r266b3479],

1	Fu’espiroIogY	NN	O	fu’espiroiogy	dep	4	SENT_29	[p2l1114t3584r1512b3648],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	1	SENT_29	[p2l1534t3584r1727b3641],
3	2009	CD	DATE	2009	dep	4	SENT_29	[p2l1534t3584r1727b3641],
4	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	10	SENT_29	[p2l1534t3584r1727b3641],
5	14	CD	NUMBER	14	dep	4	SENT_29	[p2l1761t3585r1849b3644],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1761t3585r1849b3644],
7	260-263	CD	NUMBER	260-263	appos	5	SENT_29	[p2l1880t3585r2142b3636],
8	doi	FW	O	doi	dep	7	SENT_29	[p2l905t3666r1021b3719],
9	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l905t3666r1021b3719],
10	10.1111	CD	NUMBER	10.1111	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1058t3666r2144b3731],
11	/	:	O	/	punct	10	SENT_29	[p2l1058t3666r2144b3731],
12	j.	SYM	O	j.	dep	13	SENT_29	[p2l1058t3666r2144b3731],
13	1440	CD	DATE	1440	dep	15	SENT_29	[p2l1058t3666r2144b3731],
14	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	15	SENT_29	[p2l1058t3666r2144b3731],
15	1843.2008.01425	CD	NUMBER	1843.2008.01425	dep	10	SENT_29	[p2l1058t3666r2144b3731],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1058t3666r2144b3731],

1	x	CC	O	x	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1058t3666r2144b3731],

1	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	nn	2	SENT_31	[p3l10t34r267b97],
2	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l312t35r890b112],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l926t35r993b96],
4	COPD	NNP	MISC	COPD	prep_in	2	SENT_31	[p3l1031t34r1258b97],

1	INTRODUCTION	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l11t226r842b300],

1	COPD	NNP	O	COPD	nsubj	6	SENT_33	[p3l9t430r251b495],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	6	SENT_33	[p3l291t430r350b495],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_33	[p3l391t449r433b495],
4	prevalent	JJ	O	prevalent	amod	5	SENT_33	[p3l468t427r844b514],
5	respiratory	JJ	O	respiratory	amod	6	SENT_33	[p3l880t430r1318b515],
6	disease	NN	O	disease	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1353t426r1730b495],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1353t426r1730b495],

1	”	NN	O	”	dep	6	SENT_34	[p3l1353t426r1730b495],
2	Although	IN	O	although	dep	6	SENT_34	[p3l1762t427r2133b515],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_34	[p3l8t524r133b591],
4	disease	NN	O	disease	nsubjpass	6	SENT_34	[p3l164t524r450b591],
5	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_34	[p3l479t527r538b591],
6	characterized	VBN	O	characterize	advcl	20	SENT_34	[p3l568t524r1108b591],
7	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1135t524r1231b611],
8	airﬂow	NN	O	airﬂow	nn	9	SENT_34	[p3l1257t524r1532b591],
9	limitation	NN	O	limitation	agent	6	SENT_34	[p3l1554t524r1948b591],
10	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	14	SENT_34	[p3l1976t524r2134b591],
11	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	14	SENT_34	[p3l8t622r67b687],
12	not	RB	O	not	neg	14	SENT_34	[p3l95t631r229b687],
13	fully	RB	O	fully	advmod	14	SENT_34	[p3l254t620r431b707],
14	reversible	JJ	O	reversible	rcmod	9	SENT_34	[p3l454t620r857b698],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l454t620r857b698],
16	drug	NN	O	drug	nn	17	SENT_34	[p3l890t620r1074b707],
17	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nsubjpass	20	SENT_34	[p3l1099t631r1494b687],
18	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_34	[p3l1520t622r1578b687],
19	mostly	RB	O	mostly	advmod	20	SENT_34	[p3l1607t620r1878b707],
20	based	VBN	O	base	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1900t620r2133b687],
21	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l10t737r110b783],
22	bronchodilators	NNS	O	bronchodilator	prep_on	20	SENT_34	[p3l213t716r873b794],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l213t716r873b794],
24	B2	NN	O	b2	nn	26	SENT_34	[p3l984t716r1437b803],
25	—	NN	O	—	nn	26	SENT_34	[p3l984t716r1437b803],
26	agonists	NNS	O	agonist	prep_on	20	SENT_34	[p3l984t716r1437b803],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1544t716r1693b783],
28	anticho1inergics	NNS	O	anticho1inergic	nn	29	SENT_34	[p3l1798t716r2128b783, p3l7t812r433b901],
29	.3	NN	NUMBER	.3	prep_on	20	SENT_34	[p3l1798t716r2128b783, p3l7t812r433b901],
30	’	CD	NUMBER	’	number	31	SENT_34	[p3l1798t716r2128b783, p3l7t812r433b901],
31	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	32	SENT_34	[p3l1798t716r2128b783, p3l7t812r433b901],
32	Treatment	NN	O	treatment	dep	37	SENT_34	[p3l469t818r883b881],
33	with	IN	O	with	dep	37	SENT_34	[p3l919t813r1096b881],
34	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	csubj	37	SENT_34	[p3l1136t813r1436b881],
35	corticosteroid	NN	O	corticosteroid	dobj	34	SENT_34	[p3l1478t813r2032b881],
36	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	37	SENT_34	[p3l2072t816r2132b881],
37	synergistic	JJ	O	synergistic	ccomp	20	SENT_34	[p3l9t911r432b996],
38	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l491t909r668b976],
39	bronchodilator	NN	O	bronchodilator	nn	40	SENT_34	[p3l727t909r1333b976],
40	therapy	NN	O	therapy	prep_with	37	SENT_34	[p3l1392t909r1705b996],
41	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1392t909r1705b996],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_35	[p3l1765t913r1826b975],
2	recent	JJ	O	recent	amod	3	SENT_35	[p3l1884t920r2134b976],
3	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	4	SENT_35	[p3l9t1005r228b1092],
4	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l256t1005r557b1072],
5	that	IN	O	that	complm	15	SENT_35	[p3l586t1005r744b1072],
6	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nsubj	15	SENT_35	[p3l773t1016r1168b1072],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1193t1005r1370b1072],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_35	[p3l1401t1026r1443b1072],
9	corticosteroid	NN	O	corticosteroid	prep_with	6	SENT_35	[p3l1473t1005r2027b1072],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l2056t1007r2133b1071],
11	addition	NN	O	addition	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l10t1101r344b1168],
12	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l381t1112r456b1168],
13	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_35	[p3l497t1122r539b1168],
14	B2-agonist	NN	O	b2-agonist	prep_in_addition_to	9	SENT_35	[p3l577t1101r995b1188],
15	improved	VBD	O	improve	ccomp	4	SENT_35	[p3l1030t1101r1413b1187],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_35	[p3l1449t1101r1574b1168],
17	health	NN	O	health	nn	18	SENT_35	[p3l1611t1101r1863b1168],
18	status	NN	O	status	dobj	15	SENT_35	[p3l1900t1112r2131b1168],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l10t1197r159b1264],
20	spirometric	JJ	O	spirometric	amod	21	SENT_35	[p3l230t1199r689b1283],
21	values	NNS	O	value	conj_and	18	SENT_35	[p3l757t1197r1008b1264],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1081t1197r1163b1264],
23	COPD	NN	O	copd	nn	24	SENT_35	[p3l1227t1200r1468b1264],
24	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_of	21	SENT_35	[p3l1540t1195r1911b1283],
25	,5	CD	NUMBER	,5	tmod	15	SENT_35	[p3l1540t1195r1911b1283],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1985t1197r2133b1264],
27	decreased	VBD	O	decrease	conj_and	15	SENT_35	[p3l10t1293r408b1360],
28	exacerbations	NNS	O	exacerbation	dobj	27	SENT_35	[p3l437t1293r988b1360],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l1019t1293r1101b1360],
30	COPD	NNP	O	COPD	prep_of	28	SENT_35	[p3l1122t1291r1412b1360],
31	.6	CD	NUMBER	.6	num	30	SENT_35	[p3l1122t1291r1412b1360],

1	Although	IN	O	although	mark	6	SENT_36	[p3l91t1389r463b1476],
2	several	JJ	O	several	amod	4	SENT_36	[p3l494t1389r768b1456],
3	research	NN	O	research	nn	4	SENT_36	[p3l797t1389r1132b1456],
4	groups	NNS	O	group	nsubj	6	SENT_36	[p3l1163t1410r1434b1476],
5	have	VBP	O	have	aux	6	SENT_36	[p3l1464t1389r1650b1456],
6	studied	VBN	O	study	advcl	21	SENT_36	[p3l1683t1389r1978b1456],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_36	[p3l2007t1389r2132b1456],
8	bronchodilator	NN	O	bronchodilator	nn	9	SENT_36	[p3l7t1485r613b1552],
9	pharmacogenetics	NNS	O	pharmacogenetic	dobj	6	SENT_36	[p3l654t1485r1391b1572],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1438t1485r1519b1551],
11	B2	NN	O	b2	prep_of	9	SENT_36	[p3l1558t1485r2011b1572],
12	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	13	SENT_36	[p3l1558t1485r2011b1572],
13	agonists	NNS	O	agonist	nsubjpass	21	SENT_36	[p3l1558t1485r2011b1572],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l2056t1487r2133b1551],
15	obstructive	JJ	O	obstructive	amod	17	SENT_36	[p3l10t1581r455b1648],
16	airway	NN	O	airway	nn	17	SENT_36	[p3l483t1583r748b1668],
17	diseases	NNS	O	disease	prep_in	13	SENT_36	[p3l771t1580r1146b1659],
18	,7	CD	NUMBER	,7	npadvmod	19	SENT_36	[p3l771t1580r1146b1659],
19	little	JJ	O	little	amod	17	SENT_36	[p3l1170t1581r1347b1648],
20	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	21	SENT_36	[p3l1373t1583r1432b1648],
21	known	VBN	O	know	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1458t1581r1727b1648],
22	about	IN	O	about	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1754t1581r1984b1648],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_36	[p3l2007t1581r2132b1648],
24	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	25	SENT_36	[p3l9t1679r295b1764],
25	inﬂuences	NNS	O	inﬂuences	prep_about	21	SENT_36	[p3l329t1677r740b1744],
26	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l777t1698r877b1744],
27	responses	NNS	O	response	prep_on	25	SENT_36	[p3l910t1698r1304b1763],
28	to	TO	O	to	aux	29	SENT_36	[p3l1339t1688r1414b1744],
29	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	xcomp	21	SENT_36	[p3l1449t1677r1750b1744],
30	corticosteroid	NN	O	corticosteroid	dobj	29	SENT_36	[p3l1784t1679r2128b1744, p3l8t1774r263b1840],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l1784t1679r2128b1744, p3l8t1774r263b1840],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_37	[p3l302t1778r362b1839],
2	recent	JJ	O	recent	amod	3	SENT_37	[p3l399t1784r650b1840],
3	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	4	SENT_37	[p3l689t1774r908b1860],
4	showed	VBD	O	show	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l946t1773r1247b1840],
5	that	IN	O	that	complm	43	SENT_37	[p3l1287t1773r1445b1840],
6	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	7	SENT_37	[p3l1484t1784r1851b1860],
7	differences	NNS	O	difference	nsubj	43	SENT_37	[p3l1893t1773r2128b1840, p3l10t1890r231b1936],
8	in	IN	O	in	mark	19	SENT_37	[p3l321t1871r398b1935],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_37	[p3l486t1869r611b1936],
10	corticotrophin-releasing	JJ	O	corticotrophin-releasing	amod	17	SENT_37	[p3l702t1869r1677b1956],
11	hormone	NN	O	hormone	nn	17	SENT_37	[p3l1763t1869r2132b1936],
12	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nn	17	SENT_37	[p3l8t1976r343b2051],
13	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	17	SENT_37	[p3l381t1970r411b2031],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_37	[p3l456t1968r788b2042],
15	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	nn	17	SENT_37	[p3l456t1968r788b2042],
16	)	NN	O	)	nn	17	SENT_37	[p3l456t1968r788b2042],
17	gene	NN	O	gene	nsubjpass	19	SENT_37	[p3l829t1985r1014b2052],
18	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	19	SENT_37	[p3l1045t1986r1234b2032],
19	associated	VBN	O	associate	dep	7	SENT_37	[p3l1269t1965r1684b2032],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l1713t1965r1890b2032],
21	alterations	NNS	O	alteration	prep_with	19	SENT_37	[p3l1924t1965r2128b2032, p3l10t2064r250b2128],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l284t2064r361b2127],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_37	[p3l394t2061r519b2128],
24	therapeutic	JJ	O	therapeutic	amod	25	SENT_37	[p3l552t2061r1011b2148],
25	responses	NNS	O	response	prep_in	21	SENT_37	[p3l1044t2082r1438b2148],
26	to	TO	O	to	aux	27	SENT_37	[p3l1472t2072r1547b2128],
27	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	xcomp	19	SENT_37	[p3l1583t2061r1883b2128],
28	corticosteroids	NNS	O	corticosteroid	dobj	27	SENT_37	[p3l1918t2064r2128b2128, p3l10t2157r415b2224],
29	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l443t2159r520b2223],
30	asthmatic	JJ	O	asthmatic	amod	31	SENT_37	[p3l548t2157r938b2224],
31	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	28	SENT_37	[p3l965t2155r1336b2244],
32	.8	CD	NUMBER	.8	dep	27	SENT_37	[p3l965t2155r1336b2244],
33	The	DT	O	the	det	34	SENT_37	[p3l1359t2157r1508b2224],
34	applicability	NN	O	applicability	dobj	32	SENT_37	[p3l1538t2157r2035b2245],
35	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l2059t2157r2141b2224],
36	this	DT	O	this	det	37	SENT_37	[p3l8t2254r151b2321],
37	result	NN	O	result	prep_of	34	SENT_37	[p3l197t2254r420b2321],
38	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l464t2265r538b2321],
39	COPD	NN	O	copd	nn	40	SENT_37	[p3l587t2257r828b2321],
40	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_to	32	SENT_37	[p3l875t2256r1196b2340],
41	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	43	SENT_37	[p3l1242t2256r1301b2321],
42	not	RB	O	not	neg	43	SENT_37	[p3l1347t2265r1480b2321],
43	clear	JJ	O	clear	ccomp	4	SENT_37	[p3l1525t2254r1728b2332],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l1525t2254r1728b2332],
45	although	IN	O	although	mark	50	SENT_37	[p3l1779t2254r2133b2341],
46	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	csubj	50	SENT_37	[p3l8t2350r308b2417],
47	corticosteroid	NN	O	corticosteroid	dobj	46	SENT_37	[p3l337t2350r891b2417],
48	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	50	SENT_37	[p3l919t2352r978b2417],
49	a	DT	O	a	det	50	SENT_37	[p3l1008t2371r1051b2417],
50	treatment	NN	O	treatment	advcl	43	SENT_37	[p3l1077t2361r1472b2417],
51	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l1499t2350r1610b2417],
52	COPD	NNP	O	COPD	prep_for	50	SENT_37	[p3l1638t2353r1895b2417],
53	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l1638t2353r1895b2417],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_38	[p3l96t2446r264b2513],
2	study	NN	O	study	nsubj	3	SENT_38	[p3l327t2446r546b2533],
3	investigated	VBD	O	investigate	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l602t2446r1085b2533],
4	whether	IN	O	whether	complm	8	SENT_38	[p3l1141t2446r1473b2513],
5	treatment	NN	O	treatment	nn	6	SENT_38	[p3l1532t2457r1927b2513],
6	responses	NNS	O	response	nsubj	8	SENT_38	[p3l1986t2467r2128b2513, p3l8t2563r285b2628],
7	to	TO	O	to	aux	8	SENT_38	[p3l322t2553r397b2609],
8	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	ccomp	3	SENT_38	[p3l435t2542r734b2609],
9	corticosteroid	NN	O	corticosteroid	nsubj	10	SENT_38	[p3l771t2542r1325b2609],
10	varied	VBD	O	vary	ccomp	8	SENT_38	[p3l1357t2542r1606b2609],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1638t2542r1815b2609],
12	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	nn	13	SENT_38	[p3l1854t2545r2126b2609],
13	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	prep_with	10	SENT_38	[p3l9t2649r413b2725],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l443t2640r520b2704],
15	COPD	NN	O	copd	nn	16	SENT_38	[p3l548t2641r790b2705],
16	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	10	SENT_38	[p3l820t2640r1159b2724],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l820t2640r1159b2724],

1	METHODS	NNS	O	method	_	0	SENT_39	[p3l11t2893r543b2967],

1	Study	NNP	O	Study	nn	2	SENT_40	[p3l9t3090r269b3176],
2	subjects	NNS	O	subject	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l303t3091r666b3177],

1	Eighty-seven	CD	NUMBER	eighty-seven	num	2	SENT_41	[p4l8t63r519b150],
2	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubjpass	4	SENT_41	[p4l546t65r866b149],
3	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_41	[p4l893t84r1081b130],
4	selected	VBN	O	select	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l1111t63r1433b130],
5	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l1460t63r1652b130],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_41	[p4l1679t63r1803b130],
7	‘	JJ	MISC	‘	amod	11	SENT_41	[p4l1832t63r2134b130],
8	Korean	JJ	MISC	korean	amod	11	SENT_41	[p4l1832t63r2134b130],
9	Obstructive	JJ	MISC	obstructive	amod	11	SENT_41	[p4l9t159r471b226],
10	Lung	NN	MISC	lung	nn	11	SENT_41	[p4l533t163r735b246],
11	Disease	NN	MISC	disease	prep_from	4	SENT_41	[p4l794t161r1097b226],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_41	[p4l1166t161r1451b236],
13	KOLD	NNP	ORGANIZATION	KOLD	nn	15	SENT_41	[p4l1166t161r1451b236],
14	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	15	SENT_41	[p4l1166t161r1451b236],
15	Cohort	NNP	O	Cohort	dep	11	SENT_41	[p4l1521t159r1826b237],
16	’	NN	O	’	tmod	4	SENT_41	[p4l1521t159r1826b237],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l1521t159r1826b237],
18	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	19	SENT_41	[p4l1889t159r2134b225],
19	comprises	VBZ	O	comprise	rcmod	16	SENT_41	[p4l10t257r417b341],
20	patients	NNS	O	patient	dobj	19	SENT_41	[p4l457t257r778b341],
21	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l816t255r993b322],
22	COPD	NN	O	copd	prep_with	19	SENT_41	[p4l1034t258r1276b322],
23	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l1319t276r1401b322],
24	asthma	NN	O	asthma	prep_with	19	SENT_41	[p4l1440t255r1733b322],
25	recruited	VBN	O	recruit	partmod	22	SENT_41	[p4l1771t255r2133b322],
26	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l8t351r200b418],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_41	[p4l232t351r356b418],
28	pulmonary	JJ	O	pulmonary	amod	29	SENT_41	[p4l390t351r836b438],
29	clinics	NNS	O	clinic	prep_from	25	SENT_41	[p4l867t351r1117b418],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l1153t351r1235b418],
31	11	CD	NUMBER	11	num	32	SENT_41	[p4l1266t356r1342b417],
32	hospitals	NNS	O	hospital	prep_of	29	SENT_41	[p4l1380t351r1739b437],
33	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l1773t353r1850b417],
34	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	Korea	prep_in	32	SENT_41	[p4l1883t355r2128b418],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p4l1883t355r2128b418],

1	Inclusion	NN	O	inclusion	nn	2	SENT_42	[p4l8t447r381b514],
2	criteria	NNS	O	criterion	nsubj	4	SENT_42	[p4l432t450r716b514],
3	were	VBD	O	be	cop	4	SENT_42	[p4l761t468r950b514],
4	patients	NNS	O	patient	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l1000t450r1321b534],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l1369t447r1546b514],
6	COPD	NN	O	copd	prep_with	4	SENT_42	[p4l1597t450r1839b515],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l1893t447r2041b514],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_42	[p4l2092t468r2134b514],
9	postbronchodilator	NN	O	postbronchodilator	nn	11	SENT_42	[p4l8t543r787b629],
10	FEV1/FVC	NN	O	fev1/fvc	nn	11	SENT_42	[p4l829t546r1218b618],
11	values	NNS	O	value	conj_and	4	SENT_42	[p4l1260t543r1510b610],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l1557t543r1638b610],
13	<	JJR	O	<	prep_of	11	SENT_42	[p4l1673t563r1718b608],
14	0.7	CD	NUMBER	0.7	dep	13	SENT_42	[p4l1746t548r1878b621],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l1746t548r1878b621],
16	more	JJR	O	more	mwe	17	SENT_42	[p4l1926t564r2132b610],
17	than	IN	O	than	quantmod	18	SENT_42	[p4l8t639r190b706],
18	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	19	SENT_42	[p4l242t644r323b706],
19	pack-years	NNS	O	pack-year	appos	13	SENT_42	[p4l370t639r799b726],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l848t639r930b706],
21	smoking	NN	O	smoking	nn	22	SENT_42	[p4l969t639r1310b726],
22	history	NN	O	history	prep_of	19	SENT_42	[p4l1352t639r1641b726],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l1352t639r1641b726],
24	plus	CC	O	plus	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l1691t639r1856b725],
25	no	DT	O	no	amod	28	SENT_42	[p4l1904t660r2003b706],
26	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l2053t660r2134b706],
27	minimal	JJ	O	minimal	conj_or	25	SENT_42	[p4l8t736r345b802],
28	abnormalities	NNS	O	abnormality	conj_plus	4	SENT_42	[p4l374t735r926b802],
29	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l957t756r1058b802],
30	CXR	NN	O	cxr	prep_on	28	SENT_42	[p4l1087t738r1273b803],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p4l1087t738r1273b803],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_43	[p4l96t831r246b897],
2	Institutional	JJ	O	institutional	amod	4	SENT_43	[p4l269t831r761b898],
3	Review	NNP	O	Review	nn	4	SENT_43	[p4l783t833r1068b898],
4	Board	NNP	O	Board	nsubj	5	SENT_43	[p4l1086t831r1322b897],
5	approved	VBD	O	approve	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l1345t831r1719b917],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_43	[p4l1740t831r1865b898],
7	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	dobj	5	SENT_43	[p4l1890t831r2128b918, p4l10t948r126b994],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l192t927r274b994],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_43	[p4l329t927r454b994],
10	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	13	SENT_43	[p4l520t927r805b994],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l869t927r1018b994],
12	imaging	NN	O	imaging	amod	13	SENT_43	[p4l1081t929r1406b1014],
13	data	NNS	O	datum	prep_of	7	SENT_43	[p4l1469t927r1658b994],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p4l1469t927r1658b994],

1	Individual	JJ	O	individual	nsubjpass	6	SENT_44	[p4l1726t927r2133b994],
2	informed	VBN	O	inform	partmod	1	SENT_44	[p4l8t1023r380b1090],
3	written	VBN	O	write	amod	4	SENT_44	[p4l437t1026r726b1090],
4	consent	NN	O	consent	dobj	2	SENT_44	[p4l789t1034r1104b1090],
5	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_44	[p4l1160t1044r1310b1090],
6	obtained	VBN	O	obtain	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l1374t1023r1729b1090],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l1789t1023r1981b1090],
8	all	DT	O	all	det	9	SENT_44	[p4l2043t1023r2133b1090],
9	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_from	6	SENT_44	[p4l8t1121r347b1205],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p4l8t1121r347b1205],

1	Lung	NN	O	lung	_	0	SENT_45	[p4l11t1374r223b1460],
2	function	NN	O	function	nn	3	SENT_45	[p4l259t1373r621b1443],
3	measurement	NN	O	measurement	dep	1	SENT_45	[p4l663t1381r1272b1443],

1	For	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l8t1577r139b1640],
2	all	DT	O	all	det	3	SENT_46	[p4l166t1573r256b1640],
3	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_for	7	SENT_46	[p4l281t1575r621b1659],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l281t1575r621b1659],
5	spirometry	NN	O	spirometry	nsubjpass	7	SENT_46	[p4l653t1575r1093b1660],
6	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_46	[p4l1112t1594r1263b1640],
7	performed	VBN	O	perform	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1289t1573r1715b1659],
8	as	IN	O	as	mark	9	SENT_46	[p4l1742t1594r1820b1640],
9	recommended	VBN	O	recommend	advcl	7	SENT_46	[p4l1847t1594r2128b1640, p4l8t1669r338b1736],
10	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l394t1669r491b1756],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_46	[p4l545t1669r670b1736],
12	American	JJ	O	american	amod	14	SENT_46	[p4l724t1672r1115b1736],
13	Thoracic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Thoracic	nn	14	SENT_46	[p4l1168t1669r1517b1736],
14	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	prep_by	9	SENT_46	[p4l1577t1672r1864b1756],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	16	SENT_46	[p4l1925t1674r2131b1746],
16	2130	CD	DATE	2130	dep	14	SENT_46	[p4l1925t1674r2131b1746],
17	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l10t1786r91b1831],
18	Vmax	NN	O	vmax	conj_or	14	SENT_46	[p4l173t1769r404b1831],
19	22	CD	NUMBER	22	num	18	SENT_46	[p4l493t1770r602b1842],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l493t1770r602b1842],
21	SensorMedics	NNS	O	sensormedic	appos	18	SENT_46	[p4l701t1765r1272b1842],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l701t1765r1272b1842],
23	CA	NNP	LOCATION	CA	appos	18	SENT_46	[p4l1371t1767r1501b1843],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1371t1767r1501b1843],
25	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	appos	18	SENT_46	[p4l1598t1767r1788b1842],
26	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1598t1767r1788b1842],
27	PFDX	NNP	O	PFDX	dep	18	SENT_46	[p4l1885t1769r2128b1842],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1885t1769r2128b1842],
29	MedGraphics	NNP	O	MedGraphics	appos	27	SENT_46	[p4l8t1861r562b1947],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l8t1861r562b1947],
31	MN	NN	O	mn	appos	27	SENT_46	[p4l643t1865r810b1939],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l643t1865r810b1939],
33	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	appos	27	SENT_46	[p4l890t1864r1079b1939],
34	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l890t1864r1079b1939],
35	Master	NNP	O	Master	nn	36	SENT_46	[p4l1160t1865r1435b1928],
36	Lab	NNP	O	Lab	dep	18	SENT_46	[p4l1510t1861r1652b1928],
37	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	36	SENT_46	[p4l1730t1867r1793b1939],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1730t1867r1793b1939],
39	Iaeger	NNP	O	Iaeger	nn	41	SENT_46	[p4l1871t1865r2128b1948],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1871t1865r2128b1948],
41	Germany	NNP	LOCATION	Germany	appos	36	SENT_46	[p4l9t1960r427b2044],
42	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	41	SENT_46	[p4l9t1960r427b2044],
43	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l9t1960r427b2044],

1	All	DT	O	all	det	2	SENT_47	[p4l91t2053r199b2119],
2	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubjpass	4	SENT_47	[p4l245t2055r566b2139],
3	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_47	[p4l611t2074r800b2120],
4	treated	VBN	O	treat	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l848t2053r1129b2120],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1173t2053r1350b2120],
6	ﬂuticasone	NN	O	ﬂuticasone	nn	7	SENT_47	[p4l1397t2053r1835b2120],
7	propionate	NN	O	propionate	prep_with	4	SENT_47	[p4l1883t2055r2128b2139, p4l10t2160r231b2216],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	9	SENT_47	[p4l264t2153r423b2226],
9	500	CD	NUMBER	500	num	11	SENT_47	[p4l264t2153r423b2226],
10	ug	NN	O	ug	nn	11	SENT_47	[p4l453t2153r569b2236],
11	)	NN	O	)	dobj	4	SENT_47	[p4l453t2153r569b2236],
12	combined	VBN	O	combine	prep	11	SENT_47	[p4l603t2149r1006b2216],
13	with	IN	O	with	pcomp	12	SENT_47	[p4l1028t2149r1206b2216],
14	salmeterol	NN	O	salmeterol	pobj	13	SENT_47	[p4l1232t2149r1649b2216],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	16	SENT_47	[p4l1680t2153r1793b2226],
16	50	CD	NUMBER	50	num	20	SENT_47	[p4l1680t2153r1793b2226],
17	ug	NN	O	ug	nn	20	SENT_47	[p4l1822t2153r1938b2236],
18	)	NN	O	)	nn	20	SENT_47	[p4l1822t2153r1938b2236],
19	drypowder	NN	O	drypowder	nn	20	SENT_47	[p4l1973t2149r2128b2236, p4l8t2245r308b2331],
20	inhalation	NN	O	inhalation	dep	14	SENT_47	[p4l349t2245r759b2312],
21	bd	NN	O	bd	nn	22	SENT_47	[p4l800t2245r903b2312],
22	(	NN	O	(	dep	14	SENT_47	[p4l951t2245r1171b2332],
23	early	JJ	TIME	early	amod	24	SENT_47	[p4l951t2245r1171b2332],
24	morning	NN	TIME	morning	tmod	22	SENT_47	[p4l1210t2247r1557b2332],
25	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1598t2245r1748b2312],
26	evening	NN	TIME	evening	nn	27	SENT_47	[p4l1791t2247r2126b2332],
27	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	14	SENT_47	[p4l1791t2247r2126b2332],
28	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l8t2341r119b2407],
29	12	CD	DURATION	12	num	30	SENT_47	[p4l164t2346r245b2407],
30	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	prep_for	27	SENT_47	[p4l283t2341r543b2407],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l283t2341r543b2407],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_48	[p4l583t2341r733b2408],
2	use	NN	O	use	nsubj	7	SENT_48	[p4l773t2362r905b2408],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l948t2341r1029b2408],
4	respiratory	JJ	O	respiratory	amod	5	SENT_48	[p4l1061t2343r1499b2428],
5	medicines	NNS	O	medicine	prep_of	2	SENT_48	[p4l1534t2341r1943b2408],
6	was	VBD	O	be	cop	7	SENT_48	[p4l1981t2362r2131b2408],
7	restricted	JJ	O	restricted	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l8t2437r386b2504],
8	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l421t2437r532b2504],
9	2	CD	DURATION	2	num	10	SENT_48	[p4l567t2442r608b2503],
10	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	prep_for	7	SENT_48	[p4l643t2437r884b2504],
11	before	IN	O	before	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l921t2437r1173b2504],
12	enrolment	NN	O	enrolment	prep_before	7	SENT_48	[p4l1212t2437r1648b2504],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l1212t2437r1648b2504],

1	Spirometry	NN	O	spirometry	nsubjpass	9	SENT_49	[p4l1690t2439r2136b2524],
2	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l10t2533r191b2600],
3	the	DT	DURATION	the	det	5	SENT_49	[p4l212t2533r336b2600],
4	12	CD	DURATION	12	num	5	SENT_49	[p4l367t2538r447b2599],
5	weeks	NNS	NUMBER	week	prep_after	1	SENT_49	[p4l470t2533r711b2600],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l736t2533r818b2600],
7	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_of	5	SENT_49	[p4l833t2544r1228b2600],
8	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_49	[p4l1247t2554r1397b2600],
9	performed	VBN	O	perform	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l1420t2533r1846b2619],
10	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l1870t2533r2135b2620],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_49	[p4l8t2629r133b2696],
12	daytime	JJ	TIME	daytime	prep_during	9	SENT_49	[p4l156t2629r495b2716],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l156t2629r495b2716],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_50	[p4l515t2629r665b2696],
2	differences	NNS	O	difference	nsubjpass	11	SENT_50	[p4l688t2629r1120b2696],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1141t2632r1219b2695],
4	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	nn	5	SENT_50	[p4l1239t2633r1419b2705],
5	values	NNS	O	value	prep_in	2	SENT_50	[p4l1439t2629r1689b2696],
6	before	IN	O	before	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1710t2629r1962b2696],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1985t2629r2133b2696],
8	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l10t2725r191b2792],
9	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_after	5	SENT_50	[p4l235t2736r630b2792],
10	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_50	[p4l671t2746r860b2792],
11	determined	VBN	O	determine	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l909t2725r1374b2792],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1420t2725r1569b2792],
13	expressed	VBN	O	express	conj_and	11	SENT_50	[p4l1616t2725r2007b2811],
14	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l2054t2746r2132b2792],
15	percentages	NNS	O	percentage	prep_as	11	SENT_50	[p4l8t2832r486b2908],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l516t2821r598b2888],
17	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	nn	18	SENT_50	[p4l618t2825r799b2896],
18	changes	NNS	O	change	prep_of	15	SENT_50	[p4l831t2821r1153b2908],
19	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1182t2821r1374b2888],
20	predicted	VBN	O	predict	amod	21	SENT_50	[p4l1400t2821r1780b2907],
21	values	NNS	O	value	prep_from	11	SENT_50	[p4l1805t2821r2074b2888],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1805t2821r2074b2888],

1	Compliance	NN	O	compliance	nsubjpass	7	SENT_51	[p4l98t2917r578b3004],
2	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l647t2918r824b2984],
3	the	DT	O	the	prep_with	1	SENT_51	[p4l894t2917r1019b2984],
4	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	partmod	3	SENT_51	[p4l1090t2917r1390b2984],
5	medication	NN	O	medication	dobj	4	SENT_51	[p4l1460t2917r1914b2984],
6	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_51	[p4l1981t2938r2131b2984],
7	monitored	VBN	O	monitor	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l8t3013r431b3079],
8	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l482t3013r578b3100],
9	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_51	[p4l629t3034r671b3080],
10	trained	JJ	O	trained	amod	11	SENT_51	[p4l723t3013r1008b3080],
11	nurse	NN	O	nurse	agent	7	SENT_51	[p4l1061t3034r1301b3080],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l1061t3034r1301b3080],

1	Sixty-six	CD	NUMBER	sixty-six	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l1360t3015r1687b3100],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l1738t3013r1819b3080],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_52	[p4l1864t3013r1989b3080],
4	87	CD	NUMBER	87	prep_of	1	SENT_52	[p4l2044t3018r2132b3080],

1	Table	NNP	O	Table	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l16t3703r213b3762],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	4	SENT_53	[p4l244t3705r270b3761],
3	Baseline	NN	O	baseline	nn	4	SENT_53	[p4l368t3703r675b3762],
4	characteristics	NNS	O	characteristic	dep	1	SENT_53	[p4l708t3703r1240b3762],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l1274t3702r1345b3762],
6	84	CD	NUMBER	84	num	8	SENT_53	[p4l1374t3704r1457b3762],
7	study	NN	O	study	nn	8	SENT_53	[p4l1489t3703r1692b3776],
8	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_of	4	SENT_53	[p4l1723t3703r2026b3776],

1	GG	NNS	O	gg	_	0	SENT_54	[p5l764t93r876b153],
2	group	NN	O	group	nn	9	SENT_54	[p5l913t110r1131b168],
3	GT	NN	O	gt	nn	9	SENT_54	[p5l1365t93r1469b153],
4	group	NN	O	group	nn	9	SENT_54	[p5l1500t110r1718b168],
5	P	NN	O	p	nn	9	SENT_54	[p5l1882t94r2149b153],
6	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	9	SENT_54	[p5l1882t94r2149b153],
7	va	NN	O	va	nn	9	SENT_54	[p5l1882t94r2149b153],
8	|	NN	O	|	nn	9	SENT_54	[p5l1882t94r2149b153],
9	ue	NN	O	ue	dep	1	SENT_54	[p5l1882t94r2149b153],

1	Number	NN	O	number	dep	8	SENT_55	[p5l22t276r305b332],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l334t275r402b332],
3	71	CD	NUMBER	71	number	4	SENT_55	[p5l814t278r883b331],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	prep_of	1	SENT_55	[p5l921t276r1043b338],
5	68	CD	NUMBER	68	num	6	SENT_55	[p5l921t276r1043b338],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	8	SENT_55	[p5l921t276r1043b338],
7	13	CD	NUMBER	13	num	8	SENT_55	[p5l1415t277r1486b332],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	_	0	SENT_55	[p5l1515t276r1637b338],
9	13	CD	NUMBER	13	num	10	SENT_55	[p5l1515t276r1637b338],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	8	SENT_55	[p5l1515t276r1637b338],

1	subjects	NNS	O	subject	nsubj	4	SENT_56	[p5l92t372r377b442],
2	(	JJ	O	(	amod	3	SENT_56	[p5l410t372r607b434],
3	men	NNS	O	man	dep	1	SENT_56	[p5l410t372r607b434],
4	)	VBP	O	)	_	0	SENT_56	[p5l410t372r607b434],

1	Age	NNP	O	Age	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l16t470r173b539],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l16t470r173b539],
3	years	NNS	DURATION	year	appos	1	SENT_57	[p5l203t485r390b539],
4	65.3	CD	NUMBER	65.3	num	3	SENT_57	[p5l753t471r892b526],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l925t477r969b522],
6	7.3	CD	NUMBER	7.3	number	7	SENT_57	[p5l1001t470r1139b526],
7	*	CD	NUMBER	*	dep	1	SENT_57	[p5l1001t470r1139b526],
8	67.4	CD	NUMBER	67.4	dep	7	SENT_57	[p5l1347t471r1487b526],
9	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l1518t477r1563b522],
10	6.9	CD	NUMBER	6.9	number	11	SENT_57	[p5l1596t471r1693b526],
11	0.34	CD	NUMBER	0.34	num	12	SENT_57	[p5l1944t471r2085b526],
12	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	dep	7	SENT_57	[p5l20t567r195b631],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l20t567r195b631],
14	L	NN	O	l	appos	12	SENT_57	[p5l230t567r263b621],
15	1.38	CD	NUMBER	1.38	num	14	SENT_57	[p5l758t568r892b622],
16	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l925t575r969b620],
17	0.52	CD	NUMBER	0.52	num	18	SENT_57	[p5l1002t568r1140b622],
18	1.61	CD	NUMBER	1.61	dep	7	SENT_57	[p5l1352t568r1477b622],
19	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_57	[p5l1518t575r1563b619],
20	0.58	CD	NUMBER	0.58	num	21	SENT_57	[p5l1596t568r1735b622],
21	0.15	CD	NUMBER	0.15	dep	18	SENT_57	[p5l1944t568r2084b622],

1	(	CD	PERCENT	(	num	2	SENT_58	[p5l95t663r177b725],
2	%	NN	PERCENT	%	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l95t663r177b725],
3	predicted	VBD	O	predict	partmod	2	SENT_58	[p5l211t663r558b732],
4	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	5	SENT_58	[p5l211t663r558b732],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_58	[p5l730t663r883b725],
6	45.1	CD	NUMBER	45.1	dobj	3	SENT_58	[p5l730t663r883b725],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l925t671r969b716],
8	15.1	CD	NUMBER	15.1	number	9	SENT_58	[p5l1008t663r1164b725],
9	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	10	SENT_58	[p5l1008t663r1164b725],
10	(	NN	O	(	dep	2	SENT_58	[p5l1324t663r1484b725],
11	53.7	CD	NUMBER	53.7	num	10	SENT_58	[p5l1324t663r1484b725],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_58	[p5l1518t671r1563b716],
13	17.4	CD	NUMBER	17.4	number	14	SENT_58	[p5l1601t663r1758b725],
14	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	10	SENT_58	[p5l1601t663r1758b725],

1	Smoking	NN	O	smoking	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l19t760r348b830],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l19t760r348b830],
3	48.8	CD	NUMBER	48.8	appos	1	SENT_59	[p5l754t762r892b817],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l925t768r969b813],
5	27.8	CD	NUMBER	27.8	number	6	SENT_59	[p5l1002t762r1142b817],
6	44.1	CD	NUMBER	44.1	dep	1	SENT_59	[p5l1348t763r1477b815],
7	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_59	[p5l1518t768r1563b813],
8	19.6	CD	NUMBER	19.6	dep	6	SENT_59	[p5l1601t762r1736b817],
9	0.56	CD	NUMBER	0.56	dep	8	SENT_59	[p5l1944t762r2084b817],

1	pack-years	NNS	O	pack-year	nn	2	SENT_60	[p5l95t858r465b927],
2	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubj	3	SENT_60	[p5l12t1183r334b1268],
3	used	VBD	O	use	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l405t1181r593b1249],
4	the	DT	O	the	dobj	3	SENT_60	[p5l663t1181r788b1249],
5	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	partmod	4	SENT_60	[p5l860t1181r1160b1249],
6	medication	NN	O	medication	dobj	5	SENT_60	[p5l1230t1181r1686b1249],
7	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l1756t1181r1868b1249],
8	more	JJR	O	more	mwe	9	SENT_60	[p5l1936t1202r2143b1249],
9	than	IN	O	than	quantmod	10	SENT_60	[p5l12t1279r195b1347],
10	80	CD	PERCENT	80	num	11	SENT_60	[p5l252t1283r413b1348],
11	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_for	5	SENT_60	[p5l252t1283r413b1348],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l473t1279r555b1347],
13	planned	JJ	O	planned	amod	14	SENT_60	[p5l602t1279r933b1366],
14	doses	NNS	O	dose	prep_of	11	SENT_60	[p5l991t1279r1230b1347],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p5l991t1279r1230b1347],

1	Short-acting	JJ	O	short-acting	nsubjpass	6	SENT_61	[p5l1292t1279r1789b1367],
2	inhaled	VBN	O	inhale	partmod	1	SENT_61	[p5l1844t1279r2144b1347],
3	[	NN	O	[	nn	4	SENT_61	[p5l16t1376r470b1464],
4	32-agonists	NNS	O	32-agonist	dobj	2	SENT_61	[p5l16t1376r470b1464],
5	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_61	[p5l497t1398r686b1444],
6	used	VBN	O	use	_	0	SENT_61	[p5l715t1376r903b1444],
7	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_61	[p5l932t1398r1010b1444],
8	needed	VBN	O	need	prep_as	6	SENT_61	[p5l1039t1376r1352b1444],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p5l1039t1376r1352b1444],

1	Genotyping	VBG	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_62	[p5l14t1635r529b1723],

1	Genotyping	VBG	O	genotype	partmod	31	SENT_63	[p5l14t1838r484b1924],
2	focused	VBN	O	focus	dep	1	SENT_63	[p5l504t1836r815b1904],
3	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_63	[p5l838t1857r940b1904],
4	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	prep_on	2	SENT_63	[p5l960t1836r1591b1924],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_63	[p5l1616t1836r1698b1904],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_63	[p5l1711t1836r1836b1904],
7	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	nn	10	SENT_63	[p5l1864t1839r2136b1904],
8	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	10	SENT_63	[p5l14t1954r200b2021],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_63	[p5l240t1938r634b2012],
10	rs242941	NN	O	rs242941	prep_of	4	SENT_63	[p5l240t1938r634b2012],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p5l240t1938r634b2012],
12	rs1876828	NN	O	rs1876828	nsubjpass	31	SENT_63	[p5l671t1939r1089b2012],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p5l671t1939r1089b2012],
14	rs242939	NN	O	rs242939	nn	15	SENT_63	[p5l1126t1937r1501b2011],
15	)	NN	O	)	appos	12	SENT_63	[p5l1126t1937r1501b2011],
16	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	19	SENT_63	[p5l1540t1933r1699b2001],
17	have	VBP	O	have	aux	19	SENT_63	[p5l1729t1933r1916b2001],
18	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	19	SENT_63	[p5l1948t1933r2145b2001],
19	reported	VBN	O	report	rcmod	15	SENT_63	[p5l12t2030r357b2118],
20	to	TO	O	to	aux	22	SENT_63	[p5l440t2041r516b2098],
21	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	22	SENT_63	[p5l601t2030r696b2098],
22	associated	VBN	O	associate	xcomp	19	SENT_63	[p5l782t2030r1198b2098],
23	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_63	[p5l1278t2030r1456b2098],
24	bronchodilator	NN	O	bronchodilator	nn	25	SENT_63	[p5l1538t2030r2145b2098],
25	responses	NNS	O	response	prep_with	22	SENT_63	[p5l13t2147r407b2213],
26	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_63	[p5l473t2128r550b2193],
27	asthmaticsf	NN	O	asthmaticsf	nn	29	SENT_63	[p5l615t2124r1095b2194],
28	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	num	29	SENT_63	[p5l615t2124r1095b2194],
29	Primers	NNS	O	primer	prep_in	25	SENT_63	[p5l1160t2128r1468b2194],
30	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	31	SENT_63	[p5l1530t2147r1720b2194],
31	designed	VBN	O	design	_	0	SENT_63	[p5l1787t2126r2144b2214],
32	using	VBG	O	use	xcomp	31	SENT_63	[p5l12t2226r230b2312],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	35	SENT_63	[p5l263t2224r388b2292],
34	dbSNP	NN	O	dbsnp	nn	35	SENT_63	[p5l426t2224r697b2292],
35	database	NN	O	database	dobj	32	SENT_63	[p5l734t2224r1106b2292],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p5l734t2224r1106b2292],

1	PCR	NN	O	pcr	nsubjpass	3	SENT_64	[p5l1146t2227r1314b2292],
2	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_64	[p5l1345t2245r1496b2292],
3	performed	VBN	O	perform	_	0	SENT_64	[p5l1531t2224r1959b2311],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_64	[p5l1995t2224r2144b2292],
5	sequencing	NN	O	sequencing	nsubjpass	7	SENT_64	[p5l14t2324r473b2409],
6	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_64	[p5l524t2343r674b2389],
7	carried	VBN	O	carry	conj_and	3	SENT_64	[p5l733t2321r1012b2389],
8	out	RP	O	out	prt	7	SENT_64	[p5l1069t2332r1200b2389],
9	using	VBG	O	use	xcomp	7	SENT_64	[p5l1254t2324r1472b2409],
10	an	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_64	[p5l1527t2343r1623b2389],
11	ABI	NNP	O	ABI	nn	14	SENT_64	[p5l1673t2326r1818b2388],
12	PRISM	NN	O	prism	nn	14	SENT_64	[p5l1875t2324r2143b2389],
13	3730x1	NN	O	3730x1	nn	14	SENT_64	[p5l12t2418r265b2485],
14	DNA	NN	O	dna	dobj	9	SENT_64	[p5l309t2422r503b2484],
15	sequencer	NN	O	sequencer	nn	18	SENT_64	[p5l546t2439r957b2505],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_64	[p5l1007t2418r1340b2505],
17	Applied	NNP	O	Applied	nn	18	SENT_64	[p5l1007t2418r1340b2505],
18	Biosystems	NNP	O	Biosystems	dep	14	SENT_64	[p5l1383t2420r1850b2506],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p5l1383t2420r1850b2506],
20	Foster	NNP	LOCATION	Foster	nn	25	SENT_64	[p5l1899t2422r2145b2485],
21	City	NNP	LOCATION	City	nn	25	SENT_64	[p5l14t2516r182b2601],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p5l14t2516r182b2601],
23	CA	NNP	LOCATION	CA	appos	25	SENT_64	[p5l216t2517r347b2592],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p5l216t2517r347b2592],
25	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	appos	18	SENT_64	[p5l379t2517r600b2591],
26	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	25	SENT_64	[p5l379t2517r600b2591],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p5l379t2517r600b2591],

1	Statistical	JJ	O	statistical	amod	2	SENT_65	[p5l13t2770r451b2841],
2	analysis	NN	O	analysis	_	0	SENT_65	[p5l491t2771r844b2858],

1	Associations	NNS	O	association	nsubjpass	10	SENT_66	[p5l7t2974r510b3039],
2	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l564t2971r905b3039],
3	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	5	SENT_66	[p5l957t2971r1136b3059],
4	function	NN	O	function	nn	5	SENT_66	[p5l1188t2971r1528b3039],
5	response	NN	O	response	prep_between	1	SENT_66	[p5l1582t2992r1938b3059],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1995t2971r2144b3039],
7	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	nn	8	SENT_66	[p5l17t3072r289b3137],
8	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	prep_between	1	SENT_66	[p5l320t3080r726b3157],
9	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_66	[p5l747t3090r936b3137],
10	tested	VBN	O	test	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l960t3069r1201b3137],
11	using	VBG	O	use	ccomp	10	SENT_66	[p5l1223t3071r1441b3157],
12	linear	JJ	O	linear	amod	13	SENT_66	[p5l1460t3069r1691b3137],
13	regression	NN	O	regression	dobj	11	SENT_66	[p5l1712t3071r2140b3157],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1712t3071r2140b3157],
15	adjusting	VBG	O	adjust	conj_and	11	SENT_66	[p5l14t3167r385b3255],
16	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l454t3167r566b3235],
17	age	NN	O	age	prep_for	15	SENT_66	[p5l637t3188r787b3255],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l637t3188r787b3255],
19	gender	NN	O	gender	prep_for	15	SENT_66	[p5l864t3167r1141b3255],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1212t3167r1361b3235],
21	compliance	NN	O	compliance	prep_for	15	SENT_66	[p5l1434t3167r1917b3254],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1434t3167r1917b3254],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1995t3167r2144b3235],
24	assuming	VBG	O	assume	conj_and	11	SENT_66	[p5l14t3268r397b3353],
25	an	DT	O	a	det	28	SENT_66	[p5l435t3287r532b3333],
26	additive	JJ	O	additive	amod	28	SENT_66	[p5l571t3265r890b3333],
27	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	28	SENT_66	[p5l930t3268r1217b3353],
28	model	NN	O	model	dobj	24	SENT_66	[p5l1256t3265r1528b3333],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p5l1256t3265r1528b3333],

1	Analyses	NNS	O	analysis	nsubjpass	3	SENT_67	[p5l1566t3265r1916b3353],
2	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_67	[p5l1953t3287r2143b3333],
3	conducted	VBN	O	conduct	_	0	SENT_67	[p5l14t3363r440b3431],
4	using	VBG	O	use	xcomp	3	SENT_67	[p5l461t3365r678b3451],
5	SAS	NNP	O	SAS	dobj	4	SENT_67	[p5l700t3366r845b3431],
6	9.1	CD	NUMBER	9.1	num	5	SENT_67	[p5l869t3368r976b3431],
7	software	NN	O	software	dep	5	SENT_67	[p5l1006t3363r1341b3431],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_67	[p5l1371t3366r1542b3441],
9	SAS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	SAS	nn	16	SENT_67	[p5l1371t3366r1542b3441],
10	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	nn	16	SENT_67	[p5l1565t3365r1918b3442],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p5l1565t3365r1918b3442],
12	Cary	NNP	PERSON	Cary	appos	16	SENT_67	[p5l1946t3366r2140b3451],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p5l1946t3366r2140b3451],
14	NC	NNP	O	NC	appos	16	SENT_67	[p5l13t3464r158b3539],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p5l13t3464r158b3539],
16	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	7	SENT_67	[p5l190t3464r411b3538],
17	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	16	SENT_67	[p5l190t3464r411b3538],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p5l190t3464r411b3538],

1	RESULTS	NNS	O	result	_	0	SENT_68	[p5l16t3708r491b3782],

1	Baseline	NN	O	baseline	nn	2	SENT_69	[p6l16t105r381b175],
2	characteristics	NNS	O	characteristic	_	0	SENT_69	[p6l418t105r1057b175],

1	Eighty-four	CD	NUMBER	eighty-four	num	2	SENT_70	[p6l13t305r465b393],
2	patients	NNS	O	patient	nsubjpass	11	SENT_70	[p6l510t307r832b392],
3	(	IN	O	(	_	0	SENT_70	[p6l888t309r1171b383],
4	96.6	CD	PERCENT	96.6	num	5	SENT_70	[p6l888t309r1171b383],
5	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_(	11	SENT_70	[p6l888t309r1171b383],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	nsubjpass	11	SENT_70	[p6l888t309r1171b383],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_70	[p6l1223t305r1400b373],
8	COPD	NN	O	copd	prep_with	6	SENT_70	[p6l1449t308r1691b373],
9	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_70	[p6l1738t326r1928b373],
10	successfully	RB	O	successfully	advmod	11	SENT_70	[p6l1978t326r2139b373, p6l14t402r356b490],
11	genotyped	VBN	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_70	[p6l399t402r839b490],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p6l399t402r839b490],

1	Of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_71	[p6l890t402r989b470],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_71	[p6l1026t402r1151b470],
3	three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	5	SENT_71	[p6l1198t402r1401b470],
4	single-nucleotide	JJ	O	single-nucleotide	amod	5	SENT_71	[p6l1449t402r2143b490],
5	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	prep_of	6	SENT_71	[p6l12t499r643b587],
6	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_71	[p6l729t502r944b577],
7	SNP	NN	O	snp	dobj	6	SENT_71	[p6l729t502r944b577],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	9	SENT_71	[p6l729t502r944b577],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	nsubj	6	SENT_71	[p6l1037t503r1432b578],
10	rs242941	NN	O	rs242941	nn	15	SENT_71	[p6l1037t503r1432b578],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p6l1037t503r1432b578],
12	rs1876828	NN	O	rs1876828	nn	15	SENT_71	[p6l1516t504r1913b567],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_71	[p6l1995t499r2144b567],
14	rs242939	NN	O	rs242939	nn	15	SENT_71	[p6l13t599r388b673],
15	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	16	SENT_71	[p6l13t599r388b673],
16	reported	VBD	O	report	rcmod	9	SENT_71	[p6l426t595r770b682],
17	to	TO	O	to	aux	19	SENT_71	[p6l799t606r875b663],
18	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	19	SENT_71	[p6l907t595r1001b663],
19	associated	VBN	O	associate	xcomp	16	SENT_71	[p6l1034t595r1449b663],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_71	[p6l1476t595r1654b663],
21	corticosteroid	NN	O	corticosteroid	nn	22	SENT_71	[p6l1685t597r2139b663, p6l14t693r140b761],
22	response	NN	O	response	prep_with	19	SENT_71	[p6l165t714r539b781],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p6l165t714r539b781],
24	only	RB	O	only	advmod	27	SENT_71	[p6l571t693r745b781],
25	rs242941	NN	O	rs242941	nsubjpass	27	SENT_71	[p6l768t699r1113b761],
26	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	27	SENT_71	[p6l1142t715r1293b761],
27	found	VBN	O	find	ccomp	16	SENT_71	[p6l1320t693r1558b761],
28	to	TO	O	to	aux	29	SENT_71	[p6l1583t704r1659b761],
29	have	VB	O	have	xcomp	27	SENT_71	[p6l1686t693r1872b761],
30	minor	JJ	O	minor	amod	31	SENT_71	[p6l1899t696r2145b761],
31	alleles	NNS	O	allele	dobj	29	SENT_71	[p6l14t790r277b857],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p6l14t790r277b857],

1	SeVenty	CD	NUMBER	seventy	num	2	SENT_72	[p6l319t792r809b878],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	nsubj	6	SENT_72	[p6l319t792r809b878],
3	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	4	SENT_72	[p6l319t792r809b878],
4	subjects	NNS	O	subject	dep	2	SENT_72	[p6l848t790r1170b878],
5	were	VBD	O	be	cop	6	SENT_72	[p6l1205t811r1394b857],
6	GG	NNS	O	gg	_	0	SENT_72	[p6l1433t792r1559b858],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_72	[p6l1600t790r1794b868],
8	wild	JJ	O	wild	amod	9	SENT_72	[p6l1600t790r1794b868],
9	type	NN	O	type	nsubj	17	SENT_72	[p6l1829t794r2024b878],
10	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	9	SENT_72	[p6l1829t794r2024b878],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_72	[p6l2067t792r2144b857],
12	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_in	9	SENT_72	[p6l14t898r380b975],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_72	[p6l416t887r565b955],
14	13	CD	NUMBER	13	conj_and	12	SENT_72	[p6l603t892r684b955],
15	were	VBD	O	be	cop	17	SENT_72	[p6l717t908r906b955],
16	GT	NN	O	gt	nn	17	SENT_72	[p6l941t890r1056b955],
17	heterozygotes	NNS	O	heterozygote	rcmod	6	SENT_72	[p6l1088t887r1661b975],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p6l1088t887r1661b975],

1	There	EX	O	there	expl	2	SENT_73	[p6l1694t887r1923b955],
2	were	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1953t908r2143b955],
3	no	DT	O	no	det	4	SENT_73	[p6l12t1006r113b1052],
4	differences	NNS	O	difference	nsubj	2	SENT_73	[p6l146t984r579b1052],
5	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l609t984r950b1052],
6	GG	NNS	O	gg	prep_between	4	SENT_73	[p6l980t987r1106b1053],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1136t984r1286b1052],
8	GT	NN	O	gt	nn	9	SENT_73	[p6l1316t987r1431b1053],
9	patients	NNS	O	patient	conj_and	4	SENT_73	[p6l1460t987r1782b1072],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1813t987r1890b1051],
11	mean	JJ	O	mean	amod	12	SENT_73	[p6l1919t1006r2144b1052],
12	age	NN	O	age	prep_in	9	SENT_73	[p6l14t1101r146b1169],
13	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l194t1102r276b1148],
14	smoking	NN	O	smoking	conj_or	12	SENT_73	[p6l322t1081r664b1169],
15	history	NN	O	history	nn	17	SENT_73	[p6l707t1081r989b1169],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_73	[p6l1037t1081r1273b1159],
17	Table	NNP	O	Table	dep	9	SENT_73	[p6l1037t1081r1273b1159],
18	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	19	SENT_73	[p6l1308t1085r1395b1159],
19	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	17	SENT_73	[p6l1308t1085r1395b1159],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p6l1308t1085r1395b1159],

1	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	nsubj	7	SENT_74	[p6l1445t1085r1626b1157],
2	per	IN	O	per	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l1675t1102r1807b1168],
3	cent	NN	O	cent	prep_per	1	SENT_74	[p6l1853t1092r2024b1148],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l2070t1081r2152b1148],
5	predicted	VBN	O	predict	prepc_of	3	SENT_74	[p6l12t1178r394b1265],
6	was	VBD	O	be	cop	7	SENT_74	[p6l443t1199r594b1246],
7	45.1	CD	NUMBER	45.1	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l646t1183r801b1246],
8	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l843t1189r896b1242],
9	15.1	CD	PERCENT	15.1	num	10	SENT_74	[p6l939t1182r1165b1247],
10	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	7	SENT_74	[p6l939t1182r1165b1247],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l1220t1180r1297b1245],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_74	[p6l1349t1178r1474b1246],
13	GG	NNS	O	gg	nn	14	SENT_74	[p6l1529t1181r1655b1246],
14	group	NN	O	group	prep_in	10	SENT_74	[p6l1707t1198r1939b1266],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l1995t1178r2144b1246],
16	53.7	CD	NUMBER	53.7	conj_and	14	SENT_74	[p6l14t1281r172b1343],
17	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l209t1286r262b1339],
18	17.4	CD	PERCENT	17.4	num	19	SENT_74	[p6l305t1279r531b1344],
19	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	7	SENT_74	[p6l305t1279r531b1344],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l597t1277r674b1342],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_74	[p6l737t1275r862b1343],
22	GT	NN	O	gt	nn	23	SENT_74	[p6l928t1278r1043b1343],
23	group	NN	O	group	prep_in	19	SENT_74	[p6l1107t1296r1357b1363],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l1107t1296r1357b1363],
25	a	DT	O	a	det	27	SENT_74	[p6l1426t1296r1469b1343],
26	non-signiﬁcant	JJ	O	non-signiﬁcant	amod	27	SENT_74	[p6l1530t1275r2145b1363],
27	difference	NN	O	difference	appos	7	SENT_74	[p6l14t1371r427b1438],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p6l14t1371r427b1438],

1	Lung	NN	O	lung	nn	3	SENT_75	[p6l16t1608r228b1695],
2	function	NN	O	function	nn	3	SENT_75	[p6l264t1607r627b1678],
3	change	NN	O	change	_	0	SENT_75	[p6l667t1608r983b1695],
4	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_75	[p6l1020t1608r1448b1695],
5	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	3	SENT_75	[p6l1484t1615r1574b1678],
6	genotype	NN	O	genotype	pobj	3	SENT_75	[p6l1613t1615r2027b1695],

1	After	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l7t1808r206b1876],
2	12-week	JJ	DURATION	12-week	amod	3	SENT_76	[p6l242t1808r568b1876],
3	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_after	16	SENT_76	[p6l596t1819r993b1876],
4	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l1019t1808r1197b1876],
5	ﬂuticasone	NN	O	ﬂuticasone	nn	6	SENT_76	[p6l1228t1808r1668b1876],
6	propionate	NN	O	propionate	prep_with	3	SENT_76	[p6l1700t1810r2143b1895],
7	combined	VBN	O	combine	partmod	6	SENT_76	[p6l14t1906r419b1974],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l463t1906r641b1974],
9	salmeterol	NN	O	salmeterol	prep_with	7	SENT_76	[p6l689t1906r1126b1985],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l689t1906r1126b1985],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_76	[p6l1179t1907r1304b1974],
12	mean	NN	O	mean	nn	14	SENT_76	[p6l1352t1928r1578b1974],
13	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	nn	14	SENT_76	[p6l1625t1911r1806b1982],
14	change	NN	O	change	nsubj	16	SENT_76	[p6l1858t1906r2143b1994],
15	was	VBD	O	be	cop	16	SENT_76	[p6l9t2024r161b2070],
16	6.0	CD	NUMBER	6.0	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l193t2008r304b2070],
17	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l341t2013r394b2067],
18	0.8	CD	PERCENT	0.8	num	19	SENT_76	[p6l431t2006r616b2071],
19	%	NN	PERCENT	%	npadvmod	20	SENT_76	[p6l431t2006r616b2071],
20	of	IN	O	of	advmod	21	SENT_76	[p6l650t2003r732b2070],
21	predicted	VBN	O	predict	parataxis	16	SENT_76	[p6l753t2003r1135b2090],
22	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	dobj	21	SENT_76	[p6l1164t2007r1345b2079],
23	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_76	[p6l1378t2005r1455b2070],
24	GG	NNS	O	gg	nn	25	SENT_76	[p6l1487t2005r1612b2071],
25	patients	NNS	O	patient	prep_in	22	SENT_76	[p6l1641t2005r1962b2090],
26	and	CC	O	and	advmod	25	SENT_76	[p6l1995t2003r2144b2070],

1	Respirologl	NNP	O	Respirologl	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l1116t2177r1513b2241],
2	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	1	SENT_77	[p6l1116t2177r1513b2241],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	4	SENT_77	[p6l1535t2177r1727b2234],
4	2009	CD	DATE	2009	dep	1	SENT_77	[p6l1535t2177r1727b2234],
5	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	6	SENT_77	[p6l1535t2177r1727b2234],
6	14	CD	NUMBER	14	dep	4	SENT_77	[p6l1762t2178r1850b2237],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_77	[p6l1762t2178r1850b2237],
8	260-263	CD	NUMBER	260-263	appos	4	SENT_77	[p6l1880t2178r2143b2229],

1	FE	NNP	O	FE	_	0	SENT_78	[p6l520t2620r661b2682],
2	‘	CD	NUMBER	‘	num	1	SENT_78	[p6l520t2620r661b2682],
3	h	NN	O	h	dep	1	SENT_78	[p6l520t2620r661b2682],
4	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_78	[p6l520t2620r661b2682],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_78	[p6l520t2620r661b2682],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_79	[p6l520t2620r661b2682],

1	a	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_80	[p6l520t2620r661b2682],
2	chmne	NN	O	chmne	_	0	SENT_80	[p6l717t2621r943b2683],
3	ita	NN	O	ita	nn	4	SENT_80	[p6l972t2615r1056b2682],
4	plreﬂctediri	NNS	O	plreﬂctediri	dep	2	SENT_80	[p6l1084t2615r1406b2688],

1	Figure	NNP	O	Figure	nsubj	12	SENT_81	[p7l13t1862r244b1935],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	1	SENT_81	[p7l276t1864r301b1920],
3	Lung	NN	O	lung	dep	1	SENT_81	[p7l399t1862r576b1935],
4	function	NN	O	function	nn	5	SENT_81	[p7l610t1861r912b1921],
5	change	NN	O	change	dobj	3	SENT_81	[p7l947t1862r1215b1935],
6	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_81	[p7l1248t1861r1416b1921],
7	12-week	JJ	DURATION	12-week	amod	8	SENT_81	[p7l1453t1862r1753b1921],
8	treatment	NN	O	treatment	prep_after	3	SENT_81	[p7l1779t1869r2144b1921],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_81	[p7l8t1959r165b2018],
10	fluticasone	NN	O	fluticasone	nn	11	SENT_81	[p7l211t1958r617b2018],
11	propionate	NN	O	propionate	prep_with	3	SENT_81	[p7l665t1959r1067b2032],
12	combined	VBN	O	combine	_	0	SENT_81	[p7l1112t1959r1479b2018],
13	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_81	[p7l1525t1959r1681b2018],
14	salmeterol	NN	O	salmeterol	prep_with	12	SENT_81	[p7l1729t1959r2142b2027],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_81	[p7l1729t1959r2142b2027],
16	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_81	[p7l11t2055r373b2129],
17	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	12	SENT_81	[p7l412t2062r483b2114],
18	corticotrophin	NN	O	corticotrophin	nn	21	SENT_81	[p7l523t2055r1416b2129],
19	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	21	SENT_81	[p7l523t2055r1416b2129],
20	re	NN	O	re	nn	21	SENT_81	[p7l523t2055r1416b2129],
21	|	NN	O	|	pobj	12	SENT_81	[p7l523t2055r1416b2129],
22	easing	VBG	O	ease	partmod	21	SENT_81	[p7l523t2055r1416b2129],
23	hormone	NN	O	hormone	nn	24	SENT_81	[p7l1461t2055r1795b2114],
24	receptor	NN	O	receptor	dobj	22	SENT_81	[p7l1839t2062r2145b2128],
25	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	26	SENT_81	[p7l17t2154r39b2210],
26	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	24	SENT_81	[p7l84t2150r387b2217],
27	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	dep	26	SENT_81	[p7l84t2150r387b2217],
28	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	27	SENT_81	[p7l84t2150r387b2217],
29	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	32	SENT_81	[p7l422t2159r769b2225],
30	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	32	SENT_81	[p7l804t2152r1204b2217],
31	rs242941	NN	O	rs242941	nn	32	SENT_81	[p7l804t2152r1204b2217],
32	)	NN	O	)	dep	26	SENT_81	[p7l804t2152r1204b2217],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_81	[p7l804t2152r1204b2217],

1	Mean	NN	O	mean	nn	2	SENT_82	[p7l1243t2152r1442b2211],
2	(	NN	O	(	nsubj	6	SENT_82	[p7l1481t2151r1743b2217],
3	+	CC	O	+	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1481t2151r1743b2217],
4	SEM	NN	O	sem	nsubj	6	SENT_82	[p7l1481t2151r1743b2217],
5	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	6	SENT_82	[p7l1481t2151r1743b2217],
6	change	NN	O	change	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1777t2152r2045b2225],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l2081t2152r2140b2210],
8	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	prep_in	6	SENT_82	[p7l14t2249r172b2316],
9	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l208t2265r285b2308],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_82	[p7l317t2265r352b2308],
11	per	FW	O	per	nn	12	SENT_82	[p7l388t2265r505b2322],
12	cent	NN	O	cent	prep_as	8	SENT_82	[p7l533t2256r688b2308],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l718t2248r790b2308],
14	predicted	VBN	O	predict	dep	56	SENT_82	[p7l820t2249r1162b2322],
15	FEV1	NN	O	fev1	dobj	14	SENT_82	[p7l1198t2249r1357b2316],
16	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1393t2249r1755b2322],
17	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	22	SENT_82	[p7l1785t2256r1856b2308],
18	CRHR1	NN	O	crhr1	nn	19	SENT_82	[p7l1894t2248r2144b2308],
19	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	pobj	22	SENT_82	[p7l11t2351r419b2418],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l11t2351r419b2418],
21	GG	NNS	O	gg	nsubj	22	SENT_82	[p7l464t2343r576b2403],
22	(	VBP	O	(	rcmod	15	SENT_82	[p7l623t2344r797b2409],
23	wild	JJ	O	wild	amod	24	SENT_82	[p7l623t2344r797b2409],
24	type	NN	O	type	dobj	22	SENT_82	[p7l838t2351r1020b2417],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l838t2351r1020b2417],
26	71	CD	NUMBER	71	num	27	SENT_82	[p7l1061t2346r1135b2402],
27	patients	NNS	O	patient	appos	24	SENT_82	[p7l1189t2344r1504b2417],
28	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	27	SENT_82	[p7l1189t2344r1504b2417],
29	versus	CC	O	versus	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1546t2361r1790b2403],
30	GT	NN	O	gt	nn	32	SENT_82	[p7l1833t2343r1938b2403],
31	(	NN	O	(	nn	32	SENT_82	[p7l1979t2344r2143b2409, p7l11t2448r437b2515],
32	heterozygotes	NNS	O	heterozygote	conj_versus	24	SENT_82	[p7l1979t2344r2143b2409, p7l11t2448r437b2515],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1979t2344r2143b2409, p7l11t2448r437b2515],
34	13	CD	NUMBER	13	num	35	SENT_82	[p7l468t2442r544b2501],
35	patients	NNS	O	patient	appos	32	SENT_82	[p7l572t2441r911b2514],
36	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	35	SENT_82	[p7l572t2441r911b2514],
37	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l572t2441r911b2514],
38	determined	VBN	O	determine	dep	56	SENT_82	[p7l937t2441r1361b2501],
39	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1391t2441r1476b2514],
40	linear	JJ	O	linear	amod	41	SENT_82	[p7l1502t2441r1707b2501],
41	regression	NN	O	regression	prep_by	38	SENT_82	[p7l1733t2441r2142b2515],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1733t2441r2142b2515],
43	adjusting	VBG	O	adjust	dep	56	SENT_82	[p7l11t2539r351b2612],
44	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l379t2538r484b2598],
45	age	NN	O	age	prep_for	43	SENT_82	[p7l511t2555r662b2612],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l511t2555r662b2612],
47	gender	NN	O	gender	prep_for	43	SENT_82	[p7l691t2539r952b2612],
48	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l979t2539r1111b2598],
49	compliance	NN	O	compliance	prep_for	43	SENT_82	[p7l1141t2539r1589b2612],
50	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1141t2539r1589b2612],
51	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1619t2539r1752b2598],
52	assuming	VBG	O	assume	dep	56	SENT_82	[p7l1783t2539r2140b2612],
53	an	DT	O	a	det	54	SENT_82	[p7l11t2652r94b2695],
54	additive	JJ	O	additive	dobj	52	SENT_82	[p7l131t2636r424b2695],
55	genetic	JJ	O	genetic	amod	56	SENT_82	[p7l458t2636r726b2710],
56	model	NN	O	model	prep_of	12	SENT_82	[p7l761t2636r1011b2704],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l761t2636r1011b2704],
58	P	NN	O	p	dobj	6	SENT_82	[p7l1048t2636r1156b2694],
59	=	JJ	O	=	amod	58	SENT_82	[p7l1048t2636r1156b2694],
60	0.003	CD	NUMBER	0.003	tmod	59	SENT_82	[p7l1182t2637r1394b2695],
61	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_82	[p7l1182t2637r1394b2695],
