1	Int	NN	O	int	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l189t82r238b108],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l189t82r238b108],

1	J	NN	O	j	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l249t82r268b108],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l270t104r274b108],

1	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l287t82r406b108],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l287t82r406b108],
3	123	CD	NUMBER	123	dep	1	SENT_3	[p1l420t81r482b114],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l420t81r482b114],
5	586-593	CD	NUMBER	586-593	number	6	SENT_3	[p1l493t81r621b108],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	appos	1	SENT_3	[p1l634t82r730b114],
7	2008	CD	DATE	2008	dep	6	SENT_3	[p1l634t82r730b114],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	number	9	SENT_3	[p1l634t82r730b114],
9	©	CD	NUMBER	©	dep	1	SENT_3	[p1l191t128r215b152],
10	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	13	SENT_3	[p1l235t126r307b152],
11	Wiley-Liss	NNP	O	Wiley-Liss	nn	13	SENT_3	[p1l318t126r492b160],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l318t126r492b160],
13	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	dep	9	SENT_3	[p1l504t127r558b152],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l504t127r558b152],

1	Dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	2	SENT_4	[p1l191t234r321b283],
2	products	NNS	O	product	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l351t235r564b283],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l351t235r564b283],
4	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	appos	2	SENT_4	[p1l595t234r948b283],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l978t234r1020b272],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_4	[p1l1050t235r1119b273],
7	Vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	8	SENT_4	[p1l1149t234r1323b273],
8	D	NN	O	d	prep_in	4	SENT_4	[p1l1353t234r1389b272],
9	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nn	10	SENT_4	[p1l1419t237r1612b283],
10	gene	NN	O	gene	dep	2	SENT_4	[p1l1642t246r1744b283],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1774t235r1858b273],
12	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	14	SENT_4	[p1l191t297r414b334],
13	adenoma	NN	O	adenoma	nn	14	SENT_4	[p1l444t297r652b334],
14	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	dep	2	SENT_4	[p1l681t307r931b334],

1	Richard	NNP	PERSON	Richard	nn	4	SENT_5	[p1l191t382r320b409],
2	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	4	SENT_5	[p1l333t382r367b409],
3	Hubner1	NNP	PERSON	Hubner1	nn	4	SENT_5	[p1l380t374r545b415],
4	*	NNP	O	*	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l380t374r545b415],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l380t374r545b415],
6	Kenneth	NNP	PERSON	Kenneth	nn	8	SENT_5	[p1l558t382r693b409],
7	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	8	SENT_5	[p1l706t382r740b409],
8	Muirz	NNP	PERSON	Muirz	conj_and	4	SENT_5	[p1l754t374r858b415],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l754t374r858b415],
10	Jo-Fen	NNP	O	Jo-Fen	nn	11	SENT_5	[p1l871t382r980b412],
11	Liuz	NNP	O	Liuz	conj_and	4	SENT_5	[p1l993t374r1070b415],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l993t374r1070b415],
13	Richard	NNP	PERSON	Richard	nn	15	SENT_5	[p1l1084t382r1213b409],
14	F.A.	NNP	PERSON	F.A.	nn	15	SENT_5	[p1l1225t382r1292b409],
15	Loganz	NNP	PERSON	Loganz	conj_and	4	SENT_5	[p1l1305t374r1428b416],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1305t374r1428b416],
17	Matthew	NNP	PERSON	Matthew	nn	19	SENT_5	[p1l1442t382r1584b409],
18	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	19	SENT_5	[p1l1595t382r1622b412],
19	Graingez	NNP	PERSON	Graingez	conj_and	4	SENT_5	[p1l1636t374r1788b416],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1636t374r1788b416],
21	Richard	NNP	PERSON	Richard	nn	23	SENT_5	[p1l191t424r320b451],
22	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	nn	23	SENT_5	[p1l333t424r360b451],
23	Houlstonl	NNP	PERSON	Houlstonl	conj_and	4	SENT_5	[p1l374t416r531b451],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l545t425r603b451],
25	Members	NNP	O	Members	conj_and	4	SENT_5	[p1l616t424r766b451],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l779t424r811b451],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_5	[p1l821t425r869b451],
28	UKCAP	NNP	O	UKCAP	nn	30	SENT_5	[p1l882t424r1013b451],
29	Consortium	NNP	O	Consortium	nn	30	SENT_5	[p1l1026t424r1215b451],
30	llnstitate	NN	O	llnstitate	prep_of	4	SENT_5	[p1l193t463r326b497],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l341t471r375b505],
32	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	nn	33	SENT_5	[p1l384t471r494b498],
33	Research	NNP	O	Research	prep_of	30	SENT_5	[p1l506t471r654b502],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l506t471r654b502],
35	Section	NNP	O	Section	appos	33	SENT_5	[p1l669t471r778b498],
36	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l794t471r827b505],
37	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	nn	38	SENT_5	[p1l837t471r946b498],
38	Genetics	NNP	O	Genetics	prep_of	35	SENT_5	[p1l960t471r1098b502],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l960t471r1098b502],
40	Sutton	NNP	PERSON	Sutton	nn	42	SENT_5	[p1l1113t471r1208b498],
41	SM2	NN	O	sm2	nn	42	SENT_5	[p1l1223t471r1288b498],
42	5NG	NN	O	5ng	prep_of	35	SENT_5	[p1l1304t471r1382b502],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1304t471r1382b502],
44	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	46	SENT_5	[p1l1400t471r1500b498],
45	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	nn	46	SENT_5	[p1l1512t471r1649b505],
46	2Division	NN	O	2division	conj_and	38	SENT_5	[p1l191t505r330b539],
47	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l345t513r379b547],
48	Epidemiology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Epidemiology	prep_of	46	SENT_5	[p1l386t513r594b547],
49	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l609t513r666b539],
50	Public	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Public	nn	51	SENT_5	[p1l677t513r775b539],
51	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Health	conj_and	38	SENT_5	[p1l789t513r899b544],
52	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l789t513r899b544],
53	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	54	SENT_5	[p1l913t513r1037b539],
54	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	appos	38	SENT_5	[p1l1051t513r1160b544],
55	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1051t513r1160b544],
56	Qaeen	NNP	O	Qaeen	poss	59	SENT_5	[p1l1177t513r1300b546],
57	’s	POS	O	’s	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1177t513r1300b546],
58	Medical	NNP	O	Medical	nn	59	SENT_5	[p1l1313t513r1437b539],
59	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	appos	54	SENT_5	[p1l1451t513r1559b544],
60	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1451t513r1559b544],
61	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	38	SENT_5	[p1l1578t514r1730b547],
62	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1745t513r1779b547],
63	Nottingham	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nottingham	prep_of	61	SENT_5	[p1l1786t513r1971b547],
64	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1786t513r1971b547],

1	Nottingham	NNP	O	Nottingham	nn	3	SENT_6	[p1l7t564r386b636],
2	NG7	NN	O	ng7	nn	3	SENT_6	[p1l414t565r568b621],
3	2UH	NN	O	2uh	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l595t564r766b629],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l595t564r766b629],
5	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	6	SENT_6	[p1l805t564r1019b621],
6	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	appos	3	SENT_6	[p1l1044t564r1336b636],

1	Vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	2	SENT_7	[p1l12t796r272b849],
2	D	NN	O	d	nsubj	8	SENT_7	[p1l310t797r361b848],
3	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nn	7	SENT_7	[p1l399t801r667b864],
4	(	NN	O	(	nn	7	SENT_7	[p1l708t796r913b861],
5	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	7	SENT_7	[p1l708t796r913b861],
6	)	NN	O	)	nn	7	SENT_7	[p1l708t796r913b861],
7	activation	NN	O	activation	dep	2	SENT_7	[p1l953t796r1268b849],
8	inhibits	VBZ	O	inhibit	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1306t796r1545b849],
9	proliferation	NN	O	proliferation	dobj	8	SENT_7	[p1l1583t796r1990b864],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l2029t798r2146b849],
11	angiogenesis	NN	O	angiogenesis	dobj	8	SENT_7	[p1l12t870r410b938],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l443t870r502b922],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_7	[p1l534t871r630b923],
14	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	15	SENT_7	[p1l663t871r974b923],
15	epithelium	NN	O	epithelium	prep_in	8	SENT_7	[p1l1007t870r1366b938],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1007t870r1366b938],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1398t871r1516b923],
18	inhibits	VBZ	O	inhibit	conj_and	8	SENT_7	[p1l1547t870r1787b923],
19	metastasis	NN	O	metastasis	dobj	18	SENT_7	[p1l1819t870r2146b923],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l12t944r77b997],
21	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	22	SENT_7	[p1l96t946r407b998],
22	tumors	NNS	O	tumor	prep_of	19	SENT_7	[p1l432t949r676b998],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l432t949r676b998],

1	Polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubj	15	SENT_8	[p1l702t944r1201b1012],
2	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1226t944r1286b996],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_8	[p1l1310t946r1407b998],
4	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	5	SENT_8	[p1l1433t946r1580b998],
5	gene	NN	O	gene	prep_in	1	SENT_8	[p1l1607t961r1750b1012],
6	alter	VBP	O	alter	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1775t946r1922b998],
7	receptor	NN	O	receptor	nn	9	SENT_8	[p1l1948t961r2144b1012, p1l12t1022r105b1071],
8	cellular	JJ	O	cellular	amod	9	SENT_8	[p1l129t1019r369b1071],
9	levels	NNS	O	level	dobj	6	SENT_8	[p1l394t1019r567b1071],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l591t1019r709b1071],
11	functioning	VBG	O	function	dobj	6	SENT_8	[p1l733t1018r1116b1085],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l733t1018r1116b1085],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l1141t1019r1258b1071],
14	may	MD	O	may	aux	15	SENT_8	[p1l1282t1034r1417b1086],
15	confer	VB	O	confer	conj_and	6	SENT_8	[p1l1441t1018r1643b1071],
16	altered	JJ	O	altered	amod	17	SENT_8	[p1l1668t1019r1891b1071],
17	susceptibility	NN	O	susceptibility	dobj	15	SENT_8	[p1l1915t1034r2144b1086, p1l12t1093r223b1160],
18	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l253t1097r313b1146],
19	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	20	SENT_8	[p1l342t1094r654b1146],
20	neoplasia	NN	O	neoplasium	prep_to	15	SENT_8	[p1l685t1093r1000b1160],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l685t1093r1000b1160],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_9	[p1l1031t1093r1137b1146],
2	aimed	VBD	O	aim	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1167t1093r1361b1146],
3	to	TO	O	to	aux	4	SENT_9	[p1l1391t1097r1451b1146],
4	investigate	VB	O	investigate	xcomp	2	SENT_9	[p1l1480t1093r1820b1160],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_9	[p1l1851t1094r1947b1146],
6	inﬂuence	NN	O	inﬂuence	dobj	4	SENT_9	[p1l1978t1093r2144b1146, p1l12t1183r151b1220],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l193t1167r258b1220],
8	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	9	SENT_9	[p1l295t1169r443b1220],
9	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	prep_of	6	SENT_9	[p1l486t1167r980b1235],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1022t1168r1139b1220],
11	dietary	JJ	O	dietary	amod	12	SENT_9	[p1l1181t1167r1408b1235],
12	factors	NNS	O	factor	dobj	4	SENT_9	[p1l1449t1167r1668b1220],
13	impacting	VBG	O	impact	partmod	12	SENT_9	[p1l1709t1167r2028b1235],
14	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l2070t1183r2146b1220],
15	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	17	SENT_9	[p1l11t1242r256b1296],
16	D	NN	O	d	nn	17	SENT_9	[p1l286t1243r336b1295],
17	metabolism	NN	O	metabolism	prep_on	13	SENT_9	[p1l368t1242r737b1296],
18	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l768t1259r844b1296],
19	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	20	SENT_9	[p1l874t1244r1186b1296],
20	adenoma	NN	O	adenoma	prep_on	17	SENT_9	[p1l1217t1244r1507b1296],
21	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_9	[p1l1539t1242r1744b1307],
22	CRA	NNP	O	CRA	nn	24	SENT_9	[p1l1539t1242r1744b1307],
23	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	24	SENT_9	[p1l1539t1242r1744b1307],
24	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	dep	20	SENT_9	[p1l1777t1259r2144b1296],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1777t1259r2144b1296],

1	Data	NNS	O	datum	nsubjpass	14	SENT_10	[p1l12t1317r164b1370],
2	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l190t1333r266b1369],
3	dietary	JJ	O	dietary	amod	4	SENT_10	[p1l293t1316r520b1384],
4	intakes	NN	O	intake	prep_on	1	SENT_10	[p1l546t1316r772b1370],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l799t1316r864b1369],
6	calcium	NN	O	calcium	nn	9	SENT_10	[p1l885t1316r1151b1382],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l885t1316r1151b1382],
8	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	dep	9	SENT_10	[p1l1178t1316r1423b1370],
9	D	NN	O	d	prep_of	4	SENT_10	[p1l1448t1317r1499b1368],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1526t1318r1644b1370],
11	dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	12	SENT_10	[p1l1671t1316r1839b1384],
12	products	NNS	O	product	conj_and	9	SENT_10	[p1l1865t1318r2146b1384],
13	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	14	SENT_10	[p1l11t1406r163b1443],
14	collected	VBN	O	collect	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l192t1391r470b1443],
15	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l497t1390r654b1443],
16	853	CD	NUMBER	853	num	17	SENT_10	[p1l681t1390r790b1443],
17	participants	NNS	O	participant	prep_from	14	SENT_10	[p1l819t1390r1204b1458],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1232t1390r1291b1442],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_10	[p1l1319t1391r1416b1443],
20	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	23	SENT_10	[p1l1443t1390r1658b1443],
21	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	nn	23	SENT_10	[p1l1685t1390r1983b1458],
22	Colorectal	JJ	ORGANIZATION	colorectal	amod	23	SENT_10	[p1l2012t1390r2144b1443, p1l12t1465r231b1517],
23	Adenoma	NN	ORGANIZATION	adenoma	prep_in	17	SENT_10	[p1l265t1465r571b1517],
24	Prevention	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Prevention	nn	25	SENT_10	[p1l605t1464r954b1517],
25	trial	NN	O	trial	dep	23	SENT_10	[p1l988t1464r1142b1529],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l988t1464r1142b1529],
27	a	DT	O	a	det	29	SENT_10	[p1l1176t1480r1211b1517],
28	randomized	JJ	O	randomized	amod	29	SENT_10	[p1l1245t1464r1626b1517],
29	trial	NN	O	trial	prep_in	17	SENT_10	[p1l1660t1464r1795b1517],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1830t1464r1895b1517],
31	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	prep_of	29	SENT_10	[p1l1923t1464r2146b1532],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l12t1539r129b1591],
33	folate	NN	O	folate	prep_in	17	SENT_10	[p1l156t1538r333b1591],
34	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l360t1538r454b1591],
35	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	37	SENT_10	[p1l482t1538r640b1591],
36	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	nn	37	SENT_10	[p1l667t1554r1016b1591],
37	prevention	NN	O	prevention	prep_for	33	SENT_10	[p1l1044t1538r1406b1606],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1044t1538r1406b1606],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_11	[p1l1435t1539r1556b1591],
2	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	3	SENT_11	[p1l1586t1540r1733b1591],
3	CdX2	NN	O	cdx2	nsubjpass	14	SENT_11	[p1l1763t1538r1948b1603],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1763t1538r1948b1603],
5	Fokl	NNP	O	Fokl	nsubjpass	14	SENT_11	[p1l1972t1539r2145b1603],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1972t1539r2145b1603],
7	Bsml	NNP	PERSON	Bsml	nsubjpass	14	SENT_11	[p1l8t1613r194b1678],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l8t1613r194b1678],
9	Apal	NNP	O	Apal	nsubjpass	14	SENT_11	[p1l217t1613r376b1680],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l403t1614r520b1666],
11	Taql	NNP	PERSON	Taql	nn	12	SENT_11	[p1l550t1613r697b1680],
12	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	nsubjpass	14	SENT_11	[p1l725t1612r1220b1680],
13	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	14	SENT_11	[p1l1247t1629r1400b1666],
14	genotyped	VBN	O	genotype	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1429t1614r1756b1680],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1785t1612r1844b1664],
16	546	CD	NUMBER	546	num	17	SENT_11	[p1l1873t1613r1982b1666],
17	participants	NNS	O	participant	prep_in	14	SENT_11	[p1l2011t1629r2144b1680, p1l12t1686r285b1754],
18	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l316t1686r456b1739],
19	available	JJ	O	available	amod	27	SENT_11	[p1l488t1686r774b1739],
20	DNA	NN	MISC	dna	tmod	19	SENT_11	[p1l806t1687r983b1751],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l806t1687r983b1751],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1016t1688r1134b1739],
23	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	26	SENT_11	[p1l1166t1686r1469b1754],
24	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	26	SENT_11	[p1l1166t1686r1469b1754],
25	diet	NN	O	diet	nn	26	SENT_11	[p1l1166t1686r1469b1754],
26	interaction	NN	O	interaction	conj_and	20	SENT_11	[p1l1500t1686r1849b1739],
27	analyses	NNS	O	analysis	prep_with	14	SENT_11	[p1l1882t1688r2146b1754],
28	performed	VBN	O	perform	partmod	27	SENT_11	[p1l12t1761r352b1828],
29	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l384t1761r444b1813],
30	480	CD	NUMBER	480	prep_in	28	SENT_11	[p1l476t1761r603b1814],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l476t1761r603b1814],

1	Dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	3	SENT_12	[p1l636t1761r818b1828],
2	product	NN	O	product	nn	3	SENT_12	[p1l850t1762r1102b1828],
3	intake	NN	O	intake	nsubj	22	SENT_12	[p1l1133t1761r1331b1814],
4	was	VBD	O	be	cop	22	SENT_12	[p1l1361t1777r1480b1814],
5	inversely	RB	O	inversely	advmod	22	SENT_12	[p1l1512t1761r1799b1828],
6	related	JJ	O	related	pobj	5	SENT_12	[p1l1831t1762r2054b1814],
7	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l2086t1765r2146b1814],
8	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	10	SENT_12	[p1l13t1835r171b1888],
9	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	nn	10	SENT_12	[p1l195t1851r544b1888],
10	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_to	6	SENT_12	[p1l569t1835r692b1888],
11	independent	JJ	O	independent	amod	6	SENT_12	[p1l715t1835r1109b1903],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1133t1835r1198b1888],
13	calcium	NN	O	calcium	nn	17	SENT_12	[p1l1216t1835r1464b1888],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1489t1836r1606b1888],
15	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	17	SENT_12	[p1l1629t1835r1873b1888],
16	D	NN	O	d	nn	17	SENT_12	[p1l1898t1836r1948b1887],
17	[	NN	O	[	prep_of	6	SENT_12	[p1l1976t1836r2144b1898, p1l12t1910r126b1963],
18	relative	JJ	O	relative	advmod	5	SENT_12	[p1l1976t1836r2144b1898, p1l12t1910r126b1963],
19	risk	NN	O	risk	nn	22	SENT_12	[p1l156t1910r279b1963],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	22	SENT_12	[p1l309t1910r461b1974],
21	RR	NN	O	rr	nn	22	SENT_12	[p1l309t1910r461b1974],
22	)	NN	O	)	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l309t1910r461b1974],
23	=	JJ	O	=	amod	22	SENT_12	[p1l499t1927r546b1951],
24	0.64	CD	NUMBER	0.64	tmod	23	SENT_12	[p1l582t1910r732b1975],
25	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l582t1910r732b1975],
26	95	CD	PERCENT	95	number	27	SENT_12	[p1l765t1910r905b1963],
27	%	NN	PERCENT	%	amod	29	SENT_12	[p1l765t1910r905b1963],
28	conﬁdence	NN	O	conﬁdence	nn	29	SENT_12	[p1l942t1910r1277b1963],
29	intervals	NNS	O	interval	nsubj	30	SENT_12	[p1l1308t1910r1585b1963],
30	(	VBP	O	(	parataxis	22	SENT_12	[p1l1617t1909r1794b1974],
31	CIs	NNS	MISC	ci	dobj	30	SENT_12	[p1l1617t1909r1794b1974],
32	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	31	SENT_12	[p1l1617t1909r1794b1974],
33	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1617t1909r1794b1974],
34	0.47-0	CD	NUMBER	0.47-0	number	35	SENT_12	[p1l1829t1910r2145b1975],
35	.88	CD	NUMBER	.88	dep	31	SENT_12	[p1l1829t1910r2145b1975],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1829t1910r2145b1975],
37	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l11t1984r105b2037],
38	subjects	NNS	O	subject	prep_for	31	SENT_12	[p1l131t1984r386b2052],
39	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l411t1984r471b2036],
40	the	DT	O	the	det	41	SENT_12	[p1l496t1986r593b2037],
41	highest	JJS	O	highest	prep_in	30	SENT_12	[p1l618t1984r845b2052],
42	compared	VBN	O	compare	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l870t1986r1190b2052],
43	to	TO	O	to	prepc_compared_to	41	SENT_12	[p1l1214t1989r1274b2037],
44	lowest	JJS	O	lowest	amod	46	SENT_12	[p1l1299t1986r1497b2037],
45	intake	NN	O	intake	nn	46	SENT_12	[p1l1522t1984r1719b2037],
46	tertile	NN	O	tertile	pobj	41	SENT_12	[p1l1745t1984r1953b2049],
47	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1745t1984r1953b2049],
48	ptrend	NN	O	ptrend	appos	46	SENT_12	[p1l1972t2002r2146b2051],
49	=	JJ	O	=	amod	51	SENT_12	[p1l19t2075r65b2098],
50	0.005	CD	NUMBER	0.005	tmod	49	SENT_12	[p1l95t2058r304b2120],
51	]	NN	O	]	dep	48	SENT_12	[p1l95t2058r304b2120],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l95t2058r304b2120],

1	Milk	NN	O	milk	nsubj	2	SENT_13	[p1l328t2058r481b2110],
2	accounted	VBD	O	account	conj_and	2	SENT_13	[p1l504t2059r827b2111],
3	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l851t2058r944b2111],
4	60	CD	PERCENT	60	num	5	SENT_13	[p1l968t2057r1108b2111],
5	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_for	2	SENT_13	[p1l968t2057r1108b2111],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1138t2058r1204b2111],
7	dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	9	SENT_13	[p1l1222t2058r1390b2125],
8	product	NN	O	product	nn	9	SENT_13	[p1l1414t2059r1666b2125],
9	intake	NN	O	intake	prep_of	5	SENT_13	[p1l1689t2058r1904b2123],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1689t2058r1904b2123],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1929t2059r2046b2111],
12	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l2070t2074r2146b2111],
13	analysis	NN	O	analysis	prep_on	2	SENT_13	[p1l12t2133r264b2200],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l304t2133r369b2186],
15	milk	NN	O	milk	nn	19	SENT_13	[p1l403t2133r547b2185],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l587t2134r705b2186],
17	nonmilk	JJ	O	nonmilk	conj_and	15	SENT_13	[p1l745t2133r1009b2186],
18	dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	19	SENT_13	[p1l1050t2133r1218b2200],
19	products	NNS	O	product	prep_of	13	SENT_13	[p1l1258t2134r1539b2200],
20	separately	RB	O	separately	dep	2	SENT_13	[p1l1579t2134r1908b2200],
21	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	nn	22	SENT_13	[p1l1948t2149r2144b2186, p1l12t2223r184b2260],
22	risk	NN	O	risk	nsubj	34	SENT_13	[p1l216t2207r338b2260],
23	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l368t2207r427b2259],
24	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_in	22	SENT_13	[p1l458t2207r810b2260],
25	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l841t2207r900b2259],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_13	[p1l931t2208r1027b2260],
27	highest	JJS	O	highest	amod	28	SENT_13	[p1l1059t2207r1286b2275],
28	tertile	NN	O	tertile	prep_in	24	SENT_13	[p1l1315t2207r1505b2260],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1537t2207r1602b2260],
30	milk	NN	O	milk	nn	31	SENT_13	[p1l1626t2207r1770b2259],
31	intake	NN	O	intake	prep_of	28	SENT_13	[p1l1800t2207r1997b2260],
32	was	VBD	O	be	cop	34	SENT_13	[p1l2027t2223r2146b2260],
33	half	PDT	O	half	predet	34	SENT_13	[p1l12t2281r140b2334],
34	that	DT	O	that	dep	39	SENT_13	[p1l164t2282r291b2334],
35	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l319t2281r384b2334],
36	lowest	JJS	O	lowest	amod	38	SENT_13	[p1l408t2282r606b2334],
37	tertile	JJ	O	tertile	amod	38	SENT_13	[p1l635t2281r825b2334],
38	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_of	34	SENT_13	[p1l855t2281r1208b2334],
39	(	VBP	O	(	parataxis	2	SENT_13	[p1l1239t2280r1367b2345],
40	RR	NN	O	rr	nn	53	SENT_13	[p1l1239t2280r1367b2345],
41	=	JJ	O	=	amod	40	SENT_13	[p1l1403t2298r1449b2322],
42	0.52	CD	NUMBER	0.52	tmod	41	SENT_13	[p1l1486t2281r1636b2346],
43	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1486t2281r1636b2346],
44	95	CD	PERCENT	95	num	45	SENT_13	[p1l1668t2281r1740b2334],
45	%	NN	PERCENT	%	dep	40	SENT_13	[p1l1751t2281r1808b2334],
46	CI	NN	O	ci	dep	45	SENT_13	[p1l1846t2281r1946b2334],
47	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1846t2281r1946b2334],
48	0.380.72	CD	NUMBER	0.380.72	dep	40	SENT_13	[p1l1980t2281r2148b2334, p1l12t2355r159b2422],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1980t2281r2148b2334, p1l12t2355r159b2422],
50	ptrend	NN	O	ptrend	appos	48	SENT_13	[p1l186t2373r360b2423],
51	=	JJ	O	=	amod	53	SENT_13	[p1l401t2373r447b2396],
52	3.2	CD	NUMBER	3.2	tmod	51	SENT_13	[p1l488t2356r579b2409],
53	X	NN	O	x	dobj	39	SENT_13	[p1l622t2364r664b2405],
54	10-5	CD	NUMBER	10-5	num	55	SENT_13	[p1l710t2340r898b2422],
55	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	39	SENT_13	[p1l710t2340r898b2422],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l710t2340r898b2422],
57	Whereas	IN	O	whereas	mark	61	SENT_13	[p1l932t2357r1193b2409],
58	nonmilk	JJ	O	nonmilk	amod	60	SENT_13	[p1l1228t2355r1492b2409],
59	dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	60	SENT_13	[p1l1527t2355r1695b2424],
60	products	NNS	O	product	nsubj	61	SENT_13	[p1l1730t2357r2010b2424],
61	did	VBD	O	do	dep	2	SENT_13	[p1l2045t2355r2146b2409],
62	not	RB	O	not	neg	61	SENT_13	[p1l12t2435r114b2484],
63	inﬂuence	NN	O	inﬂuence	nn	64	SENT_13	[p1l139t2431r425b2484],
64	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	dobj	61	SENT_13	[p1l452t2447r819b2484],
65	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l452t2447r819b2484],

1	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	3	SENT_14	[p1l849t2432r997b2484],
2	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	nn	3	SENT_14	[p1l1026t2431r1491b2498],
3	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	nsubj	9	SENT_14	[p1l1518t2435r1832b2498],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1859t2432r1976b2484],
5	haplotypes	NNS	O	haplotype	nsubj	9	SENT_14	[p1l2003t2432r2144b2498, p1l12t2507r235b2573],
6	did	VBD	O	do	aux	9	SENT_14	[p1l261t2505r361b2559],
7	not	RB	O	not	neg	9	SENT_14	[p1l387t2510r489b2559],
8	directly	RB	O	directly	advmod	9	SENT_14	[p1l515t2505r759b2573],
9	alter	VB	O	alter	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l784t2507r932b2559],
10	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	nn	11	SENT_14	[p1l958t2522r1307b2559],
11	risk	NN	O	risk	dobj	9	SENT_14	[p1l1334t2505r1474b2571],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1334t2505r1474b2571],
13	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1501t2507r1606b2559],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_14	[p1l1631t2507r1728b2559],
15	reduction	NN	O	reduction	nsubjpass	25	SENT_14	[p1l1754t2505r2060b2559],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l2087t2505r2146b2557],
17	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_in	15	SENT_14	[p1l12t2579r134b2632],
18	associated	VBN	O	associate	partmod	17	SENT_14	[p1l173t2579r496b2632],
19	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l534t2579r674b2632],
20	high	JJ	O	high	amod	23	SENT_14	[p1l712t2579r850b2647],
21	dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	23	SENT_14	[p1l890t2579r1058b2647],
22	product	NN	O	product	nn	23	SENT_14	[p1l1097t2580r1349b2647],
23	intake	NN	O	intake	prep_with	18	SENT_14	[p1l1387t2579r1584b2632],
24	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	25	SENT_14	[p1l1622t2595r1741b2632],
25	conﬁned	VBN	O	conﬁned	conj_but	9	SENT_14	[p1l1779t2579r2047b2632],
26	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l2086t2583r2146b2632],
27	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_to	25	SENT_14	[p1l12t2653r364b2707],
28	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l395t2653r534b2707],
29	Apal	JJ	O	apal	amod	33	SENT_14	[p1l559t2654r717b2721],
30	aA/AA	NN	O	aa/aa	nn	33	SENT_14	[p1l747t2649r966b2707],
31	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	33	SENT_14	[p1l996t2658r1281b2722],
32	(	NN	O	(	nn	33	SENT_14	[p1l1314t2653r1636b2721],
33	pinteraction	NN	O	pinteraction	prep_with	27	SENT_14	[p1l1314t2653r1636b2721],
34	=	JJ	O	=	amod	33	SENT_14	[p1l1674t2671r1720b2694],
35	0.02	CD	NUMBER	0.02	num	36	SENT_14	[p1l1758t2653r1929b2719],
36	)	NN	O	)	dep	34	SENT_14	[p1l1758t2653r1929b2719],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1758t2653r1929b2719],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_15	[p1l1961t2654r2146b2707],
2	ﬁndings	NNS	O	ﬁndings	nsubj	3	SENT_15	[p1l12t2728r263b2796],
3	indicate	VBP	O	indicate	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l288t2728r539b2781],
4	dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	5	SENT_15	[p1l565t2728r733b2796],
5	products	NNS	O	product	dobj	3	SENT_15	[p1l758t2730r1056b2796],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l758t2730r1056b2796],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1082t2730r1199b2781],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1224t2728r1283b2780],
9	particular	JJ	O	particular	amod	10	SENT_15	[p1l1308t2728r1631b2796],
10	milk	NN	O	milk	prep_in	12	SENT_15	[p1l1656t2728r1818b2794],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1656t2728r1818b2794],
12	have	VBP	O	have	conj_and	3	SENT_15	[p1l1843t2730r1990b2781],
13	chemopreventive	JJ	O	chemopreventive	amod	14	SENT_15	[p1l2015t2730r2144b2781, p1l12t2802r448b2870],
14	activity	NN	O	activity	dobj	12	SENT_15	[p1l472t2802r708b2870],
15	against	IN	O	against	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l730t2802r957b2870],
16	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	prep_against	14	SENT_15	[p1l980t2802r1138b2856],
17	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	nsubj	12	SENT_15	[p1l1160t2819r1527b2856],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1160t2819r1527b2856],

1	©	RB	O	©	advmod	2	SENT_16	[p1l12t2882r60b2930],
2	2008	CD	DATE	2008	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l99t2878r249b2930],
3	Wiley	NNP	PERSON	Wiley	dep	2	SENT_16	[p1l272t2878r603b2945],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l272t2878r603b2945],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l272t2878r603b2945],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l272t2878r603b2945],

1	Liss	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Liss	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l272t2878r603b2945],
2	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l272t2878r603b2945],
3	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	appos	1	SENT_18	[p1l623t2879r736b2930],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l623t2879r736b2930],

1	Key	NN	O	key	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l12t3074r139b3141],
2	words	NNS	O	word	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l166t3075r381b3127],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l166t3075r381b3127],
4	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	6	SENT_19	[p1l427t3074r723b3126],
5	adenoma	NN	O	adenoma	nn	6	SENT_19	[p1l765t3074r1036b3126],
6	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l1075t3091r1409b3136],
7	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1075t3091r1409b3136],
8	dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	9	SENT_19	[p1l1456t3074r1608b3142],
9	products	NNS	O	product	dep	6	SENT_19	[p1l1648t3074r1923b3142],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1648t3074r1923b3142],
11	VDR	NN	O	vdr	dep	9	SENT_19	[p1l1969t3075r2142b3136],
12	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1969t3075r2142b3136],
13	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	dep	6	SENT_19	[p1l10t3148r450b3215],

1	Colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	5	SENT_20	[p2l92t59r423b114],
2	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	5	SENT_20	[p2l452t76r660b114],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_20	[p2l689t59r895b127],
4	CRC	NN	ORGANIZATION	crc	nn	5	SENT_20	[p2l689t59r895b127],
5	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	10	SENT_20	[p2l689t59r895b127],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	10	SENT_20	[p2l926t59r975b114],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_20	[p2l1005t59r1099b114],
8	third	JJ	ORDINAL	third	amod	10	SENT_20	[p2l1128t59r1278b114],
9	commonest	NN	O	commonest	nn	10	SENT_20	[p2l1307t67r1674b114],
10	cancer	NN	O	cancer	dep	37	SENT_20	[p2l1701t76r1909b114],
11	worldwide	RB	O	worldwide	advmod	10	SENT_20	[p2l1937t59r2145b114, p2l12t143r163b198],
12	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l196t142r341b198],
13	lung	NN	O	lung	nn	16	SENT_20	[p2l370t143r508b215],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l541t143r653b198],
15	breast	NN	O	breast	nn	16	SENT_20	[p2l682t143r872b198],
16	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_after	10	SENT_20	[p2l902t160r1126b208],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l902t160r1126b208],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1161t143r1273b198],
19	two-thirds	NNS	O	two-third	nsubj	22	SENT_20	[p2l1302t143r1627b198],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1660t142r1728b198],
21	CRC	NN	ORGANIZATION	crc	prep_of	19	SENT_20	[p2l1754t143r1909b199],
22	occurs	VBZ	O	occur	conj_and	10	SENT_20	[p2l1941t160r2145b198],
23	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l12t227r72b282],
24	developed	JJ	O	developed	amod	25	SENT_20	[p2l99t227r425b299],
25	countries	NNS	O	country	prep_in	22	SENT_20	[p2l451t210r787b283],
26	.1	CD	NUMBER	.1	number	29	SENT_20	[p2l451t210r787b283],
27	Up	IN	O	up	quantmod	29	SENT_20	[p2l819t228r912b299],
28	to	TO	O	to	dep	29	SENT_20	[p2l939t236r999b282],
29	90	CD	PERCENT	90	num	30	SENT_20	[p2l1027t227r1166b283],
30	%	NN	PERCENT	%	nsubj	33	SENT_20	[p2l1027t227r1166b283],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1197t227r1265b282],
32	CRCS	NN	O	crc	prep_of	30	SENT_20	[p2l1288t227r1473b283],
33	develop	VBP	O	develop	rcmod	25	SENT_20	[p2l1501t227r1751b299],
34	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1779t227r1931b282],
35	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	36	SENT_20	[p2l1958t227r2144b282, p2l12t312r160b367],
36	adenomas	NNS	O	adenoma	prep_from	33	SENT_20	[p2l220t311r535b367],
37	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l597t312r837b380],
38	CRAS	NNP	O	CRAS	nsubj	45	SENT_20	[p2l597t312r837b380],
39	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	38	SENT_20	[p2l597t312r837b380],
40	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l899t312r1011b367],
41	colonoscopic	JJ	O	colonoscopic	amod	42	SENT_20	[p2l1068t311r1486b384],
42	removal	NN	O	removal	nsubj	45	SENT_20	[p2l1544t312r1805b367],
43	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1864t311r1932b367],
44	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	prep_of	42	SENT_20	[p2l1986t312r2147b367],
45	reduces	VBZ	O	reduce	ccomp	37	SENT_20	[p2l10t396r252b451],
46	the	DT	O	the	det	47	SENT_20	[p2l285t396r380b451],
47	incidence	NN	O	incidence	iobj	45	SENT_20	[p2l414t396r717b451],
48	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l751t395r820b451],
49	CRC	NN	ORGANIZATION	crc	nn	50	SENT_20	[p2l848t378r1096b452],
50	.2	NN	NUMBER	.2	prep_of	47	SENT_20	[p2l848t378r1096b452],
51	’	CD	NUMBER	’	number	52	SENT_20	[p2l848t378r1096b452],
52	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dobj	45	SENT_20	[p2l848t378r1096b452],
53	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1130t397r1195b451],
54	some	DT	O	some	det	55	SENT_20	[p2l1229t414r1392b451],
55	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_in	64	SENT_20	[p2l1425t396r1795b462],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1425t396r1795b462],
57	the	DT	O	the	det	59	SENT_20	[p2l1829t396r1925b451],
58	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	nn	59	SENT_20	[p2l1956t414r2144b451, p2l10t498r182b536],
59	rate	NN	O	rate	nsubj	64	SENT_20	[p2l219t489r338b536],
60	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l376t480r469b536],
61	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	prep_for	59	SENT_20	[p2l506t481r666b536],
62	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	64	SENT_20	[p2l704t480r753b536],
63	as	RB	O	as	advmod	64	SENT_20	[p2l793t498r854b536],
64	high	JJ	O	high	rcmod	52	SENT_20	[p2l893t480r1034b552],
65	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1072t498r1133b536],
66	40-50	CD	PERCENT	40-50	num	67	SENT_20	[p2l1172t480r1433b536],
67	%	NN	PERCENT	%	prep_as	64	SENT_20	[p2l1172t480r1433b536],
68	after	IN	O	after	mark	89	SENT_20	[p2l1475t480r1620b536],
69	3	CD	DURATION	3	num	70	SENT_20	[p2l1658t481r1690b536],
70	years	NNS	NUMBER	year	nsubj	89	SENT_20	[p2l1731t463r1947b552],
71	,4	CD	NUMBER	,4	num	73	SENT_20	[p2l1731t463r1947b552],
72	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	73	SENT_20	[p2l1986t481r2147b536],
73	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	nsubj	77	SENT_20	[p2l10t582r346b620],
74	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	77	SENT_20	[p2l379t564r428b620],
75	a	DT	O	a	det	77	SENT_20	[p2l462t582r495b620],
76	surrogate	JJ	O	surrogate	amod	77	SENT_20	[p2l528t573r819b636],
77	marker	NN	O	marker	rcmod	70	SENT_20	[p2l851t564r1078b620],
78	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1108t564r1200b620],
79	CRC	NN	ORGANIZATION	crc	nn	80	SENT_20	[p2l1231t565r1385b620],
80	risk	NN	O	risk	prep_for	77	SENT_20	[p2l1417t564r1537b620],
81	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1568t564r1680b620],
82	prevention	NN	O	prevention	conj_and	80	SENT_20	[p2l1710t564r2052b637],
83	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l2083t564r2151b620],
84	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	85	SENT_20	[p2l12t648r173b704],
85	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	prep_of	70	SENT_20	[p2l198t666r534b704],
86	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	89	SENT_20	[p2l560t648r609b704],
87	a	DT	O	a	det	89	SENT_20	[p2l638t666r671b704],
88	useful	JJ	O	useful	amod	89	SENT_20	[p2l695t648r888b704],
89	endpoint	NN	O	endpoint	advcl	64	SENT_20	[p2l914t648r1192b720],
90	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_20	[p2l1217t648r1309b704],
91	evaluating	VBG	O	evaluate	prepc_for	89	SENT_20	[p2l1334t648r1664b720],
92	chemopreventive	JJ	O	chemopreventive	amod	93	SENT_20	[p2l1692t648r2145b720, p2l11t732r129b788],
93	agents	NNS	O	agent	dobj	91	SENT_20	[p2l154t715r401b804],
94	.5	CD	NUMBER	.5	nsubj	37	SENT_20	[p2l154t715r401b804],

1	Activation	NN	O	activation	nsubj	6	SENT_21	[p2l91t832r428b888],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l455t832r523b888],
3	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	5	SENT_21	[p2l544t832r788b888],
4	D	NN	O	d	nn	5	SENT_21	[p2l814t833r868b887],
5	receptors	NNS	O	receptor	prep_of	1	SENT_21	[p2l894t841r1184b904],
6	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1215t832r1459b901],
7	VDRS	NN	O	vdr	nsubj	21	SENT_21	[p2l1215t832r1459b901],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	7	SENT_21	[p2l1215t832r1459b901],
9	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	7	SENT_21	[p2l1487t841r1718b904],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1745t832r1805b887],
11	many	JJ	O	many	amod	13	SENT_21	[p2l1830t849r2005b904],
12	cell	NN	O	cell	nn	13	SENT_21	[p2l2033t832r2146b888],
13	types	NNS	O	type	prep_in	9	SENT_21	[p2l11t924r195b988],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l11t924r195b988],
15	including	VBG	O	include	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l235t916r534b988],
16	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	18	SENT_21	[p2l572t916r885b972],
17	epithelial	JJ	O	epithelial	amod	18	SENT_21	[p2l923t916r1219b988],
18	cells	NNS	O	cell	prep_including	21	SENT_21	[p2l1256t916r1417b982],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1256t916r1417b982],
20	can	MD	O	can	aux	21	SENT_21	[p2l1458t933r1567b972],
21	inhibit	VB	O	inhibit	ccomp	6	SENT_21	[p2l1603t916r1811b972],
22	proliferation	NN	O	proliferation	dobj	21	SENT_21	[p2l1844t916r2144b988, p2l11t1000r151b1066],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1844t916r2144b988, p2l11t1000r151b1066],
24	angiogenesis	NN	O	angiogenesis	dobj	21	SENT_21	[p2l181t1000r589b1072],
25	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l619t1000r731b1055],
26	invasiveness	NN	O	invasiveness	dobj	21	SENT_21	[p2l757t1000r1175b1066],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l757t1000r1175b1066],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1205t1000r1318b1055],
29	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	33	SENT_21	[p2l1346t1000r1561b1055],
30	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1590t1000r1650b1055],
31	animal	NN	O	animal	nn	32	SENT_21	[p2l1677t999r1891b1055],
32	models	NNS	O	model	prep_in	29	SENT_21	[p2l1917t1000r2145b1055],
33	indicate	VBP	O	indicate	conj_and	6	SENT_21	[p2l12t1083r262b1138],
34	that	IN	O	that	complm	39	SENT_21	[p2l294t1083r414b1138],
35	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	37	SENT_21	[p2l444t1083r688b1138],
36	D	NN	O	d	nn	37	SENT_21	[p2l719t1084r773b1138],
37	supplementation	NN	O	supplementation	nsubj	39	SENT_21	[p2l807t1083r1332b1155],
38	can	MD	O	can	aux	39	SENT_21	[p2l1363t1100r1472b1138],
39	lower	VB	O	lower	ccomp	33	SENT_21	[p2l1503t1083r1684b1138],
40	the	DT	O	the	det	41	SENT_21	[p2l1714t1083r1809b1138],
41	incidence	NN	O	incidence	dobj	39	SENT_21	[p2l1842t1083r2145b1138],
42	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l13t1167r125b1222],
43	metastatic	JJ	O	metastatic	amod	44	SENT_21	[p2l149t1167r471b1222],
44	potential	NN	O	potential	nsubj	59	SENT_21	[p2l497t1167r776b1239],
45	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l802t1166r871b1222],
46	intestinal	JJ	O	intestinal	amod	47	SENT_21	[p2l890t1166r1181b1222],
47	tumors	NNS	O	tumor	prep_of	44	SENT_21	[p2l1206t1149r1535b1222],
48	.6	CD	NUMBER	.6	num	52	SENT_21	[p2l1206t1149r1535b1222],
49	"	``	O	"	punct	52	SENT_21	[p2l1206t1149r1535b1222],
50	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	52	SENT_21	[p2l1206t1149r1535b1222],
51	Ecological	NNP	O	Ecological	nn	52	SENT_21	[p2l1560t1167r1901b1239],
52	studies	NNS	O	study	dep	47	SENT_21	[p2l1929t1167r2145b1222],
53	correlating	VBG	O	correlate	xcomp	52	SENT_21	[p2l12t1250r355b1323],
54	sunlight	NN	O	sunlight	nn	55	SENT_21	[p2l390t1250r644b1323],
55	exposure	NN	O	exposure	dobj	53	SENT_21	[p2l675t1268r960b1323],
56	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l992t1250r1132b1306],
57	cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	58	SENT_21	[p2l1163t1268r1371b1306],
58	incidence	NN	O	incidence	prep_with	53	SENT_21	[p2l1401t1250r1705b1306],
59	provided	VBD	O	provide	ccomp	33	SENT_21	[p2l1736t1250r2020b1323],
60	the	DT	O	the	det	62	SENT_21	[p2l2051t1250r2146b1306],
61	ﬁrst	JJ	O	ﬁrst	amod	62	SENT_21	[p2l13t1335r134b1391],
62	evidence	NN	O	evidence	dobj	59	SENT_21	[p2l164t1335r445b1391],
63	that	IN	O	that	complm	69	SENT_21	[p2l478t1335r597b1391],
64	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	66	SENT_21	[p2l626t1335r870b1391],
65	D	NN	O	d	nn	66	SENT_21	[p2l901t1337r955b1390],
66	levels	NNS	O	level	nsubjpass	69	SENT_21	[p2l986t1335r1169b1391],
67	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	69	SENT_21	[p2l1204t1353r1297b1391],
68	inversely	RB	O	inversely	advmod	69	SENT_21	[p2l1329t1335r1619b1407],
69	related	VBN	O	relate	ccomp	59	SENT_21	[p2l1650t1335r1868b1391],
70	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l1898t1344r1958b1391],
71	CRC	NN	ORGANIZATION	crc	nn	72	SENT_21	[p2l1991t1336r2145b1391],
72	development	NN	O	development	prep_to	69	SENT_21	[p2l12t1420r424b1492],
73	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l471t1420r532b1474],
74	humans	NNS	O	human	prep_in	72	SENT_21	[p2l577t1403r904b1475],
75	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p2l577t1403r904b1475],

1	”	NN	O	”	nsubj	36	SENT_22	[p2l577t1403r904b1475],
2	Subsequent	JJ	O	subsequent	amod	4	SENT_22	[p2l953t1420r1318b1492],
3	epidemiological	JJ	O	epidemiological	amod	4	SENT_22	[p2l1366t1420r1879b1492],
4	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	6	SENT_22	[p2l1929t1420r2145b1475],
5	have	VBP	O	have	aux	6	SENT_22	[p2l11t1503r160b1559],
6	reported	VBN	O	report	rcmod	1	SENT_22	[p2l194t1503r460b1575],
7	lower	JJR	O	lower	amod	8	SENT_22	[p2l494t1503r675b1559],
8	risks	NNS	O	risk	dobj	6	SENT_22	[p2l707t1503r854b1559],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l891t1503r960b1559],
10	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	prep_of	8	SENT_22	[p2l990t1503r1151b1559],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1186t1503r1299b1559],
12	CRC	NN	ORGANIZATION	crc	nn	25	SENT_22	[p2l1334t1503r1489b1559],
13	in	IN	O	in	dep	25	SENT_22	[p2l1525t1503r1585b1558],
14	individuals	NNS	O	individual	pobj	13	SENT_22	[p2l1619t1503r1971b1559],
15	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l2007t1503r2147b1559],
16	high	JJ	O	high	amod	17	SENT_22	[p2l10t1587r152b1659],
17	intakes	NNS	O	intake	prep_with	14	SENT_22	[p2l183t1587r406b1643],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l441t1587r553b1643],
19	circulating	VBG	O	circulate	dep	25	SENT_22	[p2l584t1587r924b1659],
20	levels	NNS	O	level	dobj	19	SENT_22	[p2l957t1587r1140b1643],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1174t1587r1242b1643],
22	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	24	SENT_22	[p2l1268t1587r1512b1643],
23	D1144	NN	O	d1144	nn	24	SENT_22	[p2l1543t1570r1768b1643],
24	Vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	prep_of	20	SENT_22	[p2l1800t1587r2060b1643],
25	D	NN	O	d	nsubj	26	SENT_22	[p2l2091t1589r2145b1642],
26	plays	VBZ	O	play	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l10t1671r176b1743],
27	a	DT	O	a	det	29	SENT_22	[p2l214t1688r247b1726],
28	crucial	JJ	O	crucial	amod	29	SENT_22	[p2l281t1671r496b1726],
29	role	NN	O	role	dobj	26	SENT_22	[p2l530t1671r653b1726],
30	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l689t1671r748b1726],
31	calcium	NN	O	calcium	nn	32	SENT_22	[p2l784t1671r1035b1726],
32	metabolism	NN	O	metabolism	prep_in	29	SENT_22	[p2l1070t1671r1459b1737],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1070t1671r1459b1737],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1497t1671r1609b1726],
35	there	EX	O	there	expl	36	SENT_22	[p2l1643t1671r1801b1726],
36	is	VBZ	O	be	conj_and	26	SENT_22	[p2l1837t1671r1886b1726],
37	experimental	JJ	O	experimental	acomp	36	SENT_22	[p2l1922t1671r2144b1743, p2l11t1737r382b1821],
38	,15	CD	NUMBER	,15	number	39	SENT_22	[p2l1922t1671r2144b1743, p2l11t1737r382b1821],
39	’16	CD	NUMBER	’16	num	40	SENT_22	[p2l1922t1671r2144b1743, p2l11t1737r382b1821],
40	epidemiologic17	NNS	O	epidemiologic17	dep	37	SENT_22	[p2l412t1738r1017b1827],
41	"	``	O	"	punct	36	SENT_22	[p2l412t1738r1017b1827],
42	19	CD	NUMBER	19	nsubj	47	SENT_22	[p2l412t1738r1017b1827],
43	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l1049t1755r1161b1811],
44	clinical	JJ	O	clinical	amod	45	SENT_22	[p2l1189t1755r1423b1811],
45	trial20	NN	O	trial20	conj_and	42	SENT_22	[p2l1452t1738r1709b1811],
46	’21	CD	NUMBER	’21	num	47	SENT_22	[p2l1452t1738r1709b1811],
47	data	NNS	O	datum	xcomp	36	SENT_22	[p2l1744t1755r1876b1811],
48	indicating	VBG	O	indicate	partmod	47	SENT_22	[p2l1904t1755r2144b1811, p2l12t1839r111b1911],
49	that	IN	O	that	complm	55	SENT_22	[p2l142t1839r261b1894],
50	high	JJ	O	high	amod	52	SENT_22	[p2l290t1839r431b1911],
51	calcium	NN	O	calcium	nn	52	SENT_22	[p2l462t1839r713b1894],
52	intake	NN	O	intake	nsubj	55	SENT_22	[p2l744t1839r937b1894],
53	may	MD	O	may	aux	55	SENT_22	[p2l967t1856r1103b1911],
54	also	RB	O	also	advmod	55	SENT_22	[p2l1136t1839r1260b1894],
55	lower	VB	O	lower	ccomp	48	SENT_22	[p2l1292t1839r1472b1894],
56	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	58	SENT_22	[p2l1502t1839r1815b1894],
57	neoplasia	NN	O	neoplasium	nn	58	SENT_22	[p2l1846t1839r2147b1911],
58	risk	NN	O	risk	dobj	55	SENT_22	[p2l11t1923r145b1978],
59	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p2l11t1923r145b1978],

1	Furthermore	RB	O	furthermore	advmod	4	SENT_23	[p2l183t1923r598b1988],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l183t1923r598b1988],
3	there	EX	O	there	expl	4	SENT_23	[p2l635t1923r792b1978],
4	is	VBZ	O	be	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l827t1923r876b1978],
5	evidence	NN	O	evidence	nsubj	4	SENT_23	[p2l912t1923r1193b1978],
6	that	IN	O	that	complm	12	SENT_23	[p2l1229t1923r1348b1978],
7	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	8	SENT_23	[p2l1381t1922r1624b1978],
8	D	NN	O	d	nsubj	12	SENT_23	[p2l1658t1924r1712b1977],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l1748t1923r1861b1978],
10	calcium	NN	O	calcium	conj_and	8	SENT_23	[p2l1895t1923r2146b1978],
11	may	MD	O	may	aux	12	SENT_23	[p2l11t2023r146b2078],
12	act	VB	O	act	ccomp	4	SENT_23	[p2l177t2014r268b2061],
13	together	RB	O	together	advmod	12	SENT_23	[p2l294t2006r556b2078],
14	to	TO	O	to	aux	15	SENT_23	[p2l583t2014r642b2061],
15	reduce	VB	O	reduce	xcomp	12	SENT_23	[p2l669t2006r881b2061],
16	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	17	SENT_23	[p2l911t2006r1072b2061],
17	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	dobj	15	SENT_23	[p2l1098t1989r1514b2061],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p2l1098t1989r1514b2061],

1	”	NN	O	”	nn	3	SENT_24	[p2l1098t1989r1514b2061],
2	Dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	3	SENT_24	[p2l1543t2005r1722b2078],
3	products	NNS	O	product	nsubj	7	SENT_24	[p2l1749t2005r2021b2078],
4	are	VBP	O	be	cop	7	SENT_24	[p2l2052t2023r2146b2061],
5	an	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_24	[p2l13t2108r85b2146],
6	important	JJ	O	important	amod	7	SENT_24	[p2l114t2090r424b2163],
7	source	NN	O	source	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l455t2108r658b2146],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l689t2090r758b2146],
9	calcium	NN	O	calcium	prep_of	7	SENT_24	[p2l782t2090r1051b2156],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l782t2090r1051b2156],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1084t2090r1196b2146],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1226t2090r1286b2145],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_24	[p2l1314t2090r1409b2146],
14	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	15	SENT_24	[p2l1439t2090r1655b2146],
15	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	prep_in	19	SENT_24	[p2l1686t2090r1890b2157],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1686t2090r1890b2157],
17	milk	NN	O	milk	nsubjpass	19	SENT_24	[p2l1921t2090r2068b2145],
18	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	19	SENT_24	[p2l2096t2090r2145b2146],
19	fortiﬁed	VBN	O	fortiﬁed	conj_and	7	SENT_24	[p2l11t2174r268b2230],
20	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l300t2174r440b2230],
21	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	prep_with	19	SENT_24	[p2l470t2174r714b2230],
22	D.	NNP	O	D.	nn	26	SENT_24	[p2l746t2176r817b2230],
23	High	NNP	O	High	nn	26	SENT_24	[p2l853t2174r1010b2246],
24	dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	26	SENT_24	[p2l1043t2174r1204b2246],
25	product	NN	O	product	nn	26	SENT_24	[p2l1235t2174r1479b2246],
26	intake	NN	O	intake	nsubjpass	28	SENT_24	[p2l1511t2174r1704b2230],
27	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	28	SENT_24	[p2l1737t2174r1786b2230],
28	associated	VBN	O	associate	rcmod	21	SENT_24	[p2l1821t2174r2147b2230],
29	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l12t2258r152b2314],
30	reduced	VBN	O	reduce	amod	31	SENT_24	[p2l187t2258r440b2314],
31	incidence	NN	O	incidence	prep_with	28	SENT_24	[p2l476t2258r780b2314],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l819t2258r887b2314],
33	both	CC	O	both	preconj	34	SENT_24	[p2l918t2258r1059b2314],
34	CRA23	NN	O	cra23	prep_of	31	SENT_24	[p2l1096t2241r1314b2314],
35	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1355t2259r1467b2314],
36	CRC	NN	O	crc	prep_of	31	SENT_24	[p2l1504t2241r1812b2325],
37	,24	CD	NUMBER	,24	number	38	SENT_24	[p2l1504t2241r1812b2325],
38	’25	CD	NUMBER	’25	dep	34	SENT_24	[p2l1504t2241r1812b2325],
39	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p2l1854t2259r1966b2314],
40	milk	NN	O	milk	prep_of	31	SENT_24	[p2l2001t2258r2148b2313],

1	Publication	NN	O	publication	nn	2	SENT_25	[p2l452t2453r711b2490],
2	ofthe	NN	O	ofthe	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l728t2453r856b2490],
3	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	International	nn	4	SENT_25	[p2l873t2453r1167b2490],
4	Union	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Union	dep	2	SENT_25	[p2l1187t2453r1323b2490],
5	Against	IN	ORGANIZATION	against	_	0	SENT_25	[p2l1339t2453r1519b2499],
6	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	prep_against	4	SENT_25	[p2l1533t2453r1694b2490],

1	_	NN	O	_	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l10t2594r123b2660],
2	§	CD	NUMBER	§	num	4	SENT_26	[p2l10t2594r123b2660],
3	r.	NN	O	r.	nn	4	SENT_26	[p2l10t2594r123b2660],
4	sb	NN	O	sb	dep	1	SENT_26	[p2l10t2594r123b2660],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p2l10t2594r123b2660],

1	=	JJ	O	=	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l10t2594r123b2660],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p2l10t2594r123b2660],

1	I	PRP	O	I	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l10t2594r123b2660],
2	mm	NN	O	mm	nn	3	SENT_28	[p2l133t2592r250b2649],
3	r	NN	O	r	dep	1	SENT_28	[p2l261t2618r383b2649],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l261t2618r383b2649],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l261t2618r383b2649],
6	InEa-11	NN	O	inea-11	dep	3	SENT_28	[p2l261t2618r383b2649],
7	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_28	[p2l261t2618r383b2649],

1	consumption	NN	O	consumption	nsubjpass	17	SENT_29	[p2l9t2820r438b2893],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l9t2820r438b2893],
3	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	7	SENT_29	[p2l490t2820r683b2876],
4	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	7	SENT_29	[p2l731t2820r781b2876],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_29	[p2l830t2820r925b2876],
6	main	JJ	O	main	amod	7	SENT_29	[p2l974t2820r1134b2876],
7	component	NN	O	component	rcmod	1	SENT_29	[p2l1182t2829r1536b2893],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1585t2820r1654b2876],
9	dairy	NN	O	dairy	nn	11	SENT_29	[p2l1697t2820r1858b2892],
10	product	NN	O	product	nn	11	SENT_29	[p2l1906t2820r2151b2893],
11	intake	NN	O	intake	prep_of	7	SENT_29	[p2l9t2904r202b2960],
12	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l232t2904r324b2960],
13	most	JJS	O	most	amod	14	SENT_29	[p2l352t2913r506b2960],
14	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_for	11	SENT_29	[p2l535t2904r906b2970],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l535t2904r906b2970],
16	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	17	SENT_29	[p2l938t2922r1058b2960],
17	concluded	VBN	O	conclude	dep	23	SENT_29	[p2l1089t2904r1417b2960],
18	to	TO	O	to	aux	19	SENT_29	[p2l1445t2913r1505b2960],
19	result	VB	O	result	xcomp	17	SENT_29	[p2l1533t2904r1711b2960],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1739t2904r1800b2959],
21	“	CD	NUMBER	“	prep_in	19	SENT_29	[p2l1834t2904r2149b2977],
22	probable	JJ	O	probable	acomp	19	SENT_29	[p2l1834t2904r2149b2977],
23	decreased	VBD	O	decrease	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l9t2988r323b3044],
24	risk	NN	O	risk	nn	25	SENT_29	[p2l363t2988r519b3044],
25	”	NN	O	”	dobj	23	SENT_29	[p2l363t2988r519b3044],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l568t2988r637b3044],
27	CRC	NN	ORGANIZATION	crc	prep_of	25	SENT_29	[p2l674t2988r829b3044],
28	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l873t2988r933b3043],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	35	SENT_29	[p2l974t2988r1069b3044],
30	recent	JJ	O	recent	amod	35	SENT_29	[p2l1110t2996r1306b3044],
31	World	NNP	ORGANIZATION	World	nn	35	SENT_29	[p2l1346t2988r1550b3044],
32	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	35	SENT_29	[p2l1593t2988r1818b3044],
33	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	35	SENT_29	[p2l1858t2988r2151b3044],
34	Fund/American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Fund/American	nn	35	SENT_29	[p2l8t3072r511b3135],
35	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	prep_in	23	SENT_29	[p2l552t3072r812b3127],
36	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	for	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l855t3072r948b3127],
37	Cancer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Cancer	nn	39	SENT_29	[p2l989t3072r1215b3128],
38	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	39	SENT_29	[p2l1255t3072r1548b3127],
39	report	NN	O	report	prep_for	35	SENT_29	[p2l1588t3081r1780b3144],
40	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1821t3072r1942b3127],
41	food	NN	O	food	prep_into	23	SENT_29	[p2l1986t3072r2148b3138],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1986t3072r2148b3138],
43	nutrition	NN	O	nutrition	prep_into	23	SENT_29	[p2l8t3156r301b3222],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l8t3156r301b3222],
45	physical	JJ	O	physical	amod	46	SENT_29	[p2l324t3156r590b3228],
46	activity	NN	O	activity	prep_into	23	SENT_29	[p2l615t3156r852b3228],
47	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l877t3156r990b3212],
48	the	DT	O	the	det	49	SENT_29	[p2l1011t3156r1106b3212],
49	prevention	NN	O	prevention	prep_into	23	SENT_29	[p2l1128t3156r1471b3228],
50	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1494t3156r1563b3212],
51	cancer	NN	O	cancer	prep_of	49	SENT_29	[p2l1580t3138r1867b3212],
52	.26	CD	NUMBER	.26	nsubj	23	SENT_29	[p2l1580t3138r1867b3212],

1	The	DT	O	the	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l88t21r212b76],
2	VDR	NN	O	vdr	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l248t22r415b76],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l450t20r499b76],
4	responsible	JJ	O	responsible	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l535t20r902b93],
5	for	IN	O	for	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l938t20r1031b76],
6	mediating	VBG	O	mediate	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1065t20r1387b93],
7	the	DT	O	the	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1423t21r1519b76],
8	effects	NNS	O	effect	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1555t20r1767b76],
9	of	IN	O	of	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1805t20r1874b76],
10	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1903t20r2150b76],
11	D	NN	O	d	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l9t107r82b171],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p3l9t107r82b171],
13	and	CC	O	and	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l130t105r243b161],
14	functioning	VBG	O	function	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l286t105r657b177],
15	of	IN	O	of	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l703t105r771b161],
16	the	DT	O	the	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l810t105r906b161],
17	VDR	NN	O	vdr	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l951t107r1117b161],
18	has	VBZ	O	have	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1160t105r1265b161],
19	been	VBN	O	be	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1310t105r1461b161],
20	shown	VBN	O	show	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1507t105r1712b161],
21	to	TO	O	to	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1755t114r1815b161],
22	be	VB	O	be	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1859t105r1932b161],
23	inﬂuenced	VBN	O	inﬂuenced	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1978t105r2148b161, p3l9t189r197b245],
24	by	IN	O	by	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l237t190r315b261],
25	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l357t189r858b262],
26	in	IN	O	in	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l903t189r963b244],
27	the	DT	O	the	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1005t189r1101b245],
28	VDR	NN	O	vdr	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1146t191r1296b246],
29	gene	NN	O	gene	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1342t172r1571b261],
30	.27	CD	NUMBER	.27	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1342t172r1571b261],
31	The	DT	O	the	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1615t189r1737b245],
32	VDR	NN	O	vdr	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1783t191r1933b246],
33	CdX2	NN	O	cdx2	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1979t189r2149b245],
34	G	NN	O	g	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l10t273r184b331],
35	>	JJR	O	>	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l10t273r184b331],
36	A	DT	O	a	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l10t273r184b331],
37	promoter	NN	O	promoter	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l216t281r514b345],
38	variant	JJ	O	variant	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l547t273r771b329],
39	maps	NNS	O	map	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l804t291r971b345],
40	to	TO	O	to	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1006t282r1066b329],
41	a	DT	O	a	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1103t291r1135b329],
42	binding	NN	O	binding	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1168t273r1413b345],
43	site	NN	O	site	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1450t273r1558b329],
44	for	IN	O	for	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1593t273r1686b329],
45	an	DT	O	a	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1720t291r1793b329],
46	intestinalspeciﬁc	NN	O	intestinalspeciﬁc	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1827t273r2148b329, p3l11t357r252b429],
47	transcription	NN	O	transcription	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l298t357r707b429],
48	factor	NN	O	factor	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l750t357r939b413],
49	and	CC	O	and	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l983t357r1096b413],
50	confers	VBZ	O	confer	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1140t357r1374b413],
51	altered	JJ	O	altered	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1421t357r1639b413],
52	transcriptional	JJ	O	transcriptional	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1682t357r2150b429],
53	activity	NN	O	activity	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l10t424r331b513],
54	.28	CD	NUMBER	.28	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l10t424r331b513],
55	The	DT	O	the	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l366t441r489b497],
56	F	NN	O	f	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l520t443r571b496],
57	okl	NN	O	okl	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l573t441r674b497],
58	translational	JJ	O	translational	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l707t441r1107b497],
59	start	NN	O	start	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1144t450r1280b497],
60	codon	NN	O	codon	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1313t441r1508b497],
61	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1540t441r2011b513],
62	has	VBZ	O	have	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l2045t441r2148b497],
63	structural	JJ	O	structural	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l11t525r313b580],
64	consequences	NNS	O	consequence	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l344t542r785b597],
65	for	IN	O	for	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l817t525r910b580],
66	the	DT	O	the	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l938t525r1034b580],
67	VDR	NN	O	vdr	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1066t526r1233b581],
68	which	WDT	O	which	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1263t525r1458b580],
69	result	VBP	O	result	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1487t525r1667b580],
70	in	IN	O	in	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1696t525r1757b580],
71	a	DT	O	a	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1788t542r1821b580],
72	less	JJR	O	less	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1850t525r1967b580],
73	transcriptionally	RB	O	transcriptionally	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1999t534r2148b580, p3l11t609r412b681],
74	potent	JJ	O	potent	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l442t618r645b681],
75	protein	NN	O	protein	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l673t592r1060b681],
76	.29	CD	NUMBER	.29	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l673t592r1060b681],
77	’30	CD	NUMBER	’30	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l673t592r1060b681],
78	In	IN	O	in	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1091t610r1157b664],
79	addition	NN	O	addition	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1188t609r1468b675],
80	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p3l1188t609r1468b675],
81	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1503t609r1538b664],
82	intronic	JJ	O	intronic	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1570t609r1819b664],
83	polymorphisms	NNS	O	polymorphism	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1850t609r2148b681, p3l8t693r253b765],
84	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p3l1850t609r2148b681, p3l8t693r253b765],
85	BsmI	NN	O	bsmus	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l288t694r455b749],
86	and	CC	O	and	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l492t693r605b748],
87	Apal	NN	O	apal	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l636t693r813b764],
88	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p3l636t693r813b764],
89	and	CC	O	and	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l853t693r966b748],
90	the	DT	O	the	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1002t693r1098b748],
91	Taql	NNP	MISC	Taql	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1136t694r1284b764],
92	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1318t693r1789b765],
93	in	IN	O	in	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1826t693r1886b748],
94	exon	NN	O	exon	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1923t710r2077b748],
95	9	CD	NUMBER	9	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l2113t693r2148b749],
96	have	VBP	O	have	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l8t776r158b832],
97	been	VBN	O	be	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l197t777r348b832],
98	reported	VBN	O	report	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l385t776r654b849],
99	to	TO	O	to	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l691t785r751b832],
100	alter	VB	O	alter	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l791t777r934b832],
101	VDR	NN	O	vdr	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l971t778r1138b833],
102	expression	NN	O	expression	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1175t776r1536b849],
103	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p3l1175t776r1536b849],
104	probably	RB	O	probably	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1576t777r1863b849],
105	through	IN	O	through	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1901t776r2151b849],
106	linkage	NN	O	linkage	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l9t861r244b933],
107	disequilibrium	NN	O	disequilibrium	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l306t860r776b933],
108	with	IN	O	with	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l835t860r978b916],
109	variants	NNS	O	variant	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1036t860r1290b916],
110	in	IN	O	in	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1350t860r1411b916],
111	the	DT	O	the	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1470t861r1566b916],
112	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1628t855r1845b917],
113	’	NN	O	’	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1628t855r1845b917],
114	UTR	NN	O	utr	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1628t855r1845b917],
115	altering	VBG	O	alter	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l1905t861r2149b933],
116	VDR	NN	O	vdr	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l9t946r436b1001],
117	—	CD	NUMBER	—	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l9t946r436b1001],
118	mRNA	NN	O	mrna	dep	119	SENT_30	[p3l9t946r436b1001],
119	stability	NN	O	stability	_	0	SENT_30	[p3l468t928r801b1017],
120	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p3l468t928r801b1017],

1	“	NN	O	“	_	0	SENT_31	[p3l468t928r801b1017],

1	Epidemiological	JJ	O	epidemiological	amod	2	SENT_32	[p3l88t1048r618b1121],
2	studies	NNS	O	study	nsubj	4	SENT_32	[p3l670t1048r887b1104],
3	have	VBP	O	have	aux	4	SENT_32	[p3l937t1048r1086b1104],
4	reported	VBN	O	report	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1135t1048r1402b1121],
5	associations	NNS	O	association	dobj	4	SENT_32	[p3l1452t1048r1834b1104],
6	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1884t1048r2150b1104],
7	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	10	SENT_32	[p3l11t1134r160b1189],
8	£	CD	NUMBER	£	num	10	SENT_32	[p3l190t1133r674b1237],
9	013/morphism	NN	O	013/morphism	nn	10	SENT_32	[p3l190t1133r674b1237],
10	genotype	NN	O	genotype	prep_between	5	SENT_32	[p3l721t1142r1011b1205],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1060t1133r1172b1189],
12	risk	NN	O	risk	conj_and	10	SENT_32	[p3l1217t1133r1337b1188],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1383t1133r1451b1188],
14	both	DT	O	both	det	15	SENT_32	[p3l1491t1133r1633b1188],
15	CRA32	NN	O	cra32	prep_of	12	SENT_32	[p3l1679t1114r1990b1189],
16	"	''	O	"	punct	5	SENT_32	[p3l1679t1114r1990b1189],
17	36	CD	NUMBER	36	dep	5	SENT_32	[p3l1679t1114r1990b1189],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l2038t1133r2151b1188],
19	CRC	NN	ORGANIZATION	crc	dep	5	SENT_32	[p3l10t1218r184b1284],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l10t1218r184b1284],
21	"	``	O	"	punct	4	SENT_32	[p3l247t1200r304b1237],
22	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dobj	4	SENT_32	[p3l247t1200r304b1237],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l365t1217r477b1273],
24	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l504t1217r564b1272],
25	some	DT	O	some	det	26	SENT_32	[p3l593t1235r756b1273],
26	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_in	31	SENT_32	[p3l786t1217r1021b1284],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l786t1217r1021b1284],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_32	[p3l1049t1217r1145b1273],
29	associations	NNS	O	association	nsubjpass	31	SENT_32	[p3l1174t1217r1555b1273],
30	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	31	SENT_32	[p3l1584t1235r1736b1273],
31	modiﬁed	VBN	O	modiﬁed	conj_and	4	SENT_32	[p3l1763t1217r2047b1273],
32	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l2072t1217r2150b1289],
33	dietary	JJ	O	dietary	amod	35	SENT_32	[p3l9t1302r229b1374],
34	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	35	SENT_32	[p3l264t1302r508b1358],
35	D	NN	O	d	agent	31	SENT_32	[p3l543t1303r596b1357],
36	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l634t1302r746b1358],
37	calcium	NN	O	calcium	nn	38	SENT_32	[p3l780t1302r1032b1358],
38	intakes	NN	O	intake	agent	31	SENT_32	[p3l1067t1284r1613b1358],
39	.32	CD	NUMBER	.32	dep	35	SENT_32	[p3l1067t1284r1613b1358],
40	"	``	O	"	punct	31	SENT_32	[p3l1067t1284r1613b1358],
41	36	CD	NUMBER	36	num	42	SENT_32	[p3l1067t1284r1613b1358],
42	’	CD	NUMBER	’	tmod	31	SENT_32	[p3l1067t1284r1613b1358],
43	38	CD	NUMBER	38	num	44	SENT_32	[p3l1067t1284r1613b1358],
44	’40	CD	NUMBER	’40	dep	42	SENT_32	[p3l1067t1284r1613b1358],
45	Although	IN	O	although	mark	63	SENT_32	[p3l1647t1302r1948b1374],
46	not	RB	O	not	dep	49	SENT_32	[p3l1981t1311r2083b1358],
47	a	DT	O	a	det	49	SENT_32	[p3l2118t1320r2151b1358],
48	universal	JJ	O	universal	amod	49	SENT_32	[p3l8t1387r300b1442],
49	ﬁnding	NN	O	ﬁnding	dep	63	SENT_32	[p3l339t1369r716b1459],
50	,34	CD	NUMBER	,34	number	51	SENT_32	[p3l339t1369r716b1459],
51	’39	CD	NUMBER	’39	num	52	SENT_32	[p3l339t1369r716b1459],
52	carriers	NNS	O	carrier	dep	49	SENT_32	[p3l755t1387r991b1442],
53	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1030t1387r1099b1442],
54	variant	JJ	O	variant	amod	55	SENT_32	[p3l1130t1387r1352b1442],
55	F	NN	O	f	prep_of	52	SENT_32	[p3l1386t1388r1436b1442],
56	0	CD	NUMBER	0	nsubjpass	72	SENT_32	[p3l1438t1387r1537b1443],
57	/	:	O	/	punct	58	SENT_32	[p3l1438t1387r1537b1443],
58	<	JJR	O	<	dep	56	SENT_32	[p3l1438t1387r1537b1443],
59	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	60	SENT_32	[p3l1438t1387r1537b1443],
60	alleles	NNS	O	allele	dep	58	SENT_32	[p3l1576t1387r1776b1442],
61	have	VBP	O	have	aux	63	SENT_32	[p3l1814t1387r1963b1442],
62	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	63	SENT_32	[p3l2000t1387r2150b1442],
63	reported	VBN	O	report	dep	4	SENT_32	[p3l8t1471r275b1543],
64	to	TO	O	to	aux	65	SENT_32	[p3l299t1480r359b1527],
65	have	VB	O	have	xcomp	63	SENT_32	[p3l384t1471r534b1527],
66	an	DT	O	a	det	68	SENT_32	[p3l562t1489r634b1527],
67	increased	VBN	O	increase	amod	68	SENT_32	[p3l659t1471r961b1527],
68	risk	NN	O	risk	dobj	65	SENT_32	[p3l985t1471r1105b1527],
69	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1130t1471r1199b1527],
70	CRC40	NN	O	crc40	prep_of	68	SENT_32	[p3l1220t1453r1436b1527],
71	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1464t1471r1577b1527],
72	advanced	VBD	O	advance	conj_and	63	SENT_32	[p3l1603t1471r1903b1527],
73	CRA32	NN	O	cra32	dobj	72	SENT_32	[p3l1929t1453r2150b1527],
74	which	WDT	O	which	nsubjpass	76	SENT_32	[p3l9t1555r203b1611],
75	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	76	SENT_32	[p3l240t1555r289b1611],
76	enhanced	VBN	O	enhance	rcmod	73	SENT_32	[p3l328t1556r629b1611],
77	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l666t1555r727b1611],
78	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_in	76	SENT_32	[p3l763t1555r1116b1611],
79	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1155t1555r1295b1611],
80	low	JJ	O	low	amod	82	SENT_32	[p3l1332t1556r1448b1611],
81	calcium	NN	O	calcium	nn	82	SENT_32	[p3l1487t1555r1739b1611],
82	intake	NN	O	intake	prep_with	78	SENT_32	[p3l1776t1555r1986b1611],
83	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p3l1776t1555r1986b1611],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_33	[p3l2027t1556r2149b1611],
2	homozygous	JJ	O	homozygous	amod	5	SENT_33	[p3l8t1640r414b1713],
3	variant	JJ	O	variant	amod	5	SENT_33	[p3l445t1640r667b1696],
4	Bsml	NN	O	bsml	nn	5	SENT_33	[p3l693t1642r858b1696],
5	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nsubjpass	8	SENT_33	[p3l889t1649r1179b1713],
6	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	8	SENT_33	[p3l1209t1640r1312b1696],
7	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_33	[p3l1343t1640r1493b1696],
8	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1523t1640r1708b1696],
9	to	TO	O	to	aux	11	SENT_33	[p3l1737t1649r1796b1696],
10	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_33	[p3l1826t1640r1899b1696],
11	associated	VBN	O	associate	xcomp	8	SENT_33	[p3l1931t1640r2148b1696, p3l10t1725r141b1780],
12	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l187t1725r327b1780],
13	a	DT	O	a	det	16	SENT_33	[p3l374t1743r407b1780],
14	modest	JJ	O	modest	amod	16	SENT_33	[p3l450t1725r682b1780],
15	protective	JJ	O	protective	amod	16	SENT_33	[p3l725t1725r1045b1797],
16	inﬂuence	NN	O	inﬂuence	prep_with	11	SENT_33	[p3l1092t1725r1382b1780],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1430t1725r1490b1780],
18	CRC38	NN	O	crc38	prep_in	16	SENT_33	[p3l1536t1708r1750b1781],
19	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1797t1725r1899b1780],
20	not	RB	O	not	neg	16	SENT_33	[p3l1943t1733r2045b1780],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l2091t1725r2151b1780],
22	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	conj_but	18	SENT_33	[p3l10t1792r401b1865],
23	.32	CD	NUMBER	.32	number	24	SENT_33	[p3l10t1792r401b1865],
24	’	CD	NUMBER	’	num	26	SENT_33	[p3l10t1792r401b1865],
25	33	CD	NUMBER	33	number	26	SENT_33	[p3l10t1792r401b1865],
26	’36	CD	NUMBER	’36	dep	16	SENT_33	[p3l10t1792r401b1865],
27	No	DT	O	no	det	28	SENT_33	[p3l435t1811r530b1865],
28	association	NN	O	association	dobj	11	SENT_33	[p3l567t1809r920b1865],
29	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l953t1809r1220b1865],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_33	[p3l1253t1809r1349b1865],
31	F	NN	O	f	nn	32	SENT_33	[p3l1381t1811r1432b1864],
32	okI	NN	O	okus	prep_between	28	SENT_33	[p3l1434t1809r1534b1865],
33	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p3l1569t1809r1682b1865],
34	Taql	NN	O	taql	nn	35	SENT_33	[p3l1717t1811r1864b1881],
35	variants	NNS	O	variant	prep_between	28	SENT_33	[p3l1898t1809r2149b1865],

1	United	NNP	ORGANIZATION	United	nn	7	SENT_34	[p3l80t2081r272b2131],
2	Kingdom	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kingdom	nn	7	SENT_34	[p3l316t2081r583b2145],
3	Colorectal	JJ	ORGANIZATION	colorectal	amod	7	SENT_34	[p3l628t2081r921b2131],
4	Adenoma	NN	ORGANIZATION	adenoma	nn	7	SENT_34	[p3l966t2081r1242b2130],
5	Prevention	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Prevention	nn	7	SENT_34	[p3l1284t2081r1592b2130],
6	Trial	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Trial	nn	7	SENT_34	[p3l1635t2081r1772b2130],
7	Consortium	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Consortium	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1818t2081r2151b2131],
8	members	NNS	O	member	dep	7	SENT_34	[p3l8t2151r283b2200],
9	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l8t2151r283b2200],
10	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	11	SENT_34	[p3l312t2152r376b2200],
11	Armitage	NNP	PERSON	Armitage	dep	7	SENT_34	[p3l404t2150r686b2214],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l404t2150r686b2214],
13	V.	NNP	PERSON	V.	nn	14	SENT_34	[p3l713t2152r776b2200],
14	Shepherd	NNP	PERSON	Shepherd	appos	11	SENT_34	[p3l807t2151r1087b2214],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l807t2151r1087b2214],
16	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	17	SENT_34	[p3l1115t2151r1173b2200],
17	Elliott	NNP	PERSON	Elliott	appos	11	SENT_34	[p3l1201t2150r1394b2209],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1201t2150r1394b2209],
19	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	20	SENT_34	[p3l1420t2152r1472b2200],
20	Watmough	NNP	PERSON	Watmough	appos	11	SENT_34	[p3l1499t2150r1830b2214],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1499t2150r1830b2214],
22	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	nn	23	SENT_34	[p3l1859t2151r1909b2200],
23	Barratt	NNP	PERSON	Barratt	appos	11	SENT_34	[p3l1937t2152r2149b2209],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1937t2152r2149b2209],
25	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	26	SENT_34	[p3l8t2220r72b2268],
26	Birch	NNP	PERSON	Birch	appos	11	SENT_34	[p3l110t2219r282b2277],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l110t2219r282b2277],
28	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	29	SENT_34	[p3l318t2219r382b2268],
29	Gibbons	NNP	PERSON	Gibbons	appos	11	SENT_34	[p3l420t2219r674b2278],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l420t2219r674b2278],
31	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	32	SENT_34	[p3l710t2219r773b2268],
32	Campion	NNP	PERSON	Campion	appos	11	SENT_34	[p3l812t2219r1086b2283],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l812t2219r1086b2283],
34	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	11	SENT_34	[p3l1122t2219r1420b2283],
35	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1456t2219r1517b2268],
36	Nottingham	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Nottingham	nn	38	SENT_34	[p3l1546t2219r1885b2283],
37	Medical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Medical	nn	38	SENT_34	[p3l1918t2219r2150b2268],
38	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	School	prep_of	34	SENT_34	[p3l10t2288r220b2347],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l10t2288r220b2347],
40	Nottingham	NNP	LOCATION	Nottingham	nn	42	SENT_34	[p3l251t2288r605b2352],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l251t2288r605b2352],
42	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	appos	11	SENT_34	[p3l637t2289r753b2347],
43	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l637t2289r753b2347],
44	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	45	SENT_34	[p3l786t2289r846b2338],
45	Logan	NNP	PERSON	Logan	dep	7	SENT_34	[p3l879t2289r1075b2352],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l879t2289r1075b2352],
47	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	48	SENT_34	[p3l1106t2289r1170b2338],
48	Wright	NNP	PERSON	Wright	appos	45	SENT_34	[p3l1202t2288r1418b2352],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1202t2288r1418b2352],
50	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	51	SENT_34	[p3l1449t2289r1489b2338],
51	Patterson	NNP	PERSON	Patterson	appos	45	SENT_34	[p3l1522t2289r1801b2347],
52	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l1522t2289r1801b2347],
53	Kings	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Kings	nn	55	SENT_34	[p3l1833t2288r1999b2352],
54	Mill	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mill	nn	55	SENT_34	[p3l2030t2288r2150b2337],
55	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	appos	45	SENT_34	[p3l9t2358r264b2422],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l9t2358r264b2422],
57	Sutton	NNP	PERSON	Sutton	appos	45	SENT_34	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],
58	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],

1	Ashﬁeld	NNP	PERSON	Ashﬁeld	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l294t2358r839b2416],
3	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l868t2359r984b2416],
4	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l868t2359r984b2416],
5	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1015t2358r1079b2407],
6	Scott	NNP	PERSON	Scott	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1111t2358r1270b2416],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1111t2358r1270b2416],
8	Glenﬁeld	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Glenﬁeld	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1300t2358r1563b2407],
9	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1589t2358r1844b2422],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1589t2358r1844b2422],
11	Leicester	NNP	LOCATION	Leicester	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1872t2358r2148b2416],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1872t2358r2148b2416],
13	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l8t2428r124b2485],
14	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l8t2428r124b2485],
15	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l149t2428r189b2476],
16	Reynolds	NNP	PERSON	Reynolds	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l213t2426r496b2490],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l213t2426r496b2490],
18	Derby	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Derby	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l519t2427r694b2490],
19	City	NNP	ORGANIZATION	City	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l715t2426r835b2490],
20	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	General	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l857t2427r1080b2476],
21	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1100t2426r1339b2490],
22	and	CC	O	and	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1361t2427r1461b2476],
23	Derby	NNP	LOCATION	Derby	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1481t2426r1656b2490],
24	Royal	NNP	LOCATION	Royal	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1677t2426r1846b2490],
25	Inﬁrmary	NNP	LOCATION	Inﬁrmary	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1866t2427r2149b2490],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1866t2427r2149b2490],
27	Derby	NNP	LOCATION	Derby	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l9t2496r200b2559],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l9t2496r200b2559],
29	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l222t2497r338b2554],
30	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l222t2497r338b2554],
31	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l364t2497r424b2545],
32	Walt	NNP	PERSON	Walt	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l448t2496r601b2554],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l448t2496r601b2554],
34	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l624t2497r687b2545],
35	Martin	NNP	PERSON	Martin	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l712t2496r920b2554],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l712t2496r920b2554],
37	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l942t2497r1002b2545],
38	Bisseker	NNP	PERSON	Bisseker	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1027t2496r1285b2554],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1027t2496r1285b2554],
40	Birmingham	NNP	LOCATION	Birmingham	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1309t2496r1667b2559],
41	Heartlands	NNP	LOCATION	Heartlands	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1688t2496r1992b2545],
42	Hospital	NNP	LOCATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l2015t2497r2149b2545, p3l7t2564r150b2628],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l2015t2497r2149b2545, p3l7t2564r150b2628],
44	Birmingham	NNP	LOCATION	Birmingham	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l177t2564r551b2628],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l177t2564r551b2628],
46	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l578t2565r694b2623],
47	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l578t2565r694b2623],
48	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l724t2565r787b2614],
49	Hudson	NNP	PERSON	Hudson	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l817t2564r1052b2623],
50	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l817t2564r1052b2623],
51	Birmingham	NNP	LOCATION	Birmingham	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1079t2564r1437b2628],
52	City	NNP	LOCATION	City	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1463t2564r1583b2628],
53	Hospital	NNP	LOCATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1609t2564r1864b2628],
54	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1609t2564r1864b2628],
55	Birmingham	NNP	LOCATION	Birmingham	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1892t2564r2148b2628, p3l8t2633r145b2692],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1892t2564r2148b2628, p3l8t2633r145b2692],
57	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l174t2635r291b2692],
58	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l174t2635r291b2692],
59	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l322t2634r385b2683],
60	Hamlyn	NNP	PERSON	Hamlyn	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l416t2634r659b2697],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l416t2634r659b2697],
62	Wordsley	NNP	LOCATION	Wordsley	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l687t2633r963b2697],
63	Hospital	NNP	LOCATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l990t2633r1245b2697],
64	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l990t2633r1245b2697],
65	Stourbridge	NNP	LOCATION	Stourbridge	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1275t2633r1624b2697],
66	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1275t2633r1624b2697],
67	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1652t2635r1768b2692],
68	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1652t2635r1768b2692],
69	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1799t2635r1875b2683],
70	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	Thomas	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1905t2633r2148b2692],
71	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1905t2633r2148b2692],
72	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l8t2703r60b2751],
73	Durdey	NNP	PERSON	Durdey	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l86t2702r313b2766],
74	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l86t2702r313b2766],
75	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l337t2703r400b2751],
76	Green	NNP	PERSON	Green	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l426t2702r613b2761],
77	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l426t2702r613b2761],
78	Bristol	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bristol	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l637t2702r829b2751],
79	Royal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Royal	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l851t2702r1020b2766],
80	Inﬁrmary	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inﬁrmary	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1041t2702r1324b2766],
81	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1041t2702r1324b2766],
82	Bristol	NNP	LOCATION	Bristol	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1348t2702r1556b2760],
83	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1348t2702r1556b2760],
84	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1579t2703r1695b2760],
85	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1579t2703r1695b2760],
86	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1721t2702r1785b2751],
87	Roe	NNP	PERSON	Roe	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1810t2703r1939b2760],
88	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1810t2703r1939b2760],
89	Southmead	NNP	LOCATION	Southmead	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1965t2702r2149b2751, p3l8t2772r162b2821],
90	Hospital	NNP	LOCATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l181t2772r436b2836],
91	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l181t2772r436b2836],
92	Bristol	NNP	LOCATION	Bristol	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l457t2772r664b2830],
93	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l457t2772r664b2830],
94	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l685t2773r801b2830],
95	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l685t2773r801b2830],
96	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l824t2772r888b2821],
97	Watson	NNP	PERSON	Watson	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l910t2773r1143b2830],
98	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l910t2773r1143b2830],
99	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1163t2773r1226b2821],
100	Johnston	NNP	PERSON	Johnston	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1249t2772r1516b2830],
101	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1249t2772r1516b2830],
102	Royal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Royal	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1536t2772r1705b2835],
103	Liverpool	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Liverpool	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1723t2772r2003b2836],
104	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l2022t2772r2149b2821, p3l8t2841r200b2904],
105	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l220t2841r475b2905],
106	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l220t2841r475b2905],
107	Liverpool	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Liverpool	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l496t2841r792b2905],
108	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l496t2841r792b2905],
109	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l814t2842r930b2899],
110	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l814t2842r930b2899],
111	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l955t2841r1013b2890],
112	Babbs	NNP	PERSON	Babbs	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1036t2841r1228b2899],
113	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1036t2841r1228b2899],
114	Hope	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hope	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1250t2842r1401b2905],
115	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1422t2841r1677b2905],
116	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1422t2841r1677b2905],
117	Salford	NNP	LOCATION	Salford	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1701t2841r1922b2899],
118	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1701t2841r1922b2899],
119	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1943t2842r2060b2899],
120	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1943t2842r2060b2899],
121	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l2083t2842r2147b2890],
122	Shreeve	NNP	PERSON	Shreeve	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l10t2909r252b2968],
123	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l10t2909r252b2968],
124	North	NNP	ORGANIZATION	North	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l278t2909r443b2959],
125	Manchester	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Manchester	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l466t2909r798b2958],
126	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	General	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l822t2909r1044b2959],
127	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1069t2909r1324b2973],
128	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1069t2909r1324b2973],
129	Manchester	NNP	LOCATION	Manchester	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1351t2909r1696b2968],
130	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1351t2909r1696b2968],
131	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1722t2910r1838b2968],
132	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1722t2910r1838b2968],
133	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1867t2910r1907b2959],
134	Crampton	NNP	PERSON	Crampton	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1936t2910r2149b2973, p3l8t2986r113b3037],
135	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1936t2910r2149b2973, p3l8t2986r113b3037],
136	Wythenshawe	NNP	LOCATION	Wythenshawe	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l152t2979r552b3042],
137	Hospital	NNP	LOCATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l591t2978r846b3042],
138	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l591t2978r846b3042],
139	Manchester	NNP	LOCATION	Manchester	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l884t2979r1231b3037],
140	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l884t2979r1231b3037],
141	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1269t2980r1385b3037],
142	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1269t2980r1385b3037],
143	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1428t2979r1486b3028],
144	Summerton	NNP	PERSON	Summerton	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1528t2979r1872b3037],
145	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1528t2979r1872b3037],
146	Trafford	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Trafford	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1911t2978r2151b3028],
147	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	General	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l9t3047r232b3096],
148	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l265t3047r520b3111],
149	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l265t3047r520b3111],
150	Manchester	NNP	LOCATION	Manchester	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l554t3047r900b3106],
151	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l554t3047r900b3106],
152	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l934t3048r1050b3106],
153	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l934t3048r1050b3106],
154	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1086t3048r1142b3096],
155	Wames	NNP	PERSON	Wames	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1178t3048r1410b3106],
156	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1178t3048r1410b3106],
157	Manchester	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Manchester	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1444t3047r1775b3096],
158	Royal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Royal	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1806t3047r1974b3111],
159	Inﬁrmary	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inﬁrmary	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l2006t3047r2149b3096, p3l8t3132r169b3180],
160	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l2006t3047r2149b3096, p3l8t3132r169b3180],
161	Manchester	NNP	LOCATION	Manchester	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l197t3117r542b3175],
162	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l197t3117r542b3175],
163	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l570t3118r686b3175],
164	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l570t3118r686b3175],
165	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l716t3118r768b3166],
166	Isaacs	NNP	PERSON	Isaacs	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l797t3118r985b3175],
167	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l797t3118r985b3175],
168	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1013t3118r1088b3166],
169	Rolland	NNP	PERSON	Rolland	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1117t3117r1357b3175],
170	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1117t3117r1357b3175],
171	Blackpool	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Blackpool	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1385t3117r1676b3181],
172	Victoria	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Victoria	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1702t3117r1935b3166],
173	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1959t3117r2149b3181, p3l9t3186r94b3244],
174	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1959t3117r2149b3181, p3l9t3186r94b3244],
175	Blackpool	NNP	LOCATION	Blackpool	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l125t3186r431b3250],
176	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l125t3186r431b3250],
177	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l461t3187r577b3244],
178	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l461t3187r577b3244],
179	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l610t3186r673b3235],
180	Shorthouse	NNP	PERSON	Shorthouse	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l707t3186r1039b3244],
181	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l707t3186r1039b3244],
182	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1068t3187r1125b3235],
183	Heatherington	NNP	PERSON	Heatherington	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1156t3186r1578b3250],
184	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1156t3186r1578b3250],
185	Royal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Royal	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1607t3186r1776b3250],
186	Hallamshire	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hallamshire	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1804t3186r2150b3235],
187	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l9t3254r264b3318],
188	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l9t3254r264b3318],
189	South	NNP	LOCATION	South	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l307t3255r470b3304],
190	Yorkshire	NNP	LOCATION	Yorkshire	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l509t3254r807b3313],
191	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l509t3254r807b3313],
192	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l848t3256r964b3313],
193	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l848t3256r964b3313],
194	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1008t3256r1071b3304],
195	Hosie	NNP	PERSON	Hosie	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1115t3254r1294b3313],
196	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1115t3254r1294b3313],
197	Northern	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Northern	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1335t3255r1592b3304],
198	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	General	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1631t3255r1854b3304],
199	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1894t3254r2149b3318],
200	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1894t3254r2149b3318],
201	South	NNP	LOCATION	South	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l10t3324r173b3373],
202	Yorkshire	NNP	LOCATION	Yorkshire	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l201t3324r499b3382],
203	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l201t3324r499b3382],
204	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l529t3325r645b3382],
205	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l529t3325r645b3382],
206	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l678t3325r741b3373],
207	Bardhan	NNP	PERSON	Bardhan	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l773t3324r1028b3382],
208	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l773t3324r1028b3382],
209	Rotherham	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Rotherham	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1058t3324r1373b3373],
210	District	NNP	ORGANIZATION	District	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1401t3324r1614b3373],
211	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	General	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1642t3324r1865b3373],
212	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1894t3324r2149b3388],
213	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1894t3324r2149b3388],
214	South	NNP	LOCATION	South	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l10t3392r173b3442],
215	Yorkshire	NNP	LOCATION	Yorkshire	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l195t3392r492b3451],
216	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l195t3392r492b3451],
217	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l516t3393r632b3451],
218	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l516t3393r632b3451],
219	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l658t3393r721b3442],
220	Vellacott	NNP	PERSON	Vellacott	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l747t3392r1023b3451],
221	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l747t3392r1023b3451],
222	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	dep	223	SENT_38	[p3l1047t3393r1110b3442],
223	Knight	NNP	PERSON	Knight	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1135t3392r1536b3456],
224	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p3l1135t3392r1536b3456],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_39	[p3l1135t3392r1536b3456],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p3l1135t3392r1536b3456],

1	Davis	NNP	PERSON	Davis	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l1135t3392r1536b3456],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l1135t3392r1536b3456],
3	Royal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Royal	nn	5	SENT_40	[p3l1559t3392r1728b3456],
4	Gwent	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Gwent	nn	5	SENT_40	[p3l1751t3393r1938b3442],
5	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	appos	1	SENT_40	[p3l1960t3392r2149b3456, p3l8t3462r94b3520],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l1960t3392r2149b3456, p3l8t3462r94b3520],
7	Newport	NNP	LOCATION	Newport	appos	1	SENT_40	[p3l116t3463r379b3525],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l116t3463r379b3525],
9	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	appos	1	SENT_40	[p3l401t3463r517b3520],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l401t3463r517b3520],
11	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	nn	12	SENT_40	[p3l541t3462r604b3511],
12	Hawthorne	NNP	PERSON	Hawthorne	dep	1	SENT_40	[p3l628t3462r958b3520],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l628t3462r958b3520],
14	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	15	SENT_40	[p3l980t3463r1043b3511],
15	Thompson	NNP	PERSON	Thompson	appos	12	SENT_40	[p3l1066t3462r1421b3525],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p3l1066t3462r1421b3525],

1	—	NN	O	—	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1066t3462r1421b3525],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p3l1066t3462r1421b3525],

1	J	NNP	O	J	nn	2	SENT_42	[p3l1066t3462r1421b3525],
2	ones	NNS	O	one	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1423t3477r1565b3520],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1423t3477r1565b3520],
4	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	5	SENT_42	[p3l1587t3463r1647b3511],
5	Stenson	NNP	PERSON	Stenson	appos	2	SENT_42	[p3l1673t3462r1909b3520],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1673t3462r1909b3520],
7	University	NNP	LOCATION	University	nn	8	SENT_42	[p3l1931t3461r2148b3511, p3l11t3530r109b3594],
8	Hospital	NNP	LOCATION	Hospital	appos	2	SENT_42	[p3l133t3530r372b3594],
9	of	IN	LOCATION	of	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l396t3530r457b3579],
10	Wales	NNP	LOCATION	Wales	prep_of	8	SENT_42	[p3l474t3530r667b3588],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l474t3530r667b3588],
12	Cardiff	NNP	LOCATION	Cardiff	appos	2	SENT_42	[p3l693t3530r911b3589],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l693t3530r911b3589],
14	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	appos	2	SENT_42	[p3l936t3531r1052b3589],
15	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l936t3531r1052b3589],
16	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	17	SENT_42	[p3l1078t3531r1131b3579],
17	Watson	NNP	PERSON	Watson	dep	2	SENT_42	[p3l1157t3531r1388b3588],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1157t3531r1388b3588],
19	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	20	SENT_42	[p3l1413t3531r1476b3579],
20	Lawther	NNP	PERSON	Lawther	appos	17	SENT_42	[p3l1503t3530r1754b3588],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1503t3530r1754b3588],
22	Royal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Royal	nn	24	SENT_42	[p3l1779t3530r1947b3594],
23	Victoria	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Victoria	nn	24	SENT_42	[p3l1971t3530r2149b3579, p3l8t3600r83b3649],
24	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	appos	2	SENT_42	[p3l126t3600r381b3664],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l126t3600r381b3664],
26	Belfast	NNP	LOCATION	Belfast	appos	2	SENT_42	[p3l426t3600r642b3658],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l426t3600r642b3658],
28	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	appos	2	SENT_42	[p3l687t3601r803b3658],
29	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l687t3601r803b3658],
30	o.	NNP	O	o.	nn	31	SENT_42	[p3l852t3600r915b3649],
31	Kronborg	NNP	PERSON	Kronborg	dep	2	SENT_42	[p3l962t3600r1252b3663],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l962t3600r1252b3663],
33	Odense	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Odense	nn	35	SENT_42	[p3l1298t3600r1508b3649],
34	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	35	SENT_42	[p3l1552t3600r1849b3663],
35	Hospital	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hospital	appos	31	SENT_42	[p3l1894t3600r2149b3664],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l1894t3600r2149b3664],
37	Odense	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Odense	appos	2	SENT_42	[p3l10t3670r235b3728],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l10t3670r235b3728],
39	Denmark	NNP	LOCATION	Denmark	appos	2	SENT_42	[p3l257t3670r534b3720],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p3l257t3670r534b3720],

1	Grant	NNP	PERSON	Grant	nn	2	SENT_43	[p3l80t3739r241b3788],
2	sponsors	NNS	O	sponsor	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l262t3754r520b3802],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l262t3754r520b3802],
4	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	nn	6	SENT_43	[p3l546t3739r746b3788],
5	Research	NNP	O	Research	nn	6	SENT_43	[p3l764t3738r1024b3788],
6	UK	NNP	O	UK	dep	2	SENT_43	[p3l1043t3740r1157b3788],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p3l1043t3740r1157b3788],

1	Bayer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bayer	nn	2	SENT_44	[p3l1180t3740r1350b3802],
2	Healthcare	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Healthcare	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1369t3739r1689b3788],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p3l1369t3739r1689b3788],

1	Kellogg	NNP	PERSON	Kellogg	nsubj	2	SENT_45	[p3l1713t3738r2005b3802],
2	’s	POS	O	’s	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1713t3738r2005b3802],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p3l1713t3738r2005b3802],

1	*	NN	O	*	nn	2	SENT_46	[p4l84t8r608b74],
2	Correspondence	NN	O	correspondence	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l84t8r608b74],
3	to	TO	O	to	dep	2	SENT_46	[p4l640t14r715b60],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l640t14r715b60],
5	Section	NN	O	section	dep	2	SENT_46	[p4l752t10r963b60],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l993t10r1054b60],
7	Cancer	NN	O	cancer	nn	10	SENT_46	[p4l1079t11r1280b60],
8	Genetics	NNP	O	Genetics	nn	10	SENT_46	[p4l1309t10r1571b69],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1309t10r1571b69],
10	Institute	NNP	O	Institute	prep_of	5	SENT_46	[p4l1602t10r1833b60],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_46	[p4l1865t10r1926b60],
12	Cancer	NNP	O	Cancer	prep_of	10	SENT_46	[p4l1951t11r2152b60],

1	Research	NNP	O	Research	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l8t79r284b138],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l8t79r284b138],
3	15	CD	NUMBER	15	num	5	SENT_47	[p4l312t79r371b128],
4	Cotswold	NNP	O	Cotswold	nn	5	SENT_47	[p4l395t79r665b128],
5	Road	NNP	O	Road	appos	1	SENT_47	[p4l683t79r848b137],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l683t79r848b137],
7	Sutton	NNP	PERSON	Sutton	appos	1	SENT_47	[p4l871t79r1069b138],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l871t79r1069b138],
9	Surrey	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Surrey	nn	11	SENT_47	[p4l1092t79r1278b143],
10	SM2	NN	O	sm2	nn	11	SENT_47	[p4l1299t79r1432b128],
11	5NG	NN	O	5ng	appos	1	SENT_47	[p4l1454t79r1604b138],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1454t79r1604b138],
13	UK	NNP	LOCATION	UK	appos	1	SENT_47	[p4l1625t80r1740b128],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p4l1625t80r1740b128],

1	E	NN	O	e	nn	3	SENT_48	[p4l8t150r217b199],
2	—	CD	NUMBER	—	num	3	SENT_48	[p4l8t150r217b199],
3	mail	NN	O	mail	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l8t150r217b199],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_48	[p4l8t150r217b199],
5	richard.hubner@icr.ac.uk	NN	O	richard.hubner@icr.ac.uk	dep	3	SENT_48	[p4l240t150r967b209],

1	Received	VBN	O	receive	dep	15	SENT_49	[p4l79t218r344b268],
2	28	CD	DATE	28	dobj	1	SENT_49	[p4l364t219r429b268],
3	November	NNP	DATE	November	tmod	2	SENT_49	[p4l451t219r752b268],
4	2007	CD	DATE	2007	num	3	SENT_49	[p4l770t219r925b277],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l770t219r925b277],
6	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	dep	2	SENT_49	[p4l949t219r1217b282],
7	after	IN	O	after	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l1238t218r1367b268],
8	revision	NN	O	revision	prep_after	6	SENT_49	[p4l1383t218r1613b268],
9	30	CD	DATE	30	num	8	SENT_49	[p4l1633t219r1700b268],
10	January	NNP	DATE	January	tmod	6	SENT_49	[p4l1719t220r1939b282],
11	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	10	SENT_49	[p4l1960t219r2096b268],
12	DOI	NNP	O	DOI	tmod	1	SENT_49	[p4l80t288r203b337],
13	10.1002	CD	NUMBER	10.1002	num	12	SENT_49	[p4l230t288r738b352],
14	/	:	O	/	punct	15	SENT_49	[p4l230t288r738b352],
15	ijc	NN	O	ijc	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l230t288r738b352],
16	.23536	CD	NUMBER	.23536	num	15	SENT_49	[p4l230t288r738b352],
17	Published	VBN	O	publish	partmod	15	SENT_49	[p4l79t357r352b406],
18	online	NN	O	online	prep	17	SENT_49	[p4l380t357r551b406],
19	9	CD	DATE	9	dep	18	SENT_49	[p4l580t357r611b406],
20	May	NNP	DATE	May	tmod	17	SENT_49	[p4l642t358r769b420],
21	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	20	SENT_49	[p4l797t357r931b406],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l963t357r1016b405],
23	Wiley	NNP	O	Wiley	nn	24	SENT_49	[p4l1043t357r1214b420],
24	InterScience	NNP	O	InterScience	prep_in	17	SENT_49	[p4l1241t357r1586b406],
25	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	26	SENT_49	[p4l1617t357r2147b417],
26	www	NN	O	www	dep	24	SENT_49	[p4l1617t357r2147b417],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p4l1617t357r2147b417],

1	interscience	NN	O	interscience	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1617t357r2147b417],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p4l1617t357r2147b417],

1	wiley.com	NNP	O	wiley.com	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l9t425r334b489],
2	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	1	SENT_51	[p4l9t425r334b489],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p4l9t425r334b489],

1	DAIRY	NN	O	dairy	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l419t570r510b590],
2	PRODUCTS	NNP	O	PRODUCTS	nn	5	SENT_52	[p4l520t570r670b590],
3	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p4l682t570r743b590],
4	CRA	NNP	O	CRA	nn	5	SENT_52	[p4l755t570r813b590],
5	RECURRENCE	NNP	O	RECURRENCE	dep	1	SENT_52	[p4l823t570r1015b590],
6	587	CD	NUMBER	587	dep	1	SENT_52	[p4l1688t564r1741b590],

1	and	CC	O	and	cc	5	SENT_53	[p4l10t692r122b747],
2	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	3	SENT_53	[p4l157t692r318b747],
3	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	nsubjpass	5	SENT_53	[p4l350t709r686b747],
4	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_53	[p4l722t709r842b747],
5	reported	VBN	O	report	dep	17	SENT_53	[p4l876t691r1142b764],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l1176t691r1236b747],
7	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	8	SENT_53	[p4l1271t709r1382b747],
8	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	5	SENT_53	[p4l1420t675r1668b764],
9	.22	CD	NUMBER	.22	dobj	5	SENT_53	[p4l1420t675r1668b764],
10	To	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l1702t693r1788b747],
11	date	VB	O	date	prep_to	9	SENT_53	[p4l1823t692r1953b747],
12	there	EX	O	there	expl	17	SENT_53	[p4l1988t692r2145b747],
13	have	VBP	O	have	aux	17	SENT_53	[p4l8t775r156b831],
14	been	VBN	O	be	cop	17	SENT_53	[p4l187t776r337b831],
15	no	DT	O	no	det	17	SENT_53	[p4l365t793r442b831],
16	published	VBN	O	publish	amod	17	SENT_53	[p4l471t775r782b848],
17	reports	NNS	O	report	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l810t784r1029b848],
18	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l1062t793r1139b831],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_53	[p4l1168t775r1263b831],
20	relationship	NN	O	relationship	prep_on	17	SENT_53	[p4l1292t775r1668b848],
21	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l1698t776r1964b831],
22	Apal	NNP	O	Apal	prep_between	20	SENT_53	[p4l1988t776r2146b847],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l10t860r122b916],
24	CdX2	NN	O	cdx2	nn	25	SENT_53	[p4l145t860r314b916],
25	genotypes	NNS	O	genotype	conj_and	20	SENT_53	[p4l338t869r658b933],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l683t860r796b916],
27	colorectal	JJ	O	colorectal	amod	29	SENT_53	[p4l818t860r1132b916],
28	neoplasia	NN	O	neoplasium	nn	29	SENT_53	[p4l1154t860r1456b933],
29	risk	NN	O	risk	conj_and	20	SENT_53	[p4l1477t860r1611b916],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p4l1477t860r1611b916],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_54	[p4l87t960r196b1015],
2	aimed	VBD	O	aim	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l224t958r417b1014],
3	to	TO	O	to	aux	4	SENT_54	[p4l441t967r500b1014],
4	test	VB	O	test	xcomp	2	SENT_54	[p4l525t967r635b1014],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_54	[p4l659t959r754b1014],
6	hypothesis	NN	O	hypothesis	dobj	4	SENT_54	[p4l779t959r1118b1031],
7	that	IN	O	that	complm	12	SENT_54	[p4l1144t959r1263b1014],
8	VDR	NN	O	vdr	nn	11	SENT_54	[p4l1287t960r1453b1015],
9	polymorphism	NN	O	polymorphism	nn	11	SENT_54	[p4l1476t959r1941b1031],
10	genotype	NN	O	genotype	nn	11	SENT_54	[p4l1967t976r2144b1031, p4l8t1051r143b1115],
11	inﬂuences	NNS	O	inﬂuences	nsubj	12	SENT_54	[p4l171t1043r491b1098],
12	risk	NN	O	risk	ccomp	4	SENT_54	[p4l518t1043r638b1098],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l664t1042r732b1098],
14	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	15	SENT_54	[p4l755t1043r915b1099],
15	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	prep_of	12	SENT_54	[p4l940t1060r1277b1098],
16	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1303t1043r1381b1115],
17	genotyping	VBG	O	genotype	amod	18	SENT_54	[p4l1408t1043r1765b1115],
18	individuals	NNS	O	individual	prep_by	2	SENT_54	[p4l1793t1043r2145b1098],
19	participating	VBG	O	participate	partmod	18	SENT_54	[p4l7t1126r411b1199],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l452t1126r512b1182],
21	a	DT	O	a	det	24	SENT_54	[p4l551t1144r584b1182],
22	randomized	JJ	O	randomized	amod	24	SENT_54	[p4l621t1126r999b1182],
23	intervention	NN	O	intervention	nn	24	SENT_54	[p4l1037t1126r1423b1182],
24	trial	NN	O	trial	prep_in	19	SENT_54	[p4l1461t1126r1588b1182],
25	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l1627t1126r1720b1182],
26	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	28	SENT_54	[p4l1758t1127r1919b1182],
27	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	nn	28	SENT_54	[p4l1956t1144r2144b1182, p4l7t1228r179b1266],
28	prevention	NN	O	prevention	prep_for	24	SENT_54	[p4l205t1210r563b1283],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p4l205t1210r563b1283],

1	By	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l594t1212r684b1283],
2	examining	VBG	O	examine	prepc_by	18	SENT_55	[p4l712t1210r1047b1283],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_55	[p4l1074t1210r1169b1266],
4	data	NNS	O	datum	dobj	2	SENT_55	[p4l1198t1210r1329b1266],
5	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l1356t1228r1433b1266],
6	intakes	NN	O	intake	prep_on	2	SENT_55	[p4l1460t1210r1683b1266],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l1711t1210r1780b1266],
8	vitamin	NN	O	vitamin	nn	14	SENT_55	[p4l1801t1210r2045b1266],
9	D	NN	O	d	nn	14	SENT_55	[p4l2072t1212r2144b1277],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l2072t1212r2144b1277],
11	calcium	NN	O	calcium	nn	14	SENT_55	[p4l9t1295r261b1351],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l291t1295r404b1351],
13	dairy	NN	O	dairy	conj_and	9	SENT_55	[p4l433t1295r594b1367],
14	products	NNS	O	product	prep_of	6	SENT_55	[p4l623t1295r914b1368],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l623t1295r914b1368],
16	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	18	SENT_55	[p4l947t1313r1036b1351],
17	also	RB	O	also	advmod	18	SENT_55	[p4l1067t1295r1192b1351],
18	investigated	VBD	O	investigate	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l1222t1295r1608b1367],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_55	[p4l1636t1295r1732b1351],
20	inﬂuence	NN	O	inﬂuence	dobj	18	SENT_55	[p4l1762t1295r2052b1351],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l2083t1295r2151b1351],
22	dietary	JJ	O	dietary	amod	23	SENT_55	[p4l9t1379r228b1451],
23	factors	NNS	O	factor	prep_of	20	SENT_55	[p4l258t1379r472b1435],
24	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l504t1397r581b1435],
25	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	26	SENT_55	[p4l610t1379r771b1435],
26	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	prep_on	20	SENT_55	[p4l799t1397r1154b1445],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l799t1397r1154b1445],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l1187t1379r1299b1435],
29	potential	JJ	O	potential	amod	33	SENT_55	[p4l1327t1379r1606b1452],
30	gene	NN	O	gene	nn	33	SENT_55	[p4l1637t1379r1947b1451],
31	—	NN	O	—	nn	33	SENT_55	[p4l1637t1379r1947b1451],
32	diet	NN	O	diet	nn	33	SENT_55	[p4l1637t1379r1947b1451],
33	interactions	NNS	O	interaction	conj_and	20	SENT_55	[p4l1975t1379r2144b1435, p4l10t1463r249b1519],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p4l1975t1379r2144b1435, p4l10t1463r249b1519],

1	Material	NN	O	material	_	0	SENT_56	[p4l8t1681r303b1738],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_56	[p4l340t1682r464b1738],
3	methods	NNS	O	method	conj_and	1	SENT_56	[p4l500t1682r784b1738],

1	Study	NN	O	study	nn	2	SENT_57	[p4l8t1781r183b1853],
2	participants	NNS	O	participant	_	0	SENT_57	[p4l199t1783r591b1853],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_58	[p4l88t1881r210b1937],
2	United	NNP	ORGANIZATION	United	nn	8	SENT_58	[p4l297t1881r514b1937],
3	Kingdom	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kingdom	nn	8	SENT_58	[p4l600t1881r900b1953],
4	Colorectal	JJ	ORGANIZATION	colorectal	amod	8	SENT_58	[p4l988t1881r1319b1937],
5	Adenoma	NN	ORGANIZATION	adenoma	nn	8	SENT_58	[p4l1405t1881r1716b1937],
6	Prevention	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Prevention	nn	8	SENT_58	[p4l1801t1881r2147b1937],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_58	[p4l11t1965r326b2033],
8	UKCAP	NNP	O	UKCAP	nsubj	10	SENT_58	[p4l11t1965r326b2033],
9	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	10	SENT_58	[p4l11t1965r326b2033],
10	trial	NN	O	trial	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l358t1965r485b2020],
11	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	15	SENT_58	[p4l516t1965r565b2020],
12	a	DT	O	a	det	15	SENT_58	[p4l597t1982r630b2020],
13	recently	RB	DATE	recently	advmod	14	SENT_58	[p4l657t1965r914b2037],
14	completed	VBN	O	complete	amod	15	SENT_58	[p4l945t1965r1277b2037],
15	multicenter	NN	O	multicenter	rcmod	10	SENT_58	[p4l1306t1965r1687b2031],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1306t1965r1687b2031],
17	double-blind	JJ	O	double-blind	amod	21	SENT_58	[p4l1720t1965r2144b2031],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1720t1965r2144b2031],
19	randomized	JJ	O	randomized	amod	20	SENT_58	[p4l7t2048r385b2104],
20	controlled	JJ	O	controlled	amod	21	SENT_58	[p4l409t2048r732b2104],
21	trial	NN	O	trial	dobj	10	SENT_58	[p4l754t2048r881b2104],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l906t2048r975b2104],
23	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	prep_of	21	SENT_58	[p4l994t2048r1209b2121],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1233t2048r1346b2104],
25	folate	NN	O	folate	prep_of	21	SENT_58	[p4l1369t2048r1548b2104],
26	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l1573t2048r1665b2104],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_58	[p4l1687t2048r1782b2104],
28	prevention	NN	O	prevention	prep_for	21	SENT_58	[p4l1804t2048r2147b2121],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l9t2133r78b2188],
30	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nn	31	SENT_58	[p4l99t2133r261b2189],
31	recurrence	NN	O	recurrence	prep_of	21	SENT_58	[p4l284t2115r697b2188],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p4l284t2115r697b2188],

1	“	NN	O	“	nn	3	SENT_59	[p4l284t2115r697b2188],
2	Eligible	JJ	O	eligible	amod	3	SENT_59	[p4l727t2133r978b2205],
3	subjects	NNS	O	subject	nsubj	4	SENT_59	[p4l1008t2133r1259b2205],
4	had	VBD	O	have	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l1285t2133r1400b2188],
5	one	CD	NUMBER	one	dobj	4	SENT_59	[p4l1426t2151r1537b2188],
6	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l1565t2151r1630b2188],
7	more	JJR	O	more	conj_or	5	SENT_59	[p4l1653t2151r1815b2188],
8	histologically	RB	O	histologically	advmod	9	SENT_59	[p4l1841t2133r2144b2205, p4l9t2217r162b2289],
9	conﬁrmed	VBN	O	conﬁrmed	dep	5	SENT_59	[p4l186t2217r508b2273],
10	CRA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CRA	nsubj	26	SENT_59	[p4l532t2217r692b2273],
11	removed	VBD	O	remove	ccomp	9	SENT_59	[p4l714t2217r994b2273],
12	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l1017t2226r1072b2273],
13	full	JJ	O	full	amod	14	SENT_59	[p4l1095t2217r1203b2273],
14	colonoscopy	NN	O	colonoscopy	prep_at	11	SENT_59	[p4l1227t2217r1628b2290],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l1652t2217r1712b2272],
16	the	DT	DURATION	the	det	18	SENT_59	[p4l1734t2217r1829b2273],
17	6	CD	DURATION	6	num	18	SENT_59	[p4l1854t2217r1889b2273],
18	months	NNS	NUMBER	month	prep_in	11	SENT_59	[p4l1913t2217r2145b2273],
19	prior	RB	O	prior	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l7t2301r163b2374],
20	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l205t2310r264b2357],
21	enrollment	NN	O	enrollment	prep_prior_to	11	SENT_59	[p4l309t2301r671b2367],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l309t2301r671b2367],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l719t2301r831b2357],
24	were	VBD	O	be	aux	26	SENT_59	[p4l874t2319r1026b2357],
25	not	RB	O	not	neg	26	SENT_59	[p4l1069t2310r1171b2357],
26	taking	VBG	O	take	ccomp	9	SENT_59	[p4l1214t2301r1411b2373],
27	regular	JJ	O	regular	amod	28	SENT_59	[p4l1454t2301r1681b2373],
28	aspirin	NN	O	aspirin	dobj	26	SENT_59	[p4l1725t2301r1956b2374],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l1725t2301r1956b2374],
30	nonaspirin	JJ	O	nonaspirin	amod	31	SENT_59	[p4l2001t2319r2144b2357, p4l10t2385r224b2457],
31	NSAID	NN	O	nsaid	appos	28	SENT_59	[p4l246t2385r486b2441],
32	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l511t2403r575b2441],
33	prescribed	VBN	O	prescribe	conj_or	9	SENT_59	[p4l595t2385r928b2457],
34	folate	NN	O	folate	nn	35	SENT_59	[p4l950t2385r1130b2441],
35	supplements	NNS	O	supplement	dobj	33	SENT_59	[p4l1156t2385r1568b2457],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p4l1156t2385r1568b2457],
